♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
=The Eternal Love S3=
=Episode 01=
Cheng...
There's no need to hide.
Are the two beauties I married today
both in the room?
My two beauties,
sorry to have kept you waiting.
Isn't this exciting?
Curious about what happened?
The story began
a month ago.
As per quantum physics,
the universe is continually expanding
from a speck.
After reaching its limit,
it'll tear away to form multiple
parallel universes.
You won't know which day, or moment,
a new universe, a new Dongyue,
will be born.
But at this moment, this is still
the same Dongyue.
A Dongyue governed by
Emperor Mo Lian Cheng and
his Empress, Qu Xiao Tan.
You two, head over there to look for it.
Yes.
Little Prince.
Yu Er.
(A loving family)
Xiao Tan, look at this.
The Little Prince
threw his homework everywhere.
What should we do?
Stupid Mo Lian Cheng.
He's having it so easy.
Why should I be the one taking care of the child
and helping him with his homework?
Mo Lian Cheng, that bastard.
To think he said he'd be the one
to bear children in the next lifetime.
I regret bearing a child with him
even in this lifetime.
So what if he's the Emperor?
I still have my real estate career.
Yu Er, Yu Er!
This drawing is pretty good.
Assassins!
I'm sorry for not coming in time.
I beg your pardon, Your Majesty.
It's okay.
Yu Er,
if you really don't feel like learning,
go take an afternoon nap.
If you're going to keep behaving like this,
I'm going to collapse soon.
I'm not learning, I'm not learning,
I refuse!
What happened? Upset with Yu Er again?
Isn't Yu Er quite well-behaved?
You taught him well.
You have a talent for raising children.
Forget it, I'm not teaching him.
Just let him be a happy little fool.
Yu Er is a prince of Dongyue,
the future Emperor,
and an upright and strong man.
How can he be a little fool?
If he were a girl,
he would be able to freely…
What do you mean by "if he were a girl"?
What's wrong with being a girl?
Mo Lian Cheng, you're being sexist.
Tan Er, stop messing around.
You're tired, I'm tired too.
Men should be upright and strong,
but women can be little fools, is that it?
You're the one who brought about "fool".
Men can go to work, earn money,
and become the Emperor.
Women just stay home, wash clothes, cook,
and raise children.
Is that it?
Since when have you washed clothes or cooked?
The servants have always been the ones
doing the work.
Stay away from me. I'm frustrated.
Look at me.
My hands are red, I haven't even washed them.
Okay, okay.
I have to attend court every day,
and pamper you and Yu Er afterwards.
I'm tired too.
You're not the only one who's tired,
At the outskirts of the city with Yu Hao just now,
we...
Yu Er!
Didn't Qu Jiang Lin die a long time ago?
Am I seeing ghosts?
This must be a nightmare.
I need to go back to sleep, back to sleep,
Your Highness, don't be scared.
I'm here for you.
Jing Xin?
Your Highness, why are you frightened?
I'm here, I will ensure your safety.
Highness?
That's right.
Your Highness has finally woken up,
this is great news.
You've just recovered,
I'm afraid you may still be in shock.
Still in shock?
Yes, I'm still in shock.
Don't come any closer.
Stay away from me.
Cheng Cheng, Cheng Cheng!
Yu Er, where's Yu Er?
Cheng Cheng, Yu Er, where are you?
The Soul-guarding Pearl was unstable.
Could it be that time has been tampered with?
That can't be.
Before Qu Jiang Lin died,
I hadn't become the princess either.
Tan Er,
what's wrong with you?
You're the second princess of Dongyue!
You'll have a chance to inherit
the empire in the future.
You mustn't develop any bad habits.
Inherit the empire?
Me?
Inherit what position?
What's going on?
How did falling into the water
damage your brain this much?
Tan Er, let me be honest with you.
The Empress initially thought more highly of you.
But looking at you now,
the responsibility can only fall
onto your elder sister, Mei Er's shoulders.
Think it through carefully.
Mei Er?
Elder sister Mei Er?
I fell into the water?
No, no, no, no.
It's not what you think.
Your elder sister Mei Er is your only kin.
I swear on my life,
you falling into the water
had nothing to do with her.
Could it be that Qu Mei Er is Qu Pan Er?
The names changed?
But looking at how protective
Qu Jiang Lin is being,
it could very well be that Tan Er
falling into the water this time
was caused by this new elder sister.
You've been alive all this time?
You've always been a guard?
Tan Er, think about it.
Both you and Mei Er's mothers passed away early.
Wasn't it me
who raised both of you by myself?
If you still don't believe your father,
your mother up in heaven right now
wouldn't be pleased.
Okay, okay, okay.
Let me ask you.
I'm Princess Qu Tan Er,
and my elder sister is Qu Mei Er?
Yes.
I'm done for.
Don't tell me I...
What kind of luck do I have?
It seems that I've entered a universe
in which gender roles are reversed.
Then... what about Cheng Cheng?
And my Yu Er?
Cheng Cheng?
My Tan Er!
No, I can't trust Qu Jiang Lin.
Before I find out where Cheng Cheng is,
I can't carelessly reveal his existence.
I'll pretend to be Qu Tan Er
and try to get some inside info first.
Father,
I think my brain has indeed been damaged
after falling into the water.
But
I don't blame elder sister Mei Er.
But others might read more into it.
As a father,
I think
you're in a difficult position, right?
Yes.
Although I'm the Empress's cousin,
I'm still just a man.
What?
He's the Empress's cousin?
The Empress is my aunt?
My new sister and I are princesses?
This is a mess, it's all a mess.
Father, you must have suffered.
You're a man and you were born in the palace.
Life mustn't be easy for you.
As a man, it's never easy.
According to the rules of Dongyue,
men are subordinate to women.
After all, women
have to train themselves to govern the country.
Men should be loyal husbands,
and be virtuous and submissive.
The ruling Empress has no children,
so she wants to choose between you and Mei Er
to inherit the throne.
I'm happy for the both of you.
But I'm also worried and being extremely careful.
I'm afraid something bad might happen.
Tan Er, you've always been gentle and magnanimous.
I just want you and Mei Er to get along well,
so that I can have peace in my mind.
If I hadn't known what kind of person you were,
I would've actually believed you.
I understand.
Just that...
I'm not feeling too well now.
I want to take a rest.
Don't worry, Father.
How about you head back first?
Okay, okay, okay.
Look at me.
I got carried away because I was so happy
to see that you've recovered.
Your Highness, do take care.
Jing Xin, do you know
someone called Mo Lian Cheng?
The eighth young master of the Mo family?
Yes, yes, that's him.
Where is he now?
He should be in the palace today
taking part in the harem selection.
He should be waiting to be selected
at this very moment.
Harem selection?
Is that what I think it is?
It's to be chosen as part of the Empress's harem.
Your Highness, where are you going?
Snatching my groom.
Come.
Eighth Brother, why are you nervous?
With your qualifications,
you can definitely get chosen.
In any case, the Empress had long ago...
Eldest Brother,
I've spoken too much.
But ever since the accident,
you've become sullen and quiet.
You used to be very familiar with Her Majesty.
I sincerely wish
you may be together with the one you love.
Be together with the one you love?
As expected as the Eighth Young Master of Mo family.
But… who have you gotten involved with
before you've gotten married?
Young Master Su, please mind your words.
We are before the Empress's palace.
We are indeed before the Empress's palace,
also a familiar place to Eighth Young Master.
I wonder why he's joining the selection
together with us.
I thought
Eighth Young Master had joined the harem long ago.
According to my understanding,
the supervising officer today is Official Su,
who is Young Master Su's eldest sister.
Did she not arrange for you
to participate in the selection?
You're spouting rubbish!
You dare accuse my eldest sister
of practicing favoritism!
Eighth Brother.
You…!
Given Young Master Su's personality,
you should speak less,
in case you cause trouble for Official Su.
Eighth Brother...
Eldest Brother, don't worry.
Okay, then I'll see you off here.
I look forward to hearing good news from you.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Rise.
You may rise.
Greetings, Your Highness.
All rise.
It's different being a princess now.
This is awesome.
Jing Xin, do they all know me?
Everyone in the palace would.
Some of the lower-ranking servants
outside the palace
may not.
Your Highness,
you dropped this.
This perfume sachet is quite pretty.
Let me help you put it on.
I was in a hurry to leave the house
earlier this morning,
and almost made a big mistake.
This perfume sachet was presented
by the Empress.
The perfume powder inside is extremely precious.
Butterflies love this scent the most.
Aren't you a guard?
How do you know so much about perfume powders?
I naturally know every single detail
about Your Highness. It's my duty.
I know what girls are thinking.
Cheng Cheng, Cheng Cheng!
Your Highness, who are you calling?
My dear, my husband.
My Cheng Cheng!
Cheng Cheng!
Your Highness, please stop shouting.
They're waiting to be selected into the harem.
Before they're chosen,
they're considered the Empress's men.
Why would your husband be there?
In any case, you're not engaged yet.
That's true.
There are many people in this palace,
I mustn't expose myself.
I should figure out the situation first.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Your Highness, what are you doing?
I need to find a way to sneak in.
Sneak?
Second Princess.
Greetings, Official Su.
Greetings, Second Princess.
Could I know what you intend to do?
I'm just having a look around.
I wasn't thinking of going in.
How can that be?
Her Majesty selected Your Highness and me
to co-host the harem selection.
If you don't go in, how will we select the harem?
Co-host?
I'm just coming here to observe first.
Su… Official Su...
I'll leave it to you to handle this harem selection.
It's my duty.
Her Majesty already instructed me.
Your Highness only needs to attend it.
So she's Su Yue La,
the Empress's trusted aide.
These months, I've been trying to cover up,
and adapt to my surroundings as much as possible,
so that no one would realize I've lost my memory.
But I still feel that
the rules in this universe are hard for me to grasp.
Men are beneath women?
Abide by a code of virtue and be a loyal husband?
These practices are all so restrictive.
I just can't believe
I was raised in such an environment.
I'm trying to figure out
how things end up this way.
Eighth Brother, you're awake.
Lian Cheng.
Cheng Cheng,
Cheng Cheng.
Cheng Cheng, I'm not the Empress.
You've misunderstood.
So you don't need to enter the harem.
Pay attention to my signals during
the next selection process.
I'll find a way to get you eliminated.
Forgive me, Your Highness.
You've misspoken.
You know I'm the princess?
I'll pretend I didn't hear what you were saying.
May Your Highness
please stop speaking such heresy.
Can't you recognize me?
Oh, there are many people here, it's not convenient.
Young Master Mo,
you passed the test with flying colours.
I have much admiration for you.
I must encourage you.
Keep up the good work!
Everyone, keep up the good work!
Keep it up!
Go, go, go!
Where did he go?
Forget it.
I should find a way to get him eliminated first.
Then I'll find an opportunity to bump into him.
Not handsome enough. Eliminated.
The water is too hot. Eliminated.
There's dirt between your fingernails. Eliminated.
The tea isn't clean. Eliminated.
Pieces of your scalp have even fallen into the cup.
Eliminated!
You…
What's up with him?
He's not making any mistakes himself.
The tea is overflowing. Eliminated.
Looks like this difficult little punk
doesn't want Mo Lian Cheng
to get through even more than me.
I'm depending on you.
Bold of you!
Mo Lian Cheng has no manners! Eliminated!
I thought we were being tested
on our knowledge and skills of preparing tea.
I didn't know we were being tested on our agility.
You spilled water on me,
and now you're mocking me?
Insubordination!
Get out of here immediately!
This...
Your Highness… Your Highness, what's going on?
You and I both know he belongs to Her Majesty.
Why offend Her Majesty
over such a small thing?
Official Su, you're saying that
he must be selected no matter what?
I shall be magnanimous.
As long as Mo Lian Cheng
serves me and changes my outfit,
I'll forgive you just this once.
Bring some clean clothes for me.
But…
I wouldn't dare deny the order from Your Highness.
What's going on?
(Jing Yi Pavilion)
Cheng Cheng, I can’t do this by myself.
Come and give me a hand.
There are boundaries between men and women.
May Your Highness stop addressing me
like that, please.
You really don't know who I am?
Your Highness, I know you are the second princess.
So frustrating.
But he doesn't look like he's pretending.
But it doesn't seem like
he has lost your memory either.
Don't tell me this is just like the previous time.
He's the Mo Lian Cheng from this parallel universe.
Cheng Cheng was assassinated before.
I should confirm this first.
It seems that your clothes are wet as well.
How about we change out together?
Your Highness, are you teasing me?
What are you talking about?
Why would I be teasing you?
I'm concerned about you.
Can't you tell?
So fast?
Didn't you want to take a look?
Why are you being shy now?
If Your Highness has mercy on me,
and won't tell anyone about this,
I have no issues with
letting Your Highness have a look.
Don't worry, I won't.
He's really not Cheng Cheng.
What was she saying about pretending just now?
And now she wants to inspect my body?
Does she know something?
I'm sorry.
I've finished changing.
I'll be leaving now.
Please wait, Your Highness.
Don't worry,
I'll take it that nothing happened today.
I won't say a word. It won't affect your reputation.
When asking me to change just now,
it didn't seem like
Your Highness was someone who would care about
the reputation of others.
I asked you to change,
not to remove your clothes for me.
What were you looking for, Your Highness?
How about having a better look?
It's okay, it's okay, I got the wrong person.
Your Highness seems to be
looking for something indeed.
I was looking for some excitement.
I'm looking for excitement, okay?
I hope you can become the Emperor Consort soon.
I'm in a hurry to look for someone.
I'll be taking my leave.
Goodbye.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, you're done changing?
Let's hurry.
The other candidates
are still waiting to be selected.
But where is Young Master Mo?
He should be changing inside, I guess.
I'll take my leave first.
He doesn't need to change.
All candidates have to change
and be inspected before the harem selection.
Change?
Be inspected?
The candidates?
All removed their clothes?
This is the rule.
In case they have any weapons on them.
Of course, it's also to see
if there are any defects on their bodies.
We have to check them thoroughly.
They all can't compare to Cheng Cheng.
Too skinny.
But some of them are quite good-looking.
It would be better
if they had some abs.
Sorry.
Mo Lian Cheng, what are you doing?
You...
What are you doing here, Your Highness?
I'm staying outside to guard the place.
Guarding the place?
Do we need Your Highness to personally
guard this place?
Why not? Do I owe you?
Why's that your business?
Since you're guarding the place,
why did you peek?
Stay away from me. I'm frustrated.
Since when did you wash the clothes or cook?
The servants have always been the ones
doing the work.
Stay away from me. I'm frustrated.
Are you okay?
Tan Er?
Cheng Cheng, is that really you?
What happened to you?
Cheng Cheng, I've really missed you.
Cheng Cheng.
Why does he not recognize me again?
What exactly is going on?
No way. If he's really Cheng Cheng,
I mustn't let him get selected for the harem.
Are you okay, Your Highness?
Young Master Mo, since the inspection has ended,
prepare well for the harem selection.
Your Highness, please.
Looks like
I just need to help Su Jing Yuan.
Go in. Hurry.
I wonder if the empress is as pretty as they say.
No matter what,
forget about marrying my Cheng Cheng.
Long live the Empress.
All rise.
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪A flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part,
no matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part,
no matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind
in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪