♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fate will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
=The Eternal Love S3=
=Episode 02=
Long live the Empress.
Rise.
(She looks just like me.)
(No one finds it weird?)
(Well, they do say that)
(nieces tend to look like their aunts.)
(He must be surprised too.)
(That's Cheng Cheng.)
Oh, no.
(Why are you so excited seeing Cheng Cheng?)
(Cheng Cheng is mine.)
Now, the people live in peace
and the nation is united.
But I couldn't slack off.
So I select harem candidates
once every three years.
Is there anyone who can alleviate my concerns?
Your Majesty,
The Eighth Young Master of
the Mo family is versatile。
He's the most outstanding candidate.
Your Majesty,
I find Young Master Mo quite reserved.
He is a boring person.
I'm afraid he does not possess the talent
to entertain you, Your Majesty.
Young Master Mo has excellent sword skills.
Then why don't we have him
perform for us right now?
He'll be able to convince the other
candidates of his skills as well.
Your Majesty. Princess.
It is inappropriate to brandish
a sword in the great hall.
I'm afraid...
It doesn't matter.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Isn't this my perfume sachet?
Why is it with you?
Your Majesty, Mo Lian Cheng is concealing
a woman's personal belonging.
His actions are improper.
He has been caught red-handed.
Please deal with him accordingly.
Mo Lian Cheng, what is going on with you?
Your Majesty, please review it carefully.
We should be asking when did the owner
of the perfume sachet remove it
and when did the attendant responsible
for her attire put it back in place.
Only I, who have had my body searched,
should not be asked such a question.
Your Majesty,
there should be no problems
with clothes prepared in the palace.
I would not have come into contact
Her Highness' perfume sachet either.
You spilled tea on me on purpose.
You must have done it because you admire me
and took the sachet when I was changing my clothes.
Your Highness knows very well
how the tea was split and who
requested a change of clothes.
Your Majesty,
there are a lot of doubts regarding today's matter.
If word got out, it might do the harem harm.
Even if Young Master Mo was wronged,
everything that has happened today
proves that he is unfit to participate
in the harem selection.
Your Majesty, please remove him from the list.
Things haven't come out in the wash.
Why does Your Highness refuse to
allow me to defend myself?
Ultimately,
that perfume sachet fell out of your sleeves.
Everyone here saw that.
Or do you wish
that Her Majesty be criticized by people?
You...
Official Su.
Investigate this matter.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty is wise.
(Mo Residence)
For generations, the Mo family
has always been revered.
Yet today, you have tarnished our reputation.
Not only have we become the laughing
stock of the residence,
even the government officials
in the neighborhood
have a lot to say about you!
What do you think we should do?
Father, Eighth Brother has always been
a man with good character.
It must be a misunderstanding
regarding today's matter.
Her Majesty has ordered someone
to investigate it, hasn't she?
I'm sure the truth will come out soon.
Eldest Brother is right.
Once the truth is out,
we'll see if those slanderers
will be ashamed or not.
What do you know, Fourteenth?
Shut up!
I was asking him. Not you!
People only wish to believe
what they want to believe.
And they enjoy it.
The only thing we can do
is break the rumors by revealing the truth.
The Mo family has already been
criticized by people.
Does the truth still matter?
You don't get to decide if you were right or wrong.
Her Majesty decides that.
Before Her Majesty decides what to do with you,
you will copy the moral codes for men every day.
You will do that right now!
Yes, Father.
Eighth Brother.
You are saying that he stole your perfume sachet?
Could it be because you and Her Majesty
look alike, he has fallen
for you instead?
But that's not right.
If he didn't do something so foolish,
he'd have successfully joined the harem.
Why would he even need to shift
his attention to another person?
(The entire world knows)
(that I look like Her Majesty.)
(I guess I'll have to pretend)
(that I'm used to it as well.)
Your Highness?
He was framed.
I just
gave them an extra push.
Why?
Maybe you guys are thinking
in the wrong direction?
Have you guys never thought
that the reason this kind of thing has happened
was that Her Majesty looks like me?
You mustn't say that, Your Highness!
That is highly disrespectful.
Aren't you a brave and invincible guard?
Why are you such a coward?
Stopping Your Highness from getting
into trouble due to your loose tongue
is also part of my duties as
protecting Your Highness.
However... Regardless of what happened
between Her Majesty and him,
I only had to use a little trick
to make him pliant.
Let's see if he dares to look down on me again.
Your Highness's plan was flawless.
However, with your interference,
I'm afraid Eighth Young Master will no longer
be able to have a good marriage.
The entire Mo family will be affected as well.
Are things really as serious as you say?
Think about it.
Men's futures
have everything to do with their reputation.
If a man's reputation is tarnished,
that'll be the end of their futures as well.
The reputation of the Mo family will also...
Are you saying that he might
be kicked out of his house?
I'm afraid not only that.
Her Majesty is involved.
If he is found guilty,
a lighter sentence would mean that
he'll be sent to become a monk.
A heavier sentence might mean
he'll be dipped in a pig cage.
Dipped in a pig cage?
Oh, no. Things got out of hand this time.
His brothers
may be affected as well.
Jing Xin.
Come with me to the Mo Residence. Hurry!
Are we almost there yet?
The Mo Residence is up ahead, Your Highness.
A cherry blossom tree?
Quick, stop the carriage.
But we're not there yet.
Stop the carriage!
Your Highness!
Your Highness,
I'll go and notify them first.
Please wait here.
It really is the tree... It must be fate.
No matter how many times I come here,
the person I love is waiting for me
on the other side of the wall.
How come I awfully succeeded this time?
Oh, it's because Jing Xin isn't here.
Where is Jing Xin?
Jing Xin? Jing Xin!
Never mind. Forget about her.
I'll just climb in by myself.
This body... This process...
This body is too used to this.
Cheng Cheng! Cheng Cheng!
Cheng Cheng, it's me!
Come and catch me!
He is doing better this time.
I've lost all my limberness
from taking care of the kids for all these years.
I'm going down now, Cheng Cheng.
You have to catch me.
Here I come.
Catch me!
♪The most beautiful moment
is when I fell for you♪
♪Infatuation leads me to jump into a vortex♪
♪From breaking down the barriers
to falling helplessly in love♪
♪Every step is a desperate struggle♪
♪An opened heart, a mistake made♪
Mo Lian Cheng!
You let me fall right in front of you again.
You do that every single time!
It hurts a lot.
Men and women...
Should have no direct contact.
♪To love till the world turns upside down,
all for this moment of happiness♪
Tan Er.
(Who is that?)
(He even calls me Tan Er.)
(I've never seen him before.)
(He is quite handsome though.)
Yan Chen came late.
You're not hurt, are you?
Here, let me see if you were injured.
I'm fine.
Don't worry.
Eighth Brother knows about
our feelings for each other.
(Feelings?)
(Shouldn't Qu Tan Er and Mo Yi Huai)
(be the ones who have feelings for each other?)
(This guy said his name is Yan Chen.)
(Mo Yan Chen... Then what about Mo Yi Huai?)
(This is confusing.)
Tan Er?
You're mistaken.
I came because of...
Of course I know that
the matter with Eighth Brother
was all a misunderstanding.
And you came to resolve it.
Come with me to see my father in the main hall.
Where is Her Highness?
Please.
Please wait for a moment.
Your Highness.
Jing Xin.
Where were you earlier?
We'll talk later.
Father.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Your Highness has come to our humble abode.
Yet I did not greet you at the entrance.
Please forgive me, Your Highness.
Father...
(I almost forgot.)
(He is no longer the emperor.)
(There are so many things I have to get used to.)
Mr. Mo.
Senior.
I came here today
specifically for Eighth Young Master's candidacy.
It was all a misunderstanding.
It wasn't my intention to cause
so much trouble for the Mo family.
Your Highness' misunderstanding
did make our family
get into trouble.
I especially came here today to tell you
that I am willing to take responsibility.
To take responsibility for Eighth Young Master.
Does Your Highness mean...
Could it be...
There is no need for that.
Putting aside the fact that you and
my brother are childhood playmates,
my reputation has yet to be rebuilt.
Even if you would take responsibility,
doing so
would only tarnish your reputation as well.
It would do no good for the Mo family.
Don't worry.
I will help rebuild Eighth Young Master's
and the Mo family's reputation.
I shall wait for good news from
you then, Your Highness.
(Mo Residence)
I haven't figured out what happened
to Cheng Cheng yet.
I can't go back to Dongyue.
And I can't see my Yu Er.
And there's this mess right now.
How am I supposed to rebuild
Cheng Cheng's reputation?
Jing Xin.
Let me ask you.
Is there a way to spread one's good deeds
around fast
in Dongyue?
You could find a storyteller.
That's right.
I'll have him write a story on Mo Lian Cheng.
And
we'll get the most famous and popular storyteller
to tell the story to the people all day long.
Get it done right now.
The story must be delivered tomorrow.
Yes, Your Highness. I'll get to it right away.
Wait.
That doesn't seem enough.
Find a mason.
One that's good at carving scripts.
And find a few kids
that are smart and good with words.
We'll turn it into a nursery rhyme
and have the children sing it all across the city!
That should do it.
Go on now.
Yes, Your Highness.
Her Majesty wants to know the results
of the investigation regarding
the harem candidate incident.
That is why she has asked both of you to come here today.
So you can give Her Highness an explanation as well.
But why has Official Su
yet to report to Her Majesty?
I have failed my duties.
Please ask Her Majesty to allow
a few extra days of grace.
I will do my best to ensure that
I find the evidence that proves that
Young Master Mo was framed.
Her Majesty asked you to find the truth.
I know the truth.
Did Your Highness
find evidence that proves
Eighth Young Master stole your perfume sachet?
The truth is...
Mo Lian Cheng...
was framed.
But on the day of the harem selection,
Your Highness was the one who insisted
that it was Mo Lian Cheng who stole it.
I saw
my perfume sachet slip out from his sleeves.
I was blinded by a moment of rage.
When I thought about it again,
I realized that everyone in Dongyue
knows about Young Master Mo's
upstanding character.
But without the evidence,
how could you...
Her Majesty gave me that perfume sachet.
Once you touch the powder inside, you won't
be able to rid of the scent for seven days.
Butterflies especially favor the scent.
The harem candidates
had the largest suspicion that day.
If you wish to find out
if Young Master Mo was framed by someone,
or by whom,
you only need to...
gather
the harem candidates
and release the butterflies.
Apart from
Mo Lian Cheng and I, the butterflies
would land on...
of course the most suspicious
harem candidates.
In order to find out the truth,
this is an experiment worth testing.
There is no need for that!
This... This isn't necessary.
Everyone knows that Young Master Mo
has a good and fair character.
Even Her Highness is willing to
let the matter go as well.
Isn't that a wonderful ending?
The Mo family are descendants
of the nation's founding members.
I'm sure Her Majesty will be pleased to know
that Eighth Young Master's reputation
has been rebuilt.
I will report this matter to Her Majesty.
I was incompetent.
Her Highness was observant.
I am ashamed.
I've always known
that Official Su is loyal to Her Majesty.
However, if someone around Her Majesty
grows jealous and intends to frame another...
That is a matter that must not be taken lightly.
Yes, yes.
Your Highness is right.
I shall take my leave then.
Your Majesty, as per your orders,
I have summoned both of them to the palace.
I have verified the matter.
Su Yue La's brother, Su Jing Yuan,
has been suspected of framing Mo Lian Cheng.
Leave Su Yue La.
I still have use for her.
As for her brother...
Punish him according to the laws.
Do you also think that Qu Tan Er
spoke up for Mo Lian Cheng
during the harem selection
to earn my favor?
I suppose it may have just
been a misunderstanding
when she accused Mo Lian Cheng.
After all, she has always been
respectful to Your Majesty.
Cheng...
Oh, you're all here.
Perfect.
Your Highness.
How do you think?
Not only did I
clear your name in the palace,
but I also
rebuilt your reputation in the streets as well.
Are you surprised?
Think about how you're going to thank me.
Your Highness is indeed considerate.
I'm sure
that everyone in Dongyue
knows of my good name now.
What do you mean?
What's with that tone?
Tan Er.
The storyteller in the tea houses.
The nursery rhymes sung by the children
all across the city.
And the plaque. You did all those things?
Yes! I was trying to rebuild his...
I was trying to make sure his good deeds
are well-known and praised.
I know you had good intentions,
but Eighth Brother's mood
hasn't been the best since he saw theses
on the streets today.
Since Your Highness has helped me
rebuilt my reputation,
I'm sure Her Majesty will take pity on me as well.
I shall not trouble Your Highness any further.
What do you mean?
Are you still trying to join the harem?
I shall not disturb both of you any further.
I'll take my leave.
You...
Tan Er, Eighth Brother may appear cold and stoic,
but he is warm-hearted.
Please do not stay angry at him.
You must be thirsty.
Have a cup of tea.
Oh, right.
I just remembered that I've got some
government affairs to do.
Why don't we arrange for another
meeting on another day?
All right. I won't keep you any longer
if you are busy.
Okay.
I'll walk you out.
Don't bother. I can show myself out.
Trying to ditch me? No way.
Hold it right there, Fourteenth.
What did you give Jing Xin just now?
Greetings, Your Highness.
Do you still rank fourteenth?
Still? I've always been the fourteenth son.
That's odd.
Men in Dongyue can only marry one woman.
It takes time for a woman to carry a child...
Does that mean
that you are much younger than Mo Lian Cheng
and Mo Yan Chen?
Quite a few of my brothers are twins.
Didn't you know, Your Highness?
Twins?
I learn something new again.
Seem like they've tried very hard
to have a daughter.
I've always wanted to ask this.
Where are your other 13 brothers?
Why have I never met them?
I don't have 13 brothers.
I have a sister.
A sister?
That's another person I don't know.
Then do you have a brother named Mo Yi Huai?
No.
Oh, I remember now.
Father once said that I had another brother
before Eldest Brother was born.
But they gave him to another family
the moment he was born.
I think that was the name they gave him then.
How did you know about this, Your Highness?
(So that's why...)
(Qu Tan Er and Mo Yan Chen were childhood playmates.)
I... I have to go back now.
Please excuse me, Your Highness.
Jing Xin.
When did the two of you get so close?
Who? What do you mean, "close"?
Still hiding it.
You and Fourteenth, of course.
Well, that's because
I've been coming here with you
as your guard since young.
Naturally, we'd know each other.
Mr. Mo is quite strict with him.
Please do not misunderstand him, Your Highness.
There's nothing to feel embarrassed about.
He will be yours sooner or later.
(Didn't Her Highness always told me
to mind my distance with him)
(so that I won't tarnish his reputation?)
(Why is she saying something like this now?)
What are you thinking?
Let's go home.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Sit.
Give me a shoulder massage.
With Jing Xin guarding the palace gate
day and night,
Mo Lian Cheng
won't even have a chance to seduce others.
If he dares to come, then I'll dare to ruin his plans.
Want to be alone with her? Not a chance.
Your Highness.
What is it? Is something up?
Your Highness,
Eighth Young Master was reported
to have entered the palace.
What?
You can't go, Your Highness.
What if Her Majesty and Eighth Young Master
are discussing something important?
All right.
You've been guarding the gate
all day. You must be tired.
Go and get some rest.
I'll see
what they have to discuss
in the middle of the night!
All right. You've worked hard.
Her Highness
is like an entirely different person recently.
Always at odds with Eighth Young Master.
Why do I feel as if
you've gotten a lot smarter?
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
Stop! Let go!
How dare you be so rude to Her Majesty!
It's all right. He just spilled some tea.
Why are you here?
It was just a misunderstanding.
Cheng Cheng, why are you here?
What's wrong with him?
Should we ask for an imperial physician?
No need. I was just taken aback for a moment.
I apologize for scaring Your Majesty.
Why did you come here at this hour, Tan Er?
I've been having trouble sleeping recently.
I wanted to borrow some books from
the royal library to help me sleep,
but
I saw a suspicious figure along
the palace walkways.
I was worried about Your Majesty's safety
and got anxious, so I ran here immediately.
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
Tan Er is very considerate.
Your Majesty, that suspicious figure was me.
I am much-maligned now.
And I entered the palace in the middle of the night.
I was worried that would affect
Your Majesty's reputation,
so I took the route around
the royal library instead.
I didn't expect that I would've
alerted Her Highness.
Well, if there is nothing else,
then please allow me to take my leave.
You can leave as well.
I'll take my leave, Your Majesty.
Sorry. Sorry.
I was wrong, okay?
Then, please tell me, Your Highness.
What did you do wrong?
I... I shouldn't have interrupted you
and Her Majesty's affairs...
What are you laughing about?
Since when did Tan Er become so generous?
That you'd let someone else have your husband?
Cheng Cheng!
Is it really you, Cheng Cheng?
Then why did you pretend
as if you don't know me?
I fell from the wall.
And you wouldn't even catch me.
No. Wait.
You acted as if you don't know me
even when there was no one else around too.
Were you pulling a prank on me?
Do you know how worried I was? I...
♪I still remember the vows we made,
but the words will not come to me♪
♪I resent that we act as if we are strangers now♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fate will forever remain entangled♪
What? Did I bump into your teeth?
Please mind your propriety, Your Highness.
Mo Lian Cheng, who am I?
You are the Second Princess of Dongyue.
You are childhood playmates with
my eldest brother, Mo Yan Chen.
Please don't be so fickle-minded, Your Highness.
What's wrong with you? Do you not know me again?
I haven't even gotten my answers yet.
What exactly is going on?
Mate. You kissed me first.
Think about it again.
(It's true that I can't remember)
(how I left the room.)
(And how did she and I...)
(I only remember that I was searching
for the imperial token.)
(But why am I only missing this part of my memory?)
(This is the first time\)
(this has happened since I woke up months ago.)
(Could this have something
to do with my memory loss?)
Do you remember now?
Please do not spout nonsense, Your Highness.
All right, all right. I was the one talking nonsense.
I was the one who pulled you to me
and forced you with my tiny physique.
So what? What do you want to do about it?
Whatever the reason Your Highness
may have had for visiting today,
I ask you to stop doing it from now on.
Or else, I will have to think that
Your Highness has other intentions.
If there is nothing else, I shall take my leave now.
Could it be that he was like Tan Er and me?
Sharing the same body?
That'll make things complicated.
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪The rain showers enchant the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part for three thousand years,
no matter the calamities ahead♪
♪To love only you so deeply♪
♪I wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have to
travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part for three thousand years,
no matter the calamities ahead♪
♪To love only you so deeply♪
♪I wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have to
travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪