♪Following the way she walked through♪
♪He searches for every piece
of memory that he had with her♪
♪An unexpected encounter in the crowds♪
♪Was the start of their
destined journey♪
♪No one can tell the end of the story♪
♪Since every heart is overloaded♪
♪The dream about
blooming flowers is illusionary♪
♪Painful yet addictive♪
♪Love is too wild to be reined♪
♪Too deep to be forgot♪
♪The pain will forever
stay with the scar on the chest♪
♪He wants to linger in his dream♪
=Tears In Heaven=
=Episode 21=
Mr. Lin.
Lei Yuzheng had quite a fall this time.
It'll take a while for him
to make a comeback.
I didn't expect that.
I…
What didn't you expect?
Nothing.
Mr. Lin, it's good that
Lei Yuzheng is gone now.
Why do you still seem
to worry a lot?
You can take this chance
to get promoted, right?
Promoted?
I, Lin Xiangyuan, will never
take advantage of other people.
I was gonna fight with
Lei Yuzheng face to face.
If I win then,
it means that
I am really  more capable than him.
But the result means everything.
As long as you become the president of Yutian,
no one cares about
what means you took.
They will all look up to you.
Xieli,
what do you think
Lei Yuzheng is doing right now?
What else can he do?
He must be crying out loud at the court.
Now, the old is in hospital,
and the young is in jail.
Now it's time for you, Mr. Lin,
to take charge.
Mr. Jiang, directors are waiting for you
to join the meeting.
Look at this,
these reporters are going way too far.
They used such title as
"Yutian's stock market scandal" and
"Construction of Entertainment Center
project might be called off".
They are talking nonsense.
Mr. Jiang,
that's what reporters usually do.
As long as they can make
a big news out of something,
they would exaggerate everything.
Speaking of that,
not only those reporters,
but also our employees are
talking about rumors right now.
What do you mean?
They are all saying that
it will take a while for Lei Yuzheng
to make a comeback.
And if no one takes the lead right now,
the Entertainment Center project
will be affected.
Mr. Jiang,
everyone is waiting for you
to take the lead.
But I don't know much about
the Entertainment City project.
If I take over right now,
isn't it too hasty?
I might trap myself
later on.
By the way, Mr. Jiang,
is Fanlv feeling better?
How's her appetite?
I'm planning to go back to my hometown,
and bring some delicacies
for her to improve her health.
Fanlv is fine.
Xiangyuan, you are very thoughtful.
Ah, regarding the
Entertainment Center project,
you know it the best
besides Lei Yuzheng.
Come and join the meeting with me.
Lin, have a seat.
Regarding what happened to
Yutian recently,
I don't have to recap it.
Why don't all of you
contribute your ideas?
Such a big company
needs a leader.
Jiang, you should think of a way.
Yuzheng is in trouble,
and brother Ting is in the hospital.
Everyone must be very anxious.
But it's still important
to maintain the order
within the company.
Why don't we vote by raising hands
to elect a temporary president
to take charge for now?
How does that sound?
As far as I'm concerned,
we can skip that step.
The one who can take charge
is you, Mr. Jiang.
You should take this position.
Me?
No, no, no. How could it be me?
Don't be modest.
The Entertainment Center project
belonged to Xinsheng in the first place.
Although Yutian is in charge of
the development,
you also have the responsibility.
Mr. Jiang, don't be so modest.
Mr. Jiang, you should take it.
Mr. Jiang, I will vote for you.
I agree.
Yes, I agree.
All right. Since everyone has
such high expectation in me,
and we should take the overall interests
of the company into account.
I will just take this position for now,
and hope everyone could understand.
Of course.
But a leader cannot fight by oneself.
It's not enough to do it all
by myself.
Lin has been my assistant
for so many years.
We've built great rapport
with each other.
Everyone here has witnessed
his ability.
So I suggest that I will supervise
the Entertainment Center project,
and Lin will be in charge.
I know that Lin is my future son-in-law,
and I should have left him out of this,
so that people won't gossip about it.
But to the benefit of Yutian
and the Entertainment Center project,
I think we can entrust Lin
with this task.
Lin, the investment that
you were working on
is still possible, right?
I'll keep working on it.
I think it is possible for us to get it.
If Lin can collect money
for the Entertainment Center project,
he will be the hero of Yutian.
We can't even thank him enough.
Everyone,
at the very beginning,
Xinsheng cooperated with Yutian
on the Entertainment Center project
by offering it as a gift.
Since the board has decided
that I will take charge of this project,
I know how much responsibility I have.
I won't let anyone down.
(Police)
(Jiangkan Detention Center)
Get off the car.
According to Article 180
of the Criminal Law
of the People’s Republic of China,
the defendant Lei Yuzheng,
the prior president of Yutian,
is sentenced for 8 month detention
(Jiangkan Detention Center)
due to the charge of
disclosing confidential information,
and immediate execution is required.
(Silence)
Time is a one way road.
You can only move forward
without going back.
There's no pure luck in this world.
Everyone needs to pay the price
for their mistakes.
Go inside.
My name is Liu Siyang.
It must be the first time for you.
I can tell that
you're not used to here yet.
It will be better in a few days.
Here you are.
Xiaosu, it was on TV.
Did Lei Yuzheng actually go to jail?
I couldn't do anything about it.
There was no evidence and
nothing was beneficial towards him.
He also didn't want to explain about it,
and took all the responsibilities
by himself.
So,
I couldn't do anything
but watching him get accused.
It's all my fault.
I couldn't do anything.
I couldn't help him.
What happened to Lei Yuzheng this time
is really a big issue.
Since when...
Siqi,
Let's break up.
What did you say?
Mr. Lei went to jail,
and the chairman is in a coma.
It's all because of me.
Since the past cannot be changed,
I cannot just sit here and
have date with you.
He Qunfei, what is wrong with you?
Don't regret if you say this.
There's nothing to regret.
Things are already this bad.
I deserve whatever it costs.
He Qunfei, don't be so impulsive.
You can leave this behind.
He Qunfei,
you wanna break up, right?
From now on, let's go our own ways.
Don't you dare regret it.
Siqi.
He Qunfei, get out of here now.
Now.
Siqi, calm down.
Xiaosu.
I really appreciate your help
this whole time.
See you.
What are you two doing?
You can't fall asleep, right?
There're only two of us
in this 9-square meter room.
If you keep silent like this,
it won't be long till
we both got crazy.
You seem to be
someone who has power,
and can't bear with living in jail.
No wonder.
Rich people,
who's like you,
always seem proud when nothing happens.
As long as they get troubled,
they would look hopeless.
I look down on people like you.
What did you say?
Nothing.
I don't have respect
for people like you.
Why?
Too weak.
You hit me?
Hit me! Come, hit me!
Hit me!
Stop it!
Do it!
What are you doing?
Stand aside.
Who started first?
Xiangyuan,
was what Fanlv said true?
Did He Qunfei really fight you?
Yes.
So, you do have something to do
with Lei Yuzheng's trouble?
Mr. Jiang, I've been serving you
for such a long time.
How could you not trust me?
How could I possibly do such
disgraceful thing?
Yes.
He Qunfei fought me
because of Lei Yuzheng.
But it was because
he cares about Lei Yuzheng so much
that he lost his mind.
He's been thinking of me
as Lei Yuzheng's enemy
and always suspecting me.
But I can understand that,
because I was sent by Xinsheng anyway,
and I don't have a direct relationship
with Lei Yuzheng.
What do you mean by that?
It was my idea to send you to Yutian
for the Entertainment Center project.
If He Qunfei is opinionative towards you
just because of this,
he's really shortsighted.
You don't have to care about him.
Sure.
I will keep it in mind.
Dad, do you think it's that simple?
Fanlv,
do you think I can actually do
anything that hurts Lei Yuzheng?
Do I seem like a cunning person
to you?
I've never been fussy with you.
You loved Lei Yuzheng,
but I don't care, because I love you.
This is my fate.
I'm not complaining about anything.
But you can't just wrong me
because of him.
I'm also  flesh and blood,
and  can get hurt.
Mr. Jiang, I swear that
I never did anything
against Lei Yuzheng,
not to mention anything
that would let you down.
If you don't believe me,
you can send me to jail
to replace Lei Yuzheng.
I won't say anything.
Don't get in a rage.
Fanlv,
I can understand that
you worry about Yuzheng.
But you shouldn't wrong Xiangyuan
just because of Yuzheng.
He's your fiance after all.
If you don't even believe in him,
how do you expect him to feel?
Dad.
Mr. Jiang,
It's all worth it
after hearing your words.
Alright, I have nothing else to say.
Xiangyuan, have a seat.
She has been spoiled since
she was a kid.
Please understand and forgive her.
Mr. Jiang,
meeting Fanlv
is the best thing
that ever happened to me.
Don't worry,
I will take care of her in my whole life
and treat her well.
(Medical Room)
Fine.
Who started it?
You sure can handle a lot.
Lei Yuzheng, you just came inside.
I can understand
that you are not in a good mood.
But still, you shouldn't vent your anger
by harming your cellmate.
Read the prison regulations again.
(Prison Rules and Regulations)
Do you know why I keep you two together?
Because you two had similar charges,
you should both reflect on yourselves.
After you get out,
try to be someone
who's beneficial for the society.
Also, I'm telling you that
he has serious heart problem.
We wouldn't even let him do
the works that might exhaust him.
If you keep doing this,
you should know the consequences.
Take them away.
Go.
Don't worry, everything's fine at home.
Take care of yourself.
You too.
How was it?
I'm sorry,
but the prisoner rejected to see you.
He…
still doesn't want to see me?
Yes.
And he told you not to come again.
But he's quite worried about his father.
Is his father alright?
Please tell him that
his father…
his father is doing well.
Tell him not to worry.
Here, I brought him some books
and some food.
Please give these to him.
OK.
We'll give it to him after inspection.
Thank you.
But he's quite worried about his father.
Is his father alright?
(Jiangkan Detention Center)
(He Qunfei)
Hello, Qunfei.
Do you know
which hospital Yuzheng's dad stays at?
Miss, who are you looking for?
I'm here to see Mr. Lei.
You must be Miss Du.
Assistant He just called me.
How's he doing now?
Still the same.
He doesn't have any conscious.
So, we could just sit here and wait.
We couldn't help much.
Can I speak to him for a bit?
Sure.
Thank you.
Mr. Lei,
I went to see Yuzheng today.
He…
He's doing good.
He's just getting a little bored.
I know that the person
he worries about the most is you.
I also told him that
you are doing well too
and waiting for him to come back
and kick his ass.
Mr. Lei,
please get better soon.
If you don't get better,
you may lose Yutian
and Yuzheng would have gone to jail
for nothing.
Please wake up soon.
Let's go and see together.
What's this?
What else can it be?
Isn't it obvious?
(Announcement of Personnel Adjustment)
The guy fired by Mr. Lei
got lucky and
(List of redundant personnel: He Qunfei)
came back.
Now, assistant He is doomed.
(List of redundant personnel: He Qunfei)
Mr. Lin, please tell me
why did you fire me.
The reason is simple.
Yutian is experiencing
many difficulties.
In order to increase the efficiency
within the company,
the board decided to
simplify the company structure
and reduce the number of employees.
Is this reason good enough?
Fine.
So, is it the board's idea or
your idea?
What's the difference?
Is the job market so rigorous that
you don't want to leave so bad?
You can't decide whether I leave or now.
Mr. Lei should be the one
who decides it.
I knew you would bring Lei Yuzheng up.
Do you think it's okay
to mention him in front of me?
He can't even protect himself now.
How can he possibly
care about other people?
Lin Xiangyuan, I'm warning you.
Don't go too far.
Assistant He,
seriously,
I'm doing this for your own good.
Even just for the punch I got from you,
it will be impossible for you
to stay at Yutian.
Not to mention that
Yutian is no longer
what it used to be anymore.
It's better for you to
work at somewhere else.
Ok.
Then, I will go ask the board to decide.
The board?
Do you think that the board
has nothing to do
and they would even care about
such little thing?
If they won't, I will.
Fanlv, why are you here?
I've heard a while ago that Mr. Lin
loves making big moves after promotion,
and you have fired
many loyal employees at Yutian.
And now,
you are chasing He Qunfei away?
It's just career transfer.
And reducing staff is normal
for a company.
I don't care about other people,
but you cannot fire him.
You can think of it
as I'm pleading for him.
You can take this back.
Fanlv,
you are making this hard for me.
Alright.
Since Mr. Lin is having difficulty,
I have to go ask the board.
I will let Mr. An and uncle Wang
to grant my request.
Let's go.
Wait a second.
Fine.
Let him stay.
Mr. Jiang,
thank you so much today.
You don't need to thank me.
I'm not doing this for you.
I'm doing this for brother Yuzheng.
I don't want his people to get affected.
That guy has been really loud
for the whole night.
I'm so sleepy.
Let the boss give him a lesson.
What happened yesterday?
Boss, boss.
Who was making so much noise
that I couldn't fall asleep?
Him.
That skinny guy. It's him.
That's the person.
Hey, skinny. You got hurt?
Seems like you've got temper too.
Are your ears beaten to deaf?
I'm talking to you.
You can't hear me, right?
(Jiangkan Detention Center)
Listen,
at this place,
don't go against me, got it?
Who are you?
Who do you think you are?
Are you looking to get beaten?
He's hitting people! Police!
He's hitting people.
He's beating people up.
Stop it.
Boss.
Police, he's beating people.
Who started?
He. He started it.
It's him.
Don't you dare keep moving.
Qunfei, you have to help me.
I have to see Lei Yuzheng.
Ok.
(Civilized Prison Cell)
Lei Yuzheng,
your subordinate He Qunfei came again.
Go see him.
Captain Liang,
is he by himself?
There's also a girl.
The girl who's been coming here
often to see you
but you kept turning down.
They beg me to not tell you,
but you should go see them.
It's hard for them to keep
visiting here so often.
It's been several times already.
What happened?
I just had some nose bleeding.
It's not a big deal.
Let's go.
Bro,
how are you?
I'm good.
I said that I don't want to see her.
Why did you bring her here?
Would I be able to see you
otherwise?
Mr. Lei,
you should talk to Xiaosu a little bit.
There's nothing to talk about.
Don't you even have the courage to
hear some words from me?
We all miss you a lot.
Please take care of yourself.
Soon you will be able to get out.
Du Xiaosu,
if you come here just to
tell me these things,
there's no such need.
Lei Yuzheng.
I said that I don't want to see you.
Why would you still come here?
I hate when you act
so self-righteous.
I'm here to see you
because we are friends.
I'm your friend
who just wants to help you
as much as possible.
How do you plan to help me?
You can stay in jail for me
or you can help me fly out of here?
What's more,
I've never helped you.
Even if I have,
it was an impulsive act,
and you don't need to worry about it.
Regarding "friends",
I'm no longer the leader of Yutian,
and I'm just a prisoner.
Do you want to be friends
with a prisoner?
Lei Yuzheng,
what kind of person do you think I am?
Am I friends with you because of
your fame or social status?
Mr. Lei,
Xiaosu has been really
worried about you.
You didn't know it but
she has been running around
for you these days,
and she's pined away.
Du Xiaosu,
stop being mawkish.
Didn't you want to see me as a loser?
Watching a person who used to be proud
to fall to the bottom
like me
can satisfy your curiosity
and compassion, right?
I know what you are thinking.
The once extremely arrogant Lei Yuzheng
is no different than other people
when he has lost everything.
Maybe even worse than other people,
isn't it?
If it can make you feel better
to see me like this,
then say it.
I'm listening.
Du Xiaosu,
save it.
No matter it's your compassion
or curiosity,
you should be satisfied now.
From now on, please
live your life well
and don't think about me again,
or come here to visit me.
Not to mention caring about me.
Please leave.
Lei Yuzheng,
I...
we will wait for you.
Qunfei, you two can have a chat.
I will be outside.
Mr. Lei,
I think you have some misunderstanding
about Xiaosu.
It's been hard for her.
I know that it's been hard for her.
Just because I know it,
I have to push her away.
Don't you think that it's too selfish
to waste all her time and effort
on a prisoner?
I don't want to
get her involved in this.
But you took her here anyway,
so I had no choice other than saying
all those words.
(Jiangkan Detention Center)
So, I had no choice
other than saying all those words.
Bro,
try to think positively.
Women go check on you now
and cry in front of you.
But only few can last long.
I've seen too much.
Don't you want to talk about it?
What do you want to talk about?
You're talking now.
Actually, nothing much.
I just want to know how you got in here.
Financial case.
There're so many kinds of
financial cases.
What kind are you accused of?
Revealing confidential information
of a public company.
How much did you earn
by doing it?
Not a cent.
Then, what did you do it for?
Nothing.
You are so…
It's allowed to light a candle here?
No.
You're violating the prison regulations.
I've always been violating
the prison regulations.
Aren't you afraid that
the police might catch you?
So far,
I have never been caught.
What book are you reading?
You wouldn't know even if I tell you.
When Genius Failed
by Roger Lowenstein.
How did know that?
What about this?
The Money Game
by Adam Smith.
Cool.
No wonder they put us together.
How did you get in here?
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle
in pain and delight♪
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle
in pain and delight♪
♪Your love weeps for a withered soul♪
♪That teardrop of sadness
brings extreme beauty♪
♪Indulged in the black
whirlpool of your eyes♪
♪Dreams have never been this quiet♪