[antifan_act, hashtag anti-fan, follow]
[Choi Tae-joon]
[Choi Soo-young]
[Hwang Chan-sung]
[Han Ji-an]
[Kim Min-gue]
[So I Married the Anti-Fan]
[Episode 14]
[This Can't Be the End]
Great work to the end.
It's not the end.
It's just the beginning.
-Great work.
-Great work today.
We're home already.
Geun-young,
you've done so well to the very end.
Thanks for your hard work too.
And thank you for the ride.
Ji-hyang.
Can we cancel everything else?
No.
-Goodbye, Geun-young.
-Goodbye.
Right.
What is it?
Nothing. Goodbye.
Goodbye.
Let's go.
I can't bring myself to tell him
that I'll be moving out.
I'll tell you later.
["Who-joon's Variety Show Comes to an End!
Why the Sudden Finish?"]
You're good, Mr. Bae.
In order to shut my mouth,
you're going to cut off Geun-young first?
It's time to say goodbye
to this place too.
-Hello?
[-Ms. Lee, do you remember me?]
[I'm Kang Gyeong-su,
the editor-in-chief of Superpatch.]
Hello.
[Jae-joon]
[The person you have reached
is not available. Transferring to...]
[You should probably stop by.]
[Jae-joon]
So you're looking for an intern?
Yes, and don't mind what I said last time.
So you won't ask me
to bring you information on Who-joon
as you asked before.
You already turned down that offer.
I called as soon as I heard
you're done with the variety show.
So give it a thought.
All right. I'll give it a thought.
Anyway, if I decide to do it,
when do I start?
You're here.
I can't believe
you came here at this hour.
Come and grab a drink.
I mean,
we used to drink soju together
way back. Remember?
What did you want to say to me
and made me come here?
If this is about In-hyung, forget it.
I already watched the show.
You already know how my In-hyung
got into the audition by using you?
Well, that's that.
I was wondering if you knew
reporters are suspicious of you two.
But that history is true,
although it'll concern you.
But how are you going to explain it?
I'm sure you won't spill everything.
That's something
you can only explain
when all three of us are there. Right?
-What do you mean?
-It's all in the past,
but frankly,
you were concerned that I know.
So I suggest that all three of us
go back to Shooting Star.
I don't know what you're up to,
but that won't happen,
so quit it.
Quit it?
But oddly enough,
why am I
always the first one
to smell your weakness?
Right, I needed those eyes from you
before I could continue this conversation.
You think I'll never win against you,
don't you?
Fine, I guess that could be the case.
But I can defile your name,
no, maybe your entire life.
No, maybe not your life,
but the life of the one you love.
I think Lee Geun-young
might end up suffering the most.
So? Do you get it now?
Back when In-hyung was
destroyed in my hands
and when you think of Geun-young now.
I wonder what hurts you more.
Will you run off without
taking responsibility like back then?
Go have a good discussion with Mr. Bae.
Why are you calling me this late?
You canceled the show
because of Geun-young?
What are you talking about?
You're now going to work with Jae-joon
after getting this information?
Who says I'll work with him?
Did he come and see you?
Well, Jae-joon kept making a case
about you and Geun-young,
so I decided to take care of that.
Then you should've talked to me!
Have you been practicing communication?
Talk to you about what?
-Young-suk.
[-And you.]
[it's not like I banned you from dating.]
But think about how you got here.
You won't benefit
from a love scandal right now.
Don't you want to sing?
Don't you want to perform?
Can you abandon countless numbers of fans
who only have their eyes on you?
Hang in there for a while.
I'll take care of Jae-joon.
If you provoke him and the world finds out
about you and Geun-young,
who will it be harder for?
The only way to protect her is
to let go of this quietly.
[Superpatch]
[Who-joon tries
to make himself look cool!]
[His true nature was...]
This is
the application for your staff ID.
I need your address and number.
All right.
[Staff ID Application]
My home address...
Yes, I'm the one who's moving in today.
I wanted to ask you for the exact address.
This is a good item.
-It's cute.
-Thank you.
You should get some more of these.
[Mr. Joon: Are you really moving today?
I should be there if it wasn't for work.]
[Just Lee Geun-young:
Don't worry and focus on work.]
-You're here.
-Hey.
["Who-joon Keeps his Smile
Despite his Busy Schedule"]
He was way too busy
to continue with the variety show.
He has been working so hard
to prove that theory.
Anyway, the show is already over.
Why hasn't he mentioned the merger?
My gosh, these biographies are
giving me so much work.
[Delivery.]
Delivery?
[Yes, it's a TV.
Are you Ms. Lee Geun-young?]
That's me.
[This is from Kim Ya-ma.]
I'll be right there.
Goodness.
Where should I put it?
Well, I... Right here.
Okay. Please put it down...
-Okay.
-right there.
Anyway, you look much prettier in person.
What's going on?
You said you were too busy to come.
But still, I had to come
on your moving day.
Is this it? This is the house.
-What do you think?
-Looks nice.
Anyway, why did you get me a TV?
I'm a guy who comes out on TV.
-You need one.
-It must've been expensive.
Anyway, do you have to live alone?
You insisted on moving out.
The shooting is all over,
so I didn't think it's right
for me to live there.
Why not? That huge house is vacant.
Of course, I knew how easy it was
to live off someone
while I was crashing in that huge house.
But I'm not that brazen.
I still feel too anxious
to have a woman live out here alone.
Even though it's just an internship,
but I got a job.
I need to live my life too.
Looking cool, Geun-young.
Hello, Who-joon.
You recently finished shooting
"So I Married the Anti-Fan."
[What was it like to be
on a variety show for the first time?]
First of all, it's a shame
that we had to wrap it up so quickly.
I couldn't be on a variety show regularly
because of my overseas tour,
but this was a great experience
for me to be on a weekly show.
[In a way, the theme of the show
seemed bold and new,]
and some said it could be dangerous
since this was your first try.
I can see why my fans could've thought so.
But first off,
nothing was dangerous on the set.
I was able to make great memories,
and it was a great experience.
[You're now back as a singer.]
[When will you release your next song?]
I'm in the process of preparing my album.
A movie I had filmed will premiere soon,
so please look forward to that.
Young-mi, how do you print the documents?
You'll need the company ID.
Give me your laptop.
I'll have the data team set it up.
Oh, all right.
[Superpatch]
You can take this.
-I have it unlocked.
-Okay.
-Sure.
-Thank you.
[Spigen Entertainment Audition Project]
-It must be tough.
-It's all right.
I'll do my best.
Okay. It's already the semi-finals.
The show is going live starting this week,
-so you have to be more than perfect.
-Okay.
-Keep it up.
-All right.
Oh, and about Who-joon.
Can you ask him to make a visit backstage?
You know, coming to show you his support.
Okay. I'll ask him.
-Please do that.
-Okay.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
["Who-joon, at his Media Preview"]
I wonder if he's done.
["Walking Confidently Between His Fans"]
[I'll be there
as soon as the preview ends.]
[Mr. Joon]
[Battery low]
[Bus Stop]
["Breaking News!
File on Who-joon's Two Faces Exposed"]
["Anti-Fan Exposes Who-joon's Two Faces"]
[Who-joon's anti-fan,
Lee Geun-young, had a laptop]
["Anti-Fan Exposes Who-joon's Two Faces"]
["The File on his Two Faces,
Written by Anti-Fan Lee Geun-young"]
[filled with files
exposing Who-joon's duplicity]
[by date and incidents.]
[The exposure of his relationship
with an anonymous woman]
[became the biggest issue,]
[especially his record of violence
against that said woman.]
[According to the file,
he committed violence against a woman,]
[and he continued to meet her
even after his violence.]
Was there a serious conflict
between you and Ms. Lee during the show?
Then was the show canceled
because of your discord?
Haven't you seen the news?
Ms. Lee publicized a file
exposing your duplicity.
-Tell us.
-Give us an answer.
-What is this?
-How do you feel?
-Who's that woman?
-Please give us one word.
-Say something.
-I'm sorry.
-How do you feel?
-What's your take on this?
-Do you admit to everything?
-Tell us something.
-Who-joon, one word!
-Say something!
When will she get here?
-Ms. Lee.
-Ms. Lee!
How long have you been preparing
the file on his duplicity?
You have more things to expose, right?
Did you do the show to report on this?
-Did you only want a job at Superpatch?
-Superpatch?
-The laptop on the news is yours, right?
-Wait, what are you...
-Say something.
-Excuse me. Coming through.
-Ms. Lee!
-Please excuse us.
She'll make an official statement soon.
Please go back.
-Tell us something!
-Just one word!
-Did you do it?
-What will you do about this?
What a mess.
-Excuse me!
-Who-joon!
[The person you have reached...]
Ji-hyang, I need to go see Geun-young.
There are reporters
in front of her place too,
and of course, our office
and your studio apartment.
Let's go to that penthouse.
Why won't you pick up your phone?
My phone died.
-How can it be dead?
-Wait, but I...
-Geun-young, are you okay?
-How can she be okay?
Anyway, what's going on right now?
You didn't see the news?
Superpatch took the file
from your computer.
Anyway, how did they know where you live?
["Who-joon's Two Faces Exposed"]
You can take this.
-I have it unlocked.
-Okay.
Thank you.
Can you sue them for defamation?
And where's that guy
who knows a thing or two about the law?
You should call Who-joon.
Tell him that it wasn't you.
Tell him it's a misunderstanding.
Well, I did write it.
Why did you save it on that computer?
Su-hwan! Why are you blaming her?
I'm just frustrated, that's all.
[Spigen Entertainment, CEO Choi Jae-joon]
[CEO Bae Young-suk]
Hey, Mr. Bae.
What's happening to the merger?
Why did you ignore my...
Hey! What did you say is going on between
Joon and Lee Geun-young? They're dating?
Then why would she
publish an article like this?
-What?
[-I'm an idiot for trusting you.]
["What's in the File
Exposing Who-joon's Duplicity?"]
You're unbelievable. You should
check the facts before you make an offer!
Let me get charged.
You should go.
Bye.
But those eyes.
This can't be right.
Great job, you two.
I told you to be careful
of that anti-fan, didn't I?
Ji-hyang, what did you say?
She's starting to build trust with us?
Let me check once again.
There's nothing to check.
I saw the photos of her laptop.
I must be getting old and dull.
I should've destroyed her from the start.
She wouldn't have exposed it.
Someone must've seen her laptop.
You already know
how we started off on the wrong foot.
Do you think people tell celebrities
to be always careful?
Didn't I tell you that
everyone around is ready to betray you?
It doesn't matter if it's true or not.
This news will be a part of your image.
You can't meet any reporters now,
so you stay out of this.
The news already got out,
and it's bound to die down
if we stay in dead silence.
What are you doing?
You don't know what's going on over there.
What if she records this phone call?
What are you doing? Give it to me.
You can't patch this up anyway.
I'll take care of this. Just trust me.
[Mr. Joon]
[The person you have reached
is not available. Transferring to...]
You can't see him
even if you went there now.
I knew it. It wasn't you.
It sounds like you were disappointed.
But that file.
I did write it.
As you know, I once hated him.
It sounds like
you completely forgot about that time.
He stabbed you in the back
while getting pretentious with the media.
Yes, I once thought
he was a two-faced person.
But now,
I think I know him a little better.
What kind of power does he have?
You still trust him
even after what he put you through?
Let's just say
we have that much trust between us now.
I see.
Does he think so too?
I don't care what he thinks of me.
If he's in a misunderstanding,
he's probably hurt
with a sense of betrayal.
I need to explain this to him
and apologize.
Geun-young.
You must like him a lot.
It's love, isn't it?
I saw you two together.
Let's go.
He should be here.
His house is
probably infested with reporters.
Jae-joon.
I'm not trying to help.
This time, I'll wait and see what he does
to protect you.
But...
this happened to In-hyung too.
He was an irresponsible kid
who couldn't protect her.
I just don't want you to end up like her.
You know, Jae-joon.
Love doesn't mean
you want to protect the other
just for responsibility.
I hope you'll get to realize that.
[Geun-young, both you and In-hyung]
[can never seem to get a grasp
of how I really feel.]
[The door is locked.]
-Is he gone?
-Yes.
I need my phone.
He took it.
I'm not a kid. Has he gone crazy?
You know how he is.
I can't stay here. I need to go see her.
Joon, it's not a good idea
to be there today.
We'll deny everything
to the press tomorrow,
so let's go see her
when things get quieter.
I know this is tough for you,
but please stay here for my sake.
I didn't disclose that file.
Ms. Lee, but you wrote it yourself.
I wrote that long ago...
Fine. Let's say
you wrote that a long time ago.
But did you ever consider
how it can impact him?
That's why I wanted
to apologize to him face to face.
It's my fault
for writing it and not deleting it.
You want to see Joon right now?
You're very selfish.
We're here trying to stop
these articles from flooding out,
but it sounds like you only want
to undo this misunderstanding.
I won't say anything else.
Just let me call him and apologize.
I'll call him in front of you.
[Just Lee Geun-young]
Ms. Just Lee Geun-young.
If there's any trust between you two,
give him some time to patch up this mess.
[Give me]
[just a little more time.]
["Who-joon's Agency Releases
an Official Statement on the Exposure"]
[Once again, nobody is
interested in what I have to say.]
[Shooting Star]
Hey, I told you to lie low for a while.
Why are you here?
If this is our official statement,
what about Geun-young?
Then what?
How are we going to patch this up?
Don't you know one article is
enough to destroy someone?
You should've talked to me
before you released this.
This was an emergency.
Patching this up was our priority.
And you want to make a fool out of her
just to patch up our situation?
How long do I have to pretend
like I'm the only one
who's good and special?
Do you think
you're the only one who hates that?
I'm doing everything for you.
What if the public
turn their backs on you...
Well, forget that.
What about your dream
of living as a singer?
Do you want to call that off too?
Do you want to give up on everything
you did to this day over some girl?
Starting with her,
I could put some things down
and live more freely.
Listen to this punk.
Why?
Did she ask you to do this?
I knew she wouldn't be an easy fight
when she refuted everything I said.
Did you meet her?
How did you threaten her this time?
I did. I asked her
to stay quiet for your sake.
Have you been
threatening people and lying
whenever things like this broke out?
If someone just heard you,
they might think I'm a con artist.
I made you who you are today,
and now you're defying me?
And
I'm someone who knows everything about you
from your beginning to this day.
How dare you threaten me?
Do whatever you want. I'm not scared.
[Shooting Star]
Young-suk.
Since when have you taken advantage
of people's weaknesses?
Don't you care how others get hurt
while we try to save ourselves?
Do you think I'm doing this for my sake?
I'm doing everything for your sake.
I'm not doing anything bad.
You're right.
It's all because of me.
But that woman
who's suffering because of me
never says anything
knowing it'll make me more troubled.
But you? Instead of saying you're sorry,
you're trying to avoid the situation
with another lie.
The man I used to know wasn't like this.
You saw how people reacted
very positively.
[GBC]
Excuse me, Director Song.
Will you take one more look at him?
Mr. Bae.
There are tons of boys like him.
Stop following me around, okay?
Wait, Director Song.
But please give him another chance.
Mr. Bae.
Hey, you're here. Great work.
The chief producer is
dying to work with you and all.
You must be hungry. One second.
I forgot to withdraw some cash.
I only have 10,000 won.
You should grab something to eat.
-What about you?
-I have to meet someone.
I'm busy to death thanks to you.
And I already feel full
just to see you get bigger by the day.
I'll call you after the meeting.
-Go eat.
-Okay.
See you later.
Excuse me, Director Song!
Goodness, Director!
You used to be
such a genuine and nice guy.
I figured you lied for my sake,
that you won't do it again next time.
I thought it'd be tough for you too,
so I always felt very bad.
But come to think about it now,
you didn't do it for me. It was for you.
You think I do this for my sake?
It's for our sake.
It's for our trust.
Young-suk.
You brought up
our contract renewal last time.
Right.
Fine.
What do you want?
Tell me what your terms are.
I'm not going to renew
the contract with you.
Goodbye.
Joon.
What was just terminated
isn't our contract,
but our relationship as two people.
[Shooting Star Entertainment Company]
Joon!
Are you sure you won't regret this?
Ji-hyang.
Things are pretty tough for me.
I'd love to have you around
in times like these.
Okay.
I'm done here too.
We'll release a correction first.
Let's do an interview with Mr. Choi first.
And call her.
You remembered this in that situation?
-Thanks.
-Let's have a good run.
Hey, why didn't you pick up yesterday?
Hey.
I... I'm so sorry.
Don't be sorry. I should be sorry.
Don't worry about it.
I'll take care of everything.
Okay. Get some rest.
["Who-joon Leaves his Agency!"]
What the heck is Mr. Bae doing right now?
-You're here.
-Yes, sir. I looked into it,
and they received a photo too.
This is a photo of the man
who had that ring.
Who on earth is he looking for?
And about that lawyer
you told me to look into.
I found an old photo of him
while digging up his history,
and they're the same person.
Sorry?
Look, there's a correction.
["Lee Geun-young
did not Disclose the File"]
I told you that
Geun-young wouldn't do that.
Goodness, I'm so relieved.
Then did he leave his agency
because of her?
Exactly. What's going on?
Wait, what is this?
Then I'll publish an article saying
after you checked with Ms. Lee,
you came to know that
the exposure wasn't done by her.
-Thanks, Hee-gun.
-It's us, you know.
Joon, one second.
It looks like
things have gone haywire.
I'm getting a call.
["The Public Furious at Who-joon's Lies"]
Yes, Reporter Kim. I see.
"The Public Furious at Who-joon's Lies"?
"Oh In-hyung recently drew attention
as a trainee at Who-joon's former agency."
"However, she turned out
to be his first love."
"Who-joon's shameless history"
"of abandoning his first love
over success has been exposed."
Let me see that.
"Not only that, everything about his past
had been made up for his success,"
["The Public Furious at Who-joon's Lies"]
"including his age,
hometown, and education."
"The public became infuriated
at the truth"
"behind his fabricated life."
What on earth is going on?
["Who-joon's Past Exposed,
Is his Image Purely Manufactured?"]
His two-faced act had been
much dire than I thought.
Do you think you can deal with this?
What more are you hiding from everyone?
Is there anything else to be exposed?
Everything is over.
Don't look into the owner...
[It's about the people
who were looking for that ring.]
They said it seemed like
he was looking for his father.
-His father?
[-Yes.]
[Then are you done with the ring?]
Yes, but there is one more thing
I need you to do for me.
Find out some information
on Who-joon's family relations.
You too?
Yes, Reporter Choi, thanks. Good work.
Okay. Yes.
All right. Bye.
He says the source was anonymous,
but it's so obvious.
It has to be Jae-joon.
No.
I don't think it's him.
Don't you get it
even after everything he did?
I need to make some calls. One second.
[I'm on your side. Are you all right?]
[Just Lee Geun-young]
[Give me just a little more time.]
[Mr. Joon]
What are you doing?
My brother, this thing is heavy.
[Spigen Entertainment, CEO Choi Jae-joon]
You had to know
this was your last chance, right?
I'm sure giving you a chance was
our father's big mistake.
Your agency will be closed as of today.
I told you that I'll patch this up.
How?
You've always been this brazen.
I thought he gave up on me already.
Does he have to do this
to a son he practically discarded?
Our father said
a businessman must know
when to abandon things.
Do you think he doesn't know
this is the time to abandon you?
Wrap it up.
Big brother.
I told you not to call me that.
This is the time? But hasn't dad
and Jae-hee abandoned me long ago?
[Spigen Entertainment, CEO Choi Jae-joon]
But
why does this only happen to me?
Why am I the only one
who gets abandoned by that family?
Two, three.
[Spigen Entertainment Audition Project]
["Oh In-hyung Dreams of Success
Between Two Men"]
[She's a total gold digger.]
[I'm sure she's the one
who exposed him too.]
[Did she hit on the director?]
[Don't live your life like that.]
[Go date men instead of singing.]
-Hello.
-Go ahead and practice.
Director.
Did you see it? People are a little...
You should probably drop out.
-Sorry?
-They're here at the TV station too.
Who-joon's fans swarmed in.
You can't perform
in a live competition like this.
Director, please give me one more chance.
I'm sure you'll get another chance.
Thanks for your hard work.
Keep practicing, everyone.
-Goodbye.
And from here.
[Spigen Entertainment Audition Project]
[In-hyung]
[The person you have reached
is not available. Transferring to...]
["Who-joon's First Love
Drops Out of the Audition Program!"]
You aren't going to ask me why?
You all think I did it.
I'm not here to ask you that.
But now that I see you,
I can tell that you aren't behind this.
I'm glad at least one person understands.
It turns out
I didn't know everything about Joon.
I didn't know him fully either.
Jae-joon, are you trying to say
he had always been like that
and he deserves everything
in this situation?
I know you've been disappointed in me.
I won't make any excuses
regarding In-hyung
or everything with Joon.
I didn't want In-hyung to get hurt.
No, more than that,
what I hated was how she trusted him,
despite how much Joon hurt her feelings.
I was very jealous of him.
I knew everyone first.
And those chances were all meant for me.
But he took everything.
That's why I despised him to death.
But you never hated him
with all your heart.
No, I still hate him now.
That's who he is to me,
but In-hyung is still getting hurt.
There's nothing I can do for her.
It's all over.
What do you mean?
At first, you and I had
a pretty good relationship.
We hit it off pretty well,
and we only had each other
to vent on how evil Joon is.
Back then, anyway.
We can't seem to be
in each other's life anymore,
just like In-hyung.
Now that I say it out loud,
I always end up
becoming a jerk to everyone I like.
Jae-joon, you aren't
such a bad person to me.
Why didn't you tell me that
a little sooner?
What you just said right now
felt like something you'd say
to humor a jerk and a rebel.
Thanks for coming today.
You can't go out anyway, right?
We finally get a glass of soju together.
I thought you'd punch me.
This is unexpected.
Didn't you think it was me?
I knew it wasn't you.
It's not like
I was completely honest with you.
This is what I hate about you.
You always stay patient
and worry about everything by yourself.
Well, I was pretty surprised too.
You deceived everyone and lived your life
with such a straight face.
I hated myself too.
And I regret
how I couldn't be
completely honest with you.
You don't need to say that at this point.
I'm not looking to make up with you.
Do you hate me that much?
People say there are people
you can't help but hate for no reason.
We weren't like that at first.
Hey, man.
You're the one who started all this, okay?
If you chose to go with me,
if you didn't abandon In-hyung,
if you didn't live in those lies...
And?
Does it help you to hate me so much?
There's one more thing I haven't told you.
That ring.
I found the owner.
What are you hiding this time? What now?
It belonged to my father.
You were abandoned by your father too?
How far do your lies stretch out?
Jae-joon.
[The fact that he had everything freed me
from the guilt for hating him.]
Let us
learn to let go now.
[Cho-Yoon Law Firm: Cho Hae-yoon]
It's him.
He's your father.
[Cho-Yoon Law Firm: Cho Hae-yoon]
[So? Do you think you can
figure this out all by yourself?]
It was you?
[This is my specialty.]
[Come back.]
[I guess you can still hold out.]
It was you.
It felt like I abandoned you,
so I was very sorry.
I think I know what to do now.
Joon.
Are you sure about this?
This is the way to protect
everyone I love.
In-hyung, Jae-joon,
and above all,
Geun-young, who's tormented
just because she loves me.
Okay. Let's go inside.
Did you have to take things that far?
Why do you think it was me?
Because that's who you are.
And what makes you so confident before me?
At the very least,
both Joon and I
aren't cowardly like you are.
Cowardly?
Yet Joon wasn't cowardly
for abandoning you and leaving?
You started dating me
even though you like him.
So why did you get involved with my life?
Why?
Why? Why did you get into my life?
[Who-joon Holds
an Urgent Press Conference]
[I stand before you today to apologize
to everyone from the bottom of my heart.]
[I've always received
much more love than I deserved.]
But I'm not anybody special
like you thought I was.
I'm not a musical genius
who studied in the U.S.
or a son of an affluent family
who's highly involved in charity works.
All these charming aspects of my life
were lies created
to make Who-joon seem special.
[I deeply apologize to everyone
who showed me so much love]
["Who-joon Holds
an Urgent Press Conference"]
with all of their hearts.
If it hadn't been for you...
Everything is over.
You knew better than anyone
how desperate I've been.
Do you feel better
now that I crashed down?
It's over.
I'll disappear from your life.
No.
I don't believe a single word you say.
How about this?
In-hyung.
And I know many people are interested
in my relationship with Ms. Oh In-hyung.
Yes, we had a special relationship.
But she became a victim
to many misunderstandings and rumors
that she used me for her success.
I hope Ms. Oh will not suffer
from any speculations or rumors.
I came a long way with the wings I got
thanks to those lies.
I realized I had nowhere to return to
with the wings made of lies.
I admit to everything as reported,
and I will gladly accept any decisions
you make at your disposal.
[Did you hear of JJ
and Oh In-hyung's accident?]