[antifan_act, hashtag anti-fan, follow]
[Choi Tae-joon]
[Choi Soo-young]
[Hwang Chan-sung]
[Han Ji-an]
[Kim Min-gue]
[So I Married the Anti-Fan]
[Episode 12]
[Did Fate Bring Us Here?]
Geun-young.
This isn't an accident.
This isn't a prank, accident,
or a confusion.
So don't be suspicious from now on.
This was it? This was your surprise?
-What a success.
-It's not like I made this up.
Didn't you read the comments?
Didn't you see how his fans were
determined to set the TV station on fire?
I finally get to burn this place down
just as I wished ten years ago.
Really?
I wonder what the building is made of.
There's no talking to a guy like you
who thinks all is going well.
Either the TV station will burn down
or you'll end up burning me up.
The result will be the same.
Don't be like this.
Let's go out for some beer.
You said they'll burn this place down.
Let's leave before they come.
How can you want some beer right now?
Tomorrow is the shooting.
What are we going to say to them?
Darn it.
What? Are you finally worried
now that you think about tomorrow?
Of course. If you're a human,
I'm sure you'd be worried.
But do you think I came back
to work with you in ten years for this?
Do-yoon. Will you keep
making me anxious?
Why? Do you
finally feel anxious and stuff?
And you? Anxious? No way.
You always think everything is well.
I'm sorry, but stop talking.
Why should I?
If you keep talking,
I'll want to kiss you.
No, that's not what... Well, I...
I actually, well... What I meant...
I mean I'm actually anxious right now.
You have a knack for causing trouble.
No, it's no trouble. Well, I...
So? You won't?
-What?
-Let's just get in trouble, then.
Go home safely.
Okay.
Didn't you just tell me to go home?
What is it? Should I stay?
No, you should go.
Don't read any comments,
and get a good sleep.
Keep your door locked.
Bye.
I'll watch you get inside. Bye.
"This isn't an accident."
He said it's not an accident.
Then he grabbed my arm like this.
Hey, how can I go home in peace
if you're like this?
You should go.
[Going up. The doors are closing.]
She's so cute.
That was embarrassing.
[So I Married the Anti-Fan]
[You witch. You pretended to be
an anti-fan to go after his lips.]
[My Who-joonie]
[I got chills.
What a big twist like "The Sixth Sense."]
[Must Have Who-joon:
Will they let this fraud be on TV?]
"She'll only come to her senses
after a good beating."
[So I Married the Anti-Fan]
Things seem more serious than I thought.
Should I just kill Director Han?
When will he make me look sane on TV?
It's not like
I can blow up the TV station.
And what's Ms. No doing?
She acts all nice in front of me,
but she never does anything.
Right.
I have girls who show me their support.
[-You traitor.
-Is she a psycho?]
[Joon Scumbag]
[Go Back Who-joon]
-What?
[-How can an anti-fan change?]
[The Official Community
of Who-joon's Anti-fans]
Even you girls abandoned me?
[The moderator here. Let's hold off
from withdrawing our support for her.]
[Poll]
[It looks like
she wanted to give him physical damage.]
I knew it. I knew it, the great moderator.
Yes, I need at least one person
who will take my side.
Anyway, why does this moderator
hate him so much?
What do you know about Who-joon?
[Spigen Entertainment, CEO Choi Jae-joon]
[Poll]
[Who-joon Sniper, Moderator]
I can't even go outside
because of his fans.
Taking a walk before the shooting is
now a luxury I can't afford.
This place looks as good as my room.
Stop laughing.
-You just made trouble.
-It's not trouble.
The internet is in an uproar.
Why isn't this trouble?
Right, I thought
you were talking about yesterday.
No, not that!
Hey, you got here early, Geun-young.
You're here early, Geun-young.
Geun-young, did I mention how we hit
the highest viewer rating yesterday?
Mr. Han, did I tell you
people insulted me the most yesterday?
You finally hit the rock bottom!
All you have to do is jump back up...
To be completely honest,
here's the thing, Geun-young.
We were a little concerned,
but when we saw that moment on camera,
how can we not put that on the show?
His fans will calm down in a while, okay?
What has gotten into you?
You're giving me an empty talk.
Is that so?
And it's not like you two actually kissed
while you were dating.
I mean, at the least,
at the very least, that won't happen.
Of course, it won't.
It won't even happen at the most.
Okay.
Geun-young, it's just a variety show.
Geun-young, why did you read the comments?
Goodness.
They've always been bad.
But they are especially horrible.
They need to learn a lesson.
Unbelievable. They make me so angry.
Anyway, are you sure
you really had a tough time?
You're looking even better.
-Right, Kang-yeon?
-Yes.
Really? Are you dating someone?
What?
But Geun-young, don't let anyone find out
until the show ends. Dating...
Did something good happen to you too?
Are you the one who's dating someone?
No, everything is troubling for me.
Come on. Goodness.
Over there.
Let me see that.
Who-joon, you're here.
You saw me coming in.
Did you watch the show yesterday?
Who's this?
Our youngest manager is here instead.
But the good news is that
we hit the highest viewer rating.
What's the bad news?
Well.
To be completely honest,
here's the thing, Who-joon.
We were a little concerned,
but when we saw that moment on camera,
how can we not put that on the show?
Your fans will calm down in a while, okay?
It's not like you two actually kissed
while you were dating.
At the very least, that won't happen.
Hey, that was a laugh, right? Right?
Isn't this much better than
letting the show get ignored?
Yes, anything is better than that.
Let me get ready.
Okay.
You are dating someone.
You're overreacting.
Who's dating?
What? I mean, Geun-young looked great,
so I'm just teasing her.
Anyway, Joon. The youngest kid is here
instead of Ji-hyang?
-Yes, he had to do something else.
-I see.
Hey, rookie manager.
Good luck today, okay?
[Client: Oh In-hyung]
[Notice of Contract Cancellation]
Fine, let's call it over.
Let's terminate the contract,
and put an end to our relationship too!
Who says you can end it here?
For whose good?
Did you contact Cho-Yoon Law Firm?
When will he get here?
[Yes, I did.
But the CEO asked you to come in.]
What?
Okay. We researched the things
couples want to do the most
when they're on a date at home.
So today, you're going to do nails
and resting on each other's lap.
Well, the timing is a little odd.
Things will get worse
if we do that at this moment.
We'll do a great job today
and make them root for us.
I knew it.
Who-joon is so good at show business.
Then let's get started right away.
-Get ready.
-Geun-young, you got this.
We'll get started right away.
Please get ready. Let's tidy up.
You already knew
they couldn't care less about anything.
Let's make it work.
It's okay.
Doing nails and what now?
No idea. Something like
lying on your lap or something.
I don't think that's a bad idea.
Gosh, this is nice.
Look at how well they get along.
Isn't this much sweeter than we expected?
-Right.
-What's with them?
Just a little harder.
-I was worried for nothing.
-That's good.
I knew they'd do well.
[Jealous? Then we can be sweet too.]
What is this? He told me to be here.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
This is Mr. Cho, our CEO.
Cho Hae-yoon.
We never met, Mr. Cho.
I wondered who ordered me to come and go.
We looked it over.
She only has a year left
of her seven-year contract,
and the clauses on the termination
weren't worded strongly.
It looks like your initial contract
with her was a bit casual.
So you're saying it's my fault?
Whatever. So you're saying
I can't do anything about her leaving.
Of course, she'll have to pay a penalty.
But if she takes it to court,
it'll put us in a tight spot.
So you believe
I have nothing to earn from this business?
You already have been
earning nothing from your business.
That's why I'm telling you
to find another way.
It's not that we won't.
However, it won't do any good
for your agency to sue an artist
who only has a year left in her contract.
And I called you to figure that out.
The chairman called us,
and he told us
to do business that makes a profit.
Getting angry won't get you anything.
You know who I am,
yet you dare speak like that?
Do you think you'll still be a CEO
after talking like that to me?
You should discuss it with the chairman.
I have a meeting to attend.
What the heck is wrong with him?
Hello?
Is that so? When can I get it?
Where are you going?
Did Jae-joon tell you
to keep an eye on me?
Well, I'm sure you've been reporting back.
-Get in the car.
-I'm leaving that agency.
So pretend like you didn't see me.
Will you go around
handing out your profile on your own?
It won't make you look good.
I've been your manager for five years.
Do you think
I'm a guy who only reports to him?
Get in. You'll catch a cold.
Anyway, is that girl, Lee Geun-young,
really all right?
All the stories about your first love
and your song leak went away
after yesterday's episode, so that's good.
But something doesn't feel quite right.
You saw the show. It was an accident.
And if something didn't feel right
or felt eerie,
you should've called Director Han.
You didn't do anything until now.
But the chief producer called me
and said they had the highest rating,
so I had nothing else to say.
Ji-hyang, tell him to be more careful.
Think about how concerned we get
about his kissing scenes.
Yes, I'll talk to him.
Anyway, something funny happened.
People have been
sending that leaked song to each other,
[Shooting Star Entertainment Company]
and it apparently became a huge hit.
There's no official source,
so many made a demand on streaming sites.
Who-joon,
everything you do is a huge success.
Anyway, let's release that song.
But Mr. Bae, it was already leaked.
Why don't you make some edits...
Hey, it's not my first day at work.
I listened to the song, and it was fine.
There's no need to tweak around.
What's fine isn't the song,
but how it doesn't cost you any money.
Hey, it takes a lot of work to use money.
So who's the female singer?
Well, she's an indie singer.
It was already on the guide track,
so I don't know who she is.
That's even better.
There are lots of great indie singers now.
Let's blow it up with the media,
then make an official release.
We can show people who she is
when she performs.
-It's...
-I'll talk to the songwriter.
Who-joon, if anything,
you're one lucky guy.
When something bad happens,
something good stops it from blowing up.
Joon, what's your plan?
Just pretend like you didn't know.
It's not like we'll tell everyone
who she is.
It'll end up getting disclosed.
She was that desperate.
I wanted to do this one thing for her.
Don't worry about it, Ji-hyang.
Everything will be fine.
What happened to your trip to Japan?
Someone already came and retrieved it.
Someone took it? Who did?
I checked their information,
but they wouldn't pick up the phone.
I told others to look for them.
It seems like
it wants to go farther away from me.
We'll find it.
While we look for the ring,
let's meet those men first.
Okay. Please contact them.
Right, Ji-hyang.
I have another favor to ask of you.
I've only been eating out lately,
so I got sick of it.
-My gosh.
-Hey.
Thank you.
I'll take it up for you.
No, it's okay. You're a busy man.
Go take care of the song leak.
Anyway, I'm a bit worried.
About what?
Do you think I can't carry these upstairs?
Not you, but Geun-young.
I'm not sure if we should
keep letting her live there.
You should go.
-Okay, bye.
-Go home, then.
-Bye, Ji-hyang. Thanks.
-Get some rest.
Okay.
If he was going to come,
why didn't he say so?
Wait, what's all this?
You can't go out for a while,
so you'll be stuck at home.
-And?
-And what?
Are we going to cook?
Are we going to cook at home?
You probably haven't eaten.
And it's not mealtime yet.
Since many of your fans
already know about this place,
and I feel uncomfortable and anxious
whenever the crew comes here.
I should probably move out
before I get in trouble, right?
-Don't.
-Wait.
It'll be more convenient
for you to come and go without me.
How will it be more convenient?
It'd feel too empty here without you.
Think about it. You left your traces
on everything in this house.
I clean up the house every day.
I didn't leave any of my stuff outside,
and it's all in there.
No, you can't go.
Just stay here for now.
You've been having a tough time
ever since you met me.
You ended up getting ugly comments
and too much attention.
-So you know.
-Stay here.
I'll be good to you.
Great job.
Let me make you something.
What is it?
Get ready to be blown away.
-Hello.
Hello.
I'm Lee Won-ho,
the manager for Oh In-hyung, a rookie.
She's a rookie of our agency,
so if you have any new programs...
Ms. No.
Mr. Kim.
You're a big shot now.
Come on. A little, right?
You're still the same.
What are you staring at?
-Oh In-hyung.
-I'll do my best.
-Please give me a chance!
-Why can't that great girl get her break?
-Who's Oh In-hyung?
-Hello.
She's what this industry calls
an old rookie.
Right, Mr. Kim.
Aren't you doing an audition show?
-Hello.
-Yes. Isn't she at JJ's agency?
JJ's doing this audition,
but she wasn't on the list.
-What?
-But right.
We were told to only go with real rookies.
Hey, you've worked long enough
to know better.
She used to be a trainee with Who-joon.
-She can bring in lots of attention.
-Hello.
Really?
-Do you know their number?
-I'll find out.
Please do.
You must be a good cook.
But you're the type
who ends up making too much food.
A real cook is someone
who makes just about enough.
You didn't know, did you?
I have everything planned out.
Wait, you probably
have never thrown out food waste.
When you don't have
any leftover ingredients to throw out,
you truly feel proud...
Are we expecting company?
No, you should check.
This is scary.
Hey, what's going on?
What are you doing? Open up.
Hey!
-What's going on?
-Hey!
-Hello.
-Come on in!
-You didn't have to.
Thank you for coming.
Don't mention it.
I was going to quit my part-time job
if they didn't let me take the day off.
It's my honor to meet you.
We only passed each other by, but...
Yes, Shin-hyuk.
You know my name? It's such an honor.
I think that's enough greetings.
I was actually cooking.
-I see.
-You can cook?
It's nothing special.
You can take a look around.
-It's so huge.
-Take a seat.
Don't be like that.
-Over here.
-It looks great.
-I love it.
-My gosh, look at how big it is.
What is this?
Was that a surprise?
So? Wasn't that a bit touching?
Go hang out with them.
-I love the sofa too.
-It's so comfy.
I've seen this place on TV.
-Have you been well?
-Yes, I've been doing great.
-It's so uncanny to be here.
-Isn't it huge?
-Please enjoy.
-Thank you.
Thank you. It looks great.
I didn't think you'd actually invite us,
and you invited us here of all places.
What did you think of him?
I trusted you, sir.
Don't mention it.
"Sir"? Is he older than us?
He was 21 when he debuted in 2014,
so 6 years later, he's now 27.
I believe we're all the same age.
You know a lot about me.
I actually began to study law
thanks to you, Who-joon.
A top star can't trust just anybody.
I thought you'd need a friend
who'd understand you before the law.
So I decided to get into this
as I listened to your music.
Please pass your bar exam and help me out.
Thank you.
Shin-hyuk, you're a funny guy.
Is this house empty
when you two don't shoot?
Well, I think he stops by
from time to time.
-Yes.
-Who-joon, you need another drink.
Oh no.
-I'm sorry.
-Are you all right? Stay calm.
-Don't touch it.
-My gosh.
-Don't touch that.
-You okay? I didn't do that on purpose.
Don't touch it. You'll get hurt.
-It's fine as long as you aren't hurt.
-You should put these on.
Why do you have these here?
-These are his.
-What?
-Yes, these are mine.
-I see.
It's a bit short for me,
so it'll be perfect for you.
You should get changed.
It's too dangerous.
-I'm getting drunk.
-Just one more.
I want another drink too.
We seem to drink a lot whenever we meet.
Am I bothering with your studies?
It's all right. That's life.
I love the view here.
Seeing you here
makes you look like you live here.
I mean, there was a time
when we criticized him for his character.
So why is he so nice to you?
What?
I don't know.
This house. This life.
He's very different, isn't he?
Right.
His world is
completely different from mine.
So? Are you intimidated?
What? Hey, why would I be?
I know you.
-When times are tough...
-I'm good at being patient.
you don't just stay patient,
but you try to understand.
No one else may know,
but you know I do, right?
You didn't do anything wrong.
Come on, girl.
Gosh, whatever.
I'm going back for another drink.
Wait, I think that guy is
worth your patience.
What? Don't say that.
No? Let's go.
Great work.
Okay, then.
-Get home safely.
-Okay.
Bye, everyone. Thanks for coming.
Aren't you leaving?
-Me? I should go.
-She'll leave.
This is our set,
so we're going to clean up together.
I see. Then we should help.
No, let's go.
Let's just go home.
Who-joon, please stay healthy
until the day we meet again.
-All right. Go home safely.
-Thank you.
I'll take her home safely, so don't worry.
-Please do.
-Bye.
-Let's go.
-Yes, you should go.
-I won't go out.
-You'll be late.
-Bye!
-Bye, Shin-hyuk.
-Okay! Bye!
-Try to sober up.
-Make sure Mi-jung gets home.
-Just go.
-Bye!
-Bye, Who-joon!
I had a lot to drink.
You probably did.
They're all heavy drinkers.
Are you okay?
All done.
-Thanks.
-I should clean up after them.
It's not easy to have guests over.
So why did you do this?
I'm glad if you're glad.
Gosh, but I had so much fun
with my friends for once. Thanks.
You must be tired. Go home and sleep.
Aren't you leaving?
I had too much to drink,
so I have to sleep here.
But there's nowhere to sleep.
Where are you going to sleep?
Don't worry. There are lots of rooms here.
I can sleep on the second floor.
Anyway, do you still sleep there?
But there's a bedroom.
It's not even my house,
and I'm comfortable enough there.
Sleep in a bedroom, okay?
Goodnight.
[Mr. Joon]
Going to sleep.
[Are you asleep?]
[Just Lee Geun-young]
[I'm about to. Aren't you going to sleep?]
[Mr. Joon]
[I should.]
[Goodnight.]
So cute.
["Who-joon's Duet Song Released"]
It's Ms. Lee Geun-young.
She had a meeting today.
This is the CEO.
-Hello.
-You must be Ms. Lee.
Doing all right on the show?
Yes, I guess.
Please be good to Joon.
Make sure he keeps his reputation up.
Okay.
Then good luck with your meeting.
This way, please.
You're here. Please take a seat.
[Shooting Star Entertainment Company]
I'm sorry I asked you to come.
It's all right.
Things were quiet out front too.
I guess my popularity is all gone.
You're responsible.
Whatever.
He received an offer for an ad.
Again? Gosh, congrats.
You should treat me.
You and Joon will be
making an appearance together.
Me?
Who is this crazy advertiser?
She finally came to know herself
after reading "Socrates" again and again.
It's a company that worked with him
soon after he debuted.
I thought he might get cut off
after the last episode,
but they actually liked it.
What a loyal company.
Well, of course, they'd want him,
but why me?
You must've been troubled
through everything that has happened,
but you have a positive spin on the media.
It's difficult to create
a memorable character like you.
Also, your image is
the opposite of Joon's image,
so you'd be effective in marketing.
Really?
Since you're working alone, it might be
difficult to process the contract.
If it's all right with you,
I'd like to help you while working on his.
Right.
But if people begin to hate me
and start resenting me
once the ad gets out,
do I have to take responsibility?
Why should you?
That's my part. Don't worry.
You won't have to.
And something like that won't happen.
You can stay confident, Geun-young.
And I've never done anything of that sort.
It's not like
we're all born in front of cameras.
Also, you won't play a huge part,
so don't worry.
Did you look at her storyboard?
Will they make her do weird stuff?
Of course, I did.
It'll be great on her image.
Don't get off. Please. This is too much.
Bye, Ji-hyang.
So you're doing whatever you want now?
-I thought work was work.
-I see.
You did this
because you were that professional?
Weren't you trying to drive me insane?
It's not like that, Jae-joon.
Hey, In-hyung is signed with my agency.
How dare you fool me without a word?
If I told you, would you have said yes?
You're now pushing the blame on me,
just like you pushed In-hyung at me.
I really want to stop discussing
something like this with you.
Jae-joon, we were close enough
to help each other out like that.
And like I said,
I'll do everything as I want.
I see, if you were dying
to help her release a song,
why didn't you disclose her name
and that you two were exceptionally close?
You can't do that.
That's why I keep saying you're a coward.
The least you can do is
beg me to be good to her!
Jae-joon!
What happened to you, really?
You weren't like this.
Don't you...
Don't you feel bad for her?
You've changed a lot.
Joon, are you all done?
There's one more thing we have to do.
We'll talk on the way.
You got an ad gig. Once you do this,
it'll be a jackpot. We have to hurry.
Who-joon,
is it tough for us to meet today?
You can't talk right now, can you?
Don't I feel bad for her?
I'm the one
who was the most concerned about her.
What can I do
to make both Jae-joon and In-hyung
happy?
Don't you think this is too showy?
-No, it looks great.
-Really?
Have you eaten anything?
-Hello.
-You're here.
You can get your outfit
and makeup done over there.
Please follow Ra-ra.
Shall we?
She's here.
-Is that all for Joon today?
-Yes.
-I'm done.
-Looking great. Look in the mirror.
-Once you're done...
-You look great.
-Doesn't she?
-Ta-da.
-Gosh, you look wonderful.
Pretty, isn't she?
What's going on?
Isn't the skirt too short?
Bring her a blanket or something.
Why? She looks pretty.
I mean, it's getting chilly,
so bring her a blanket.
What is this outfit?
Bring something that suits her.
Fishnets? How embarrassing.
What do you mean?
Are you saying I look bad in this?
That's not what I meant.
-The concept...
-All right, then. Let's begin.
[Bowling Lounge]
-Okay.
-You'll be fine. Let's go.
Let's go.
Can you pull this up?
If you had to wear this,
you should've said no.
That's the concept. What can I do?
Am I that embarrassing?
That's not it.
Other people can see you.
Yes, so are you that embarrassed about me?
Joon, we have to go.
Okay.
Darn it.
Her legs are way too pretty for this.
[Spigen Entertainment Audition Project]
It's the preliminary round,
so be bold with your evaluations.
We'll only get less than half of these
on the show anyway. Let's do this.
-Okay.
-All right.
[Open Audition for Rookies]
Thank you.
Sure.
[Open Audition for Rookies]
Hello, I'm Oh In-hyung.
-Hello.
-Nice to meet you.
But you aren't a trainee, In-hyung.
I'm not. I debuted once before,
but I'm as good as a rookie.
Do you not have an agency?
No, not at the moment.
I came here today
thinking of myself as a rookie.
-Please look forward to my performance.
-Sure.
Now that you're here,
let us see what you got.
Okay.
♫ Please do not leave me ♫
♫ I'm just a small child ♫
♫ Do you want to see how I crumble down? ♫
♫ I'm also just a small child ♫
♫ Ah-ah, once again ♫
♫ I've been left alone ♫
♫ Ah-ah, where will ♫
♫ My unending heart journey to? ♫
[Spigen Entertainment Audition Project]
Have you gone crazy too?
I think I really am.
I'm not even scared anymore.
You said you don't have an agency
right in front of my face.
I don't remember the last time
I looked you in the eyes with confidence.
It sounds like
that was a gratifying moment for you.
I just realized
I was still capable of that.
I heard I was like that before.
"Before"?
Did Who-joon say that?
I don't think you remember,
but you were always behind him, you know.
Is that why you're afraid?
That I may become famous?
Don't get your hopes up.
You won't be seen on TV.
Okay. I'm moving out of that home
you found for me.
So that's that.
-Where are we going?
-Just hop in.
Thank you.
I've always wanted to do
something like this with my girlfriend.
Girlfriend?
Why? Aren't you?
Nothing.
Anyway, "this"? Like going on a drive?
We've done that a lot.
You're right.
Anyway, when did you get your license?
Why can't you drive?
Wait, are you on your way
to make me practice?
Haven't you heard? Couples should
never teach each other how to drive.
People get into fights.
So where are we going?
I just wanted to show you
how well I can drive with one hand.
You came out to show that off?
Of course. Look how good I am.
Don't get off.
You want to take a walk here?
We've walked around together a lot too.
It was never a real walk.
You're right.
Why didn't you tell me before?
But I guess I can walk. Let's go.
I got you comfortable shoes.
Why did you get me these?
Stop getting me stuff.
I heard giving shoes is like
asking them to leave.
Exactly. You got me another pair.
You're practically begging me to run away.
No, if you run away
with the shoes I gave you last time,
you can come back in these.
People might think we had plastic surgery.
We have to run away if we run into my fan.
I see, that's why you put me in sneakers.
We're standing out.
Let's take these off.
Are you sure you'll be fine? But...
It's fine.
Your shoelaces came undone.
What are you doing? I'll do it. Get up.
From now on,
I'll always tie your shoelaces,
so hang tight to your senses
and just follow me.
I get it, so get up.
Can't you just adore me
when I say things like these?
You're adorable.
Let's go.
Oh, right. And that thing.
Can you change my name on your phone?
How can you call me a punk?
When did you see that?
That's what it says
on your social media page, "yam-a," punk.
-You saw that?
-I look at everything.
I'm your anti-fan.
Anyway, what does it mean?
-It's from my father's ring.
-What?
That's what it said
on the inside of his ring. "YAMA."
Then your father is...
I'm sure he's doing well
somewhere out there.
Don't look at me like that.
You were just curious.
And you've seen that ring too.
-I did?
-Yes.
The ring you picked up in Japan.
I was glad that I lost it,
but you, my fool, found it.
What? That's...
But I lost it again.
I went to get it back,
but someone else already picked it up.
Do you know what that ring is?
Yes.
It looks similar to the one
I picked up in Japan.
Wait, is it yours?
Did you lose it
when you were at the hotel?
Yes.
Wait, can you let me off here
for a second?
-What? Why?
-Quickly. Can you stop the car?
Wait.
What's going on?
You can go home first, okay?
What's happening?
You wanted to see me first.
There's no reason.
It's great to see you like this.
Hey, about that ring you lost.
Yes, I found it thanks to you.
I was going to thank you for that.
May I see it?
Sure.
Here.
What is this ring?
[YAMA]
Right, it's nothing special.
But it was a bit too nice
for me to lose it.
It would've been really bad
if it hadn't been for you.
What's wrong? Is something going on?
You know,
I still
wanted to understand you.
I wanted to be a good friend for you
to the end.
What's wrong? You're scaring me.
When I hated Who-joon,
you bashed him with me and took my side,
and it was honestly comforting,
so I was grateful.
Are you saying
you don't hate him anymore?
Geun-young, I already told you.
He's trying to fool you!
What about you?
When I fell for your lies,
how did it make you feel?
Did you have fun?
You knew whose ring this was
from the start.
Even if I still hate him,
I can't be a friend
who'll take part in something like this.
She hasn't even called. Where did she go?
Hey, where have you been?
I'm sorry, really.
What's wrong? What's going on?
This.
Why is this...
I was such a fool.
It's okay. What's going on?
This ring is
putting a lot of people in trouble.
Anyway, why did you go there
to get it back yourself?
You could've told me.
Of course, I should.
It came down to this because of me.
Don't do that from now on.
Don't try to do everything on your own.
I'm here for you.
Why? Why are you staring at me?
You'll poke a hole through me.
You suddenly became a different man.
It's scary.
Would you rather have me be a little edgy?
It'd make me feel at ease, actually.
Anyway, what could this mean? "YAMA."
["Former Trainee from Who-joon's Agency
Shocks the Audition"]
[Jae-joon]
It has been a while.
Did you call to apologize?
What are you talking about?
You should apologize to me.
Hey, let's set the record straight.
Did you have to say In-hyung was
a trainee at Who-joon's agency?
[It won't do anyone good
if they get involved again, no?]
If you know that so well,
how can you let her sing a duet with Joon?
-What?
[-Gosh.]
You had no idea either.
You only adored him all the time,
but look at how ridiculous you've become.
[Once I say a word
about your beloved Joon,]
you know what will happen, don't you?
So you better keep him under control.
Hey, so the duet you mentioned...
You just...
Darn it, he hung up on me first too!
How did he know?
One second.
-Hey, Ji-hyang.
[-Mr. Bae wants to see you.]
[Where are you?
He's going to your place right now.]
No, I'll go visit him. I'm out anyway.
Okay.
I have to go.
You have to work at this hour?
Of course, do you see
how hard your boyfriend works
by day and night?
Boyfriend?
Wait, then do you go around
doing something like this
with someone who isn't your boyfriend?
Is that who you are?
You must be insane.
Go, now.
Bye.
I can't seem to make myself leave.
-Go back inside.
-Let me see you go.
Okay, then.
Let me get charged.
You should go. You'll be late.
Bye.
You'll be late.