(All characters, locations, organizations, religions,)
(and incidents in this drama are fictional.)
(3 months later)
This is a miracle.
Look.
(Episode 15)
How is this possible?
How could this actually happen?
How can your tumor get smaller...
every time we take the scans?
Right?
By next week, it will be gone.
Is this possible?
Did I misdiagnose you?
No, you didn't.
- I'm sure you didn't. - I've been a doctor for decades,
but I've never seen a case like yours.
I've never read anything like this in any of the medical papers.
I guess I was lucky.
Have you been taking something else in secret?
Did you tell your family?
I bet they are over the moon.
What did your boyfriend say? Isn't he so happy?
Seeing your scan, you can have the wedding you postponed.
I'm going to postpone that a bit more.
Why?
He...
went away far from here.
Was everything a dream?
Did all of that...
truly happen?
Were you really...
in my life?
Tak!
How did you get my number?
You never changed your number.
But still. You don't get to call me so carelessly like this.
I wasn't careless. I was very careful.
I told you who I was in a text message.
You said I could call you, so I called you.
Whatever. I won't sign with you.
Can I ask why you won't?
Isn't it obvious?
I made a debut.
I don't have time to write.
I'll be in trouble if people find out that I'm a writer.
You will be?
Of course. The reputation I built...
Forget it. Anyway, my answer is the same. End of the story.
If you'll be in trouble, I have the upper hand.
What?
Then, you must get on my good side.
What did you just say?
You're not on social media or the Internet.
And you had no intention of becoming a celebrity...
or an actor. Isn't that the reputation you built?
But it turns out that innocent guy, Park Young,
was a superstar online writer.
Do you even know what "superstar" means?
But you're not supposed to know these words.
And he picked Young Prince as his pen name himself.
Did you just laugh at me? You're mocking me, right?
I didn't pick my pen name.
My mom did.
Well, it suits you. It does.
Anyway, I might share what I know with some people.
And you'll be in trouble.
Are you blackmailing me?
Blackmail? No, I'm trying to appease you.
Look. My hands are empty.
You don't need a weapon to blackmail people.
Yes, you do.
Do you think your scary tactic will work on me?
I clearly told you where I stand that day.
I won't work with anyone...
other than Ms. Tak Dong Kyung.
I see. Is that all you need?
(Tak Dong Kyung)
Yes. What do you want?
This is Cha Joo Ik.
I know. What?
Come as soon as you're done with work, my dear chief manager.
What?
Are we good?
I hope I'll get a positive answer from you.
I must get going. I'm busy.
Gosh. Seriously.
What's up with this guy?
- Who was that? - Cha Joo Ik.
How come he hasn't changed even a bit?
He must still think that he's my senior colleague.
Seriously. He can be so rude.
Why did he tell me to come to him without any explanation?
Gosh. And he wants me to come to his house.
Ji Na, can you drop me off somewhere in that vicinity?
I'll do you one better. I'll drop you off at his house.
Ji Na. Why don't you come with me?
You've met Mr. Cha before.
I'm good.
- Ji Na. - What?
You're not talking to him anymore?
- You know... - You know what?
You don't talk to him?
- I'm sorting things out. - Why?
He and I both need some time.
I don't think he's going to call you...
until you call him first.
Probably. That's what he's like.
Is that why you like him?
Don't try to get in my head.
You won't fall for it.
You're all grown up now.
I've been driving you around from and to the hospital...
for three months as your guardian. So I'm a grown woman now.
I'll pay you back for everything...
throughout my life in installments.
There's no need. You already did.
Your recovery is good enough for me.
I'm so proud of you and grateful to you.
Same here. Thank you.
I'm grateful to you,
my auntie, and Sun Kyung.
And...
So you already signed all the writers you just listed?
No. I plan to sign them.
I found an office.
The name of the company will be Top 10 Media. What do you think?
Is being in the top 10 publishing house your goal or something?
No. I'm declaring my resolution that I'll only sign writers...
that would be in the top 10.
Whom are you declaring that to?
You.
I heard you've been feeling good lately, so it's my official offer.
Come work for me. I'll take good care of you.
How will you do that?
I have a lot of money.
I could brag all I want as well if I never had to prove it.
Fine.
I'll show you my bragging has teeth through your salary and position.
Do you want to be my supporting evidence?
Chief Manager Tak?
Gosh.
I guess you must be confident that you can sign all those writers.
Well, I guess I am confident.
How come you didn't include Lee Hyun on the list?
You know that her rank is going up every day, right?
- I do. - Then, why won't you sign her?
It's not that.
I'm letting her be for a while.
Why would you do that?
She's not some cultural asset or artwork.
She's a human being.
Go and snatch her whether as your girlfriend or writer.
Don't regret it later.
She probably needs some time now.
Gosh. Why are you both...
Time is overrated.
Do you think you'll have all the time in the world?
You are taking it for granted.
I've been in your shoes,
but you don't need time.
You need courage.
Hey, that was pretty cool.
I can't believe I'm giving advice to Cha Joo Ik.
- "Cha Joo Ik"? - You're not my boss yet.
I'm leaving.
I'll get back to you on your offer after I think about it thoroughly.
Hey, that's not how I trained you.
Don't think about it thoroughly. Just do it half-heartedly.
Yes. This is how you trained me.
You're the one who needs to do things without so much care.
Think about it briefly and make your move quickly.
But don't some feelings...
get clearer as time goes by?
Like what?
Longing.
Seriously. You always have a comeback.
That's how I made my living.
Gosh. I thought I would be the one schooling you today.
Goodness. I'm so sick of getting schooled.
You always teach me something.
And I always end up learning from you.
- What? - I'm leaving.
Bye.
Gosh, kids these days.
Recharge.
Why couldn't you cross the street?
Dong Kyung.
Are you crazy?
- Dong Kyung. - Why are you holding my hand?
Wait up.
Gosh. You've completely recovered now. You're so strong.
So what? Are you not happy?
No. I'm happy.
See? I'm wearing the shoes you bought me!
What do you think? I'm wearing blue and gray today.
You look good.
Gosh, that was so mean!
Why did you say it like you don't even care?
This shirt means so much to me.
Treat it nicely.
Look. Doesn't the shirt make me look so fresh?
Yes, it does. It looks like only you're in summer.
Aren't you cold?
That brings me to my question. Can you give me your cardigan?
What?
Forget it.
Your cardigan won't match...
my overall outfit today.
See? I have a really sensitive sense of color.
If I were a professional colorist...
Hey.
It's not too late.
Do you want to go to school for that?
Forget it. I was just joking.
I have a real dream now.
A real dream? What is it?
I won't tell you until I fulfill it.
Hey.
I think it's too small for you. Do you want the cardigan?
- Gosh, you don't have to. - Okay.
- Fine. - What?
- Give me your cardigan. - Forget it!
Touch my arm. It's so cold!
It's cold!
This is why you catch a cold!
- I won't catch a cold. - Don't be silly.
My body is strong. This is how I can stay strong.
- You're embarrassing me. - Ta-da!
To me, everything feels like a miracle.
Whenever I wake up every morning,
I wonder if I'm dreaming or not.
I sometimes sit there and think.
We're not dreaming.
Dong Kyung, you had all the herbal tonics I gave you, right?
I'm telling you. That must've been it.
- Is that it? - No.
No? Then,
is it because of your cooking?
Is that it?
I think that might be possible.
"Might be"? Then, what is it? What's the secret?
- Love. - "Love"?
Right.
This is all thanks to my biggest love for you.
After going through this,
I realized a lot.
So I'm going to move back to Korea.
- What? - All of a sudden?
It's not sudden. I was planning to move back.
Kevin is settling everything in Canada.
No matter how much I think about it, I can't bring myself to leave you.
I can't go back now.
What about Kevin? Is he okay with the move?
He's totally on board.
He values family a lot as you know.
He's so excited to live with you guys.
No way.
Then, I get to eat your food every day?
Yes.
Ask me to cook for you all the time. That's what I live for.
Since we're sharing, I have to tell you something.
I'm going back to work.
- What? - What? Already?
No.
Right. It's too soon.
I want to work.
My doctor said I'm fine now.
Did we ask you to go out and make money?
You should rest. It's okay to take a break.
Right, Dong Kyung.
Or do you want some money?
That money was yours, to begin with. Use that money for now.
I'm sick of just lounging around.
Well, scratch that. I didn't mean it.
I'm not sick of lounging around,
but I want to have fun while working.
I guess I need work in my life.
No.
Her work ethics is making her life harder.
- No. But still. - I'm really okay, Auntie.
I can't live my life like some sick person all my life...
when I'm so strong.
I'm eating a lot too.
She has a point.
She twisted my wrist.
She was super-strong.
Why did you make her twist your wrist?
That must've been exhausting for her.
Auntie. Are you serious?
She twisted my wrist. I'm the one in pain.
Why would she be tired?
Be quiet. Just eat. Eat up.
Zucchini again?
- You're killing me. - When do you start?
The photo of her and her boyfriend is still her phone wallpaper.
I don't think they broke up.
Then, what? What happened between them?
I don't know.
She never talks about him.
She just told us that he had to go back to the States.
That's all she said.
Let it go.
If she didn't tell us, there must be a good reason for it.
Exactly.
Exactly. What's the reason?
Can you ask her? I'm too scared to ask.
Hey, I'm scared too.
No. Let it go.
She just started getting better. Let's not upset her.
Stress is the cause of all illnesses.
Right.
Your package has been shipped out.
Your package was left at your door.
What on earth did I buy so much of?
Even so. How come I haven't heard from him all this time?
Gosh. That can't be.
No way.
It can't be, right?
Right.
The look on your face tells me you were doubtful it'd be me.
Was I right?
Someone told me...
that I needed courage, not time.
I don't know if she's right,
but I want to take a chance with what she said.
So I came.
That must've been Dong Kyung.
Why? Did she tell you the same thing?
Yes.
But...
I couldn't muster up my courage.
I don't think that's the case. I just beat you to it.
- I didn't call you because... - Sign with me.
You broke the contract first.
You want another contract?
Let's start working together first.
I can't go a day without seeing you again.
I know you feel uncomfortable and I caused all of it.
But I won't apologize for it.
I'll be the bad guy.
Follow my lead and go with the flow.
You're not a bad guy.
You can't even leave a crying girl alone.
So sign with me.
I'm a kind man.
No. I don't think I can write romance novels anymore.
- Why not? - I don't think it's my thing.
You can't write a romance novel based on me.
- That's not what I meant. - No?
No!
I've been thinking about this a lot,
but I don't think I have a knack for writing romance.
You read it too.
I'm a writer. I must create stories.
But why do I always write based on my life?
So what we have between us is romance?
- What? - If it is, drink with me.
- All of a sudden? - Make another mistake.
I'll put up with all of your mistakes.
Make a mistake with me.
It wasn't a mistake.
I didn't make a mistake.
What I did wasn't a mistake.
That's how I felt.
Your story is romantic.
My heart just skipped a beat.
That won't get me to sign with you.
That's not what I was asking.
If you didn't get it, forget it.
Let's stop here. I'll come back another time.
Another time? When?
When you want to sign with me?
Or...
when you want to kiss me again.
Auntie.
Aren't you going to work?
How come you're not answering me?
At this rate, you'll be unemployed forever.
What's wrong?
What I said about you being unemployed made you this sad?
I'm not dreaming, right?
Did you have a dream?
I didn't go to your dream.
I missed you.
I really...
I really wanted to see you.
Then, you can see me.
Look at me all you want.
We were apart for one night. Why did you miss me this much?
What are you marking every day?
You know...
- Good days. - Good days?
Of course. Every day is a good day.
Are you going to eat before you go?
You said you're meeting your old colleagues today.
Ms. Tak, how long has it been?
It's been so long since we met. And the first thing you tell me...
is that you're working for Mr. Cha.
- It sort of happened that way. - What?
I'm a chief manager now.
I'm going to steal all of your best writers.
You'd better be on your toes.
Why would we be?
Steal them. Go ahead.
Mr. Park is the one going under, not me.
There are tons of publishing houses we can work at.
Is Mr. Cha recruiting more employees?
We're just starting out.
He'll probably need more people once we get things going.
- Then, scout me first. - Scout me next.
Then,
I'll stay here.
I'll stay here and aim for a higher position.
Did you hear him?
He's always on the lookout to get a promotion.
I guess he wants to boss us around with the promotion.
Gosh. Your company seems to be doing so well.
It's hard to see such an ambitious man these days.
Wouldn't Mr. Park prefer someone like him?
Good for him.
Since we're talking about him,
let me tell you how crazy it's been with Mr. Park lately.
What? What's going on?
So you're telling me that Ms. Jo here...
is going to be in charge of my novel, right?
I'm a chief manager now.
Hey, this isn't right.
I told you a thousand times.
To writers, their novels are like their babies.
And my baby is very shy around strangers.
I see.
Gosh, come on.
Ms. Jo is great at her job.
Why don't you work with my beautiful editor here?
She has to be beautiful for me to work with her.
Come on, man. Goodness.
That ugly man always asks for pretty editors.
Seriously. He never changes. Hence, his pen name.
- Hey. - What?
What did you say to me when I told you...
- that I was quitting? - What?
You told me this kind of incident would never happen again.
I only stayed because you promised me that.
"This kind of incident"? What do you mean by that?
What? Did you already forget what you did to Ms. Tak?
How could you have not learned anything after that incident?
I'm so sick of this man. I quit!
Ms. Jo. Don't be like that. Sit down.
Why are you begging her to stay?
Let her quit.
She's not the only editor in Korea.
Hey, man. Be quiet!
Hey, did you just yell at me?
Listen. Don't be like that, Ms. Jo. Sit down, please.
Hey, are you bringing in that coffee or not?
Did you go to Blue Mountain to grind the coffee beans?
I'm upset as it is because my rank has been going down lately.
Both of you are getting on my nerves. Darn it.
Gosh.
Goodness.
Jijo King.
Do you really not know why the ranking of your novel...
has been going down lately?
How can anyone tell you the truth...
when you can't work with anyone?
What kind of nonsense is that?
The readers these days have low standards in novels.
They just don't understand my sophisticated novel.
That's why that loser,
Shanghai Park's novel has been topping the list lately.
Hey, Shanghai Park...
What are you still doing here?
What are you staring at?
Are you staring at me?
This is driving me crazy.
These new editors are looking down on me these days.
Gosh, no way.
I'm not looking down on you. You were talking about me.
"That loser, Shanghai Park".
That's me.
- What? - What?
Should I explain to you why my novel is topping the list?
Or why readers nowadays don't read your novels?
What? You were Shanghai Park?
Seriously. You never see what's in front of you.
Right.
Every editor tried out writing at least once.
I was so surprised.
So after that incident, whenever Mr. Park sees her,
he always tries to read her...
What? What's up with him?
I don't know. What's up with him?
How come you didn't tell me?
- What? - The promotion and Shanghai Park.
Well...
Didn't I tell you? I'm the chief manager now.
Ms. Jo...
Okay. I can understand why she didn't tell me.
But at least, you should have told me.
- "You"? - "You"?
Well, sweetheart.
- "Sweetheart"? - "Sweetheart"?
Since everyone shared something,
I'll share my secret now.
I'm...
dating her.
- What? - What?
Did you know about them, Mr. Cha?
What? That Da In was Shanghai Park?
No. That Da In and Jung Min are dating.
What?
Gosh. I didn't see that coming at all. Kids these days are sneaky.
Anyway, let's talk in person.
In person? Where?
Your office.
Send me your address. I'll head over now.
- Hey. Wait. - Bye.
Will you marry me?
- How much is this flower here? - Hold on.
What's this?
Is this the office?
How is this...
You said you got an office. So I came.
But you only have two desks here?
It's a modest office, isn't it?
I prefer keeping things simple these days.
I don't have a vase at the office.
What are you talking about?
I didn't get this for you.
Why would an employee buy a flower for the CEO?
Then did you get it from someone?
I obviously...
bought it for myself.
You even buy flowers for yourself? What a life.
Are you being sarcastic?
No, I'm just relieved.
I'm just relieved to see that you have a happy life.
Stop changing the subject.
You said I was going to be the chief manager.
That's why I came. But what's this?
You are the chief manager. You're Chief Manager Park.
Then where's my team?
You're the manager...
and a member of your team.
Chief Manager Park.
That's how startups work these days. You should know that.
And what's this news about Da In and Jung Min going out?
Oh, right. You won't believe it.
Da In's last name is Kim, right?
So I found it weird that her pen name was Shanghai Park.
And it turns out she used "Park" because it's Jung Min's last name.
I saw them almost break up and make up again.
It was unbelievable.
Are all writers like that?
Why do they create their pen names based on the person they like?
- Did you meet Ji Na? - What?
Yes, I did.
But she told me she doesn't want to write romance novels.
Apparently, she's not up for it anymore.
So what? Are you're going to give up on romance?
What else can I do? She says she's not up for it.
But judging by her behavior,
she doesn't seem completely uninterested.
I guess you haven't given up on romance.
I encourage writers to write whatever genre they want to write.
No, not that. I was talking about the romance between you and her.
At this rate,
you guys will fight and end up going to Bali to reconcile.
"Bali"?
I prefer Hawaii to Bali.
I obviously wasn't being literal.
Do you lose your common sense when you like someone?
I didn't know that about myself, but I guess so.
Forget it. Give me the contract. I'll make her sign it.
I already gave her the contract.
But you didn't get her to sign it?
I wouldn't put it like that. Let's just say I postponed it.
What are you doing? Are you playing hard to get?
Yes.
But deep down inside, I'm trying to lure her to sign it.
That's what he said.
I think I picked the wrong guy.
I agree.
How are you going to beat that guy?
How did you end up liking a guy like him?
- I don't... - What? You don't like him?
I do.
You're finally acknowledging your feelings.
You're all grown up now.
I have no idea what to do.
Ji Na.
Once you reach an ending, it means it's time to write a new novel.
But who knows how that one's going to end?
How would anyone know? You'll only know once you're there.
What if I give up and never finish it?
That's still okay. You can always write a new novel.
Some stories just don't have a clear ending.
That kind of stuff sometimes end up attracting more attention.
You know Young Prince, right?
After he suddenly stopped writing, he suddenly got more subscribers.
Because he stopped, he ended up becoming a legend.
So just do it. Give it a try.
I'll always be there to support you.
What about you? What happened to that guy?
The doctor.
I'm waiting.
You're waiting?
Yes.
He went somewhere really far away.
It's somewhere I can't follow.
Plus, he wouldn't want that either.
So I'm going to stay healthy and happy until we meet again.
Otherwise, he might nag at me as soon as we meet.
He wants me...
to be happy for as long as I live.
Hey. The weather's nice today. How about we go for a drive?
Sure.
Did you think I'd say that?
You're not done writing.
Can't I just leave it here?
No, finish it.
Finish writing that and sign the contract.
That's what I'm waiting for.
You're like a thief.
- Are you threatening me? - Ji Na.
You were determined to do anything for me.
Did you forget how determined you were that day?
Did you?
I already signed it. Take it.
Thank you, Ji Na.
Now go ahead and write your next episode.
Hey, you should try writing a novel.
Don't be absurd.
I heard all editors have experience writing novels.
I heard you guys get motivated...
to write your own stuff as you edit manuscripts.
Gosh, but I had absolutely no idea that Da In...
would actually put that into action.
You used to be a good writer back when you were in school.
You should also...
give it a try so we can share this pain together.
I don't know if your goal is to make me write...
or if it's to give me pain.
But I can see that "pain" is the object of the sentence.
Forget it. I have nothing to write about.
What do you mean?
Just think of it as a diary.
At first, we all start by writing about ourselves.
I see. Like you?
And how did that work out for you?
Forget it.
I dug up my own grave.
But what's that flower? Who gave it to you?
I'm just going to think that I got it from someone.
I see. It's pretty.
Yes, it's pretty, right?
What should I do now?
If you're done with work, you can get ready to go home.
No, not that.
I mean, from now on.
My sister's okay now,
so there's nothing more I ask for.
But after having experienced something so big,
it really makes me think a lot.
Think a lot about what?
Just about what I should do from now on.
What I should do for a living. Stuff like that.
Should I help you out with that?
How would you like to run a second location?
- What? - You told me you enjoy this job.
I've been watching you, and you're good at this.
I'll give you a hefty paycheck. What do you say? Interested?
Do you need time to think about it?
What's there to think about? I'm totally up for it.
I'm totally grateful.
- Hey, Mr. Lee. - Yes?
I actually have something to confess.
Sit down for a second.
You have something to confess? What's that?
I'm fine as long as it's not a love confession.
Well, it's kind of similar.
What?
To be honest,
I'm friends with Ji Na.
- Your first love. - What?
How do you know her?
She's close with my sister, so I've known her for 10 years.
And now she's like a sister...
She's like a brother to me.
I didn't know from the beginning. I found out later on.
But I couldn't find the right time to tell you,
which is why I haven't.
I'm sorry.
You don't need to be sorry.
I'm not trying to make excuses,
but after I found out you were that jerk...
I mean, after I found out you were that guy,
I really wanted things to work out between you two.
I mean, you're a really great guy.
Thank you.
I'm serious.
Every time I saw you spacing out,
I got really upset.
Did I do that?
I should've made more of an effort to help you out.
It's okay. There's no point.
That's what I think these days.
It wouldn't have worked out even if anyone tried to help.
After all, I brought this upon myself.
Mr. Lee.
- You sound like an adult. - Hey.
I'm already older than you.
But you're okay now, right?
Yes, of course. I'm always okay.
I'm done thinking about the past.
I'm going to run toward the future...
Is everything also okay with your friend?
- What? - It's just that...
I don't want you to end up losing a friend as well.
Gosh, I'm sorry. That was out of line.
How about we go for a game?
You win.
You're right. That's a first.
You said you wanted my car, right?
No, let's just forget about that bet we made.
I want to start over again.
Sure.
Neither of us should go easy on the other person.
How's your new place?
It's okay, I guess.
Do you need anything?
Joo Ik.
I'm sorry, but I can't give you that.
Let's play ball from time to time.
Not too often.
And we can go for some drinks afterward.
Wouldn't that be impossible?
I like that answer of yours.
You sound determined to beat me.
But I really hope that happens one day.
Hey.
Are you doing well?
I'm...
doing okay. It's the same every day.
The flowers you gave me have wilted.
And looking at them made me feel sad.
So I got myself a new one pretending like I got it from you.
It's pretty, isn't it?
Once this one wilts,
I'll buy a new one and pretend like you got it for me again.
I'll do that again and again.
That's how I'll continue to live.
That's okay, right?
One day, Doom came through my front door.
(One day, Doom came through my front door.)
Hello.
Who are you?
Myul Mang.
The world had come to a stop,
and Doom and I were the only ones that could move.
Doom, standing across the street, slowly walked toward me...
as if he was taking a walk.
I stared at him as if I was bewitched.
I was down on my knees,
and he held out his hand.
"Choose."
Choose. Will you die here and now?
Or will you take my hand?
I just sat there and stared into his eyes.
His deep, yet emotionless eyes.
"Is this hand of yours the long-awaited answer..."
"to my question?"
My hand trembled as I held his hand.
And he gave me a smile of satisfaction.
And just like that, I held Doom's hand.
Here.
How could you not even give me a heads up?
That CEO of yours has huge eyes,
pale white skin, and really tall.
I was really scared, you know.
I thought he wanted to meet me to suck my blood out.
He does suck your blood dry.
- What? - He really does that.
He sucks your blood dry.
I'm not going to sign this contract.
How do you expect me to sign a deal after hearing that?
No, he'll suck your blood dry if you don't sign the contract.
He doesn't mess with people who are on his side.
Instead, you'd better make sure no one finds out who I am.
My goodness, of course.
Should I order something else for you?
No, it's okay. I'm on a diet.
You're eating tteokbokki when you're on a diet?
What? Do you have a problem with that?
Gosh, no. I'm just really worried. That's all.
"How can he eat nothing else but tteokbokki?"
"I feel so bad for him."
That's what I meant.
You little punk.
Oh, by the way, I read that novel.
You know the storyline you told me about last time?
If you choose the person you love, the world comes to an end.
If you choose to protect the world, the person you love has to die.
What was it called again?
I have no idea.
Anyway, that story about doom is the story you mentioned, right?
Dong Kyung, are you close with the writer?
What? Why do you ask?
Because I can already tell that it's going to be a sad ending.
I want it to have a happy ending.
Can you ask the writer if it's going to be a sad or happy ending?
I cry easily, so I can't read it if it's going to be sad.
If it's going to be a sad story, I shouldn't even start reading it.
Aren't you close with the writer?
Forget it then.
So live.
As you live life, you'll realize one day...
that there was a reason behind everything you went through.
You'll find out that it was a happy ending.
I still have no idea...
what kind of ending I'm going to have.
I just stand here imagining myself holding hands with you...
and having my body wrapped around your arms.
Because this world is still filled with things that disappear.
It's filled with you.
Auntie, where are you?
Should we all meet up for a meal?
Here.
How did you find this place?
I know, right?
I love this place.
I'm using the bag Dong Kyung got me...
for the first time today.
Ta-da.
Me too. The sneakers Dong Kyung bought me. Number eight.
I didn't bring mine because it's a pen.
But I'll pay for dinner.
- Come on. - No.
I have good news. I want to pay.
Good news? What?
It's too soon to say.
I'll tell you once it's all set,
so wait a little.
I'm the oldest though. I should pay.
It's okay, all of you.
Since it's my celebration, I'm buying.
What are you celebrating?
Being healthy? Getting a new job?
No.
Celebrating spending a day that was full and healthy.
Celebrating how sunny it was today.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
True. It really was nice out today.
Me too.
I worked super hard.
The laundry dried really nicely.
It felt good.
Well... It would've been nice if he...
could've joined us.
I know. I miss him.
Is he doing well?
Should I book a flight right now?
Let's fly over there. I got 900 on the TOEIC.
He thinks he's all that because he's American?
I'll tell him...
that you all miss him.
Are you doing a video call? When? Let me join you.
Stay out of it.
You'll just whine as soon as you see him.
Let me join. I'll scold him...
Enough.
Just eat.
- Eat. Eat up. - Eat up.
I know you don't want to do this, but try to smile.
It's not that I don't want to do it.
But what's the purpose?
- What? - To look at it from time to time?
Yes. To look at it from time to time.
(Human)
(Message)
I had dinner with everyone tonight...
and they all say they miss you.
(New Messages)
I saw you in my dream today.
I saw you in my dream again today.
I miss you.
It's just that I never tried before. Now that I did, I can figure it out.
I thought a lot about what to send in my first text...
You're happy, right?
I trust you are.
You couldn't do it.
You couldn't send it.
(Send)
I'll be back.
Hi.
How have you been?
How about you?
You weren't in the hospital.
I got surgery.
Surgery?
Can you feel it?
It's beating well.
Human heart is very warm.
It's strong and keeps beating.
I think it'll be the longest life yet thanks to you.
I'm glad.
Thank you for being alive.
That's what I wanted to say.
You beat me to it.
I should go since I saw you were doing well.
See you again.
Take this. It's raining.
What about you?
Me?
It's close. I can run.
It's so pretty and growing nicely.
Hey, there.
Don't give me that.
How is she?
Is she doing well?
She's doing well and not well.
Don't be sad. Today is a happy day.
It grew well.
You've become a good kid.
You've grown a very pretty flower.
- What do you mean? - You're a butterfly.
A butterfly for flowers in my garden.
Do you think the butterfly knew...
that once it died, it would become a flower as well?
No.
You didn't know, but that was what you chose.
For your one and only flower.
This flower bloomed...
from the dead butterfly turning into fertilizer.
You made this flower bloom.
It's you.
You're no longer a butterfly.
You're the first flower that I created.
- This is me? - That's right.
So...
my real fate is...
Living happily in this garden.
Not as a butterfly, but as a flower. As a human being.
Was this your plan from the start?
- Did you know from the start... - I didn't know,
but I always believed in you two.
Sorry,
but I always had faith and hoped.
So go.
You can resent me and regret later.
She's waiting.
I don't resent you.
I'm simply...
happy.
Because...
I can see her again.
Good.
I've always wanted to see you smile like that.
I'm good now that I saw it.
Since I got to see it.
Let's say bye here.
Go. Don't stop.
When you get there, love. Don't stop.
Live happily like that.
But you'll be alone again if I leave.
No. We're always together.
I'm always with you.
I'll always watch over you, water you, and raise you.
Always hoping you'll be happy.
Let's meet again later. Much later. Here.
Smile.
I always want you to smile.
Don't forget that.
Take this with you. It's raining there.
Get going. She's waiting.
Happy birthday.
Goodbye,
Human.
Hi. How are you?
Everything's good with me as usual.
Thank you. Come again.
- Hi. - One gimbap please.
I smile at times...
The event is as I described last week...
Hello? Hello?
Did you hang up? Hello?
Seriously!
I get angry at times.
Darn it.
I get bored at times.
(You've fully paid off your loan.)
(We'd like to thank you and congratulate you.)
Then at times,
there are moments that feel like gifts.
There are also moments that are excruciating.
But I still live...
because you gave me this life.
But I still walk because that is life.
I wonder where you are.
I wonder what you're passing by right now.
Perhaps you've already come to me.
With a completely different face, with a completely different look.
As a completely different being.
When I think about that,
I end up looking carefully at every person's face that I see.
I end up looking into every person's life that I meet.
I wonder...
"Is that him?" "Is that him?"
If I walk past you,
will you take my hand as you always did?
Even if it's only briefly.
It's okay if it's only for a brief moment.
Please hold my hand.
Please hold me.
Do you have an umbrella?
It's raining out.
What...
What's your deal?
I'm your hand holder.
(Doom at Your Service)
I no longer bring doom.
I am human just like you.
This isn't a dream, is it?
Hey!
Are you listening?
Are you sleeping?
So? Will you be my girlfriend?
What if I refuse?
How's life?
It's nice.
Live with me forever.
I thought it was the end...
since destiny doesn't change.
Don't disappear on me. Ever.