♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 28=
(Luofeng Pavilion)
Are you sure?
I knew what Qingqing wants most
is to get rid of the Meteor Mark.
I should have done this earlier.
Pulling out the string is just like
pulling out your tendons.
Can you bear it?
I’m a bit reluctant to do it.
You’d better do it yourself.
If I can do it,
why bother to come to you?
I tried.
It’s hard to pull it out.
You have to use your power.
Then, get ready for it.
Come on.
I think you’d better give up now.
Don’t stop!
Can you still hang in there?
Cut the cackle. Keep on.
Dragon King!
What are you doing?
Stop!
It will hurt his soul!
You’re killing him!
Come here.
He wants to give you the string.
I don’t want it!
How silly you are!
Do you know what you are doing?
Meteor Mark is just a mark.
I don’t mind it now.
Why are you worried about it?
It’s just a string.
I’ll be fine.
I don’t allow you to hurt yourself.
Don’t you know that it’ll break my heart
to see you do this?
Don’t cry.
I like to see you smile.
You have a beautiful smile.
Smile.
You taught me last time
how should I smile to look natural.
Fool.
Like this.
Do it like me.
Curl up the corners of your lips
like the gold ingot.
Why can’t you learn?
You have to learn it hard.
I don’t want to see a cold face
that does not smile every day.
Let’s try together.
You hurt yourself again
after you just recovered.
Here. Have the tea.
Eat the leaf, too.
Tea leaf?
It helps you recover faster.
Do I look that funny?
No, no.
I…
I’m laughing at myself.
I suddenly feel that
I’m so unfaithful in love.
Who is that?
Who else do you like?
Look at you!
I haven’t finished my words.
I mean
I like every look of you.
So do I.
Look at you!
You need to get well quickly,
then we can…
We can what?
I won’t tell you.
Your Majesty,
I got a secret report, saying
that the King of Dongluo has died
and the Second Prince has ascended
to the throne.
And, they are preparing to break
our agreement and start a war again.
What a liar!
What do you think we should do?
I request to go to fight them
and defend our country
so that they can’t cross the border.
Great!
That’s my Great Lady General.
Your Majesty,
(Memorial)
This is the evidence of the
secret meeting between Mr. Guo
and the Crown Prince of Dongluo.
Minister Xu! That’s nonsense!
You’re slandering me!
Your Majesty! I’m wronged!
Your Majesty, Minister Xu
is slandering me!
(Help to get in…)
Shut up!
Consort Rui has told me everything.
You mean she is also slandering you?
Guards!
Take him out and punish him with
a hundred strokes of the plank,
dismiss him from his position
and send him to the border.
He should never be hired again!
-Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty! I’m really wronged!
-Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
-Go!
-I’m really wronged!
Your Majesty! I’m wronged!
Your Majesty!
General, you have killed many
enemies this time.
Your kung fu has improved.
We killed the enemies together.
General.
Why is a kid here in the military camp?
Sweetheart.
Sweetheart! Come here.
I told you not to run around.
Uncle Zhao, she is…
Look.
Does she look like me?
She is my daughter.
Baby, I’ll take you to practice
sword later.
Sword? Please don’t!
Chenyue, don’t blame me for saying this.
You have achieved great war credits.
Now it’s time for you to get
a perfect beloved mate
to make a happy family.
That’s the best ending.
Uncle Zhao, just go back
to your business.
Even if you dislike my nagging
and drive me away,
I still have to say that.
-I will say it every time I see you.
-Alright, alright.
Alright, let’s go
to play over there!
Look! Look!
Uncle Zhao is right.
I have to build a family.
After coming back from the battle,
it’s good to have
someone to talk to
and rely on at home.
Do you think so?
General, they are still waiting for me
to train.
Excuse me for my leave.
Here. This is delicious.
Chenyue!
No matter how many times
you will escape
and not admit,
I just have the feeling that
you are my Dragon King.
Report!
General, Emissary Lu is here.
Let him in.
-Mr. Lu.
I applied to His Majesty
to come back here to be the Emissary.
It’s in the middle of nowhere here,
not like Wind City.
I’m willing to even if it’s hard.
Don’t you understand my feelings?
Zheng,
I already have someone in mind.
Someone in mind?
Chenyue, I know.
You can tell me directly
if you want to reject me.
I can bear it.
My love to you is my own business.
You don’t need to worry.
Zheng,
that is not my excuse.
It’s true.
I never had this feeling before.
Feeling?
I have got this feeling
since the first time I met him.
It has never stopped,
but it’s even getting stronger
and stronger.
I’m sorry.
You don’t need to apologize to me.
Why are you telling me this?
Zheng,
you will definitely find
your true love one day.
Then,
you will still call me Zheng, right?
Of course.
Dragon King!
I know you’re by my side!
Why can’t you show up and face me?
Dragon King,
you will come to me,
right?
Chenyue,
forgive me for not being able
to face you
and tell you the truth.
But I’ll always be by your side.
So many butterflies!
Yuchi! Look!
These butterflies can perceive
human emotions!
Yuchi.
Dragon King,
I have got the answer in my mind.
It’s been only half a day.
Your wound is healed so soon.
It’s not serious.
How long will you protect me?
Forever.
Keep your words.
Or you’ll get punished by military laws.
♪Sleepless moon is in green hills♪
♪Colorless water flows the yellow dusk♪
I know
♪I’m not sure♪
that you must have some difficulties,
so you can’t face me.
It’s OK.
As long as you are always by my side,
I don’t care about anything else
and I won’t ask again.
♪Has your heart ever beaten for me♪
♪Wind in my ears is chirping♪
♪I can hear your response♪
♪Sleepless moon is in green hills♪
♪Colorless water flows the yellow dusk♪
♪I’m not sure if I can see you again♪
♪Three lives passed without complaint♪
♪Fallen flowers can’t figure out
the love of the world♪
♪All colors of missing block me
from seeing you♪
♪Like a dream Like a fantasy♪
Yuchi, I’ll never forget you!
♪Worries intertwining
the smoke and rain♪
I thought
one day you would tell me
that you are him,
but unfortunately,
I failed to hear it this life.
But I think it was worth
the wait,
because no matter it’s the battlefield
or the beautiful scenery,
you always
stay by my side.
But, Yuchi,
aren’t you going to accompany
Liuying, the girl you love?
You are Liuying.
You’re the same person.
We’re the same?
A long time ago, your name was Liuying.
Later, you were called Ayu.
You mean,
I’m your beloved
Liuying?
Yes.
I’m Yuchi Longyan.
You used to
call me Dragon King.
Dragon King?
Finally you’re willing to admit
that you are the Dragon King.
Yes.
Finally I can
have you for real.
General!
Qingqing? Why are you here?
Why is the physician also here?
Qingqing is a Blue Bird actually.
And he is
the Lord of Luofeng Pavilion.
Blue Bird?
So, you’re also not an ordinary person?
Lord of Luofeng Pavilion?
Now you look
matched with my Qingqing.
Qingqing is always
with Luofeng Pavilion.
She is never yours.
Chenyue, I’m a bird demon,
but we can still be friends, right?
Of course!
Then, do you always know
that he is the Dragon King?
Yes!
I know everything!
But I can’t tell you anything!
You know me.
I know so many secrets
but I can’t tell any of it!
It makes me so anxious!
Sorry, Qingqing.
But, why did you all hide it from me?
We won’t do it again.
This time,
you can’t pour the Lethe Tea again.
That’s against the rules of Heaven.
But, will I forget everything
after I drink it?
Including Dragon King?
Yes.
The Lethe Tea is supposed
to make people forget the past.
Then, I disagree to drink it.
Even if you don’t remember,
I will go find you
and marry you in the human world.
But, why should I wait for you
in the human world?
Let’s go.
Why is Chenyue taking Dragon King away?
What
are they going to do?
Get married.
(Luofeng Pavilion)
Chenyue, where are you taking me to?
To get married!
What’s wrong?
Yes, let’s get married!
You’re the Dragon King. Do you have
a palace underwater?
Let’s go get married there!
I’m not the Dragon King of the sea.
Come with me.
Alright.
I’m flying in the sky now!
You’re taking me fly in the clouds!
This is just like what I imagined!
You imagined this?
Yes, I did!
For so many times.
I imagined flying with you
in the clouds for so many times,
just like we rode the horses
through the woods.
Hold on tight!
Yes!
This is my Dragon Pool.
Now,
you call tell me about
Liuying and Ayu.
Don’t miss anything.
Sure.
♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
We drew
this painting together.
So,
I can even draw a painting?
♪Bright or dim♪
♪Fate is like a rain of flowers♪
This is
the small dragon embroidered by Ayu,
right?
If the Star Halo
shows up again in three days,
you need to give me a token as well.
Anything can be accepted.
♪Does my heart ripple with memories♪
♪Only to remember you♪
I see the dragon on your handkerchief
is half embroidered.
So I finished embroidering it on my own.
Liuying started embroidering it.
But it’s finished by Ayu.
Liuying.
Ayu.
Chenyue.
So,
you’re always with me.
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
No matter who you are,
I’ll always be with you.
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I wanna stay with you in this life♪
Dragon King must have taken Chenyue
back to Dragon Pool to get married.
No!
I have to prepare the dowry for Chenyue!
It’s not the human world here.
There is no need for
betrothal gifts and dowry.
Your immortals’ marriage is so boring!
No. Other things can be unnecessary,
but the red wedding dress and
the love token are indispensable.
They have already had love tokens.
Then, they need red wedding dress!
I need to go to tell them!
I’m going!
But the red wedding dress and
the love token are indispensable.
So beautiful!
-Is it you…
-Not me.
It’s God’s will.
With the Star Halo as a proof
and the Dragon Pool as the present,
Chenyue,
will you marry me?
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪