♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 27=
General.
I heard the sound of fighting.
Where is the assassin?
Jin got poisoned.
Long Yan is helping her.
Let me have a check.
Ah, it looks painful.
Dragon King is only gentle to Chenyue.
That’s really him.
How is her now?
The poison of Mandrake is removed.
Great!
(General’s Mansion)
Over the years
I have mistaken Han Xiyun
as my benefactor
and helped him do
countless wrong things.
You shouldn’t have saved me.
You still have me.
(Jin)
General, your old injury recrudesces.
You should take more rest.
You came quickly tonight.
Why do I feel like you’re watching me
every minute of every day?
Don’t you need to sleep?
It’s my duty.
Oh, really?
Is there any other reason?
It’s late now.
General, you should go to bed.
Are you alright?
You haven’t answered my question.
You make my wound hurt.
You have to relieve my pain.
General, how should I do it?
Take me to the city wall to watch
the fireworks again.
City wall?
There are no fireworks now.
It’s late at night now.
You need more rest.
Alright, alright.
But, before I fall asleep,
you can’t leave.
Yes, General.
Let’s see if I can dream
of the fireworks on the city wall.
This dream is so beautiful!
Yes.
Yuchi!
You finally come to see me.
It’s so beautiful.
Now you’re a general,
but you still like these things.
I like the fallen flowers,
the fireflies,
and the fireworks.
Yuchi,
are you going to leave me
after I wake up?
This is just a dream.
I’m not the real me in the dream.
You will forget this dream.
Since I will forget it,
I can do whatever I want now.
♪Pure white sunshine♪
♪Clouds hide the moss♪
♪There comes the deer’s call♪
♪Run slowly with soft footsteps♪
♪Wind blows the skirt’s hemline♪
♪You’re in the shadow of the tree♪
This moment.
Only this moment is enough.
♪Will you only hesitate♪
♪The leaves rustling not too loud♪
♪The heart beats fast and deafening♪
♪Wait until the red sunset♪
♪Embraces the delicate breeze♪
♪Thousands kinds of beautiful flowers♪
♪Are not as good as your grace♪
♪Like a thick wine flows into the sea♪
Seems like
I had a nice dream last night.
But
I can’t remember it now.
What…
What’s wrong with me?
Tell me!
Or I will kill you!
Your Highness, please calm down.
Your symptoms seem to be
the addiction to Mandrake
after taking Life-saving Pill.
Now you have to go back to Dongluo
to take new Life-saving Pills.
Only that can relieve your pain.
Life-saving Pill?
How…
How come I took Life-saving Pill?
Go back to Dongluo now!
After I recover,
I will find out the truth!
(Tiger’s Howl Valley)
I’ve checked what happened
seven years ago.
The Tiger’s Howl Valley back then
was a trivial area on the border
of four countries.
Later, someone said that
secret treasures of the former dynasty
were hidden there,
which attracted people from four
countries to fight for it.
At that time, Feng Army was on guard
at the border,
and was not involved in the seizure
of the treasures.
You mean,
my father went there
to find the treasures?
I don’t know who got the treasures
seven years ago.
But, I found a map.
(Tiger’s Howl Valley)
I planned to go there
to check in person.
But now I think
you should go find the truth yourself.
(Tiger’s Howl Valley)
Seems that there was
a fierce fight here.
(Tiger’s Howl Valley)
This should be the place where
the treasures were hidden back then.
(Jin)
This is…
Dad is so great!
Does it look good?
Yes!
Excuse me.
I’m Jin Ge, a guard of the King
of Dongluo.
Father!
It’s really you!
What happened?!
I’m Jin Ge, a guard of the King
of Dongluo.
I was ordered to come here to find the
treasures of the former dynasty.
Kill!
But, when we
found the treasures
and prepared to leave,
we got attacked by the Feng Army.
We fought with them,
but we were outnumbered.
The enemy’s sword went through my chest.
But he didn’t know that
my heart was born on the right side.
His sword
didn’t kill me.
When I woke up from the coma,
I found that all my brothers were dead.
And the Feng Army was packing up
the treasures.
Then, I heard people talking.
Their voices were so familiar to me.
Your Highness,
with these gold,
we can bribe all the ministers.
You are sure to get
the throne of the Crown Prince
Burn all the bodies.
Yes.
I sneaked away while they were
packing up the treasures.
-But…
-Take a head count before that.
The Eldest Prince found that
a body is missing
and knew that I escaped.
The man who escaped is Jin Ge.
He has an only daughter, Jin.
If Jin Ge is still alive,
he will go find Jin.
We can go back
and get Jin under control.
If you find Jin Ge,
bury him alive.
If you can’t find him,
you won’t need to come back.
Yes, Your Highness.
I wanted to risk my life to fight,
but if I die,
Jin will be in danger.
If they don’t know whether I’m
alive or dead,
they won’t dare to hurt Jin.
Father,
you did all this for me.
It’s been days.
But we still haven’t found him.
Yes. When can we find him?
Anyway, just keep searching.
Alright, let’s go.
I have spent my life
(Jin)
working for Dongluo.
But in the end, I was killed
by people of Dongluo,
(Jin)
and got my daughter involved.
Now I know I will die of my
severe wounds.
I write this letter with my blood
to tell the truth,
hoping one day
my beloved daughter Jin can read this.
Jin,
forgive me for not being able to
protect you anymore.
Take good care of yourself.
Jin Ge’s last words.
Father!
I’m not filial
that I’ve just found you.
Han Xiyun,
I will give what you
did to me all back to you.
My Lord,
your tea.
Have it when it’s still warm.
When can you stop being so shy?
I don’t know.
I was not like this
when I saw you before.
I could even say bad things about you.
But now…
Stop looking at him.
I’m getting more and more nervous!
My Lord, since you finish the tea,
I will take it away.
Why is my face so hot?
Am I having a fever?
My heart is beating so fast!
Calm down! Calm down!
Calm down!
But,
he really
looks better now.
The Three Pearl Leaf Tea
really works.
There’s only a little bit left?
Qingqing.
Why are you here?
What’s in your hand?
No… Nothing.
Feather?
Who hurt you?
Nobody hurt me.
Tell me!
It’s myself.
Why?
No reason.
Look at me.
Look at me!
Alright, I’ll tell you.
But, you can’t get angry.
I won’t.
You got hurt.
So, I went to Immortal of Fate
for Three Pearl Leaf Tea.
You know his principles.
I can’t get it for free.
So, I pulled out a Feather
to exchange it with him.
You said you wouldn’t get angry.
I’m angry with myself.
Don’t waste your power.
Now the most important thing
is that you get well.
Shut up.
♪On the riverbank
A beautiful face alone under the moon♪
♪Meet like a dream♪
Why are you so silly?
♪The thin figure is missing someone
at the frosty night♪
It’s alright. It’s fine.
They are just some feathers. I’m fine.
♪Parting is the hardest♪
♪Zither is playing melodiously♪
From now on,
♪Miss you from dawn♪
I won’t allow you to hurt yourself
like this again.
♪To dusk♪
♪Sing a song of sorrows♪
♪A lonely toast to the good time♪
I got it.
♪How to forget in the running time♪
♪The day the person the love♪
♪But one day we will say goodbye♪
♪When and where to meet♪
Why are you here?
You…
You good-for-nothing!
You only fail!
Get lost!
It’s painful, right?
I know a way to stop the pain.
You know how?
Jin. Jin.
Jin.
Help me.
Help me! Help!
You want to know it?
Yes. Yes. Yes!
(General’s Mansion)
General!
What’s wrong?
General, I just got the news that
the Crown Prince of Dongluo was
assassinated by his guard
when he was leaving Wind City.
And I heard the assassin has been
torn into pieces.
Nobody can identify the assassin.
Take me to have a check.
Sure.
General, the Crown Prince
got assassinated here.
General.
(Jin)
It’s really Jin who did it.
Jin left a smiling face,
that must mean she is fine.
Right?
Don’t worry.
Jin will not be controlled by
anyone again.
I’m Chenyue. What about you?
Let’s be friends.
Jin.
Then, let’s hunt here tomorrow.
So annoying.
At noon, here.
See you then.
Let’s be friends.
I’m Jin.
What’s your name?
Feng Chenyue.
Then, let’s
go hunting tomorrow.
Alright.
She is free now.
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪