fTiming and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ No longer panicking on the night of the blackout ♫
♫ You're by my side, illuminating a beam of light for me ♫
♫ Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet ♫
♫ Your breath ♫
♫ brushes up against my cheek ♫
♫ With you warming up the stage,
happiness never comes to a close ♫
♫ Boring jokes add some sweetness to the dinner ♫
♫ Daily life is even more like a comic than comics themselves ♫
♫ Happiness and sadness ♫
♫ Make up the moments of life ♫
♫ Rainy days become very special because of you ♫
♫ Picked up a pitiful youngster off the street ♫
♫ No matter when and where, you always appear ♫
♫ Holding me tightly and spinning in circles ♫
♫ Rainy days make me so nostalgic because of you ♫
♫ Becoming some part of the memories ♫
♫ Walking down a street with lights lighting up
one after another ♫
♫ Warming up the whole world ♫
[Please Feel at Ease Mr. Ling]
[Episode 22]
how are you two doing?
all good now
how did you find me?
we caught Lingyue, lets meet in half an hour
we have seen him before a few times
probably someone is in trouble and called him to clean up
Follow him.
what about it? I came just in time
like a super hero
thank you, brother
thank me? I didn't come to save you
only i'm allowed to pick on you
then be nicer to your brother, stop plotting against him
that was just a misunderstanding
i originally did want to do something...
who would have known those two idiots couldn't even open the car door
after looking around came back
he switched lanes, do you think he noticed us?
not you?
When president Ling went missing, security cameras caught his car also in the parking lot
why didn't you tell me earlier
i didn't know the my car would have that
Lingsheng!
no, impossible
when the cooperation plan for the anniversary event was leaked to Gu company
I already know there was a spy in our company
and a while ago the conflict between New Way and Gu Shi company
was also by a company employee leaking the Ling Xiao plan
when I signed that document...
although it did not reveal the name
but it had our father's signature stamp
the stamp was in our family safe
and only Lingsheng could open
and only he could have both the cooperation plan and Ling Xiao plan
thats true
he was meeting with company shareholders and our head managers lately
when Allen kidnapped Anxin
I thought this might have something to do with him
Anxin
Brother?
how did this happen?
why are you here?
you awake?
Yuguo, how are you feeling?
tell us, who is your accomplice
kill me then
Yuguo, stop lying to yourself
we were there together and the gas was leaked
if it wasn't for Lingfang, we would have really died
no way... she wouldn't
Yuguo
that person you speak of
is she, Yanghong?
child don't be afraid
from now on, i'm your family
from now on I will take care of you
Auntie Hong, you are so nice to me
I wouldn't know how to repay you
I'm just trying to atone in place of Anxin
she is my adoptive daughter, our whole family has wronged you
slowly, don't rush
don't blame yourself
blame those who harmed you
karma will make them pay
so you already aware
I saw my mothers accounting books
she had been transferring money to Yuguo
so I started to have suspicion
so to force Lingyue to sign over equity rights and get rid of you two
it's killing two birds with one stone
sign over equity, to whom?
Lingsheng
my mother has already set a date for Lingsheng and Xiner's wedding
we don't have any evidence right now
to take them to court
you guys go back, pretend we are really dead
I will secretly arrange someone to collect evidence
be careful not to be caught
it can only be this way
we can stall for some time
go ahead, what can brother help you with
take care of Yuguo
make sure the fake death looks real
ok i'll think of something
why was there a fire? give me an explanation
the weather is dry, a fire is normal
wouldn't it be good since it rids of any evidence
what if there was a flaw, you know the consequences
relax boss, I locked the door
and there would be no other people around
when I left they, were already on deaths door
even with that loser Yuguo, they wouldn't be able to run
I don't trust a death with no bodies
when you have the chance go take a look
Okay, I won't let them show up alive
Allen I only trust you right now
Relax, our whole family is in debt to you
I will for sure clear any obstacles
'Ling...Yue'
"Ling...Yue'
"Father can I help?"
little kids get in the way, go get your 2nd brother
I can feel assured when given task to LingYue
he can take care of it, he is my most promising child
I am willing to help father too not just my brothers
the world of business is like a battlefront
you must determine your enemy and allies and most of all prepare the right weapons
"boss, what to do next?"
I wanted to use Ansheng to ruin New Way
but Lingyue wasn't tricked and actually dragged in Gu Shi
but it wasn't all a loss
do not relax, keep a close watch
when the fake news of New Way selling expired goods comes out
the sales will definitely be affected
and now Lingyue cannot be the clutch savior of the company
Using the family name transferring the company assets
resulted in the company loss
and now without Lingyue
If you make a move, you can turn the tides
then the shareholder only recognize you
but I wouldn't have known it would shock my father and cause him to be hospitalized
and I did not know he had sent out an emergency company sign over
from this situation Ling Shi will be run by Mr. Lingyue
and ruined again by Lingyue
I can only be rough
Du Ming was too useless last time
this time I will use Anxin to lure him he will definitely come
remember, at all costs
you must make him sign
their life and death leave to Yuguo
here it is
after all these years brother Wu like to hide the key under the flower pot
who is brother Wu?
when I left school, I met some friends here in Xiao Yu village
brother Wu is one of them
the most magnanimous and the one that treated me the best
the this brother Wu...
is he good looking
oh super good looking
when I think about brother Wu, whom so dashing and so lively
I think all girls would have a crush
brother Wu!
watch your image don't be rude
stop playing
so brother Wu is a woman
on the outside...
I am a woman
I'm Lingyue
bother Wu
tell me, what do you need help with
I want to ask brother Wu to take care of a guy named Allen
no problem, I just need some information about him
thank you, you can ask me for anything
"If you have Anxin, then Lingyue will come"
"when you get what you need to"
"let them stay together for a while"
whats wrong Ansheng? you seem down
eat
Mom,
Our life right now..
what are you not satisfied about
why do you ask so out of the blue?
nothing, really
I'm just really lost...
Dad, I applied to return to school
you are leaving?
I remember, you promised me
to take over our business
yeah Lingsheng
you father is getting old, he can't manage without you
the company also needs you
i'm full, you guys continue
Bro...
what happened
Xiner
he didn't tell you anything?
no
don't mind him mom
brother is like this
'unfortunately the number you have dialed...'
Sorry, you...
why can't I contact Yuguo
nothing happened right?
no, it was cleaned up well
you don't need to worry
what...what did you do with them
I just made it look like a natural accident
relax
I don't care what you do
just make sure Gu Anxin is completely gone
what are you doing?
I'm asking what you are doing?
the thing that they gave me
where did I put it?
what thing?
the joint stock documents for the cooperation?
yes
I just gave it to you and you put it on your desk
you gave it to me?
why don't I remember?
whats wrong with you lately?
do you want to go check it out at the hospital?
no need, I know my own health
Presiden't Ling
It was my mistake that you got hurt
don't blame yourself
if they wanted us dead
they would always think of other ways
go back after this, make our death seem real
but if I leave, who will ensure your safety?
do as I say so they believe our death
these guys are ruthless
although they hit your noggin' that hard
you didn't get a concussion or a hemorrhage is pretty good
are you sure you were not seen?
when we came by car then by boat...
to middle of nowhere. I don't think anyone would have seen us
Aili has checked there was no followers
we can now confirm, kidnapping was by Yanghong and Lingsheng
if they wish us dead
then we will give them what they wish
in the mean time we will collect evidence of their crime
we also have handled Yuguo situation
so there is no one else that know we are still alive
even though the situation happened we still don't have physical evidence
we can't expose ourself this early
make sure you don't get caught
Anxin and I will live here
I already discussed with my elder brother, he will keep the secret
and spread news that we are dead
I'll leave the care of my father to you
relax
what do you need to say behind a closed the door?
we haven't been able to chat for a long time
I wanted to discuss something
what do you want to discuss? go ahead
Mom
do you remember when we first came to Gu residence
you told me you will find me a great father
and a perfect family
do you remember?
and when you divorced my bio dad
and took on so many jobs
and told me to just study
and don't worry
is it that I was too young to remember
but I always did
I know these years
you for me and Xiner
you carried so much
Son...
you and Xiner's happiness
is my happiness
mom we grew up
we don't need you to worry anymore
we can support you
our family priority is just to stay safe and sound
lets not fight for whats not meant to be
fight?
Mom
from young
I always listened to you
I never asked for anything or troubled you
please this one time listen to me
son, I don't understand listen to what?
what am I listening to?
Let go, Mom it's not to late just let go
doing this, did you think of the consequences?
will Xiner be happy? what about our family?
what are you talking about? I still don't understand.
and Anxin... Gu family already owes her so much
we owe Anxin too much
stop mentioning Anxin she is not Gu family
when i was small you taught me
if we did a crime
we will have to pay
what crime did I do?
what have I done to make you accuse your mother?
the assets transfer
I saw the Gu Shi accounting books
aside from you no one else has the authority
Son... mom is just putting the company assets
in a safe place
we are family
whats your father's is mine
is this wrong?
what did I do wrong?
stop overthinking
I understand
stop this nonsense
I feel like this was a long day
You didn't sleep at all
didn't we agree to watch the sunrise
but why does it feel like calm before a storm?
I'm sorry
I thought it would make you feel better
when we are alive together...
there is nothing better
we will never separate again
'Ling Yue'
Everyone, my brother Lingyue has signed all equity to me
this is the shares transfer document
I hope there are no more doubts
our priority is to lead Ling Shi back on track
I must emphasize...
that no one bring personal feelings to the workplace
hope everyone keeps this in mind
'why would he transfer the shares to him?'
'yeah, thats ridiculous'
attention
what are you all doing
who are you pouting to?
both Ling family heirs are still here
what are you still dissatisfied about? speak up
brother, thank for that
your my brother when have I not been on your side
hey!
Lingyue's dog
your dead if you touch me
you killed President Ling
brother, calm down
what are you blabbing about. how could I harm my 2nd brother?
you stole his position don't act ignorant
hey
this is Ling Shi not your New Way
I am Ling Shi's heir that position was mine to begin with
take her away
brother
she is just a crazy woman why get yourself roughed by her
let your older brother see, Is your nose okay?
Boss...
I'll take care of it
This is so you remember
because of your mistake it affected my brother
I only have one last younger brother
I won't let him get hurt too
Brother, It's not Allen's fault
It is his fault
this body guard is not reliable, fire him
Allen is loyal
how many people are watching you right now
this bastard is notorious keeping him will damage your reputation
boss...
take this opportunity to take a break
got it
this is a critical time
Ling Shi cannot have anymore negative reports
what do you think? President Sheng
I'll listen to you, brother
let's go
your nose is fine, right?
'Cai Niao'
Xiner
your in a good mood today
I resolved a difficult problem
so I wanted to meet you first thing
It must be hard
to run a company
No not hard
You know, Xiner, I can finally prove to you
I'm not any less of Lingyue
You don't have to compare to him
just be yourself
I out paid all his shares back to him yesterday
I cut off all connection to him
I never knew a goodbye was so simple
just like this little by little
disappear from each others lives
just like we've never met
rest assured
he will never come back into your life
actually i've been practicing self therapy
but I didn't want to let go
thank you
cured my obsession
you gave me courage
to restart
I heard when people turn 40
their fingerprint will become permanent
like these 5 years
my feelings to you
are permanent
if you have to say anything changed
Is that I like you more and more
without explanation
I remember reading about climbing when I was young
Mount Everest
as of then I decided
I would collecting travel expenses
and save it into a bank account
so one day
I could use it for my adventure
so where did the funds go
these funded my life's most challenging adventure
Xiner
I will give you a better life
Miss Gu Xiner, will you marry me?
Xiner you don't have to love like this
you also deserve to be loved and treasured
just a nod
I can without hesitation
run to you
as long as you are willing, I'll always be there
so if you'll accept
that I run to you
Yes
'Ling Shi company Lingyue transfered all personal assets to younger brother Lingsheng...'
'then suddenly disapeared...'
'Ling family is in a crisis'
'with a sudden asset transfer and a funeral in plan'
I hope they are alright
This worry...
also includes Anxin?
from young
she is just like a weed
whenever she acts strong
I just have inexplicable hostility
but...
she is still family
I don't wish her harm
hearing this from you i'm glad
glad?
who's brother would like to see his siblings fight each other
although we don't have a good sisters relationship
but I still wish for her to come back safely
let's talk about some good news
Lingsheng proposed
I said yes
thank you for the blessing
no...I mean
you two... already... getting married
but you two didn't date for long
isn't it a little rushed?
I am clear
I wasn't happy in the past
because I kept waiting for someone I couldn't be with
It was Lingsheng that taught me
a step backwards
can show me the full picture
but do you really know him? both of you...
thats enough, brother
why is it that every choice I make everyone has something to pick at
what have I not been able to accomplish since young...
how is it that in the end you don't even trust me in my own relationships
Xiner, thats not what I mean. a relationship is...
its not this straight forward
what grounds do you speak from
Xiner
I just wanted to protect everyone.
I'll always stand behind you.
This Allen is probably more troublesome than you guys think.
Because the person who rescued his whole family and raised him to do bad things is the same person.
In order to pay back his benefactor from his narrow escape, he won't count the cost, even his own life.
So, you must not take this situation lightly; take great care in everything.
Thank you.
And, he doesn't have the right to talk.
This all happened too quickly.
We're all long-standing shareholders...what are they doing?
Exactly.
How could President Ling Yue transfer his stocks to him?
This shouldn't be.
- This company can't be tossed around like this.
- Right.
Will it be okay in his hands?
Everyone, according to the Group's decision,
whoever owns the most stock shares
becomes the Group's CEO.
At this moment, President Sheng has30% of the stocks.
Without a doubt, that is in first place.
Based on the Board's resolution,
President Sheng becomes the new CEO for Ling Shi Group.
All of you present here are senior to me,
I'm young; everyone please help guide me
into Ling Shi' Group's new future.
You're looking more and more handsome these days.
These clothes...are rather absurd.
As long as Second Brohter is here, it's fine.
Such a big thing happening to the family,
even though he's adopted; I still feel like it's been hard for him.
Why are you bring him up? It's great that the two of us are left.
Don't worry, Brother, it's difficult to separate good and bad, outside from inside.
From now on, you'll surely have a position in the Group.
Buddy, be clear. You aren't capable enough on your own and there are lots of problems.
But, think about it. I'm not young.
If I don't succeed in this enterprise, our dad will have me sweeping the garbage out.
You're fine right now. Shouldn't you help me now?
Brother, you shouldn't say that.
You're always outstanding.
You little brat.
You don't know if I can tell right from wrong, outsider from inside?
You really think of yourself as a director general.
Why am I like that?
You've always been like that. Don't you know that?
When am I like that?
All the time.
It really is hard to imagine
that I can let go of New Way, let go of everything
and become a person of leisure like right now.
So, you have to enjoy today.
This is known as being in the perilous middle while striving for victory.
Tell me, will Ling Sheng really believe we're dead?
Even though he's the youngest, he's been held back for so long.
That means his shrewdness and schemes are surely even deeper than we know.
He'll only believe half of what Ling Fang says; the other half he'll check out.
So that means that
our days of peace will only last a few days.
At least this time, you're not alone.
True. We're together.
You know how to pick up the lines quite well.
Isn't this Fifth Brother's supermarket?
Yes.
Didn't you say that it was boring staying at home?
Fifth Brother and I discussed it. We're prepared a
private shopping spree.
Okay, good. Then, I'll go choose some good things to eat to take home.
Let's go.
- Are you ready?
- I'm ready.
- We're off!
Stop, stop, stop. We're here. Hot pot ingredients.
There, that package.
Let me look. Yes, this is it.
- What's wrong?
- It expires tomorrow.
There's still an hour until tomorrow. It'll take 1/2 an hour to get back home.
We can't eat hotpot tonight. But I really want to eat hotpot today.
- Let's start.
- Okay.
You don't have to get so many. Thank you.
There's not more meat. I'll go get some more.
I'm back.
I forgot to grab the Weixun [a drink].
I'll go get some.
- Cheers.
Do you want to have some fruit?
It's already prepared.
Here.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Soaking the memory wet ♫
♫ Fate works bizarrely ♫
♫ The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly beats out of normal ♫
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Obviously, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness,
for it has always been you ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Yet the reminiscing has never been able to stop ♫
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Using all of my most beautiful adjectives ♫
♫ Is still not enough to describe your name ♫
♫ Our story is exclusively ours ♫
♫ Our palms hold onto the key to the future ♫
♫ Using love to slowly open up a lifetime ♫