=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 12=
Qiong Qi appeared in the lower realm?
It’s true.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Now the Southsea in Immortal Realm
is in a mess.
If True God Shanggu
and True God Bai Jue weren’t there,
I’m afraid
there would have been disaster.
Bai Jue and Shanggu
went to the Immortals?
Tianqi.
True God Shanggu ordered me
to return to the God Realm quickly
and report to you.
Please thoroughly investigate
Qiong Qi’s case.
You may leave.
Yes.
Stop frowning.
Qiong Qi is an ancient beast.
But Shanggu and Bai Jue are there.
Nothing will happen.
I’m afraid it’s not that simple.
Don’t you forget that
Qiong Qi came to invade
the God Realm last time,
which could be seen
as the Devils’ trick.
But now Qiong Qi appears
in the lower realm.
There must be something wrong
in the Demon Realm.
Fine.
I’ll go have a look and we’ll know.
The Demon Realm is originally of mine.
If anyone dares to make chaos
on my territory,
I will teach him a good lesson.
Let me give you some God power.
No need.
It’s just an old wound.
I’ll recover soon back in the God Realm.
Use your God power to take over
the instruction feather of Chief God.
Now there is an abnormal change
in the Immortal Realm.
We have to go back to the God Realm
as soon as possible.
Did you think
I am still as useless as I was
a thousand years ago?
Today’s fight is a real one.
I had a good time.
We have a better tacit understanding
than we were at Mount Lookout.
Now your God power
has greatly increased.
You indeed have the prestige
of Chief God of the Three Realms.
Qiong Qi and its clan
have been living in
the Wasteland of the Demon Realm
sealed by Ancestral God.
They were led by the Devils
to the God Realm before.
I thought it was weird.
I didn’t expect them to break through
the barrier to come here again today.
I think Zhiyang and Tianqi
already went to the Demon Realm
to investigate.
No need to worry.
Let’s go back to the God Realm first.
(Bai Jue)
(The Pilgrimage Hall)
Shanggu,
tomorrow you will take over
the instruction feather of Chief God.
Then, all the gods in the God Realm
and the giants in the lower realm
will come to watch the ceremony.
The Inheritance Ceremony
will be complicated.
Rest assured.
I already learned the ancient rituals
by heart a few days ago.
It won’t go wrong.
All right.
And also,
the instruction feather
of Chief God contains
the Power of Rules
and the Power of Chaos.
Be careful when you take it over.
The Power of Chaos in my body
has merged with the Power of Rules.
The instruction feather of Chief God
can’t hurt me.
That’s good.
True God Bai Jue.
Do not worry.
I will successfully take over
the position of Chief God
and inherit the God Realm.
I know. They were just kind reminders.
If goddesses who like you are here,
seeing True God Bai Jue
turn into an old man who likes to nag,
do you think
they will fall in love with others?
Why should I care about them?
I’m going back to have a rest. Just go.
Wait.
When you take over
the instruction feather of Chief God,
can you go to Taoyuan Forest with me?
I have something
hiding in my heart for long.
I want to tell you about it there.
An appointment between True Gods.
I will definitely go there.
(The Pilgrimage Hall)
Master,
are you really going to…?
No need to ask.
I have made up my mind.
This is the only way.
But we can tell Master Zhiyang
and Master Bai Jue.
Zhiyang and Bai Jue’s
destinies are to take care
of all beings.
Between Shanggu and billions of beings,
which do you think they will choose?
What?
You’ve just finished using me,
Goddess of Snow.
And now you want to
go back on your word?
Don’t panic, Goddess of Snow.
Now you are about
to fall into the Devils.
Counting it up,
you and I are of the same clan.
Nonsense!
I am Goddess of Snow!
How could I be of you Devils!
It’s okay.
You have enough time to think about it.
But don’t forget what you promised me.
In the Inheritance Ceremony tomorrow,
you will be the Eye of the Overlord.
We have helped you
return to the God Realm.
This small request
isn’t too much, is it?
Wu Huan.
Elder.
I haven’t seen you for years.
How are you?
Everything is fine.
Elder, please come in.
Okay.
Wu Huan.
Now she is glamorous,
totally different from when she was in
the Phoenix Clan thousands of years ago.
Just like a small man
being intoxicated by success.
When Queen of Phoenix
returns from Nirvana,
there will be no place for her
in the Pilgrimage Hall.
Of course.
Wu Huan, help me get changed.
Wu Huan.
Why... are you here?
I thought it was getting late.
But I couldn’t find you.
So I came here to find you.
Wu Huan said you didn’t want to get up
and asked me to get you up.
Your Grace.
It’s getting late now.
You should get up and freshen up
to meet the gods from the lower realm
at the Barrier Gate.
I am Chief God.
Why should I go to greet them? You go.
You go for me.
Even if you don’t go to the Barrier Gate
to greet them,
you also should get up.
All people of our Pilgrimage Hall
are gonna go down soon
to the Heaven and Earth Platform
to prepare for the Inheritance Ceremony.
Your Grace, who in the hall
can serve you then?
I’ve learned everything
in the Nether World.
You go mind your business first.
I’ll stay in bed for a while.
Just for a while.
Then... you’d better
get up quickly later.
A period for a stick of incense at most.
It’ll be improper if you’re late.
You overslept, right?
No way.
I am the one who will be Chief God.
How could I
be so ridiculous on the day
of the Inheritance Ceremony.
I just took a nap.
Just a nap.
Yes.
Chief God is in charge of everything.
You should take a nap.
You just said
you looked for me everywhere.
For what?
Divine Brocade.
I found some to make your robes.
You can use it
after you become Chief God.
Only it can be worthy of
Chief God of Chaos.
The silk brocade
which can only be weaved
by goddesses from Endless Mountain
for ten thousand years!
Where did you find it?
I heard that in the entire God Realm,
there is not a piece of clothing
made of Divine Brocade.
A few years ago,
I knew that
one day you would inherit
the position of Chief God.
I prepared it for you then.
A few years ago?
Many years ago,
I read a handwritten note
written by a little girl.
There was a little girl
who was born with blocked God vessels,
but she wanted to practice seriously
more than anyone else.
She didn’t have the God power
to redeem all beings.
But she quietly wrote down
all the sufferings in this world.
When she didn’t have the God power
of Chief God of Chaos,
she had the heart
to benefit the common people.
Along the way,
she hid everything in her heart.
But I saw her desire to advance
and hard work.
Everything she put efforts in,
I understand it
better than anyone else in this world.
Since that day,
I’ve believed
she will be able to be
Chief God of Chaos who cares about
all the beings in the world.
I waited for this day
for a thousand years.
Go get changed.
I’ll accompany you
to the Heaven and Earth Platform.
(The Hidden Pavilion)
Greetings, God Zihan.
Why did God Zihan come to
the Hidden Pavilion today?
Does Master Tianqi
need more treasures
to cultivate his magic weapons?
You are clever.
Yes.
Master Tianqi got
a new piece of obsidian.
He plans to forge a magic sword.
So I come here to get some Sacred Grass.
God Zihan.
You forgot to give us
the warrant of True God Zhiyang.
Oh, yes.
I must have arrived too hurriedly
and left it in the Taichu Hall.
How about this?
I’ll give it to you later.
This won’t work.
You must have the warrant
from True God Zhiyang
to enter the Hidden Pavilion.
There are too many treasures
and most evil things
in the Hidden Pavilion.
We can’t afford this responsibility.
Okay.
Then I will go back
and fetch it for you.
Thank you.
(The Hidden Pavilion)
Who is there?
God Zihan!
God of Four Seasons, together with Gods
of Wind, Rain, Thunder and Lightning,
congratulate Chief God on the succession
of Chief God of Chaos.
God of Stars congratulates Chief God on
the succession of Chief God of Chaos.
Congratulate Chief God on the succession
of Chief God of Chaos.
May Chief God long live
and the Three Realms prosper.
and the Three Realms prosper!
Feel free.
Thank you, Chief God.
Brothers, thanks for all your
kind teaching for thousands of years.
I will bear it in my mind.
It’s the time.
Please take out the Yingsheng Stone.
Chief God of Chaos,
please open the Yingsheng Stone
and take over
the instruction feather of Chief God.
Tianqi?
Tianqi!
Tianqi, what are you doing?
Tianqi.
I’ve been planning for this for tens of
thousands of years! You’re ruining it!
Tianqi.
This is not a place where you can joke.
Return the instruction feather
of Chief God right now.
Don’t come over.
What if I don’t give it to you?
Tianqi, don’t mess around today.
Why she was born to have
the instruction feather of Chief God?
Am I not qualified
to be in charge of the God Realm?
Tianqi, the instruction feather
of Chief God is the God Realm’s Seal.
Only Chief God of Chaos can have it.
If you snatch it, this is a big crime.
So what?
You also said that
the instruction feather of Chief God
is the Seal of the God Realm.
Now this instruction feather is mine.
Given time,
I will be the most powerful God
in the God Realm.
And I will become
the most honorable Chief God
of the God Realm!
Tianqi!
You stay at
the Heaven and Earth Platform,
and I will get him back.
Report to you, True God.
God Zihan broke into the Hidden Pavilion
and killed the guardians.
Now he’s heading
towards the Barrier Gate.
Pass my order.
Ring the Chaos Clock.
Never let the instruction feather
of Chief God leave the God Realm.
Yes!
Bai Jue, you lead the guardians
and arrest Zihan back.
You are way too much today.
When are you going
to stop making trouble?
Step aside.
I don’t want to fight with you.
Me either.
But in front of others,
I have to give an explanation
to the gods.
Explanation?
Do you know what I will suffer
if I fall into their hands?
You can’t be clearer that
how they treated Xuanyi
70,000 years ago.
But you are not Xuanyi.
In their eyes,
the True God who is not loyal
to the God Realm
is the second Xuanyi.
Shanggu, if you still miss
our friendship of the past.
Let me go.
I promise you that
I only borrow the instruction feather
of Chief God temporarily.
When the matter is over,
I will definitely return it to you.
Tianqi,
what trouble exactly do you have?
Can’t you talk to us?
My trouble is much bigger
than you may think.
In the lower realm,
you can still worship the God for help.
But what should the True Gods do
if they are in trouble?
Let me think.
It’s too late, Shanggu.
Do you really want to watch me
being asked for accountability
by the gods
and doomed eternally?
Zihan.
What happened in the Hidden Pavilion?
Did you really kill the guardians?
What?
The guardians died?
I did not do that!
That’s good.
At least you didn’t kill any god.
Come back with me
and explain the things
happened in the Hidden Pavilion clearly.
No.
I can’t go back.
Zihan.
Tianqi has rebelled the God Realm.
If you continue to make trouble,
you will only hurt him.
True God Bai Jue.
Master entrusted me with a crucial task.
I can’t go back.
Excuse me.
How come the Purple Jade Whip
is in your hands?
Zihan, you dare to instigate
the Demons to cause chaos.
Are you insane?
What exactly is Tianqi’s plan?
If you really want to help him,
just go back with me.
True God Bai Jue,
I have no choice.
You will understand it in the future.
Idiot.
I ordered you to keep a close eye
on the God Realm
and let Shanggu inherit the throne
of God smoothly.
How dare you let Tianqi
ruin my ideal plan!
Please calm your anger down, Overlord.
It’s my fault.
How will we end now?
If only Shanggu were dead,
there would still be three people left
to deal with. It’d still be troublesome.
But since Tianqi rebelled the God Realm,
we will just take this opportunity
to let the gods fight themselves.
Then the situation
will be better for us.
Yes!
Tianqi.
Now that you have broken
the Rules of God Realm,
you will be killed
by the hands of all gods.
Master Tianqi has snatched
the position of Chief God openly.
He’s so unrestrained.
Please pass the order
of severe punishment for Tianqi.
Master Zhiyang,
how could Tianqi betray the God Realm?
Don’t you know his temperament?
He always dodges the political affairs
you asked him to do.
How could it be possible that he wants
to snatch the position of Chief God?
Shanggu and Bai Jue have gone
to capture them.
I don’t believe they can escape
from the God Realm.
The Trial of the Three Halls
hasn’t come out an answer yet.
The truth about the Hidden Pavilion
has not been found out.
We can’t easily condemn Tianqi.
Master Zhiyang, do you want to
cover up for the Taichu Hall?
Goddess of Snow,
be careful with what you say.
Master Zhiyang,
I’m just worried about the God Realm.
If it weren’t for Tianqi instructing Zihan
to rebel the God Realm,
why did he commit the crime
of killing gods?
That’s right, Master Zhiyang.
The witness of Zihan’s crime
is still there.
If you didn’t make a decision early,
I’m afraid the disaster 70,000 years ago
would reappear.
Master Tianqi fought for the God Realm
in the north and south,
making great contributions.
If he hadn’t encountered
an extremely difficult thing,
he wouldn’t have got to this point.
Even if you don’t believe in him,
I do.
If all gods don’t protect him, I will!
Quiet.
Don’t talk nonsense in the Chaos Hall.
God of Wind.
Did you mean that
Tianqi should be sentenced to death?
I dare not to say that.
I know all your worries.
I will never believe that
Tianqi will be like Xuanyi back then.
Before God’s punishment comes,
he is still the master of Taichu Hall.
A True God of the God Realm.
I and the other two True Gods
will find out the truth
and give a satisfactory answer to you.
Yes.
Hurry up and report to the True God!
Tianqi has escaped from the God Realm!
Bai Jue.
How could you get hurt so badly?
Just now at the Barrier Gate,
in order to resist the Purple Jade Whip,
I used the Power of the Original Being.
My old wound of spirit got hurt.
It seems that I can no longer use
the Power of the Original Being
in a short time.
Tianqi has escaped from the God Realm.
You let him go?
Yes.
Have you ever thought about it?
If you did this,
the gods would no longer respect you.
Even if you took back the Chief God’s
instruction feather in the future,
you might not be able
to take over the God Realm.
But I can’t stand it
watching you and Zhiyang
cut his God bones
and imprison him in the Nether World.
Zhiyang and I would never do that.
But even if he is exempt from death,
a severe punishment is inevitable.
Bai Jue.
Ten thousand years ago, I was born
on the Heaven and Earth Platform.
The first person I saw was Tianqi.
He and Yuemi accompanied me every day
and took care of me when I grew up.
He is my closest elder brother.
He’s also the person I trust most
among the Three Realms.
Shanggu.
We don’t know
what Tianqi is going to do now.
Only if he stays in the God Realm
can we save him.
I only know that
if he really wanted to be Chief God,
in these ten thousand years,
he would have countless opportunities
to kill me
and defect.
He wouldn’t choose today.
Yeah, I know.
Tianqi is stubborn and obstreperous.
Even if the position of Chief God
were given to him,
he wouldn’t accept it.
His deeds today…
Master!
There must be something else hidden.
Your Grace,
what’s wrong with Master?
His spirit is extremely damaged.
The Pith of the Plane Tree
from the Phoenix Clan
and the Original Being of Chaos
should be used together
to heal his injury.
I’ll go to the Phoenix Clan in a while.
You must guard Changyuan Hall.
No one is allowed to come inside
until I come back.
Yes, Your Grace.
Hongri,
tell me everything
that happened to your Master
these one thousand years.
Tell me in detail.
As long as she is safe,
let alone ten thousand years’ lifespan,
even if it’s
a hundred thousand years’ lifespan,
I won’t mind.
So you got hurt so badly
because of protecting me
in the Nether World.
You’ve always been with me.
Your injuries are all because of me.
However, I have been here
for thousands of years
suffering from gains and losses.
You obviously love me.
Why didn’t you tell me before?
♪Above the clouds♪
When you wake up,
♪Outside the world♪
let’s not miss each other anymore, okay?
♪Could you lend me more years♪
♪I embrace the Milky Way for long♪
♪But where are you♪
♪Only a shadow is left♪
♪Wandering in the old dreams♪
♪After countless sufferings♪
♪How many years have I wandered♪
♪If you were here If you were far away♪
You shameless Devils!
I have shown you
the Inheritance Ceremony.
What else do you want me to do?!
Why a rare beauty like Goddess of Snow
still so unrefined?
You and I are both of Devils.
If you kept being so noisy,
could it be that you hope
the entire God Realm
find you have fallen into the Devils?
Nonsense!
It’s all your fault!
If you hadn’t done something to me
in the Nether World,
how could I have been contaminated
with the Devilish Energy?
Such a pity.
Even though you have returned
to the God Realm now,
you still can’t get True God Bai Jue.
What is the delicacy for?
As long as you cooperate
with me obediently,
Overlord will definitely help you
achieve whatever you want.
Wu Huan.
I didn’t know Goddess of Snow
would suddenly arrive. Forgive me.
What can I do for you?
You are really loyal to her.
No wonder you are from the lower realm.
You are really silly.
I heard that right after
she returned to the God Realm,
she ordered you to go
to Mount Kunlun to cultivate yourself.
Does she know
how hard you have been working on
taking care of the halls of True Gods?
You have to attend to
the dignity of Chief God
and balance the relationships
with the gods from other halls.
This is much harder
than cultivating yourself.
Does Goddess of Snow
come to the Pilgrimage Hall
specially to care about me?
Wu Huan.
I just want to tell you
that I understand you.
Chief God is in the high position.
She has big things to deal with.
She could leave you
in the Pilgrimage Hall
without gratitude.
Does she know how hard it is to manage
the Pilgrimage Hall for the first time?
Has she ever cared about you?
Does she know what you did for her?
I have no leisure time. Excuse me.
By the day,
the spirit of Queen of Phoenix
is about to be reborn from Nirvana.
By then,
will Shanggu still have
a miscellaneous phoenix
around?
Without the blessing
of the Pilgrimage Hall,
you will live worse
than a thousand years ago.
Her Grace won’t treat me like that.
You don’t have to sow discord here.
We’re the same poor people.
Just to remind you.
Did you know that Shanggu
is going to the Phoenix Clan?
You can go back and ask her
whether it’s true or not.
It’s my own business.
I won’t bother you, Goddess of Snow.
Shanggu.
Yuemi.
Shanggu,
Did you really let Tianqi go?
I did it alone.
But I have something urgent
to deal with right now.
When I come back,
I will explain to the gods.
At this critical moment,
where are you going?
What?!
How could his spirit be seriously injured
and he be in a coma?
I suffered several times
in the Nether World.
It was his power of spirit
to help me out.
I didn’t expect Bai Jue
to be more affectionate
than you were back then.
But the situation in the God Realm
is so tense now.
Don’t let others know
that Bai Jue is injured.
Otherwise, everyone in the God Realm
will feel insecure.
Just because of this,
he kept hiding his injury.
The Four True Gods
are being questioned right now.
So there has to be no problem at all.
Luckily, the Pith of the Plane Tree from
the Phoenix Clan can heal his injury.
I will go get it now.
Before I’m back,
I hope you can stay
in the Pilgrimage Hall
and help Wu Huan preside over
the overall situation.
I’m afraid of her being bullied.
Do not worry.
I’ll guard the Pilgrimage Hall for you.
And I won’t let others
embarrass Wu Huan.
The situation of the Demons
is not clear now.
You must be careful
on your way to the Phoenix Clan.
There is one more thing
I want to remind you of.
I heard that Feng Yan
is about to reborn from Nirvana.
When you get to
the Phoenix Clan this time,
why don’t you bring her back with you?
The spirit of Queen of Phoenix is fake.
Even after another thousand years,
she won’t reborn.
What’s wrong?
Is there any problem?
I know you pity Wu Huan.
But now the God Realm is in chaos,
with her alone,
it’s hard for her to contend with
Xueying and the other gods.
To keep her guarding the Pilgrimage Hall
will do no good to her.
And over the years,
I have witnessed her temperament.
She’s still surly
and she needs to temper herself more.
Moreover, the Phoenix Clan is the head
of all the clans of the Divine Beasts.
With the help of Queen of Phoenix,
your authority of the Pilgrimage Hall
can be as firm as a rock.
I understand what you said, Yuemi.
Wait for me to come back.
Let’s discuss it then.
Alright.
The Phoenix Clan.
Queen of Phoenix.
Yuemi.
I said it before.
Don’t let Her Grace go down
to chase Tianqi.
Who knows what kind of relationship
is between those two?
That’s it.
She just let that traitor
escape from the God Realm so easily.
I heard that the Demons
are already full of barriers.
And the Demons have already rebelled.
What do you think this place is?!
How dare you be so ignorant!
Yuemi.
Although you are Chief of Gods of Stars,
here is the Chaos Hall.
It’s not your turn to give us orders.
Where is Her Grace?
Tianqi escaped from Her Grace.
Why didn’t Her Grace
give us an explanation?
Greetings, Master.
As you said,
I asked Shanggu to capture Tianqi.
Could it be that I am also the one
who let go of Tianqi?
I dare not mean it.
Shanggu went down to the lower realm
to find traces of Tianqi.
She’s not in the Pilgrimage Hall.
If you dare to mess around here,
don’t blame me for being impolite.
In my opinion, it is inappropriate
for Master to do so.
Tianqi’s case is serious.
Hesitation will only cause chaos.
Watch your mouth!
You’re not qualified to judge
the affairs in the God Realm.
I dare not.
My words are all for
the God Realm’s good.
Chief God is still young.
Considering her relationship
with True God Tianqi,
she wouldn’t want to punish
the Taichu Hall severely.
We can understand that.
But Master and Master Bai Jue
both have experienced the rebellion
of the Devil God 70,000 years ago.
Do you want that devastating disaster
to repeat in the God Realm?
How could the God Realm and all beings
be safe at that time?
What Goddess of Snow said is true.
Please take the world
as the most important thing, Master.
So, Goddess of Snow,
what do you think we should do
with Tianqi?
According to the Rules,
remove his title,
give him God’s punishment,
cut his God’s bones,
imprison him in the Nether World
and never let him out of it.
Rest assured, all gods.
The disaster happened 70,000 years ago
will never replay.
The disaster caused by Tianqi this time
affects the entire God Realm,
I am willing to accept the result
on behalf of him.
Master Zhiyang has always been fair.
Since Master has a word,
then we’ll wait for Her Grace
to come back
and decide on this accordingly.
I finally came to the God Realm
from the Phoenix Clan.
No one can let me go back.
No one.
Wu Huan.
It was such a mess outside.
Why didn’t you go out and help Master?
Her Grace did let go of Master Tianqi.
I was afraid the gods
would make it difficult for me.
I didn’t know how to deal with it
for a while.
If so, I would let the gods
see the weakness.
Even if they made things difficult,
we would have Master protect us.
What are you afraid of?
I…
Her Grace is Chief God.
Even if she made a mistake,
no one would dare to judge her.
But you and I
would be treated differently.
We are just the low-grade
in the God Realm.
If the gods blamed it,
I’m afraid we couldn’t afford
the consequences.
Master treats you and me very kindly.
She trusts us deeply.
If something really happened,
Master would definitely protect us.
You must believe in her.
I... I believe in Her Grace indeed.
It’s just that...
I really panicked at that scene.
It can’t blame you.
But now the situation is so tense.
We must keep the Pilgrimage Hall
for Master.
Your Grace.
This is the Pith of the Plane Tree.
Thank you, Elder.
The Pith is extremely hard.
Only with fig wine,
refining it with Chaos Fire,
can produce curative effect.
Elder.
Is it the spirit of Feng Yan
in the canopy?
Exactly.
Calculating by time,
after a few more months,
Queen of Phoenix will be reborn.
Although you have mercy
and don’t fuss about
the origin of my Phoenix Clan,
after Queen of Phoenix’s Nirvana,
she will go to the God Realm
to be your Divine Beast.
Elder,
I want Wu Huan to accompany me always.
Well…
Your Grace.
Wu Huan was just
a Colorful Phoenix after all.
Her God power is limited.
I’m afraid
she won’t be a great assistant to you.
I know her talent for cultivation
is not much.
But since I chose her,
I would wait for her.
I am Chief God of the God Realm.
If I abandon her
because of her weak God power
and choose Queen of Phoenix,
then in the future,
if there are someone else
stronger than Queen of Phoenix,
what choice should I make then?
Your Grace is right.
All right.
I just hope
she can concentrate on cultivation
and win honor for my Phoenix Clan.
Thank you for your understanding, Elder.
Then, after Feng Yan is reborn,
she…
Just let her be carefree
and grow up freely.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪