=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 11=
Master.
How dare you escape from
the Nether World,
inciting Qiong Qi and them
to break in the God Realm?
You asked for it.
Master.
Welcome back.
Your Grace.
It’s been a thousand years.
How have you been?
Today, your behavior was heroic.
But I have one doubt.
You were supposed to guard
the Nether World.
Where did you hear from the news
of Qiong Qi?
Master.
Today, Her Grace broke the barrier
and went out.
I was meant to greet her.
Then I saw a demon sneaked out
of the barrier.
I worried that he’s up to something.
So I followed him.
That’s how I found
out Qiong Qi’s behavior.
It seems like after exiling
for a thousand years,
you’ve learned a lot.
I should praise you for today.
I’m incredibly honored.
I was trapped in love
a thousand years ago
and made a huge mistake.
All I did today was to atone for it.
If you can understand,
please allow me to go back to God Realm.
I will never cause any trouble again.
Well.
God Realm’s always been righteous
on reward and punishment.
From now on, you can resume your post
to be in charge of four seasons again.
Thank you, Master.
I was practicing in
the Deicide Flower Field that day.
All of a sudden, a bunch
of Demons attacked me.
Countless arrows aimed at me.
(The Pilgrimage Hall)
I had no chance to take a break.
During the fight,
someone wanted to sneak attacked me
while I got blew up.
Sharp sighted as I was,
I grabbed a branch.
When I was about to steady myself,
the branch broke.
Broke?
Did you get hurt?
Weirdly,
an inexplicable spiritual power
caught me.
Spiritual power?
There’s more than that.
During the past thousand years,
a familiar voice has always lingered
in my ears.
Shanggu.
He always gives me strength
when I’m helpless.
I guess
it’s from one of you.
You came to the Nether World
to help me cultivate.
Who do you think
it’d be among the three of us?
It’s you. Ice Cube.
Bai Jue.
Maybe it’s God’s will which helped you
out of the danger.
Yeah, Shanggu.
You and Devil God sat the barrier
outside the Nether World.
Even we can’t break in.
But I saw that man’s figure.
You saw Bai Jue?
Not only Bai Jue,
but also Zhiyang, Wu Huan,
Gu Jun and Yuemi.
I guess
you just missed us too much.
Shanggu.
You’ve had a hard time
in the Nether World.
Though it’s hard,
it brought me fortune.
Without having cultivated in there,
my spiritual power wouldn’t
improve this much.
Here.
Let’s raise our glasses.
To Shanggu’s spiritual power.
How come you can’t drink
as much as before now?
I can’t hold the liquor.
Ice Cube.
What a bummer.
You knew Shanggu was coming back
but you hurt your spirit.
You hurt your spirit?
It’s nothing.
I practiced too hard.
Shanggu.
Now you’ve acquired
the power of chaos, you should
take over the instruction feather
of Chief God now.
You only care if I can
take over the instruction feather.
Bai Jue.
You were too impatient.
We have waited for tens
of thousands of years.
Give it a few more days.
Shanggu.
Take a good rest.
Then we’ll talk about the rest.
Yeah.
Ice Cube.
If you can’t drink more,
go back to sleep.
I know that
the Lower Realm’s spiritual power
is losing.
You’ve been waiting for me for long.
I pity all living creatures.
As Bai Jue wishes,
I’ll take over
the instruction feather
after half a month.
That day will be a day
of a brand new start.
I have other business to do. See you.
Bai Jue.
Never mind.
His presence would make it awkward.
Luckily I’ve got you two.
Let’s enjoy tonight!
Enjoy tonight!
Here. Let’s drink hammered.
Master.
I’m fine.
You are the best at making bed.
You also prepared my favorite
Goddess Incense.
I can finally have a good sleep tonight.
Your Grace.
You’ve suffered a lot
in the Nether World.
You should take a good rest
for some days.
Let me take good care of you.
I know it’s been harder for you.
Those immortals are always snobbish.
I left in a rush.
You were inexperienced.
I guess it wouldn’t be easy for you
to be in charge of the Pilgrimage Hall.
No matter how hard I had to work,
I’ve never felt wronged.
Now, Your Grace has gained
the spiritual power
and is taking over
the instruction feather.
The Pilgrimage Hall
is finally becoming the primary hall.
It doesn’t matter if it is.
It’s all nonsense that I used to say.
Don’t worry. Now that I’m back,
I’ll definitely protect you
in the future.
From now on,
just relax and focus on cultivating.
In my opinion,
your power can’t compete
with Muguang and Gu Jun.
Does Your Grace think
my power is too weak
to be in charge of the Pilgrimage Hall?
Silly. That’s not it.
God Realm always respects those
who are powerful.
The newly promoted immortals
all have great power.
Now you’re in charge
of the Pilgrimage Hall.
They seemingly show respect to you.
But if you don’t improve your power,
they won’t be convinced.
Except for Yuemi and Gu Jun,
you are my closest one.
My wish for you is
that even if you leave the hall someday,
you can still be a qualified Goddess.
I’m not smart enough.
Your Grace thinks highly of me.
I will surely
not let you down.
Well.
It’s been a long day.
Now, go and have a rest.
Wu Huan’s personality
needs to be more cultivated.
I’ve thought about you
for a thousand years.
But you...
(The Pilgrimage Hall)
Wu Huan.
What are you thinking?
Chief God left for a thousand years.
Did you really think
you can stay in the Pilgrimage Hall
forever?
A fake would always be a fake.
It’d never be real forever.
(Changyuan Hall)
Can you report to Master
that I’m here to see him?
Master Bai Jue is
no longer your teacher.
I used to be Master
Bai Jue’s apprentice.
Now I’m back to God Realm.
I ought to pay him a visit.
Go. Go. Go.
It’s very late now.
Master has gone to bed.
You should leave.
Hongri.
Master.
Greetings, Master.
After so many years,
Master is still elegant.
You’ve fought your way back
to God Realm.
You should mind your business.
Don’t cause any trouble anymore.
Don’t come here again.
I don’t want
to see you anymore.
Master.
Master!
- You can’t break in.
- Master!
Do you know how much effort I spared
to come back to God Realm?
Master.
Why don’t you want to see me?
Master. Master.
(Changyuan Hall)
Master.
Let it go.
Just forget it.
Master.
No matter what you do,
Master has made up his mind.
You are not the one in his heart.
Stop doing this.
If you continue to do so,
I would despise you as well.
(The Pilgrimage Hall)
Here.
What do you think?
Are you satisfied with it?
You are the honorable Chief God
of the Three Realms.
It’s such an honor for you
to prepare for my birthday party.
I couldn’t be happier.
This is to celebrate your
one hundred thousandth birthday.
I’m afraid you wouldn’t be satisfied
if I don’t throw you a big party.
I’m thrilled with all of this.
However,
when have you become a fan
of such big occasions?
It’s to make you look good.
So pretty.
It’s so much better.
Yeah.
- Happy Birthday
- to Goddess of Moons & Stars.
You sure seized the chance.
You’re having a baby now.
If it weren’t
for Yuemi’s credit,
we wouldn’t have a chance to be married.
Thank you.
Your love is solid as gold.
I only provided you a chance.
Today is the Goddess’s birthday.
Don’t be restrained.
Enjoy as much as possible.
I brought you a birthday gift
from the Nether World.
I will show you
after they leave.
What is it?
Well, it took me three whole days
to prepare it.
Your birthday gift
has to be the most precious thing
in this world.
Shanggu.
Thank you for the party.
I have a gift for you, too.
What is it?
Let’s go. Let me show you.
Wu Huan.
Take good care of the guests for us.
Yes, Goddess Yuemi.
Let’s go.
What a scenery!
No wonder it’s the Taoyuan Forest.
Well?
Is this the gift
for me?
What if it is?
Of course I’d like
the gift you give me.
I’m happy, too.
I saw the God of Night and God of Day.
It reminded me
Puhua once held
the Dating Event here.
It feels like yesterday.
Who’d know
a thousand years have passed.
Do you still remember it?
How come you suddenly
thought about that?
Do you feel lonely?
Puhua went to the Lower Realm
for practice.
When he’s back,
I’ll ask him
to set you up with many blind dates.
In this life,
I don’t think I’ll ever meet the one.
You’ve only lived for tens
of thousands of years.
Your life is still long.
It’s too early to say.
How about you?
How about your love life?
It’s been a thousand years.
Do you still think about that Ice Cube?
In his mind,
the Three Realms matter more
than his personal emotion.
I’d rather give other people a chance
than just focusing on his.
Do you mean it?
Of course not.
I practiced hard for a thousand years
just to be as good as him.
But I don’t want to be swayed
by emotions like I used to.
Shanggu.
I asked you out
to say something to you.
What do you want to say so seriously?
Actually,
during the time you left,
I could rarely see Bai Jue in God Realm.
He only showed up on serious occasions.
But whenever I saw him,
he’s always pale.
It looked like he was weak.
Weak?
What else did you see?
Nothing much.
You know him.
He doesn’t like being close to others.
He’s always alone.
I didn’t dare to ask about it.
However,
I think there must be something wrong.
During the past thousand years,
a familiar voice has always lingered
in my ears.
He always gives me strength
when I’m helpless.
Original being comes to one.
Break the three pure ones together.
I guess
it’s from one of you.
You came to the Nether World
to help me cultivate.
Maybe it’s God’s will which helped you
out of the danger.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
If he separated his spirit from his body
to help me in the Nether World,
it’d be a huge damage
to his original being.
I wonder...
What are you thinking about?
Shanggu.
♪Memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
(Endure the Hardship)
♪I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away♪
You’ve joined us for some time.
If you pass this test today,
I’ll start to teach you
the power of rules.
Really?
What are you doing?
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
How dare you use Mind Reading to me?
Shameless!
You look respectful
but you scold me in the heart.
Isn’t it shameless, too?
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past♪
♪When we wake up♪
What’s this?
Kite, rattle-drum
and trotting horse lamp.
These are some childhood toys.
Yeah.
There are balls and shuttlecocks.
Yeah. Yeah.
My childhood was much more meaningful.
It’s flying. It’s flying.
It’s flying.
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds♪
♪And rain drops♪
♪When everything♪
♪Works out♪
The kite is just a toy to you.
But not to me.
Shanggu.
♪A thousand years♪
Wasn’t the kite broken?
How come here’s another one?
Your Grace.
Hongri.
Hurry up and tell me
what happened to your Master
during this time.
Alright.
(The Pilgrimage Hall)
Shanggu.
How is it going?
Say something.
There’s an important thing for me to do.
What’s that?
Fix him.
And...
Marry him.
Marry...?
Marry him?
Do you mean
you want to marry Bai Jue?
Do I need to prepare
betrothal presents for him?
Yes.
To marry an ordinary immortal
requires some betrothal gifts.
He’s a True God.
If to marry him,
I have to gather
all the priceless treasures
in the world for him.
Because
he’s been waiting for me
for a thousand years.
Though you left God Realm,
your personality didn’t change at all.
Wu Huan.
What are you doing here?
Where’s Shanggu?
Goddess Yuemi.
Her Grace went to the Lower Realm
a few days ago.
She asked me
to give you the instruction feather
after three days.
She’s got some wicked ideas.
Goddess.
Is there anything wrong with Her Grace?
Not at all.
Don’t worry.
Shanggu is pretty smart.
Just guard the Pilgrimage Hall for her.
No matter what I do,
I can never be the same as you.
Master Bai Jue.
Master.
What happened?
I was inspecting the Lower Realm today.
But surprisingly there was Qiong Qi
in the Southsea, too.
I fought with them already.
But I wasn’t enough to beat them.
There’s a riot going on now.
Hongri.
Go and ring the bell
to gather all immortals.
Yes.
No... It’s too late.
Shanggu went down after being noticed.
Well.
I’ll go and gather everybody.
You go and help her.
Forget it.
Your power is too weak.
You won’t be much of help.
Just stay here and guard
the Pilgrimage Hall.
I’ll go to the Chaos Hell
to tell True God Zhiyang.
Stay here. I’ll go.
Just some Qiong Qi.
Judging from Her Grace’s power,
she can handle them all.
Our Master
has been a True God for so many years,
how come he couldn’t think it through?
(Southsea)
So weird.
There’s no sign of Qiong Qi here.
Is the beast gone?
Wonders in the Heavenly Realm.
Traditional handicrafts.
Come and check it out.
Wonders in the Heavenly Realm.
Traditional handicrafts.
Come and have a look.
The craftsmanship of my store is superb.
Goddess flying to the moon.
Divine dragons guarding the sea
and so on.
(Traditional Handicrafts Workshop)
If anyone’s wood carving
can exceed my craftsmanship.
I am willing to buy out
with three times the price.
I never break a promise.
Immortal.
You have been shouting
in Southsea for three days.
You’ve taken all the good things
in this city.
Why aren’t you leaving yet?
Immortal.
I’ve only won a few treasures here.
Southsea is the most famous place
in the Immortal Realm.
I think the collectors
are willing to part
with wood carving treasures.
You are so articulate.
I brought my family ancestral
wood carvings today.
- Family wood carving?
- Is it better than yours?
This treasure is perfect.
The craftsmanship...
It looks good.
It’s really good.
Why did you trick me into coming here?
Ice Cube, why are you here?
The chaos of Qiong Qi isn’t true.
The chaos
of Qiong Qi?
What are you talking about?
I’m going to become the Chief God.
That’s why I’m here for a few days.
Are you looking for an excuse
to come here for a tour?
What a coincidence!
It’s destined that
we met here.
How about we travel together?
Nonsense. Go back.
Stop it.
Are you going?
Do you know each other or not?
- Right
- Right.
Do you know each other?
Dear Immortals,
a thousand years ago,
I started to learn from him.
Unexpectedly I fell in love with him.
But I did not know how to confess.
So I paid all my attention
to him.
As a result,
he decisively pushed me away
for various reasons.
I was hurt deeply.
So I decided to forget him
and travel all around the world
for years.
Guess what?
Now he regrets it
and comes to me.
Pestering me all the time.
But
I don’t know if I should forgive him.
What should I do?
Immortal.
A man of integrity never
regrets things given up.
Ignore him.
- Yeah...
- Ignore him!
But I think
he is still in love with her.
I have swore
and made up my mind
to not go back together with him.
But whenever I see him,
the feelings in my heart
got aroused by him again.
You see.
He likes wood carvings.
So I wanted to gather
all the traditional handicrafts
of the Three Realms to him.
Tell me.
How come I’d be so obsessed with him?
Did he go too far?
He doesn’t know how
to cherish a good relationship
and misses it.
It’s too bad, isn’t it?
Right.
- Be together!
- Yeah!
Be together! Be together! Be together!
I didn’t expect that True God Bai Jue
would have such an awkward moment.
How does it feel?
It’s unpleasant to
be misunderstood, right?
It’s too miserable.
But there’s someone who’s willing
to endure it for a thousand years.
Do you think this person deserves it?
I did not push you away ruthlessly.
Not to mention pestering you
all the time.
This is a new storybook I read.
Do you think I was talking about you?
This is a relief of Donghuang.
This is a root carving of Qingqiu.
Shanggu.
You’re about to take over the place
of the Chief God.
Don’t waste your time around anymore.
Wasting my time?
There was a man who’s worse
than me a thousand years ago.
He often showed up and disappeared
from time to time.
There is no one else here.
You can say whatever you want to say.
He just doesn’t like the crowd.
Not only that.
He’s not good at getting close
with others, too.
Then how do you think
that person should do?
I think...
♪Time disturb my feelings♪
♪Like you do♪
♪Hold tightly with your warm hand♪
♪Look up at the meteor
across the darkness♪
♪Your tall figure♪
♪Is even clear in the haze♪
♪I save some time♪
Just act in this way.
♪Every second sounds so sweet♪
Does this Kylin look like Hongri?
Yes.
Not only this Kylin.
♪To have the next life♪
♪When we meet again♪
But also all the root carvings
in this room are for you.
Do you want to be with me?
♪Listen♪
What did you say?
♪We feel each other♪
I used to think
you value my position of Chief God
more than your feelings for me.
You care more about if I can take
the responsibility of the Three Realms.
It seems that every day
you stayed with me
was to make sure I inherit
the instruction feather.
Shanggu...
For example, you opened
my vessels for me
to improve my strength.
I also took credit for sealing
Overlord Xuanyi.
You helped me subdued the Feng Clan
and took over Gu Jun.
It was to calm the God Realm’s doubt
to me as the Chief God.
You asked me to go to the Nether World
to practice a thousand years
for self-improvement,
and deal with the crisis of the collapse
of the chaos power in the Three Realms.
Shanggu.
You are the God of Chaos.
It’s your duty to succeed to the throne.
The later you take over the throne,
more dangerous the Lower Realm would be.
I know.
All beings in the Three Realms
are my duties.
But I’m afraid that when I become
the Chief God,
it’s harder for you to say
how you feel about me.
You will think that the duty
of the Chief God comes first.
Nothing else matters.
In fact, in my heart,
I just want you to be safe.
Who wants to hear this?
Do you still remember the moves?
♪Until I meet you♪
♪I make every attempt♪
♪To have the next life♪
♪When we meet again♪
♪I’ll travel around with you
without hesitation♪
♪Listen♪
♪We feel each other♪
♪And get close♪
Tonight is the Valentine’s Day.
It should be bustling with activities.
Do you want to go out for a stroll?
The feeling of being struck
back and forth
is not pleasant, is it?
But you are not a fish.
How do you know the joy of a fish?
(Fairy lantern)
Yes.
It’s beautiful.
Right.
Didn’t you love the peach
blossom stuffing before?
I’m used to the spring and fruits
in the Nether World.
I don’t like these sweet things
any more.
Let’s go. Let’s go over there.
Will you buy the latest
rabbit lantern for your sister?
Excuse me.
Why did you say that?
You should say that the two
of us make a good couple.
And we should buy a pair
of Mandarin duck lanterns.
Don’t mislead me.
I have seen all kinds of immortals.
But you don’t
look like a couple.
Why did you say that?
You stayed so far away from each other.
So you don’t look like a fairy couple.
I will buy them all.
Great. Great.
Which one do you like?
I do not like these.
You don’t like these?
Then you must like this.
How did you get this kite?
Guess.
What are you doing?
Don’t you even know this?
Immortals will write the lover’s name
on the lanterns.
Then put the lanterns into the water.
They’ll sincerely pray to us
to bless them for a lifetime of love.
So that they can get what they want.
But Puhua is still in
the reincarnation path.
What is the point of writing these?
If you keep talking nonsense,
I’ll throw your kite in the water.
How did you get this kite?
It wasn’t just this kite.
Someone’s been
keeping my beloved toy
and the notes I wrote
in his study room.
It’s been a thousand years.
Why do you think he
saved my stuff like this
as if they were treasures?
What do you want to say?
I’ve said what I want
a thousand years ago.
I wanted to say in the Taoyuan Forest,
and in the Mount Lookout.
Bai Jue.
I...
Who is it to interrupt
my romantic moment?
Your Grace.
I didn’t know Your Grace and True
God Bai Jue came to the Lower Realm.
Sorry for meeting you so late.
I am the God of Water
I did not call you out.
Just now, I received the lanterns
from Your Grace.
The lantern also says...
- That Bai...
- Shut up!
I must have written it
too fast to be clear.
This night is dark without light.
You didn’t see it clear either, did you?
What do you want to say?
What is written on the lantern?
It’s not important. It’s really not.
I also arranged a lot of fun activities.
Qiong Qi! Qiong Qi is coming.
Qiong Qi?
- Hurry up and go!
- Go! Quickly.
So the chaos by Qiong Qi is true.
It seems that the seal
of the Demon Realm is broken.
So Qiong Qi has been
causing troubles all around.
Muguang and Gu Jun just returned
from the Wasteland.
How? How come it happened again?
When we find out the truth,
everything will be clear.
Go to the God Realm
and report to Master Zhiyang.
Tell him that
Bai Jue and I are here
to suppress the rebellion.
Ask Tianqi and Master Zhiyang.
to go check the seal of the Demon Realm
and see what happened
in the Demon Realm.
Yes.
You have not yet recovered.
Let me do it.
I’m fine.
We must trap and kill Qiong Qi.
If we let one go,
there will be a great disaster
in the Immortal Realm.
The natural chaos power
in the Heavenly Realm has thinned.
It’s unsuitable to use spiritual power.
If you and I fight them now,
this place will be in ruins.
What should we do then?
Do you remember the swordsmanship
I taught you on the Mount Lookout?
You mean to use the sword power
of the Ancestral Sword?
Right.
The Ancestral Sword is one
of the four Divine Weapons.
Add it with your power,
I think the power on the Ancestral Sword
would be enough to kill Qiong Qi.
Okay.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪