♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
We are five kilometers from the next village.
Shall we crash in the village tonight?
Something's wrong.
No one is in the field at all.
Brother San.
I'll go take a look.
Be careful.
Should there be wolf thieves
in Tian Dou Empire too?
If you want this woman to live...
Xiang!
come get her with your lives.
I will definitely protect you.
San.
What move did you use?
Look. What is that?
[Episode 161]
You're asking for your death!
What should we do?
I'll handle it.
Brother San!
San!
Fourth Skill,
White Tiger Meteor Strike!
Blue Silver Emperor Tyrant Spear!
Tang's Clan's One Hundred Hidden Weapons,
Fourth Weapon,
One Thousand and One Nights!
One thousand and one hidden weapons
attack from all different directions
in both straight and curved lines.
Unless one can teleport,
there is no way to avoid them.
In the history of Tang's clan,
no one has ever come out alive
after being attacked
by One Thousand and One Nights.
How is that possible?
Brother Dai.
How is it?
Your guess is correct.
This soul bone
is called Bloodthirsty Tornado Right Leg.
Its skill, Bloodthirst,
allows me to enter
the Berserker state immediately.
My attack, defense, and speed
will be doubled,
but I can't use other skills.
But in the Berserker state,
you will lose your consciousness.
It's better not to use the soul bone skill for now.
When sometime in the future
that we find a skull soul bone
and you have it,
your spirit power will increase
and will be able to control yourself
in the Berserker state.
OK.
Brother San!
Ma Hong Jun is...!
Get him in the carriage first.
The wound is too big.
We have to stitch it.
Brother Dai,
please hold him down for me.
I'm afraid that he's going to twitch from the pain.
OK.
Xiang.
Can you do it?
Yes.
I...
don't really have much ambition.
I just want to live happily
and have enough to eat.
Stupid Fatty,
move away!
You know that I'm fast
yet you still blocked me.
Did you do it on purpose?
But...
if it was for someone I cared about,
I can also sacrifice myself like that.
Xiang!
I will protect you!
[Soul Land]
You're awake.
That's great!
Xiang.
I'm sorry.
I failed to protect you
and you got hurt.
Why are you apologizing?
This isn't your fault at all.
It's all because I'm too weak
and dragged you all down.
That's not it!
If it hadn't been for you
fighting with the wolf thieves,
those villagers would have been dead.
You saved them.
Even if that's the case,
you still don't need to apologize to me.
Besides, you got wounded so badly
in order to save me.
I'm thick-skinned and not afraid of pain.
You...
It'll be bad if a weak girl like you gets hurt.
Are you dumb?
Who doesn't feel pain after getting hurt?
No one cares about me anyway.
Then you just keep laying there!
Fatty.
You really are dumb.
That's right.
A true dummy.
Why are you all calling me that?
Why did Xiang get mad at me again?
Fatty.
Do you think Xiang would have stayed by your side
waiting for you to wake up
if she didn't care about you?
That's what Xiang meant?
Fatty.
Xiang's safety is on you from now on.
No problem!
Brother San.
I will definitely do this job well!
Xiang will never get injured for the least bit.
Xiang! I'm here.
Look! I'm fully recovered.
Training is the easiest way
to recover from exhaustion.
That's strange.
Ever since I got the Vast Sea and Universe Shield,
I keep feeling the warmth from the four soul bones,
especially when I use soul skills.
Even though it doesn't cause me pain,
the four soul bones are getting warmer
as my training increases.
Why is this happening?
[Hanhai City]
Look at that! Look!
How's everything going?
The wind and the sea wave are so strong lately.
It's not safe
to sail.
I wouldn't recommend a journey out there.
Hanhai City
really is Tian Dou Empire's
biggest harbor city in the west.
But...
the ocean is so vast.
How are we going to get to Haishen Island?
We need to rent a boat at the pier
and sail out.
It'll take us about ten days
to reach Haishen Island.
Brother San, don't worry.
We have enough money.
Let's go.
Steamed buns!
Fresh steamed buns!
Come and take a look.
They're fresh and hot.
So delicious!
Come and see!
-This filling is fish.
-Come take a look!
They're fresh!
Hello there!
Wow, the colors of these pearls are so special!
Pink,
light blue,
brown,
light purple,
and black!
What is that smell?
It's strange.
This is your first time in Hanhai City, right?
That's the smell of the ocean.
The beautiful ocean
is to the west of Hanhai City.
When the wind blows,
you can smell the salty air.
May I ask
where the city's Soul Arena is?
In the center of the city.
It's very easy to find.
San.
You're going to compete in the Soul Arena?
Before we left,
Teacher told me
that the way ocean soul masters fight
is so different from which of normal soul masters.
If I can compete with some of them
in the Soul Arena,
it'll help a lot
when we're on the island.
No problem!
We'll take a look at the Soul Arena first tomorrow.
We've been traveling all this way
and haven't exercised in a long time.
Fatty.
You are indispensable in the fight to come.
Hurry!
Hurry and bet on the Haipo Brothers!
The competition is about to begin!
Welcome to the Hanhai Soul Arena's
two versus two soul battle!
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 161 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1508 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2433]
[Total scene: 59890]
[Total CGI: 27924]
[Total plan of action scene: 12566]
[Total scene model: nearly 564]
[Total character model: nearly 1021]
[Total props model: 13386]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
♪ I'm faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods ♪
♪ Who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching ♪
♪ Any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven't told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
Hanhai Soul Arena
is indeed unique.
Oh no!
Fatty has used too much soul power in the beginning
and is about to lose.
This next auction item
is a very rare soul guiding tool.
It can withstand the attack
from a Century Soul Beast.
Deal!
It looks like we need to attend the auction.
[Soul Land]
[10 AM every Saturday]