♪Waking up in a nightmare♪
♪Facing this cruel world♪
♪Whose heart is flipped♪
♪Missed farewell to lover♪
♪If the ending is tragic♪
♪Fearlessness is born in adversity♪
♪Even if the wings are torn♪
♪And fall back to the abyss♪
♪Hold your hands and move forward♪
♪Never stopping day or night♪
♪Transcending time and distance♪
♪I may be hurt and heartbroken♪
♪Yet be brave to fight on♪
♪As a hero♪
♪Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops♪
♪Turning behind, you are always there♪
♪Lash out the curse in life♪
♪Let the story be eternal♪
♪Martial Soul surges aggressively♪
♪To embrace your lone wolf braveness♪
♪Even if the future is harsh♪
♪I will never give up♪
♪When there is no way out in reality♪
♪Hope is vexed by desolation♪
♪Yet smiling freely♪
♪Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant♪
♪The power of twin souls illuminates♪
♪Surviving in every plight♪
♪I will never give up♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
We indeed successfully enter Haishen Island,
but this is just the beginning.
Great!
[Black Level Seven Test]
Is this the difference between
the top-tier and the black tests?
The challenge is about going up the stairs
but we need to pass through
the forbidden area of Haishen Island.
This pressure can bring out our potential.
Bai Chen Xiang, please accept the test
of the Ocean Delusion Beast in the Sea Within a Sea.
I am ready.
(Forty-nine, fifty...)
(The recovery of soul power
can't keep up with the consumption.)
Be careful, Brother San!
[Episode 171]
This is what it feels like to be stuck.
Wu, don't get close to
the Light of the God of the Ocean.
You will get hurt!
San is running out of soul power.
(Within the Light,)
(the teleporting skill is ineffective)
(and I can only use
the Invincible Golden Shield against attacks.)
(I can't go any further under such pressure.)
I'm fine.
I need to keep trying to finish this challenge.
You should all have a try.
Okay.
San.
The pressure from the Light
comes from the front entirely.
We can defend ourselves with soul power.
But what about Wu?
As long as Wu stays close to me,
I can protect her with my soul power.
But you will use your power even faster.
Wu's body will also be affected by the pressure.
That's why I need to get stronger as fast as I can.
Do you have a way?
Teacher once said
that the bigger the pressure,
the more likely to bring out one's potential.
The best time to improve
is when a soul master's life is in danger.
The Light of the God of the Ocean
is the best catalyst for our growth.
(My breathing underwater
can only last for 30 minutes.)
(I need to quickly find
the Ocean Delusion Beast and pass the challenge.)
(A millennium soul beast...)
(Is that the Ocean Delusion Beast?)
(It looks very aggressive.)
(I won't have an advantage
if I attack head-on.)
(I need to remain hidden
and take it down with one shot.)
(Oh no, it saw me!)
(Made it!)
(Everyone is doing their best
to pass the challenge.)
(I can't fall behind!)
No... I can't do it anymore...
Thirty steps
is my limit.
Rong Rong, are you alright?
My body is too weak.
Even with the amplification
from the Jiubao Amber Pagoda,
I can't enhance the resistance.
Support branch soul masters are at
a big disadvantage against the Light.
Moreover, you have to climb
more stairs than most of us.
One hundred and thirty-six steps...
Don't push yourselves too hard. Safety first.
Can we really finish
a challenge like this?
(My cultivation speed
has significantly increased.)
(I no longer feel weak.)
(This is the same state I was in
when I was at the waterfall.)
(The longer we last
under the pressure of the Light,)
(the faster we cultivate.)
(But...)
(If I can't talk to Wu about her health in time,)
(she will be easily hurt)
(when we pass through
the Light of the God of the Ocean.)
(This time,)
(I have to awaken her soul.)
Wu.
Brother.
Wu, we are already on Haishen Island.
Did you feel the thing
we experienced so far?
Are you angry?
What's wrong?
Wu.
Wu!
(Her climbing speed)
(is even faster than when I first
entered the Light.)
(Does this mean)
(Wu is more powerful than me?)
Be careful.
Brother Dai stopped at the 38th flight of stairs.
(This is Wu's first attempt
and she didn't use any skills.)
(Her body can even sustain more pressure
than Brother Dai.)
(It's the Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet!)
(No wonder why.)
(Legend says that it can help one
cultivate an unbreakable physique.)
(Wu must have absorbed its effects)
(and greatly increased her endurance
and soul power.)
Forty-eight, forty-nine...
Fifty!
[Soul Land]
Wu, how are you feeling?
My body is not at my upper limit,
but my soul cannot take it anymore.
If you're just carrying my body,
you don't need to worry about
the first sixty flights of stairs.
I can bear even more.
Come back inside of me now.
Your soul can't be damaged.
So what if it is?
You're always worried about me,
but what about yourself?
Tang San, remember.
When we're in danger again
and you only protect my soul
but not yourself,
I won't talk to you ever again.
That's why you're upset? I...
Brother, let me come out every day
and cultivate with you from now on.
The pressure on me just now helped exercise
both my body and my soul.
I should be able to hang on for a longer while.
I should go back. Don't forget what I said.
Or else I'll...
(If Wu can do all that for Brother San,)
(then I can't give up either.)
(Or else, how can I protect Xiang?)
(It recovers so quickly.)
(Oh, no, the water is impeding my speed.)
(I can't keep my balance.)
(In order to move against the water,)
(I need to keep consuming
my soul power and the oxygen.)
(But this means I will run out of strength soon)
(and die from suffocation.)
(If I let the water carry me
and give one hard strike,)
(I might still have a chance.)
(Now it's time!)
(Third Soul Skill, Flight!)
(First Soul Skill, Delusion!)
(What?)
(It's much faster than me!)
(Oh, no, I'm running out of oxygen...)
(I'm still too weak.)
(I can't even deal with a millennium soul beast...)
(I'm the same age as everyone else,)
(but I will never be like them.)
(Am I... just a burden?)
Xiang! Run!
(Fatty!)
(No!)
Don't worry. I will protect you well.
Don't worry, I will protect you well.
No!
I'm most scared of being a burden
but I'm always making trouble for you.
I'm so useless.
Xiang,
don't cry.
I'm alright.
I said that I would always protect you.
No! Don't die! Don't die!
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 171 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1578 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2585]
[Total scene: 62794]
[Total CGI: 28590]
[Total plan of action scene: 12714]
[Total scene model: nearly 580]
[Total character model: nearly 1055]
[Total props model: 13419]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪We still have to part from each other♪
♪I'm faint-hearted to stop you from leaving♪
♪Amidst the grieving woods♪
♪Who is crying out there♪
♪I still relentlessly hold on♪
♪I refuse to accept this destiny♪
♪Desperately searching♪
♪Any signs of you♪
♪The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight♪
♪In your eyes, the world never changes♪
♪Yearning grows and interweaves with the past♪
♪Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven't told you♪
♪You are the memory I refuse to let go♪
♪And the craziness of my desperation♪
♪Can you hear♪
♪My calls♪
♪Breaking through extreme dolours♪
♪Rushing towards your embrace♪
♪You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair♪
♪And the wish I made upon a star♪
♪One day♪
♪You will turn up gorgeously♪
♪And hold my hands♪
♪To envisage our future♪
[Next episode]
Yellow Level One Test is not hard.
Bai Chen Xiang used her wits
and advantages...
The pain of skipping levels
and absorbing soul rings
is almost unbearable.
Fatty has really changed a lot
after meeting Xiang.
Xiang's well-being is in your hands.
It's almost been a month.
Feel it carefully.
Use your utmost willpower to endure it.
You've found the true mystery
of the Light of the God of the Ocean so quickly?
Much less Fatty, who's always carefree.
He can definitely do it.
No wonder the God of the Ocean chose you.