(Praomook)
So this contract is real.
Now that you know the truth,
what will you do next?
I want you to be careful
of your brother-in-law.
I think Nuch and Danai
seem suspiciously close.
How close do you think they are?
I don't love Praomook.
Are you happy?
So far you haven't been
honest with me.
Go be with whoever you want.
I will take care of her.
If people knew why you got married,
wouldn't you feel ashamed?
Let's get a divorce.
Alright.
(Divorce Certificate)
Uncle, I appreciate your kindness.
But I'm firm about my decision.
If it were back then,
I wouldn't accept this.
But you got hurt because of my son,
and I'm not okay with that.
About your house, you can have it.
Think of it as compensation
for the trouble.
It's too much.
I will move out as soon as I can.
(Divorce Certificate)
Did she get anything?
She wouldn't accept anything.
Dad's possessions are intact.
Are you happy?
Very.
I'm glad she's left our family.
I think she became free.
You can think whatever you want.
Just know that
I finally feel at peace.
Oh.
And if you're thinking about
getting back with your ex,
I suggest you find a new girlfriend.
Treenuch can only be your ex.
I don't want her
as my sister-in-law.
Our company is facing trouble.
I want you all to find out together.
There are complaints about
our products not meeting standards.
That they are unstable,
are made of low-quality materials,
and are overpriced.
Even worse,
our new products
were available on Lan's Much app
before their launch.
I ordered some of them.
They really are our products.
Have you checked how they got out?
I have. They probably got out
during production.
I've also checked
our defective furniture.
The issue occurred during
the material selection process,
resulting in overpriced,
low-quality products.
The person responsible is
the design and development manager.
All the evidence points to Rawin.
He might be the culprit.
(Reviewer: Rawin Mahadeshoshai)
Now that we have hard evidence,
we should look into it
and contact the police.
I don't think we should
involve the police yet.
Let me handle it.
However, I will need
full authority on this.
Alright then.
Prepare a report on this for me.
Okay.
Poom, check
the merchant in question on Much.
Find out who they are,
where they are located,
and where they procured
the products.
Got it.
Have you told the police?
Not yet. I asked my dad not to.
Why?
If my sister is involved,
I won't be able to help her.
What about Mook?
Dad told her to stay at
the condo for now.
Anyway, I'll leave her to you.
Lan, aren't you worried
about her at all?
I'm doing this because I'm worried.
Right.
Talk to you later.
Lan, you have to suspend Rawin,
or put together a team
to investigate this. I will help.
I will handle it myself.
You can help me with the press.
Alright. But you can't be
lenient about this.
No matter who they are,
if they are dirty,
I won't let them get away.
(Subject: Review of suspension)
(Chalantorn Anantanapat
Vice President)
Oh, Lan.
You seemed focused today.
But you didn't.
Are you worried about the company?
I've been watching Rawin
for a while.
Now that we have evidence,
I'm ready to get rid of him.
Like removing a cancerous finger.
Let's worry about the outcome later.
I hope the finger we plan to remove
is actually cancerous.
If it isn't, cancer may spread
to the whole hand.
The evidence points to him.
We have the culprit.
According to what I have found,
Rawin could be a scapegoat.
What do you mean?
He might have been framed.
The true culprit
could go unpunished.
Who is it?
How do you know that?
I've known for a while,
but wasn't sure.
Once I have all the evidence,
I will let you know who they are.
When you know,
let me know.
Where are you going?
Out of here.
Let me give you a ride.
For your safety.
Let go.
Even if we're no longer married,
I'm still worried about you.
Your concern is unwanted.
If you want to take care of Mook,
give me a straight answer.
Do you love her?
Take care of her for me.
You didn't answer my question.
I will take that as a no.
Don't worry.
I will keep her safe.
The evidence points to him.
We have the culprit.
According to what I have found,
Rawin could be a scapegoat.
He might have been framed.
The true culprit
could go unpunished.
Once I have all the evidence,
I will let you know who they are.
Lan.
Mook and I got a divorce.
Congratulations on your freedom.
You don't look happy.
Do you regret losing her?
Don't forget that
she doesn't love you.
She wanted your money.
It's best to stay away
from that selfish woman.
What about you?
Why did you come back into my life?
Why do you ask?
Do you think I'm like her?
You two are different.
I'm asking you that
because I want to know you
and everything about you.
I came back into your life because
no one else deserves you like I do.
I love you.
Thank you for the ride.
I will find time to visit you.
I'm still concerned about
your safety.
Alright.
Don't tell Lan where I am.
I want to start over
and forget about what happened.
Okay.
(Poom)
I know. I'll handle it.
I have to go. Excuse me.
I have to go.
That's all I have to say to you.
I will wait for you.
I hope it won't be a waste of time.
Of course.
Get yourself ready.
I will come back later.
If you shoot, I shoot.
Let's see who is faster.
Wait, Rut.
I will handle him.
But...
You know who he is, don't you?
Get yourself ready.
I will come back later.
Good timing.
Take your stuff with you.
From now on we won't talk again,
unless it's about work.
Never come back here.
And return my keycard.
As soon as you found out
they got a divorce,
you get rid of me.
You know we aren't a thing.
Now that I've found
someone better, richer,
holding the vice president position,
I have to choose him.
Don't compare me to Lan.
You can't compete with him.
Do you think he loves you?
You're just a toy.
When he gets tired of you,
he will leave you.
You have no right
to talk to me like that.
If he knows you slept with me,
he won't want you.
If you tell him, I will tell Lak
she has an unfaithful husband.
If you tell her, I will kill you.
There are no secrets in this world.
Lak.
Don't.
I've seen enough.
Do you take me for a fool?
Snake.
You stabbed me in the back.
You pretend to be high and mighty
when in fact,
you're as dirty as a pig.
Sleeping around with a married man.
You're just a mistress.
- I'm not a mistress.
- Then what are you?
A man's plaything?
You're cheaper than I thought.
You!
Stop seeing Danai
and get out of Lan's life
before I deal with you.
A cheap woman like you
doesn't deserve my brother.
I told you before, didn't I?
If you betray me,
I will make you regret it.
If I can make your life comfortable,
I can ruin it too.
Your life is in my hands.
If you hurt my sister,
I will send you to jail.
Lan.
Do you think
you can do anything to me?
Why don't we find out
what the evidence I have here
can do to you?
Evidence?
What is it about?
It's about the fraud,
showing that
the culprit isn't Rawin,
but Danai.
In this,
there is proof that the documents
and Rawin's signature are fake.
Documents you created to cover up
years of embezzlement
are also in here.
Lak.
Don't believe him. He is lying.
He is trying to get rid of me.
There could be nothing on that.
I knew you would doubt me.
All the evidence against him
is in here.
If you don't believe me,
we can prove it
in front of the police.
Lak, listen to me.
Greedy pig.
I'm going to remind you
that you are here today
because of me and my dad.
Piece of trash.
Right, I'm a piece of trash.
But you made me become this man.
Don't put the blame on me.
I'm telling you the truth.
You've walked all over me,
telling me I'm worthless,
incapable,
even though I've worked so hard
as if I were a slave.
In the end, I really am a slave.
No one appreciates me.
My life isn't in your hands.
You're always ready to ruin my life.
And I don't know when
you will take everything back.
I never thought about leaving you.
I've done everything for you.
You've done it for yourself.
You put me down.
That's why I had to do something.
I can't lose.
Everything is your fault.
It's in your nature.
My sister has nothing to do with it.
I will make sure you go to jail.
Lan.
Let him go. I'm begging you.
After all of that,
you're still protecting him.
I have to catch him.
Lan.
If this gets to the police,
it will be out of our control.
If it gets on the news,
it will affect the company and Dad.
Are you going to let him get away?
It won't end here.
I will end it myself.
I will take responsibility
for what he did.
I'm the reason why
he became this man.
I put too much pressure on him.
I did it for his own good.
I love him.
However,
it's my love for him that hurt him.
Please let me deal with this, Lan.
Alright.
I will let him get away this time.
If something happens after this,
I won't give him another chance.
Lan.
We will talk later.
Okay.
Danai, you ruined everything.
Find Danai and bring him back.
Give him time.
I will deal with this myself.
No. Even though you two are married,
you don't have to take the blame.
If he has to go to jail,
will you go to jail in his place?
I can do it.
Laknara.
If I hadn't put him down
or made him think I could leave him
anytime, he wouldn't have done this.
This is partly my fault.
It still doesn't
justify what he did.
Come on, dear.
Let's not send someone to jail.
We should end this discreetly.
If you want a second chance,
find Danai and bring him back.
Lak.
Do as he said.
It's our best solution.
The number you have dialed
cannot be reached at the moment.
Please try again later.
You just let a wild animal get away.
You don't know what he will do
once he finds his footing.
Let him try.
Then I will make him pay
once and for all.
That way, I won't break
my promise to my sister.
I know you can look after yourself.
But what about Mook?
We can't guess
what his next move will be.
Where did you hide her?
You don't have to know.
Just know that
she is in a safe place.
Then you do your job.
If you fail, I will make you pay.
Who are you to make me pay?
Ex-husband?
Childhood friend?
Both titles
entitle you nothing.
Whatever.
Have you finished packing?
Do you need my help?
It's almost done.
Let's start a new life.
Although this house is smaller,
I'm sure we'll be happier.
No matter what happens,
we will get through it together.
If you want to do something,
you can go ahead.
You should do things
for yourself too.
Alright, Mom.
All the evidence against him
is in here.
If you don't believe me, we can
prove it in front of the police.
Greedy pig.
Did you take me for a fool?
Right, I'm a piece of trash.
But you made me become this man.
- Don't put the blame on me.
- I'm telling you the truth.
You've walked all over me,
telling me I'm worthless.
My life is in your hands.
You're always ready to ruin my life.
And I don't know when
you will take everything back.
I'm scared that
I will lose everything.
That's why
I had to look after myself.
I will not struggle again.
Come on.
Let go.
You!
You released the video, didn't you?
I asked you a question.
Somebody, help me!
Help me!
Nobody will help you.
You snake, you ruined my life.
It's your own doing.
Alright.
Since you ruined my life,
I'm going to make you
unable to face anyone again.
No, don't.
Lan ordered me to do it.
He said he let you go
to make you think you got away,
then he would make you pay later,
so you would finally
get out of his sister's life.
He wants to destroy me, doesn't he?
I was just following his orders.
I'm sorry.
Alright.
Since he destroyed my life,
I'm going to take him down with me.
Tell him
he will suffer with me.
And if I can't hurt him,
his loved ones will have to do.
I will start over with you
as a friend.
Even if this didn't happen,
we wouldn't be able to continue.
It's you who believes
we can't continue.
Do you think
I don't know how you feel?
You may be with me,
but your heart is somewhere else.
I know where my heart is.
That's why
I want to be clear with you.
If you don't feel anything for me,
you can leave.
I refuse to be
the only one who loses.
I'm sorry, Lan.
Okay, I just secured your bookings
for this week and
the beginning of next month.
Okay, thank you.
Hey, Mook.
You just got more gigs.
You're booked up for three months.
That's good.
You're lucky in game
and unlucky in love.
You can have a good life
without a man.
I guess so.
Did they go to Chiang Rai?
Yes, Mook, Oak,
and Petch went there.
Don't they realize it's dangerous?
Dangerous? How?
It's nothing.
Nampetch.
Wait here. I will be back.
Rut.
Why didn't you tell me
you came here?
Let's talk about that later.
I'm worried about my sister.
She just left all of the sudden.
Lan.
- Mook!
- Lan!
Rut, catch him.
Somebody, get a doctor!
Lan,
are you okay?
I'm okay.
Please wait outside.
Please move aside.
Let us take a look at her.
How is she?
The patient is safe.
Mook, how are you?
Does it hurt?
A little.
I will be fine though. Don't worry.
Oh, my poor girl.
You're safe now.
Okay.
Mook.
I'm sorry that my family
dragged you into trouble.
Also, thank you for saving my son.
Without you,
he would have died.
About Danai, I will handle it
as soon as possible.
Alright.
Lak, help me.
Take it easy.
That's for hurting my brother.
And that's for betraying me.
You said I put pressure on you,
forcing you to steal money.
I admit that
I played a part in this.
But my mistake is
marrying a piece of trash like you.
Lak.
I was wrong. I'm sorry.
I didn't mean for this to happen.
Don't.
Don't give me stupid excuses.
You planned the whole thing.
This isn't your first time.
Lan told me everything.
Lan.
If only you could stop being nosey
and leave me be.
You messed with my life.
You took the position
that was supposed to be mine.
You're such a greedy pig.
- Calm down, ma'am.
- Lak, that's enough.
Listen to me.
Even if Lan didn't come back,
I wouldn't let you be in charge.
Did you think
you're smarter than everyone?
Did you think you could
get away with everything?
We just gave you a chance
to redeem yourself.
I'm disappointed
in how stupid you are.
Right, I'm stupid.
I'm stupid for working so hard,
hoping that somebody
would appreciate me
and give me a chance.
Win.
You want to be the president's
son-in-law, don't you?
Go ahead. You can have the title.
- Hey!
- Don't do it.
Did I hit the nail on the head?
If you don't shut your mouth,
no one here will help you.
This is your fault, Lan.
You ordered Treenuch
to release the video.
- I didn't do it.
- I don't believe you.
She confessed
that you told her to do it.
Everything
was going nicely.
When I get out,
I'm going to kill you first.
Hey, stop!
Go over there. Move.
Come here.
Move.
Rawin,
after you're done here,
you can go back to Bangkok.
Also, you're free to take leave
if you want to.
I want to get back to work quickly.
There are many things to be fixed.
Good. I'll leave it to you.
Of course, sir.
Lak.
Dad.
You knew that
Danai is untrustworthy, didn't you?
I want you to find out
who attacked Lan.
Do you suspect someone?
I don't trust Danai.
But I'm unsure if he is connected.
If something seems suspicious,
let me know immediately.
Yes, sir.
Yes, I did.
I thought he would repent.
And I was wrong.
You and Lan
don't trust me.
You thought I was also involved.
I wasn't sure, so I investigated.
If you were involved,
I would try to make it
less hard on you.
I may love Danai,
but I love my family more.
I wouldn't let
anyone hurt my family.
Dad.
I'm sorry for marrying an evil man
and causing you trouble.
No, Lak.
It isn't your fault.
Don't blame yourself.
Listen to me, Lak.
I'm very proud of you.
Do you know that?
Hi.
I'm sorry that Danai hurt you.
It isn't your fault.
You don't have to apologize.
I'm not ready to be
completely nice to you.
But I understand
how it feels when
you want to save your loved ones.
That's all I want to say.
Thank you, Lak.
Don't think I will always
let you hurt me.
If you slap me again,
I'm going to press charges and
you'll be in jail with your husband.
That was nothing compared to
what you did.
You ruined Danai's life.
You caused my company trouble.
But your useless husband
hurt me first.
He lied and said he loved me.
My life went downhill
the moment he came into my life.
I know you don't want me
to be your sister-in-law.
You used me,
just like your husband did.
I should have made you suffer more.
He blamed you,
saying it wasn't his fault
because he is selfish.
Getting rid of him
is the best thing for both of us.
Removing you from my brother's
life is also the best thing.
You don't deserve Lan.
If you truly love him, you wouldn't
have released that video.
You're free to do whatever you want.
But if she comes after our family,
I won't let her get away with it.
Just yell at me
and get it over with.
I'm sorry.
We can't go back to
what we were, can we?
We can't.
Smells nice.
- It's a new recipe.
- Hm?
- I'm trying out a new recipe.
- Oh.
Hm.
Well.
Go on, say it.
I'm tired of waiting.
I want to talk to you about work.
You can quit and
do your own thing if you want to.
You can even submit
your resignation letter tomorrow.
Aren't you going to try to stop me?
No, I've had enough.
I already have Lak.
I don't know why I would need you.
I heard your company
needs a marketing manager.
Well, I could let
our assistant manager be in charge.
Come on, Dad.
Well, what do you want to say?
I want to be the marketing manager.
I have a degree in this field.
I can do it.
Well, what about your company?
I can work two jobs.
People can have more than one job.
If your company fails,
I will still have my own company.
Hey, don't jinx my business.
Dear, did you hear what he said?
Should I disown him?
Can you kick him out?
Alright, be honest with me.
What made you decide to work for me?
After trying both at the same time,
I realized I can do it.
Also,
Mook told me I still have
a chance to work for you,
while she doesn't have that.
Wow, this son of mine.
I kept telling you that, and
it went completely over your head.
But when Mook said it,
you understood.
Alright, if you say so.
I'm warning you though. If you don't
do well, you'll be fired.
And if I do well,
you have to give me a bonus.
It's a deal.
Yes, let's go.
Oh, I love you.
Love you.
How is Mook?
Wound is healing. No complications.
She can leave the hospital.
Thanks for looking after her.
As someone who loves her,
I'm entitled to say it.
Aren't you worried
that I will be mad at you?
No.
I've handled everything. I can
tell you how I feel about her now.
Don't you think it's too late, huh?
I've given you many opportunities.
You said you didn't feel
anything for her.
And now you're saying you love her?
What are you playing at?
I'm being serious.
I want to be clear with you.
And if you're upset by that,
I'm sorry.
We've never fought
over a girl before.
Can't you just leave her alone?
I will stop when Mook tells me to.
We agreed not to
go for the same girl.
You have to stop this,
otherwise,
our friendship will be in trouble.
Hey.
Lan.
Ting, why did you let him in?
Well, you didn't tell me not to.
If you did,
I wouldn't have let him in.
This time, just give him a pass.
Make it up to her quickly.
I will leave you two alone.
Say what you have to say.
I made my decision.
I will make you love me again.
Lan, it's enough.
I've moved on. Please leave.
Your lips say one thing,
but your heart says another.
You can't move on from me, duckling.
You're right. I haven't moved on.
But if you keep making me
feel like a loser,
one day I might be
able to stop loving you.
Lan, let go.
Calm down, Mook.
You never lost.
Your love always wins.
It overcame death.
If it wasn't for you,
I would have been dead.
I came here because I love you.
I won't accept your love easily.
Alright.
I will ask you again.
Do you love her?
Yes, I do.
Then you don't have to worry.
We aren't interested
in the same girl.
What?
I don't love her the way you do.
She is a friend.
Then why did you punch me?
I did it for Mook.
You were horrible to her.
How many times did you make her cry?
I had to teach you a lesson.
Look.
If you want her to love you again,
you have to put in your best effort.
Jerk.
Yay!
Good job, Petch.
Congratulations on
the launch of your game.
You did it, Nampetch.
Good job.
Thank you.
You convinced me you're capable,
that you're not just playing around.
My sister is the best.
Thank you.
Do you think I can get myself
a man after finishing the game?
Oh, if I get a guy in real life.
The creator can't even
get herself a guy.
Petch, who are you trying to get?
I mean, a character in the game.
- Right.
Right, Mook.
Can you do the music festival gig?
If you can't,
I can cancel it for you.
I can do it.
Can I go with you?
Can you keep Rut away?
If you can do it,
I will help you get him.
Follow me.
What are you doing?
Move.
Where are you taking me?
Hey! What are you doing?
Stay still
if you don't want to fall down.
Why are we here? What do you want?
I want to know
how you feel about me.
I don't want to talk about that.
But I want to hear it.
Don't lie.
Tell me how you feel.
I can take it.
If I say I don't love you,
what will you do?
I will disappear from your life.
Forever.
I love you, jerk.
I love you so much that I want to
make you lose and love me back.
But I realized that
winning is useless.
You can't win love.
Are you happy?
We were married against our will.
This time we're both willing.
More importantly, you love me,
and I love you.
We love each other.
Duckling,
will you marry me?
Hey!
What's gotten into you?
I'm really not dreaming.
Now, will you marry me?
If it's a yes, give me your hand.
There you are.
Now that you're wearing
the ring I chose,
I will consider today
our wedding day.
Our first of many anniversaries
will be on this day.
Today is the day we love each other,
and no one else gets a say in it.
I want you to know
that I love you.
I know.
And I will remember
that we love each other.
Chalantorn,
I love you.
I know you love me back.
Will you be my boyfriend?
Praomook,
I love you too.
Hold on.
Where are you taking me?
I'm going to see your sister.
You can't.
Why not?
- Because...
- Because?
Because Mook is busy.
And you have to come with me.
To do what?
To...
To watch the balloons over there.
Rut.
Can I take my sister's place?
No, you can't.
It's because
I'm still a kid, isn't it?
I'm eighteen now.
I will be twenty in two years.
Then you will be twenty-six
or twenty-seven.
It isn't a big gap.
Can you see me as a woman?
I will show you that I...
- I love...
- I said no
because you aren't
a substitute for anyone.
You're you, not your sister.
Everyone has their own worth.
Don't compare yourself to others.
Besides, I know you love me.
You know but you don't care.
I know and I care.
I just realized that
the person I like
is the little sister,
not the big sister.
What?
What did you say?
Do you like me?
I won't repeat myself.
Okay. You like me.
And?
I kept telling myself
that you were a kid.
But it was an excuse for me
because I refused to face the truth
that I have fallen you
for who knows how long.
Now I can only wait.
Wait for what?
Wait for the girl to grow up
and be sure about her feelings.
That way,
I won't get my heart broken.
I won't break your heart, trust me.
We'll see about that
after you turn twenty.
I don't want to break
a girl's heart.
I wonder whose heart
will break first.
Watch out.
I will make your feel sorry.
I doubt it.
Hey, Rut!
If you don't stop flirting with me,
I will knock some sense into you.
This is just the beginning.
Brace yourself.
My love is reciprocated.
Thanks, Lan.