(Praomook)
I have to find out who you are
and end this madness.
You have to figure out
who could be at a disadvantage
and have a lot to lose
from your return.
Lak.
For now, let him
try to absorb the fact
that his sister
is our prime suspect.
How much can you trust Treenuch?
Fifty percent.
I don't think you should trust her.
I've decided to step down
from that position.
You may be successful in life.
To me,
you're a bad father.
Lan!
Dear!
Why did you take me here?
To relieve your stress.
Your special order has arrived.
I'm going home.
Oh, you can't leave yet.
Mook has prepared
everything for you.
Do you want to ruin her plan?
Isn't that right, Mook?
Right.
This is for you. I don't want
you to get drunk somewhere else.
Think of it as
you're DJ Prao's VIP guest.
Do you want to try?
Sure.
Let me.
Come here.
This is play control.
Mook is with him. Don't worry, Pat.
That's a relief.
Mook is always there for him.
Please take care of my son.
Of course.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for looking down on you
and thinking that
you're an irresponsible person.
Today I saw that you don't
fool around with your life.
No matter what you do from now on,
I'm willing to support you
in everything.
What do you want in return?
I just want to watch you
go forward on your own.
Are you sure I can do that?
I believe in you.
I accept your apology.
Thank you for believing in me.
Well.
You look much better now.
If you want to stay over,
you can stay in the studio.
I'm selfish like you.
We're different.
I do what I do for my family,
for the company, for your future.
Have you ever asked me
if I want that future?
I don't want it.
You may be successful in life.
To me,
you're a bad father.
Lan!
Dear!
Lan.
I'm sorry.
Can I take a shower?
Sure.
Stay still.
I'll move.
- Oh no.
- Hey!
Lan, there's a gecko.
- Lan.
- What?
There's a gecko. Get it out of here.
- Then stay still.
- Get it out of here.
- I know. Just get it out of here.
- Come on.
Just get it out of here.
I don't care how.
- Please get it out of here.
- Alright, alright.
- Oh my goodness.
- I can't do it if you don't let go.
I won't let go. Just find a way.
- Come on, Lan.
- Hey!
Is it gone?
- Calm down.
- Get it out of here.
- Lan!
- Don't get excited.
Focus on the gecko.
- Oh.
- What?
It disappeared.
What? How?
You have to find and catch it.
Otherwise, it will come after me
and I will die.
Do you hear me?
It's a sin to
ruin people's happiness.
You will be punished.
Do you think I'm scared?
I'm not scared. I'm not scared.
I'm not scared.
Hey!
You have something on your head.
What is it?
- What is it?
- Don't move.
What is it?
It's this.
- Where are you going?
- No!
- What?
No, get it away!
Come here.
No!
No, get it out!
- How do you like that?
- Get it out!
It ran off.
What?
- Are you sure?
- Absolutely.
Watch this!
- Lan!
- What? There's nothing.
- Jerk, you scared me.
- Ow.
- Take this.
- Hey, duckling, stop.
Oh no!
Lan, close your eyes.
- Right, got it.
- Don't look. Close your eyes.
- Both eyes.
- Okay.
Let go of me. Lan, come on.
- Open your eyes when I say so.
- Okay.
It's not like I want to look.
Lan!
- Oh.
- Move.
Ow!
Cute.
What?
Hey.
Are you scared that
I will do something?
Nonsense. I'm not scared.
You aren't scared, right?
Then explain this.
Do you think it will keep you safe?
Well, which cheek
should I start with?
It won't keep you safe.
What are you doing?
You said you weren't scared.
I won't do anything to you.
Petch.
Did you come here by yourself?
Yes, I did.
There's a very important guest
at my house.
I don't want the owner of this house
to feel lonely, so I came over.
Wait, Petch.
The thing is...
I can't contact Lan. I'm worried
So I came here.
Lan is away right now.
But don't worry.
He can handle himself.
I know that but I can't help it.
If you're worried about him,
you can drop by every day.
You're always welcome at this house.
What do you want in return?
I just want to support
my friend's love life.
I want to support you too.
I want Mook to
finally find her own love.
I don't support you two.
This is an adult matter.
A kid should stay out of it.
I'm not a kid. I'm mature
enough to know what is proper.
Not only do you
try to be the other woman,
but you also try to destroy
the love between two people.
No.
I'm not destroying anyone's love
because there's no love
in the first place.
Then take a look at this.
Do you see love in this picture?
(Delete)
There's nothing to see now.
Anything else?
Your behavior is immoral.
You don't care about others.
You only care about yourself.
You're selfish.
Nampetch,
you're crossing the line.
Honestly,
what are you insulting me for?
Your sister, Lan,
Rut, or yourself?
If you're doing it for yourself,
you're just as selfish.
Nampetch, stop.
Come here.
Nuch is my guest.
You have no right to do that.
If you're still acting immature,
you will not come here again.
Rut.
Have you changed your mind?
No, I haven't.
Here.
Are you calmer now?
If you are, you should have
a talk with your father.
I don't want to talk to him now.
If you say so.
Life is unpredictable.
Anything can happen.
If you have a problem,
you should solve it quickly.
You don't know
what tomorrow will bring,
if you will be alive or dead.
Look at me and my dad.
I have tomorrow,
but my dad doesn't.
I have to go to work.
Tell Lan to call me when he's back.
Sure.
- Nuch.
- Lan.
She was worried because she couldn't
contact you, so she came here.
I'm fine. Thanks for your concern.
I'll leave you two alone.
If something is troubling you,
you can talk to me.
If you mean my dad,
I already handled that.
Really?
I have good news for you.
Your company launch video
has over a million views.
With this great feedback,
your company will do well.
I know you can achieve anything
that you set your mind to.
What if I don't succeed?
That day won't come. I'm sure of it.
A reward for being awesome.
I should head to work.
See you later.
What did your dad say
about you resigning?
He was angry
and we fought, as usual.
He wouldn't let me quit.
Did you tell him the reason
why you're resigning?
No.
You know I can't tell him.
Right.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Where were you last night?
Well?
I went to Mook's house.
Did you go with her?
Yes, I did.
Do you have something
to tell me about her?
No, I don't.
Everything remains the same
between me and her.
That's good to know.
Try to be honest with me.
I want to hear it from you.
Don't let me find out on my own
because it will end differently.
Boss.
I've finished checking the documents
from Lan's company.
Just as you suspected,
millions worth of products
were lost.
Financial statements
were manipulated.
Poom has traced these transactions.
The account holder's name is Rawin.
Don't underestimate this guy.
Rawin is our prime suspect now.
It's the contract.
You left it at my house.
Thank you.
Did you come to talk to me
about this contract?
Yes, I did.
But I've changed my mind.
I want my son to work for me again.
And if you can do that,
just tell me
what you want in return.
What if I ask you to give your son
a chance to follow his own path?
I want to see him enjoy his life
and do what he loves.
I don't care
if he fails or succeeds.
Just seeing him on his own journey
is good enough.
Mook,
real life isn't pretty.
I know you want to help him.
But I must insist on this.
I want my son to come back.
We can follow our dreams
while doing our duty.
We don't have to make a choice.
I'm not trying to impede him
or ruin his life.
He chose to give it up.
He chose to do only one thing.
And I can't accept that.
Do you understand me?
Does this mean
you will give him a chance?
That's right.
But you have to convince him
to come back and do his duty.
Alright, I will try.
I handled it.
If the auditor finds out,
you will be in trouble.
If this can help you,
then it's worth it.
Don't worry about me.
You can carry on with your plan.
If you need my help, let me know.
No matter how risky it is,
I'm willing to do it for my friend.
Win.
If Rawin did attack me
to cover up the fraud,
he should have done it
when I started working there.
But this began in Korea.
It could be that email.
Do you think these sales figures are
lower than they are supposed to be?
Right.
You should tell your dad
to take a look at it.
I'll send it to my sister.
If something is wrong,
she should be the one to tell him.
Okay.
Lak.
She might know about the fraud
and doesn't want you to find out.
Not to mention
her position in the company.
If you consider these factors,
the whole thing makes sense.
Impossible.
It's possible and you know it.
Look.
What proof do you have
that my sister is behind everything?
that your sister didn't do it?
Nothing.
Then your sister and Rawin
are the suspects.
It could be someone else.
It could.
If you're afraid of the truth,
you should back away.
Ignore it and let them work it out
while you focus on our company.
Right. I should do that.
But I'm not a coward
who shies away from reality.
Then it's time to change the game.
Your attacker is
keeping a low profile,
figuring out your next move.
If you want to catch him,
you have to lure him out,
vice president.
I have to be a hunter
who acts like prey.
Check where Rawin was
and if he left the country
- while Lan and I were in Korea.
- Got it.
If you're still acting immature,
you will not come here again.
Could you show me this side?
Here.
Are you upset that
Boss gave you a scolding?
He just gave me a scolding.
I'm not upset by that.
How is Lan?
He is calmer now.
It worries me that
Lan has a problem with his dad.
I understand him though.
He's doing it for his future.
If it's possible,
I want to help him.
Don't worry.
Lan can take care of himself.
That's good to hear.
Is that all you want to say to me?
There's one more thing.
Well?
Will you and Lan stay together
until the term is over?
I can't give you an answer.
That's in the future.
Why are you asking?
I'm worried about you.
If I were to guess,
Dad probably helped you
with your financial situation.
Otherwise, you wouldn't have
agreed to marry him.
If one day being around Lan
makes you feel uncomfortable
and you're afraid to tell Dad,
you can talk to me.
I may be able to help you.
Think of me as your brother.
Thank you for your concern.
But I don't want to bother you.
If that's all,
I'd like to get back to work.
Alright.
(Lan)
Do you want to go with this concept?
Mook?
Yes?
It's the concept for the new line.
I want you to create a design.
Okay.
Are you okay?
Do you feel unwell?
She is fine.
Lan.
Do you have business here?
I heard you quit.
I came to deal with something.
Can I have a moment with
your co-worker?
Sure.
You're a charmer.
Where are you taking me anyway?
- You'll be my witness.
- Witness.
Don't tell me you're going to quit.
If I decide to do something,
will you still support me?
If it isn't wrong or illegal
and it makes you happy,
I will be on your side.
(Chalantorn, a passionate CEO)
What's your business?
I will work here again.
What are you saying?
Yesterday you announced
to everyone that you were resigning.
Now you want to come back.
This is a company, not a playground.
You can't just come and go
whenever you feel like it.
Are you going back on your word?
- You...
- I'm sorry.
What did you say?
I'm sorry for
thinking only about myself.
If it isn't too late,
I'd like to come back
to help you and my sister out.
I'm serious.
Okay.
If you can convince the board
to put their trust in you,
you can return to work.
I won't help you.
You are responsible for your words.
Alright.
If I can do it,
I want full control of the company.
I want to show them
I got this job because I deserve it.
Alright.
However, you will be
accountable for any consequences.
This emergency meeting
is about Chalantorn's resignation
as vice president.
Alright.
I will let him explain.
Go ahead.
My announcement may have
consequences,
especially for
the company's credibility.
I have reconsidered it
and decided to
continue working here.
Your indecisiveness
affects the company anyway.
You should just resign.
If you don't, your company's
credibility will be affected too.
Don't worry about us.
We can handle this on our own.
I caused this problem,
and I will find a way to solve it
if you give me a chance
to prove that I'm capable.
You have your own company.
Time management
may be an issue for you.
He has been managing
his time well so far.
I don't think it will be an issue.
I have a plan for the future.
Please hear me out.
I want to focus on the online market
to promote our products
without relying on other platforms.
This will reduce costs
and boost sales.
We will target new markets
in Asia to improve distribution.
Well, that sounds interesting.
If you can't do it,
will we be able to remove you
from your position?
Of course.
I will earn your confidence.
Very well.
We will let him continue his work.
After that,
we will do an evaluation.
Lak, send me the vice president's
work as soon as possible.
I want to get to work.
Sure. I will handle that.
I hope you can keep your promise,
vice president.
Alright. Thank you, everyone.
You're dismissed.
I have one more thing to say.
I want all the documents
on your project, Lak.
Rawin and Danai, I want yours too.
Is that all?
Yes.
I'm glad to hear that
you're serious about this.
If you need my help, let me know.
Dad, you don't have to worry.
This is just the beginning.
We still have a long way to go.
I can't be too confident.
Lak!
Lak, stop it.
Get a hold of yourself.
I'm as calm as I can be.
You should give me props for
not giving him an earful back there.
If he wants everything back,
he can have it.
- Let him have it.
- Hey!
Listen to me.
If you want everything back,
I will help you.
What will you do?
Talk to Dad?
Don't even think about it.
As for Lan, with his arrogance,
I don't think he will listen to you.
I know a way to make you
become the company's number one.
If you want it,
I'm willing to do anything for you.
Trust me.
I can do it.
I want to be number one.
Help me.
Why did you change your mind?
What are you planning to do?
I want to give it a try.
You're willing to do
what you don't want to.
Does this have
something to do with your sister?
You suspect that
she could be involved
in the incidents.
You knew?
I also know that you refused
the position because of her.
So why the sudden change of plans?
Can I trust you?
Look into my eyes
and make your own decision.
Are you going to
use yourself as bait?
If I don't do that, we won't
know who is behind the whole thing.
This matter is too
important to ignore.
What will you do
if the attacker shows up?
I will catch him.
And what will you do
if you don't catch him?
Don't you have another plan?
No, I don't.
You only have one life.
Don't play around with it
as if you're playing a game.
Just be careful.
If something seems wrong,
tell me, Rut, or Poom.
Don't go it alone.
Do you understand?
You're bossy.
How will telling you help me?
I don't know. But I won't let
anything happen to you.
You stay out of it.
I can deal with it on my own.
I want to stay out of it
and leave you on your own,
but I can't do that.
I'm worried about you.
I know about Lan's decision.
It's very risky.
I'm envious of him.
If it were me, would you be worried?
Of course I would.
We're friends after all.
We may be friends now,
but we don't know about the future.
Rut.
You should be careful too.
Don't forget you're the only one
who saw the attacker.
I'm scared he will come after you.
Alright, I will be careful.
Hey!
- What?
- Come on.
Oh.
Hey.
Lan!
Lan and Praomook's
marriage contract.
She married for money and her house.
I thought she did it out of love.
Do you think Lan knows about this?
I don't think he knows.
If he did, he'd have thrown a fit.
What do you want me
to do about this?
It's up to you.
You could show it to him
and bring him to his senses.
I have someone else in mind though.
Who?
Lak.
I assure you.
She will burn the house down.
From now on,
Rut won't see me as a kid anymore.
Lan!
Do you think
the attacker will show up?
Soon.
Lan.
What happened?
What's wrong?
I dreamed about the attacker
and you.
Did I get hurt in your dream?
It's just a dream.
It doesn't mean anything.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday. Happy birthday.
- Bang!
- Wow.
Happy birthday, my dear.
I wish my daughter
good health and happiness.
You're 18. You're an adult now.
Always think before you act.
Thank you, Mom.
Well, I wish you success
in your career and studies.
And in love.
Come on. Make a wish.
I hope I succeed in everything I do.
Happy birthday to you.
Bang!
Yay!
Are you waiting for your girl?
No.
I see.
Don't wait. She won't come.
Did you forget that
you told her not to come here?
I told you I'm not waiting for her.
Sure.
Well.
Who is at the gate?
Boss.
Someone sent you a threat.
I've checked the cameras.
His face is covered.
Shall I go to the police?
No.
We don't have any leads on him.
He was well prepared.
We won't find his fingerprints.
Using myself as bait worked.
Now that I've returned to
the company, he's on the move again.
I can't believe
it's actually what I thought.
Don't assume things.
We don't have proof
that can identify the attacker.
I can't help it.
Everything is abundantly clear.
Lan.
What is it?
It's nothing.
I'm just being paranoid.
You're paranoid.
Do you think he is nearby?
Forget about it.
What will you do if he comes out?
You know the answer.
Don't put your life at risk
because of me.
Think about this.
Would you do nothing
if I'm targeted and in danger?
You can't help it.
The only way to stop me
is to catch the attacker.
I will try to remember
more details about him.
Even if I didn't see his face,
I may be able to identify him.
What is it?
I brought you coffee
and your favorite dessert.
You need energy from sugar
and starch while you work.
- Poom.
- Hm?
Tell me how to make Rut fall for me.
Poom.
I also brought you my work.
Hand it to me.
(How To Be Romantic)
How to be romantic.
It's a catchy title, I promise.
You brat.
I'm not a kid anymore.
I should get back to work.
Mook is very worried about you.
She is either worried
or is stressed.
She has always been with me
when the attacker showed up.
If this continues,
it will take a toll on her.
If it really takes a toll
on her mental health,
what will you do?
What will you do if he comes out?
You know the answer.
Don't put your life at risk
because of me.
Think about this.
Would you do nothing
if I'm targeted and in danger?
What's wrong?
Let's go home.
I'm going to take her home.
If something comes up,
leave it for tomorrow.
- Come on.
- Wait.
Let me clean my desk.
You leave work on time,
vice president.
You two seem to get along well now.
Is it you who convinced him
to come back here?
You're mistaken.
The person who made me
change my mind is you.
Why?
I want to help you.
With work.
I don't want you to work too hard.
I don't need help.
But I want to.
One day you will understand.
Why did you take me to my house?
You have to stay away from me.
For now you will stay here.
Don't worry about me.
I can take care of myself.
I don't want to be around you.
Being around you
makes me miss my chance
to be with Nuch.
You make me feel uncomfortable.
Do whatever you want then.
If it makes you happy,
I told you I'm willing to
support you in everything.
He is so stubborn.
I can tell he is worried about her.
Oak.
Oak, I have urgent news.
You don't want her to put her life
at risk, so you sent her home.
That's right. This place isn't safe.
The attacker came to our front door.
Something could happen to her.
Staying away from me is best.
And she agreed to stay home
even though she's very worried?
I guess you hurt her
with your words again.
Like I can convince her
by being nice. She is stubborn.
She will listen
if you explain things to her.
Just admit you're worried about her.
Tell her how you feel.
Don't be so stoic.
It's already done. What's the point
of bringing it up?
It's to make you think.
What worries me is,
what if he targets her instead,
who will be there to help her?
That won't happen.
Anything can happen.
Don't forget that
Mook is our witness.
Nuch, are you free tomorrow?
I want to see you.
Come in.
Oh, your complicated relationship
gives me a headache.
Not to mention the attacker
and the love triangle.
Now he goes back to Nuch.
And I'm a crazy woman
who worries about him.
Who knows, he could be worried
about you and want to keep you safe.
Don't give me hope.
It's possible.
(I will take care of him.
You can't get him back now.)
He is a man of his word.
Can you tell me
what's troubling you?
Is it about your work?
Yes, it's about my work.
Don't think of other things.
Focus on me.
(Lan)
(Praomook)
(Rut)
Rut, did you miss me?
How is Mook?
She didn't answer her phone.
Nampetch,
I have to speak to your sister.
Can I talk to her?
Let me think about it.