(Praomook)
I don't agree with your attempt
to sabotage their relationship.
I'm just pushing her
to get a divorce early.
I'm trying to help my brother here.
It's never a secret
when you say it's a secret.
The culprit will hear
about my request for the documents.
This rumor that Lan
is going to be vice president,
I want to hear
his reasons right now.
Why does Dad refuse to
recognize my capability?
It's unfair.
Help me choose. Leave this house,
or I will leave myself.
I'm getting back together with Nuch.
From now on,
I will pursue you.
I want to see you.
Can I come to your place?
Danai's car.
Hey, Lan.
Hey, are you home?
No, I'm out. Do you need anything?
Nothing.
I want to know if you and Lak
saw the news about me.
We saw it.
Who do you think spread the news?
I don't know. I don't want to guess.
Do you want to know about
Lak's reaction or mine?
Both.
What did she say about it?
She didn't say anything.
It's just a rumor.
There's nothing to worry about.
Okay. I've got to go.
She just flew into a rage.
Hey. I've been searching
for this book.
Here.
The book is mine.
Do you have my permission?
I won't read it then.
Sorry for touching your stuff.
Rut.
If you want to read this book,
I can let you borrow it.
In return, you have to
stop being mad at me.
I'm not mad at you.
I'm just frustrated.
I don't like being paranoid.
What are you smiling about?
I like it.
Rut.
I like it when
you're honest with me.
I want to know
how you feel about me.
You can feel anything
you want about me.
As long as you don't hate me.
I want to see you.
Can I go to your place?
He wants to see me.
Should I let him?
You can't beat me, Mook.
Will you go after him?
I can go with you.
No. He can go wherever he wants.
Can you be my witness?
I'm going to keep this file
as evidence and sue that woman.
Sure.
Win.
Why did you just arrive?
I just finished my work.
You've drunk a lot.
I think it should be enough.
No. I want to drink.
Don't stop me.
Win.
My dad spread the news
about Lan becoming
vice president himself.
And?
In the end,
Dad doesn't care about me.
He doesn't appreciate my dedication.
I've worked like a dog
hoping that he would
at least recognize me.
Look where it got me.
It's pointless.
Lan is still number one.
To be honest with you, Win,
I want everything
and I will have it.
Win.
You have to stay by my side.
I won't leave you.
You're important to me.
Lak.
Danai.
(Chalantorn)
Lan, I want to meet you.
You wouldn't understand adult love.
This is an adult matter.
Mind your own business.
Jerk, I'm not a kid anymore.
You're under 18.
To me, you're a kid.
Alright. If you think turning 18
means you become an adult,
I will show you.
We'll see once it's my birthday.
Lak.
- Hey, Lak.
- Don't bother me.
Did I scare you?
No, you didn't.
What happened anyway?
Why is my sister drunk?
She had a fight with your father.
What was it about?
She doesn't want you to be a
vice president with zero experience.
And your father doesn't care
what she thinks.
I think you should take her home.
Danai won't be pleased
if I take her home.
I'll take it from here.
Thank you for being there for her.
Sure.
(Where are you?
Why aren't you home?)
He can go wherever he wants.
You don't have to care about him.
He wants to make you feel restless.
You have to be calm
and keep a cool head.
Just ask him if you're curious.
Then you can feel at ease.
Get it over with and go to bed.
Don't ask him. Stay calm.
Just ask him and
get him out of your mind.
- Don't do it.
- Do it.
- I said, "do it!"
- Don't do it.
- Come on.
Why didn't you tell me
Lak had a fight with my father?
I didn't want to worry you.
She is at the condo.
If I take her home in this state,
it will only cause problems.
It's my fault.
If I were there for her,
she would be more cautious.
Stay with her. I'll be there soon.
Okay.
What a mess.
Lan.
Yes, it's me.
How did you get here?
Win called me to pick you up.
You passed out.
Don't bother next time.
I can take care of myself.
From what I saw, you were hammered.
If it wasn't for Win,
you wouldn't be in this state.
I know what I'm doing.
Can you leave me alone?
Danai is on his way here.
Why did you tell him?
I don't want to see his face.
You all are annoying.
If you're angry at Dad,
don't take it out on Danai.
Someday he will lose
his patience with you.
Can you stop complaining?
I'll leave once he arrives.
You fought with Dad about the news,
didn't you?
I won't accept the position.
So you don't have to worry.
Don't worry?
How can I not worry?
You don't know what you're doing,
but Dad thinks you do.
He tries to make you
take responsibility
even though you're incapable.
He will stop only when you give in.
I'm begging you.
Can you go back to living abroad?
Go back to do what you love
quickly before I...
hate you.
I don't want to see you.
Go back to do what you love
quickly before I...
hate you.
(Lan)
Oh.
Lan.
(Lan)
He didn't pick up his phone.
What's wrong with him?
Who called you?
Lan called me just now.
I didn't answer. When I called back,
he didn't answer.
I guess he doesn't want
to talk to you now.
I guess so.
I feel sorry for myself.
I can't please everyone.
One wants that thing.
The other wants the other thing.
This one wants...
It's true, dear.
We only care about ourselves.
Now,
how can I let it go?
Oh, come on. Don't sulk.
Dear, trust me. I'm sure that
eventually our kids will realize
that you're doing it out of love.
Come on.
I hope I don't die
before it happens.
Don't say that.
Whatever.
I'll try to call him again.
If he doesn't answer,
we can figure it out tomorrow.
Well, if you say so.
Lan.
Lan, can you hear me?
Lan, wake up.
Lan.
We should call an ambulance.
This looks serious.
We don't know what happened to him.
- Okay.
- Don't.
- Lan.
How do you feel?
Tell me where it hurts.
What happened?
Why are you lying on the ground?
I was hit from behind.
You were hit?
- Where? Oh.
- Ah!
How did you get here?
He came with me.
(Location Tracking App)
(Open)
(Get Started)
Condo...
This isn't Treenuch's condo.
Where is he?
This is his family's condo.
I see.
That's his car. He really is here.
If you want to go to his room,
I can arrange that for you.
This way.
Rut, whose hand is that?
Wait here. I'll go check.
- Lan!
Lan, what's wrong?
Lan, can you hear me?
- Lan.
- Lan!
Answer me, Lan.
- Lan.
- Lan, can you hear me?
Lan.
What happened, Mook, Marut?
You cling to me like a sharksucker.
No wonder
you're always there when I get hurt.
It's suspicious.
Is this the time to be saying that?
I'm trying to help you.
I don't owe you anything.
We should tell the police.
Do you remember what happened?
I was walking toward my car.
Suddenly
it felt like I was hit
with a hard object.
Does this belong to you?
Yes, it's mine.
I think it was a robbery.
You had one job.
How could you let this happen?
I'm going to inform your manager
about your negligence.
I'm sorry.
No, it's fine.
Let me help.
Careful.
I'm okay.
Call the police.
Check the cameras
and do a thorough investigation.
- Let me know if you see something.
- Absolutely.
- Here is my card.
- Okay.
Get your superior.
Yes, sir.
You should see a doctor.
I agree with him.
You have to see a doctor.
Alright.
I'll handle the police.
You can go to the hospital.
Danai,
could you keep this a secret?
I don't want
my family to know about this.
Why, though?
I don't want to worry them.
The factory incident is unsolved.
Now there's this.
You know that
it will become serious if Dad knows.
If you say so.
Mook and I will take care of him.
Let's go.
- Take care of him.
- Sure.
Careful.
What did the doctor say?
His brain is undamaged.
Just inflamed, swollen muscles.
A fever is expected tonight.
I think you should rest
for a couple of days.
Lie low for now.
Good idea.
I don't feel like working anyway.
Poom,
check up on the condo's cameras.
Got it.
I don't think it's a robbery.
I agree.
If it was a robbery,
he should have taken
your phone or watch
or found a way to ransack your car.
Only your money was stolen.
I think it's a cover-up.
Right.
I'm heading to bed.
I'll think about other things later.
I want to be alone.
After Chalantorn fell,
we don't see the robber anywhere.
Get images from that camera.
Rawin.
Hey.
What's that position?
Why are you here?
I told you to leave me alone.
I want to check up on you.
If you don't seem alright,
I will call an ambulance.
Come here. Let me apply a cold
compress to keep swelling down.
I can do it myself. Leave me alone.
Ouch, hey!
I told you to stay still.
I'll do it for you.
I want you to think carefully
who could be your enemy.
I think it's the same attacker.
Well, you're my enemy.
If you want to believe that, fine.
But it's a good idea
to consider someone else too.
Even small leads are important.
They could prevent you
from getting hurt.
I don't want to see you die.
I'll give it a try.
Oh, he is burning up.
Will he be okay?
Lan.
Lan, how are you feeling?
Nuch.
Wait, don't go.
Please stay with me.
Jerk, I don't care anymore.
I'm leaving.
You could have mentioned
someone else but her.
I should have gone to bed
and left you to die.
Have you ever seen me?
He hasn't seen you.
But I have.
Rut.
You seem annoyed this morning.
Let me guess.
Lan is the cause, isn't he?
I think we should be honest
with each other.
About what?
I made it clear
that I'm going to pursue you.
I'm a man of my word.
I don't trust you.
Why?
You're suddenly pursuing me.
Lan is getting back with Treenuch.
The timing is too coincidental.
You could be trying to trick me
into divorcing your friend.
Well.
That's possible.
But I only have one plan.
And that is to make you love me
and forget about him.
I think he made it clear
that he hates you.
I want you to stop
thinking about him.
Forget about your past with him.
And give me a chance.
I'm not ready to
give anybody a chance.
Like my sister told you,
although he doesn't love me,
we're technically married.
I want to wait until it's over
before I start my life over.
That's fine with me. I can wait.
However, I have the right to
try and make you interested.
I will make you take off this ring
without regretting it.
Even if I don't have you,
I can take this ring off
without regretting it.
Within a year,
if you take off the ring,
I will take it as
you giving me a chance.
Hold on.
That condition clearly benefits you.
Who would make a condition
that doesn't benefit them?
So, are we clear?
Wait, Rut.
I haven't agreed to your condition.
Who cares?
What are you doing?
I'm taking your temperature.
If you have a high fever,
I'm going to call an ambulance.
I'm fine. Leave me alone.
Hey!
Stay still.
Your temperature came down.
You should rest a while longer.
I'm doing this for your parents.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have bothered.
Then don't bother next time.
You can leave me to die.
Hey! What was that for?
Don't talk about death.
It's a bad omen.
If you talk about it again,
I will give you another smack.
Hey!
Lan.
Sorry, I didn't mean it.
Why did you kick it?
It's in my way.
You look much better.
Do it yourself then.
The new collection
will arrive next week.
I want you to clear the area
and arrange things accordingly.
If there are any changes,
I will tell you later.
Sure.
Win.
You can go back to work.
I'm sorry about last night.
I was so drunk.
Don't get that drunk again.
It's dangerous.
If I wasn't stressed,
I wouldn't do it.
Drinking won't solve your problem.
I think you should deal with
the cause of this problem instead.
You mean...
You know who
the cause of your problem is.
You have to handle that instead.
There are many ways to do it.
It's up to you to decide.
I'll need to think about
which way is the best.
(Dad)
You spread the rumor about me
becoming vice president, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
Dad,
you do things however you want.
Have you asked me how I feel?
Why do I have to ask you?
This is your responsibility.
Whether you want it or not
doesn't matter.
I didn't ask for
this responsibility.
You can hand the company
over to Lak. I don't want it.
And if you don't listen to me,
I will ruin everything.
Lan, I haven't finished talking.
You...
Come on, you stupid son.
- Lan!
Lan, are you okay?
Lan!
I want to talk about Lan.
He is sick.
What's wrong with him?
He has a fever.
He talked about you in his sleep.
Why are you telling me this?
Don't you feel jealous
that he talked about me?
I think you know the answer.
I want to hear it from you,
whether I was right or wrong.
Lan and I are just friends.
Where is he?
I'm going to visit him right away.
I was wondering why
you asked me to find her number.
So this is your evil plan.
Do you want me to be evil with you?
No, I don't want to bother you.
Nuch seems untrustworthy.
Do you think it's a good idea
to let her get this close to Lan?
That's exactly why
we have to keep her close.
We must lure enemies
out of the shadows.
That way,
we can keep an eye on them.
I knew you did this to help Lan.
You wouldn't be selfish
and use people for your own gain.
Getting fired or a pay cut.
Which one do you choose?
I think I should take a look
at the images we got from the condo.
Leave him be.
I'm helping him.
If there's something wrong with him,
we can get an ambulance.
Is he okay?
He is alive. He just fainted.
Lan.
Nuch.
How did you get here?
Rut called me saying that
you're sick and miss me very much.
I've really missed you.
Anyway, are you okay?
Do you have a headache?
I can take you to the hospital
if you want.
I'm okay.
I feel better
after seeing your face.
I'm still worried though.
I'm going to stay with you today.
What are you doing?
Oh, don't mind me.
If you want to flirt with your ex,
or your mistress,
feel free to do so.
I just want to record it as evidence
for the divorce
and sue you for having an affair
with my husband.
Do you think you can stop me
with that threat?
I'm not stopping you,
you can do as you please.
Now, having an affair with
a married man,
don't you feel ashamed of yourself?
Or is your moral sense so low
that you feel nothing?
I see that
you still have no manners.
I'm just trying to protect my right.
If you can't handle that,
you're free to leave.
You have no right to kick me out.
And don't give me
the excuse that he is gay.
Rut told me the truth.
Lan faked being gay
to avoid marrying you.
Pathetic. You forced
a man to marry you.
If I were you,
I wouldn't have done it.
If I were you, I would wait
for him to get a divorce
before following him to his house.
I don't know who is more pathetic
between you and me.
I came here as his friend,
but you keep calling me
his mistress. I should leave.
Lan, it looks like I have to leave.
Take care. I'm worried about you.
Don't go anywhere. Stay with me.
- But...
- I said you can stay.
If someone is upset about that,
they can leave.
I have to talk to her.
Then talk to her.
I'm not stopping you.
Alone.
Since you chose not to leave,
listen to this.
Nuch,
you asked me
if we could get back together,
now I have the answer.
After I divorce Praomook,
we will get back together.
Is that true? I'm so happy.
I want you to wait for me.
Of course, I will wait.
And don't worry.
I don't feel anything for my wife.
Let the countdown begin.
At least you're going to wait
for the divorce.
Before that day comes,
try to control yourself.
If I catch you sleeping with her,
I'm going to be a murderous wife
and cut your member off.
An immoral man should be rid of
the ability to reproduce.
Do you think
you can do anything to me?
You smart mouth.
Why don't we find out about that?
Now, you,
if you want to eat my leftovers,
I don't care.
But I will make sure
that you don't find happiness.
If you want to suffer in this hell,
go ahead.
Wait, I don't think
that's necessary.
With the idea of taking him from me,
you already entered this hell.
- You!
- Nuch.
Don't pay attention to other people.
Let's focus on us.
Alright. We are more important.
You asked me
if we could get back together,
now I have the answer.
After I divorce Praomook,
we will get back together.
I recorded everything.
Try to keep your promise.
Because if you don't,
you will break your own word.
I don't have to be scared of you.
I can do whatever I want.
You're self-centered.
Don't think you can hurt me
by pretending to love her.
I don't feel anything.
Hang in there, Mook.
It doesn't hurt you.
It doesn't disappoint you.
You don't feel anything.
That jerk doesn't feel anything.
Why should you?
You don't love him.
(Uncle Lim)
Hello, Uncle.
Mook, are you with my son?
Yes, I am.
Can you take him to the company now?
We have to discuss his future
and the future of the company.
Before you talk to him,
I want to talk to you first.
Lan.
You asked me to wait for you.
Did you mean it?
About us getting back together,
did you actually mean it?
Or was it meant to hurt her?
I meant it.
I want to figure out
my feelings for you.
Is it because you're my ex?
Is it an awkward feeling
between old friends?
Or is it because I still love you?
I'm happy to hear that.
At least I still have a chance
to get back into your life.
Give me some time.
I'll let you know
as soon as I get the answer.
You can let me know
when you're ready.
All I want is the truth.
Whatever your answer is,
I can take it.
But please know this.
I still love you.
Rut, how can I help you?
I have work for you.
Work?
That's my game!
Your game is very interesting.
I've studied the market.
The young female demographic
has interesting purchasing power.
I think if you develop this game
and release it,
we're going to get a new market
for the company.
But if you don't want to work on it,
I can throw this in the bin.
No, I will work on it.
I want to work on it.
However, if you don't
finish it by the deadline,
I will throw it in the bin.
I will make sure
to finish it by the deadline.
I will do my best.
We'll see.
I made your favorite shrimp
rice porridge with extra garlic.
Let me feed you.
I'll get the door.
Hey, guys. Mook asked me to keep
an eye on you until she comes back.
She worries that you may develop
a fever, so she asked me to be here.
I will take care of my friend's
husband as though he is my own.
I will protect you at all costs.
Not even a fly can touch you.
Were you having a meal?
Yes, we were.
I'll take it from here.
Lan, have a seat.
No, I can feed myself.
Ouch!
Please.
Why didn't anyone tell me that
my son was attacked?
He asked us not to tell you.
But I think you should know.
This wasn't the first time
he was attacked.
He was being shot at
when I met him in Korea.
I bumped into him and saved him.
I didn't know you were at the scene.
Rut and Lan told me
he got the wrong guy.
It was the right guy.
After that incident, Lan got into
many troubling situations,
and I was always there.
Mook, thank you for saving him.
I'm not sure
I can save him every time.
I'm certain that
someone is trying to hurt him.
I think we have to find
the person behind this whole thing.
Do you have a conflict with anybody?
It could be my competitor.
But it isn't a feud.
Do you think I'm the cause of this?
I don't know.
I'm trying to figure out who would
benefit the most from this.
But I can't think of anyone.
I'll look into it.
For now,
you and Lan have to be very careful.
Let me know immediately
if something happens.
I will.
By the way,
could you keep this a secret?
I don't want to fight with him.
Sure.
I need your help
with one more thing.
What is it?
Make him accept the position
as vice president.
Danai.
I've been looking for you.
What do you want with me?
Win?
This is why I need to
talk to you in private.
I don't want the others
to hear about this.
I don't know why Rawin was there.
On the bright side,
he might have a friend there.
On the dark side,
he could be the attacker.
What would be his reason
for harming Lan?
What would he gain from this?
I'm looking into it.
I don't know what his motive is.
Also, I have a suspicion
that the incident at the factory
could be his doing.
I won't believe he is the culprit
until I have proof.
Me too.
I just want you and Lan
to be careful
and help me.
Help you with what?
Help me keep an eye on Rawin
to see if he is guilty.
You work with him.
You should be able to
get close to him.
And let me know
if you find anything.
We have to work together
for Lan's safety.
Are you okay with that?
Okay.
Oh, Mook.
I thought you took a day off.
I came to discuss something
with the president
and visit you.
Visit me? Is there something wrong?
I came here in case you had
an update on the project.
Oh, I was about to
send you an email.
The client wants to
change the design.
Then shall we discuss it right away?
Absolutely.
I think we should try this.
If we want to add roundness
to the middle,
we may have to increase
the angle of the main wall.
Um...
What's wrong?
I just noticed that
you're ambidextrous.
I thought you were left-handed.
Oh, I can use both hands
equally well.
I broke my left arm,
and it was in a cast for months.
I had to train my right hand.
After it healed,
I could use both hands.
Is that strange to you?
It just surprised me.
There's a lot about me
that will surprise you.
How are you?
Let me check your temperature.
Here.
Ouch!
Hey!
That's enough.
This is not enough for people who
try to take someone else's husband.
Enough.
Nuch.
I think you should leave.
If you stay,
my fever will come back.
Hey!
Are you calling me to say thank you?
I'm calling you to yell at you.
You asked Nuch to come here
and meet Duckling on purpose.
It's for your own sake.
I saw that you were sick,
so I asked Nuch to take care of you.
You should thank me instead
for giving you the opportunity
to get close to her.
So you can finally realize
that you still love her.
I owe you nothing.
You also benefit from this.
You allowed a stranger like her
into your house,
sacrificing your privacy.
This must be worth it.
Let's say we both benefit from this.
You and Nuch get to work things out.
And I get to pursue Mook
the way I want to.
That's a win-win situation for us.
I'll call you back.
What?
We heard everything.
Why didn't you knock
before you came in?
You told Treenuch to go to
your house, didn't you?
I asked you a question.
We knocked, but you didn't hear us.
I also asked you a question.
Answer me.
That's right. It's my house.
Anyone with my permission can enter.
You use people to create
opportunities for yourself.
That's right.
I believe it now that
you always get what you want.
You don't care how you get it
or if it's right or wrong.
What about this opportunity
you gave me to develop the game?
Do you actually care about it,
or are you just using it
to get on my good side?
You want me on your team,
so I'll help you with my sister.
Believe whatever you will.
If I was given the opportunity
because of Mook, I don't want it.
Hold on, Petch.
I won't let you become the bad guy.
I will do everything to make sure
you don't get together with her.
I don't want to have a sly man
like you as my brother-in-law.
Petch.
Come on, Boss.
She misunderstood everything.
Why didn't you tell her
that her game is incredible?
Leave her be.
If she thinks her work is worthless,
I will think it's worthless too.
I'm sorry for doing this.
I don't want you to be created
by someone's selfishness.
Lan.
Rawin was at the condo
while you were attacked.
From what I know,
he is Lak's friend from college.
He has a degree in interior design,
so she asked him to work for us.
He could have followed me
because he was worried about her.
I see.
Unrequited love.
I guess so.
I don't know what he would gain
from hurting me.
He might've been in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
Alright.
You evil, sly jerk.
You immoral, useless man.
Let's say we both benefit from this.
You and Nuch get to work things out.
And I get to pursue Mook
the way I want to.
That's a win-win situation for us.
I will make sure you don't succeed.
You will learn about failure.
You can't beat righteousness.
(The Next Vice President
Of A Major Furniture Manufacturer)
(Sorry, girls. Chalantorn is taken.
His bride is DJ Prao.)
Duckling.
- Hey.
- You did it, didn't you?
What are you doing? Let go.
Answer me. Did you do this?
(Sorry, girls. Chalantorn is taken.)
That's our wedding photo.
You leaked the news, didn't you?
Answer me.
I didn't do it.
Let go. You're hurting me.
- Ow!
- You did it.
You want people to know that
you're my wife, that I'm taken,
to stop me from seeing Nuch.
You're worse than I thought.
I didn't do it. What do I have to do
to make you believe me?
I know nothing. I have no idea
how they got the photo.
Instead of yelling at me,
why don't you look for the truth?
I'm doing that right now,
getting the truth out of you.
Tell me that you did it.
You want me.
You want my father's money so much
you don't care how you get it.
You're capable of this.
I didn't do it.
Let go. You're hurting me.
- Lan!
- I won't let go until you admit it.
- Lan.
- Let go.
Let go of her.
You can talk about this.
No way.
She ruined my relationship before.
Why can't she do it again?
I've had enough.
I won't take it anymore.
- Answer me.
- I didn't do it.
- Lan.
- Ow, Lan.
If you don't stop
this senseless behavior,
I won't let you talk to her.
Do you let a woman
come before your friend?
I do.
If my friend is crazy,
I have to take her side.
Get lost.
Rut!
You're too hotheaded.
Calm yourself down,
then we will talk.
Mook,
please come with me.
I figured out who leaked
the news about their wedding.
Who is it?
I will end this madness.
From now on, I will be the hunter.
Think who could be at a disadvantage
and have a lot to lose
from your return.
My sister.
Lan!
Dear!
I want to know
what he planned to do about work.
I need you to find out.
I will free you from Praomook.
On one condition.
How much can you trust Treenuch?
Those who seem friendly
could be worse than you think.