(Praomook)
I don't think it's a robbery.
I think it's a cover-up.
Win?
Rawin could be the attacker.
I will do everything to make sure
you don't get together with her.
I don't want to have a sly man
like you as my brother-in-law.
Did you do this?
Did you leak the news?
I didn't do it.
- Lan.
- Ow, Lan.
Do you let a woman
come before your friend?
If my friend is crazy,
I have to take her side.
Get lost.
Rut!
I believe you didn't leak the news.
Why do you believe people easily?
You aren't stupid.
You wouldn't leak the news
and ruin your reputation.
What?
You're a DJ. You have a lot of fans.
You wouldn't leak the news
to make yourself look bad.
I'm glad you believe me.
Unlike the man I grew up with,
he didn't even listen to me.
He is close-minded with you,
while I'm open-minded.
Excuse me. I should go.
Mook didn't leak the news.
You're mad at the wrong person.
Mook, I made breakfast for you.
Thank you.
Lan, have breakfast with us.
Wait, Lan.
Let's eat.
Don't mind him.
(Future Vice President Of Furniture
Manufacturer, Chalantorn, Is Taken)
They look perfect together.
Being on the news
is actually a good thing.
Now people will know
that they're married.
Hm?
It may be good,
- but...
- Dad, you broke our agreement.
What did I do?
You leaked the news
about my marriage.
No way, I didn't leak the news.
I was wondering what backlash
Mook could be facing right now.
Don't you worry about me?
Why should I?
You aren't affected by this.
Now that I think about it,
people knowing you're married
might be a good thing.
Now you will behave
and won't try to see another woman,
especially your ex.
From now on, you will consider
your situation before you act.
What situation?
Do you mean as your son
or the vice president position
that I never asked for?
- Are you challenging me?
- Yes, I'm challenging you.
Enough, both of you.
- I didn't start it.
- Right, I started it.
Stop.
Lan, your dad said
he didn't leak the news.
So stop being angry at him.
About your work,
you're in charge of a project now.
So get it done.
I didn't teach you to be
irresponsible. Do your duty.
- Now, you.
- What?
Stop ordering your son around.
Be nice to him. Can you do that?
But he started...
Are you arguing with me?
Absolutely not.
- Are we clear?
- Crystal clear.
- Sit down.
- Yes, ma'am.
Lan, have breakfast with us.
- Ja, could you get a bowl for him?
- Of course.
Here is your breakfast.
For you, Lan.
Did your mother follow us?
Not yet.
Alright.
You have to come to work
with me today.
We made a deal, didn't we?
Once you're married for a year,
I will leave you alone.
But before that,
I can do whatever I want with you.
If you think I'm so irresponsible,
why did you assign me a big project?
Aren't you scared I will ruin it?
I am scared.
But if it can make you grow up
and become more responsible,
I'm willing to risk it.
You have to come to work with me.
- I will...
- What are you guys talking about?
Nothing, dear.
I just asked him
if he wants to come to work.
- That's good.
- Sure.
- Lan, talking like adults is good.
- Right.
I wonder why you two
always act like children.
- Dear.
- Hm?
It's time to go.
Lan, it's time to go to work.
Go.
Okay. Bye, Mom.
See you later, dear.
Alright?
Do you think this can stop me?
(Sorry, girls. Chalantorn is taken.)
I refuse to lose to you, Praomook.
Pity. If I were there, I'd help you
kick him into the pool three times.
Always irrational,
what kind of man is he?
I lose my mind
whenever I'm around him.
Listen, just give Rut a chance.
He is handsome, cool, smart,
and more importantly,
he has feelings for you.
Stop trying to encourage me.
Why? Does he make you feel things?
He doesn't make me feel things.
Besides, now isn't the time
to encourage me to fall in love.
We have a bigger problem
ahead of us.
I really want to know
who leaked the news.
Could it have been Lim?
Uncle is a man of his word.
I think it was someone else.
Find the person who leaked the news
about their marriage ASAP.
Alright.
The photo is very high quality.
I think it's from one of the guests.
I won't let you become the bad guy.
I will do everything to make sure
you don't get together with her.
I don't want to have a sly man
like you as my brother-in-law.
I want it as soon as possible.
Of course. I will find them
as soon as possible.
Good morning, vice president's wife.
Good morning, Treenuch.
News spreads fast as usual.
Do you think announcing your status
will make him yours?
It's up to Lan to decide.
Others have no say in this.
Right, an outsider like you
has no say in this.
It's between husband and wife.
You should mind your manners.
You don't want to be condemned
for trying to take my husband.
A mistress is always guilty.
Mook.
Good morning.
I've been looking for you.
Is there something wrong?
I'm concerned about the news.
Come on. Let's talk in my office.
Sure.
Lan.
Come with me.
She wants people to know who she is.
She wants to be important.
Next she will take everything
from my family.
Take it easy.
She has always kept
a low profile at work.
Keeping a low profile
doesn't mean she isn't greedy.
I have to get rid of her.
Your parents adore her.
You have to be very careful
with what you do.
I'm their daughter.
Blood is thicker than water.
You have to make her
reveal her true colors.
How will I do that?
She hasn't given me a chance.
Just buy her with money.
I have no idea how it got leaked.
However, from now on,
I want you two to act properly.
I will act the same way as always.
Are you done?
Lan.
You have to do
your duty as a husband.
She deserves that
after what she has done for you.
Since she came back into my life,
it's only been chaos.
It's you who created all the chaos.
Am I supposed to be
in debt to her forever?
I don't want anything from you.
Are you saying
you're a good, selfless person?
Come on, Lan.
Will you stop being sarcastic?
And you don't have to
make yourself feel grateful to her.
Just act properly
as a good husband should.
I don't want to.
Besides, I'm sick of this madness.
I consider marrying this woman
a terrible misfortune.
- Lan!
- I don't need anyone to help me.
Do whatever you want.
My only job is to be
your wife for a year.
I don't care what happens
to you after that.
Excuse me.
I should get back to work.
What?
Come on. This is a mess.
A total mess.
Practice what you preach.
I will.
I told you to stay away from him.
Didn't you understand me?
I did. I just didn't want to
listen to you.
Don't test me.
I'm not testing you.
I want him.
How dare you say you want
another man in front of your lover?
Calm down.
I have a proposal.
I'm going to make Lan mine
and you're going to
make Mook your mistress,
forcing them to get a divorce.
Let's work together.
I can handle Praomook
without having to rely on anyone.
I haven't finished.
If I have Lan,
I will keep us a secret,
and you will have her
and the benefit of their divorce,
and continue to be
Lak's loving husband.
What if I don't agree to this?
Then I can't promise
this won't reach Lak's ears.
If Lak finds out about us,
I will ruin your life.
Why don't we find out
whose life will be ruined first?
If we work together,
it's a win-win for both of us.
Just say yes.
Yes.
I have to find out who you are
and end this madness.
What did you find?
I figured out
who leaked the news of the wedding.
Go on.
Promise me you will stay calm
and be rational.
Who is it?
The person who leaked the news is...
You leaked the news
about your sister's wedding.
You're accusing me.
Do you have proof?
I wouldn't say it without proof.
You know what Poom and I
are capable of.
It's not hard to discover
the identity of an online source.
I will give you a chance.
Will you admit it,
or do I have to get it out of you?
- Well...
- If you choose the latter,
besides getting caught,
you will be forced out of my life
because I don't like cowards.
Alright, I did it.
Why did you do it?
To stop you
from doing immoral things
and going after a married woman.
I warned you but you didn't listen.
Now I will let society stop you,
so you can get a hold of yourself.
I have a hold of myself.
My actions have been thought out.
I've done nothing wrong.
It's you who are being irrational.
I thought this through.
Have you thought about
how it affects your sister?
You want me to do the right thing,
but what you did isn't right.
If your good intentions
hurt Mook and Lan,
I don't want it.
Rut...
I'll give you some time to consider
if what I said is right.
One more thing.
Even though the news was leaked,
I won't stop.
I will win her heart.
Your childish plan
can't stop me.
Stupid rain, are you mocking me?
Poom, was I so wrong?
Yes.
I didn't think it'd be
such a big deal.
I'm sorry.
For what?
For
offending you
and leaking the news.
I accept your apology
for offending me.
However, for leaking the news,
you don't owe me an apology.
What you should do is to
admit to Lan and your sister
that you leaked the news.
- But I...
- I hope you aren't a coward.
I'm not a coward.
I always own up to my mistakes.
Well, I...
I leaked the news
about your wedding.
Did someone tell you to do it?
I did it on my own.
Mook wasn't involved.
I apologize for not asking
for your opinion first and
for the bad timing.
But I won't apologize
for leaking the news.
Nampetch.
You said I should
own up to what I did.
So I will say how I feel.
Whether it's on the news or not,
your wedding happened.
Lan.
Are you done?
Yes.
When we end the marriage,
please tell people about that too.
Hi, Mom.
You know
the reason for this marriage.
We all know how it will end.
Why can't you let it end quietly?
I'm sorry, Mom.
I'm sorry, Mook.
Saying sorry doesn't mean it's over.
What do you want me to do?
What you should do
is try to learn from this.
Think before you act
because you can't undo what you did.
This will be my lesson.
I'm going to go to my room.
Petch.
Mom, I'm really okay.
Now that it became public,
after this is over, you will be
the one who has the most to lose.
You also got hurt for helping Lan.
I don't know
if the prophecy is true.
But what scares me right now
is that you may get hurt worse.
It was just a coincidence.
What if it happens again?
I'm scared you will be in danger.
You don't have to do so much
for me and your sister.
If you can't do it,
if you aren't happy,
you can end it. I won't blame you.
What about this house?
Your father isn't with us anymore.
I don't know why
we should keep the house.
My children are the most
precious thing to me right now.
If you are unhappy,
I don't want you to go through it.
I agree. Why should you endure it?
Let's find another solution.
I can't let it go, Mom.
This house was Dad's.
He built it for us
to live comfortably.
As the eldest daughter,
I will never let go of this house.
I can keep going, Mom.
Alright.
If one day you can't keep going,
whatever your decision may be,
I'll always be there for you.
Thank you, Mom.
You don't have to worry.
Right now I can go through anything.
- Lan!
- Why?
Did you think I would push you?
Yes.
I wouldn't do that.
If I were to get back at you,
I'd rather kick you.
You can try.
Rut.
I've made my decision.
I'm going to end this madness.
What do you mean?
The whole thing isn't caused
by my misfortune.
He caused it.
The man who attacked me
and ruined my life.
That makes sense.
What will you do next?
I'm tired of being the prey.
From now on I will be the hunter.
Will you help me?
Absolutely.
From today,
I will stop playing everyone's game
and show them who's boss.
So,
you've gotten attacked since
you moved back home to Thailand.
This means your return
has an impact on the culprit.
Possibly.
At first, I suspected Duckling.
But if it was just
to create a situation,
she wouldn't almost kill me.
If you drop your prejudice,
you will realize that
she walked into you by accident.
I know.
You have to figure out
who could be at a disadvantage and
have a lot to lose from your return.
You don't know what you're doing,
but Dad thinks you do.
He tries to make you be in charge
when you're incapable.
Can you go back to living abroad?
My sister.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
I still haven't figured out
who has a lot to lose.
I think the man who attacked you
at your condo could be Rawin.
This is his background.
He comes from
a middle-class background.
He has known your sister
since university.
Is he her friend?
The person who'd benefit the most
if something were to happen is...
For now, let's just say
Win is our prime suspect.
We will make him reveal his
true colors as quickly as possible.
As for his motive,
I will discover that myself.
I need to look at something.
Poom.
You suspect his sister, don't you?
Yes.
I think he feels the same way.
If it were true,
what do you think he would do?
For now, let him
try to absorb the fact
that his sister
is our prime suspect.
You have to figure out
who could be at a disadvantage and
have a lot to lose from your return.
Please let it be anyone
but her.
Stop drinking already. You're drunk.
It's gone. Now go to bed.
What are you doing?
You're so nosy.
You said you don't care if I die.
It's not like I want to.
I just can't stand looking at you.
If you're stressed, go to bed
and figure it out when you wake up.
Don't drink like a fish.
Did you call me a fish?
I can do worse.
Do you want to try me?
No.
Go to bed.
I think you've had enough.
I'm not drunk.
See? I'm completely fine.
Lan!
I'm okay. Look at me.
Go to bed. I'll walk with you.
No.
I want to get drunk.
Get drunk and forget everything.
Do you know how much my life sucks?
It sucks so much I wish
I'd fall asleep and never wake up.
- You can't think like that.
- Yes, I can.
Why can't I?
My life is funny, don't you think?
I was attacked by somebody
I don't even know.
Besides getting hurt,
I was forced to marry you as well.
I was forced
to do a job I don't like.
My father controls
everything in my life.
He wants me to work for him,
but my sister doesn't.
She even thinks I'm going to take
everything from her.
This one wants one thing.
The other wants something else.
What do I have to do
to please everyone?
Lan.
It's pitiful to be me.
No one cares how I feel.
They act like I feel nothing,
like I'm heartless.
But I feel it all.
I feel angry.
I feel sad.
I care how you feel.
That's not true.
You're selfish. You want to beat me.
That's right.
I don't know
if I should or shouldn't love you.
I know that my parents
used the prophecy as an excuse.
They've wanted to
set us up for a long time now.
I can't love you.
If I love you,
then my parents get their way.
But to hate you,
I can't bring myself to do that.
What about you? How do you feel?
You don't have to care how I feel.
Answer me.
If you don't answer me,
I will make you.
Lan, you're so drunk that
you don't know what you're doing.
Let me get you to bed.
No.
Answer me first.
If you don't, I will kiss you.
Lan, hey.
Lan, don't do this.
Lan!
Lan, let go.
Enough. I'll get you to bed.
Rut, you interrupted us.
Mook, go to bed.
I'll take care of him.
Hold on. She hasn't answered me yet.
Lan, that's enough.
I came to see Mook.
I also brought breakfast.
I came to see
everyone.
Sorry.
Here. Wear this
so you don't spread the virus.
I'm fine. I just sneezed.
Wear it.
If you don't wear it, go home.
Come here.
Ow! Rut, that hurt.
Worry about yourself
before you worry about other people.
Grouchy old man.
I heard that.
Lan is out.
He left early this morning.
Where did he go?
He can go wherever he wants.
I don't care.
Here you go.
I'm thirsty. My throat hurts.
I don't think it's a love triangle.
It's a quadrangle.
Win, it's me.
Oh, Lan.
I'm sorry. I was startled.
It's fine.
It's my fault for startling you.
If it weren't me,
you'd finish the job, right?
You're exaggerating.
Anyway, how can I help you?
I want to talk to you
about our project.
Okay.
I'm still inexperienced.
I will need your advice.
I hope we can work well together.
Of course. I will do my best.
This project will prove to
the board and everyone
that you deserve
to be vice president.
Is it him?
Make it quick.
I'm in the middle of something.
I'll do the project I got assigned.
After that, I will quit.
You're still stubborn.
Is that all you want to say?
I've got work to do.
I don't want to be the heir.
I don't want to replace you.
I will build everything on my own.
Anybody can say that.
I'm serious.
I hope you can do as you say.
Lan.
Nuch.
What's wrong? You look troubled.
I'm a little worried about work.
If you're troubled,
we can go somewhere quiet and talk.
I want to discuss
something with you.
But if you're not okay with that,
we can go to your office instead.
I'm fine with it.
Let's go somewhere else.
I'm tired of this place.
Okay.
Lan!
What's gotten into you?
That man on a bike
tried to shoot you.
I'm at the front of the building.
I guess I imagined it.
Are you so desperate to stop us
that you have to lie like that?
Don't you think that's too much?
What if you scare someone to death?
I wasn't lying.
Forget it.
What's up with you?
I don't care what you do with him.
Please give me another chance
to develop the game.
If I don't say yes,
I will lose my chance to see
your exciting game.
I will give you one last chance.
Thank you.
I promise I will do my best.
Now get back to work.
There's one more thing.
We will keep our professional
and personal lives separate.
If you're upset with me,
don't take it out on my work.
Do we have a deal?
- Deal.
Poom, Rut let me
work on my game again.
Awesome.
I said exactly what you told me.
It's clear and to the point.
As expected from his favorite
secretary, you really know him.
Of course, I know everything.
- Good job.
- Sure.
Do you know
what I have in mind right now?
What is it, Boss?
I want a new secretary.
The old one knows too much.
Petch, come on,
let's get back to work.
Right, let's get back to work.
- Petch.
- Hm?
You have a temperature.
A little. I should be fine after
taking some medicine. Don't worry.
Let's go.
Let's get back to work
before a storm blows up.
- Come on.
- Alright.
Nuch is going to do
media planning for us.
It's a pleasure to work with you.
Of course.
Lan told me about your work.
I will be very efficient
with media planning.
I believe he will choose
what's best for us.
Shall we begin?
Sure.
Even the news can't stop them.
(Come to Rut's office right now.
Treenuch is with Lan here.)
(Mook)
Mook, I feel sick.
Can you pick me up?
This is our media usage and budget
that I've planned.
I'll leave you two to discuss it.
I have to check with
the graphic team.
Hm?
Come on, Poom. Everyone is waiting.
- I'll leave it to you, Nuch.
- Of course.
Let's look at our plan.
Boss, do you have an appointment?
Did I miss something?
I see. An imaginary appointment.
I'm at the glass stairs.
Where are you?
Wait right there. I'll walk to you.
Okay.
Mook, I have a headache.
Did you take any medicine yet?
I haven't requested sick leave yet.
Follow me.
I'm glad you trust me
with your important project.
You're perfect for the job.
Just the job?
Can it be more?
If it can, what will you do?
I will free you from Praomook.
On one condition.
Come with me.
If you want your life back,
don't mind her.
That way, you will be able
to move forward.
I'm really okay.
If you aren't okay,
you don't have to force yourself.
Boss.
I feel much better.
Alright.
Here you are.
I've been looking for you.
Hi, Mook.
Let's go home, Mook.
See you later.
See you.
(Lak)
I'll be right back.
Hello, Lak.
I want to know what Lan
has planned for the project.
I need you to find out.
Why do you want to know?
Do I need a reason
to inquire about my brother?
You're right,
but I've got nothing for you.
If you find out anything,
let me know immediately.
Sure.
Look into Treenuch right away.
Yes, Boss.
How much can you trust Treenuch?
Fifty percent.
I don't think you should trust her.
If we work together,
it's a win-win for both of us.
Just say yes.
Yes.
You never know
what people actually think.
Those who seem friendly
could be worse than you think.
I know what to do.
Don't worry.
What would you like me to do?
Should I tell Lak?
This isn't enough to incriminate
Rawin for fraud.
Watch him and wait for my order.
Of course.
Why didn't you do anything
when you saw them together?
What do you want me to do?
Yell at them
and say that he is mine?
Anything but
surrender to that woman.
It's your right.
Chasing after someone
who will never love you back
is painful and tiring.
Thank you for helping me
see the two of them together.
It may be time to make my decision.
Hey, you're back.
What are you talking about?
It looks fun.
Are you okay?
I'm still okay.
You two have matured.
Back then, you were happy
every time you saw him.
Was I?
You even counted the days.
Are you still happy
when you're with him?
Whatever reason you have
for marrying him,
I respect your decision.
But don't neglect
your own happiness.
If living in this house
means sacrificing your happiness,
I'd rather lose it.
When it's time to make a decision,
you can let yourself come first.
What do you want to talk about?
It's about our agreement.
Well,
I want your advice.
If I end it...
(Lan)
What were you saying?
Well, I...
Dear, come here quickly.
Dear.
Dear, what's wrong?
It's Lan.
He's launched his own company.
My son looks so smart.
Much is an application
where goods from all over the world
are gathered in your hand.
Much is a platform designed
to cover every continent.
A real-time marketplace
is our highlight.
Buyers and sellers can
communicate directly.
We also offer translation service.
With a single tap,
you can communicate
without boundaries.
No matter
where you are in the world,
download Much and you will be
able to shop online 24/7.
We provide worldwide shipping
using the concepts of
distance, speed, and safety.
So you may rest assured
that wherever you are in the world,
you can order products
from a different country
to your own country
swiftly and safely.
Dear, it has everything.
Mook, did you know about this?
No, I didn't.
Is LS Design partnered with L&R?
This company was found by me
and Marut, CEO of Mars Wiz.
What about your position
as vice president at LS Design?
I've decided to step down
from that position.
However, if LS Design would like to
enter the e-commerce market,
my company is ready to
provide assistance.
Dear, take it easy.
Don't be mad at him.
You need to keep
your blood pressure down.
Congratulations.
Here.
Are you ready for the consequences?
I'm ready.
Hey, Dad.
Come home right now.
Lan,
let me go with you.
I want to handle it on my own.
If I can't deal with this,
how will I deal with
something bigger?
Have you gone crazy?
Why did you announce
that you're quitting?
Have you thought about
the consequences of your actions?
I chose the best option
for everybody.
The best option for you.
You only care about yourself.
Have you considered
how people around you may feel?
I'm selfish like you.
We're different.
I do what I do for my family,
for the company,
and for your future.
Have you ever asked me
if I want that future?
I don't want it.
That's why you do crazy things
to spite me.
Do you think you're so clever?
You must feel amazing.
You have your own company.
You're arrogant.
You think I'm childish.
You keep controlling my life
and arranging everything for me.
You think I'm stupid.
You know, we always fight
when we're around each other.
I feel unhappy when I'm with you.
You may be successful in life.
But to me,
you're a bad father.
Lan!
Dear!
Get out!
Get out of my house!
Go!
Lan.
Dear,
am I a bad father?
I'm a bad father, right?
What you did today
affects the company's credibility.
I know.
But I chose what's best for us.
Are you saying I caused this?
I'm the cause of this whole thing.
Without me,
everything would be easier.
That's shallow and childish of you.
I can deal with all the trouble.
If you want to prove yourself,
then keep your promise.
If you can't do that,
it will all just be a childish joke.
I don't joke around with my life,
but everyone is joking around
with mine.
Lak, wasn't that too harsh?
It was too soft.
Lan.
You said you don't care.
So try to be consistent.
Don't follow me.
I don't want your sympathy.
I think if he went this far,
you should let him do what he wants.
Danai and I will handle the press.
As for his position, you should
find a better replacement.
I agree with her.
Lan hasn't handed me
his resignation letter.
He will remain
in the position for now.
I will do everything I can
to get him back.
Why do you still insist on
giving him the position
when you have Danai and me?
Just do as he says.
You may be successful in life.
But to me,
you're a bad father.
Lan!
Dear!
If you want to prove yourself,
then keep your promise.
If you can't do that,
it will all just be a childish joke.
Why did you follow me?
I didn't. I was just passing by.
I want to be alone.
You did your best.
Good job, Chalantorn.
You're annoying.
You said you wouldn't
care about me anymore.
Thanks, anyway,
for being here.
Look.
What proof do you have
that my sister is behind everything?
that your sister didn't do it?
Nothing.
Then your sister and Rawin
are the suspects.
Lak, please stop.
I'm as calm as I can be.
If he wants everything,
he can have it.
- He can have it.
- Hey, Lak.
If you want everything back,
I will help you.
Someone made a threat against you.
I can't believe
it's actually what I thought.