(Praomook)
(Previous Episode)
Mook, what's wrong?
Dad went into cardiac arrest.
Goodbye, Dad.
This is where we part.
Start your journey before me.
And one day I will follow you.
During this time,
you should be by her side,
consoling her, reassuring her.
It's not my place.
You're her husband.
A husband who doesn't love her.
So I don't have a duty to fulfill.
It's actually a good thing
that you're mean to her.
The more you hate her,
the greater chance I have
of making her fall in love with me.
I will begin my own game.
And I'm sure that in this game
I will be the winner.
You keep haunting me
even when you're not here.
- Hey, Mom.
- Lan.
Where are you and
what are you doing?
Is Mook with you?
I'm at Rut's house
and I'm about to go to bed.
Mook isn't with me.
If you're asking me
to go see her, I won't go.
But...
It's okay if you don't want to go.
I'm not saying anything.
Besides, I don't want to
disturb your precious bedtime.
It's actually a good thing
to only care about yourself.
Are you sure that's not an insult?
It's absolutely not an insult.
I just worry about her.
She might seem fine in front of us.
But she could be crying
when we're not around.
So I can't help but worry about her.
Look. I know you're trying
to make me feel sorry for her.
I'm not doing that.
I just think that
if she has you by her side,
I would be less worried.
I wouldn't be of any help.
You don't have to do anything.
Just stay by her side
and console her.
Being partners in life means
when one falls,
the other is there to pick them up.
- But Mook and I aren't...
- In your case,
though you're not partners in life,
you two are childhood friends
who have been there for each other
and grew up together.
I know it doesn't really matter.
Besides, I believe
Mook can handle her emotions.
She can rely on herself
to cope with sadness.
In fact, you don't have to
be concerned about her.
I guess that's all I want to say.
It's late. Let's go to bed.
Good night. I love you.
Dear, we haven't...
Mom?
- Take your hand off.
- What is it?
I can't speak
when you cover my mouth.
Dear, why didn't you just
tell him to go see her?
We already told him that at
the hospital, and did he listen?
No, he didn't.
Then why should we
keep pestering him to do it?
Don't you know your son?
The more he is pressured,
the more he resists.
That's why I believe hearing that
will make him worry about her.
I've raised him after all.
How did I get here?
Hey!
Well, are you here for Mook?
No. I'm just passing by.
I see. So, you're leaving.
Good night.
Wait.
What is it?
My mother asked me
to see how Mook is doing.
So I thought I should stop by
on my way home.
So you're not really
concerned about her.
No.
She is doing alright.
She's just locking herself in her
room and hasn't eaten anything.
I also heard the sound of
someone crying uncontrollably.
She must have no tears left to cry.
Do you call that doing alright?
Right, I'm worried that
she'll be overcome with grief.
She was close with her dad.
You aren't worried though.
You can head home. It's late.
Let's see if he still feels nothing
after hearing that.
He really feels nothing.
Mook,
eat something. You haven't
eaten since this morning.
You don't want to fall ill.
I'm not hungry.
Please try.
Mook!
Mook, what's wrong?
Easy.
Lan.
When did he get here?
Oak, let's go.
Go where?
Her husband is taking care of her.
Let's not be third wheels here.
- But...
- No buts.
Come on. Let's go.
Come on, Oak.
Stay away from me.
You can't even stand upright.
Don't be arrogant.
I don't want you to see me
in this state.
I've seen worse.
This is nothing.
No, I can walk on my own.
Don't be stubborn.
Just let me help.
I don't want to take you to
the doctor when you fall.
Your body is weak because
you haven't eaten anything.
I'm not hungry.
You have to eat either way.
You just puked your guts out.
If you don't eat,
I will force it down your throat.
Now, eat.
I can feed myself.
Do you like to be forced?
Here.
For your eyes.
They are horribly swollen.
Ow, hey!
You're exactly the same.
My baby.
My poor baby.
If your next life isn't good to you,
please be born as my baby again.
My poor baby.
It's just a guppy.
Do you have to be this sad?
Stop crying already.
My baby.
Puffy-eyed duckling.
- A cold compress for your eyes.
- Ow.
- No.
- You need it.
Stay still.
If you don't apply a cold compress,
you'll look disgusting.
Why are you here?
My mother told me to check on you.
Since when did you start listening
to your mother?
Normally you are more defiant.
I've always listened to my mother.
If I don't listen, she'll scold me
until my next life.
Mothers are capable of that.
Now that you've done what
she asked of you, you can leave.
Are you kicking me out?
Yes. I have no energy left
to fight you.
If you don't start it,
I won't get into a fight with you.
What are you doing?
Thank you for checking on me.
For making me feel less alone.
Many people are here for you.
You aren't alone.
I'd rather have you by my side.
You should go.
What's wrong with you? Asking me
to stay then kicking me out.
I don't want to force you today.
You can do whatever you want.
I will stay here tonight.
Lan.
It's very late.
I don't want to drive home.
I'm going to bed.
Mook, I can't sleep.
Can I stay with you?
Lan, how did you get here?
No, you can't stay the night here.
You have to think of Rut.
I told him I'd stay the night here.
- So this bed is mine, okay?
- No.
I want to stay with her.
You go somewhere else.
- No.
- I want to sleep here.
- Stop yelling.
You want to sleep beside me,
don't you?
Then sleep on the bed.
Lan, you can choose
between the sofa and the floor.
Hold on. I'm your husband.
This is the best solution.
Let's go to sleep.
I'm so sleepy.
Petch!
Hey!
Mook, let's switch places.
Enough, Petch. Go to sleep.
Well,
we have a guest.
Auntie, good morning.
I'm going out. Want to join me?
No.
I will spend the night
somewhere else.
Go ahead.
I didn't think you would stay here.
I made myself clear about
what I'm going to do with Mook.
But you're far from clear.
I did make myself clear.
If you want to pursue her,
that's fine with me.
I will give you another chance.
Let me know if you change
your mind about Mook.
Our rule is
don't love the same girl.
If you like her, you can tell me.
I stand by what I've said.
I will never love Praomook.
Good.
I don't want to stab someone
in the back.
And I don't like being
stabbed in the back either.
I will never betray my friends.
I will remember that.
(Treenuch is calling)
Nuch, do you need anything?
I'm just wondering
if I came to the right place.
Nuch.
Hey, Lan.
How did you get here?
Alright.
Let's see who will last longer.
(Have a good day.)
(Rest in peace, Dad.)
Lak, do you know about
Mook's father's funeral?
I'd like to offer my friend
my condolences.
I saw it on Mook's post and searched
where the funeral would be held.
I'd like to offer my condolences.
We are friends after all.
Could you take me to her?
Sure.
Nuch, are you okay?
I don't know.
Ah, my ankle.
- Let's find you a seat.
- Okay.
Careful.
Da.
Thank you, Pat, Lim, and Lak
for coming here to send him off.
It's not a problem.
If you need anything,
don't hesitate to let us know.
We would be glad to help you.
What are you looking for?
Is there something wrong?
We're leaving. Could you fetch Lan?
I saw him heading that way.
Okay.
Lan.
Why didn't you answer
any of my calls?
Did I do anything wrong?
If I did something
that offended you, I apologize.
I apologize for everything.
No, it's nothing. I was just busy.
Let me see your ankle.
Does it hurt?
Ow.
Yes.
But I think it should be fine
after a little rest.
Are you sure?
I'm really okay.
I'm happy to see that
you worry about me.
This reminds me of the old days
when you used to take care of me.
Good job, pup.
Mook.
I was about to go find you.
I'm sorry about your loss.
Thanks for coming.
Would you like to send
my father off? I can take you there.
- Ah!
- Nuch, are you alright?
Careful.
I'm alright.
She probably didn't know
I hurt my ankle.
You can't be too sure.
She doesn't care about
people's feelings after all.
It could've been her intention.
It wasn't my intention.
Like I would believe you.
Lan, you're overreacting.
She didn't do anything.
I'm telling the truth.
You will soon realize that you
should stay away from this woman.
I will use my own judgment on that.
I don't have to be told.
It's fine, Rut.
In his eyes, I've never been good.
Excuse me.
I need to rest for a minute.
Go ahead.
You can ask Lan to take you there
when you're ready.
Thank you for your condolences.
I'll leave you two alone.
You told Treenuch to
come here, didn't you?
She wanted to come here.
I just answered her question.
I don't agree with your attempt
to sabotage their relationship.
I haven't done anything.
They started the fight themselves.
I'm just pushing her
to get a divorce early.
I'm trying to help my brother here.
I know you, Lak.
If it doesn't benefit you,
you won't care.
If you know me,
you'd know not to get in my way
when I start doing something.
And you will help me.
- But...
- Danai.
Don't forget.
You got to where you are today
because of me.
So you should pay me back.
Just tell me what you need me to do.
I know you can do it.
I feel better now.
I will walk you to your car.
Okay.
Lan, I'm really okay.
It's fine.
This place is peaceful.
Where is your brother?
- Dear.
- Hm?
There he is.
Does he have to carry her?
Is your friend okay?
Why does she have to be carried?
She fell and hurt her ankle.
I carried her here
so I can take her to her car later.
I see.
Excuse me.
Where does it hurt?
Ow.
- Lan, let me see her ankle.
- Lan, come here.
Wow. It's so swollen.
Shall I take you to a doctor?
I'm free today.
No.
I'm fine. I can go home
and take some medicine.
Are you sure you don't
want to see a doctor?
I'm sure.
- Oh.
- Hey.
Thank you for your concern.
See you later, Mook.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Thanks.
Mom, let's go home.
Please excuse us, Uncle, Auntie.
See you later.
Lan, I think you should follow Mook.
Your friend will be fine.
That's right. I can take care
of your friend for you. Alright?
Nuch, come on.
I'll walk you to the car.
Okay.
Dear, look at him.
- Dear.
- Hm?
What's wrong? You look stressed.
I'm stressed out.
Lan keeps causing me trouble
and it's driving me insane.
I got him a good wife
and he doesn't care.
You have to give them
some time to adjust.
Married couples make adjustments
throughout their entire marriage.
It's about taking
one step at a time.
It's not about
getting back at each other.
I'm telling you.
Life is unpredictable.
The only certainty is uncertainty.
We have to live each day
as if it were our last
because we may not have tomorrow.
Dear.
To tell you the truth,
I'm scared I'll end up like Pethai.
He wasn't prepared
to leave this world.
His kids aren't ready
to stand on their own two feet.
If it were me,
I wouldn't be able to rest in peace.
So, are you stressed because
you're worried about your kids?
That's right.
I think
it's time I make myself clear.
What are you planning to do?
We have a lot of memories
of this house.
I was shocked when I found out
we were going to lose it.
I tried everything to save it,
hoping that one day
when Dad woke up,
he would still have this house,
and we would start over.
But now that Dad is gone,
it makes me feel like
I can't lose this house.
This house represents him.
I will do everything I can
to take it back.
I will endure.
You mean with Lan.
Are you sure you can do it?
I'm sure.
Then I will give you
another thing to worry about.
What is it?
Next Friday night? Sure.
I'll let DJ Prao know.
I don't agree with your attempt
to sabotage their relationship.
I haven't done anything.
They started the fight themselves.
You can't make two people who
hate each other fall in love.
I'm just pushing her
to get a divorce early.
I'm trying to help my brother here.
I know you, Lak.
If it doesn't benefit you,
you won't care.
Besides Treenuch, you have to
be careful of Lak and Danai.
You have enemies on all sides.
Good. That sounds fun.
The more they want to get rid of me,
the more I want to stay.
I will persevere and make it
through this year.
It's quiet in here.
Cold and distant atmosphere,
like the house owner.
If you prefer a place
with loud noises, you can leave.
It's peaceful here.
I'll get the door.
Lan, you have a parcel.
What's in there?
Some documents from the factory.
I asked for them.
I need these documents
for the past seven years.
Send them to this address
as soon as possible.
What are you going to do with them?
I want to see the budgets
and how they have been allocated.
Okay.
Please keep this between us.
Of course, Chalantorn.
If you check the last five years,
you should find it.
I just want to read through it
in case I find something.
From what I previously found,
the profit stays the same while
product amount looks strange.
It could begin at the factory.
Like that time I read my dad's email
and told Lak about it.
Right, I remember that.
But how can you be sure
that these documents are authentic?
These are just for my reference.
Because I will have our hacker
search for the real ones.
You can trust my hacking skills.
I will find you the real data.
I can detect forgery.
It's never a secret
when you say it's a secret.
The culprit will hear
about my request for the documents.
There are no secrets in the world.
If there are people behind this,
the incident at the factory
wasn't an accident.
It's a possibility.
If you were attacked for this,
I think it's too risky.
Your life is in extreme danger.
You need to have a plan
before you do something.
Don't challenge them.
My plan is to put pressure on them,
making them reveal themselves,
and end this as soon as possible.
Good. If you win, you survive.
Your father's company is safe.
That's right. I must win.
- Ting, where is my mom?
- Oh.
Petch, why do you look like that?
You know why.
Oh, my poor girl.
You can be sad,
but there must be a limit.
I know.
Where is my mom anyway?
Right, Pat picked her up
this morning.
She said she would come back
in the evening.
Pat is a nice lady.
She doesn't want Da to get lonely,
so she hangs out with her every day.
You too, Petch.
You can't mope around all day.
It gives me a bad feeling.
Have you eaten? I made breakfast.
It's over there.
Petch.
Where did she go?
Where are you guys going?
I'm driving Mook to the house
of her husband's friend.
I don't want her husband to
forget that he has a wife.
See you later.
I'm going with you.
Why would you want to go with me?
I don't want to be alone.
I miss Dad.
I'll help you.
The figures don't match.
Hey, guys.
I was just thinking about you.
We've brought food for dinner.
That's great.
I was wondering what's for dinner.
Where are Lan and Rut?
They're working.
Here. Let me help you.
Oak, you can let go.
I'll get this.
Come in.
Poom, where is Rut?
He is with Lan.
Are we disturbing them? I feel bad.
Come on, Petch.
We've disturbed them several times.
It's too late for regrets now.
Well, they might want to
enjoy their time with each other.
I don't think they're enjoying it.
Why don't you check it out?
I will fetch them for you.
Let's see that one.
Who's here?
Mook and her team.
Her team.
Petch and Oak.
She shouldn't have come back.
This is annoying.
It's a good thing she's here.
Now I can take care of her 24/7.
Boss.
I have a question about
this investigation.
Should we let Mook know about this?
I mean, the documents are
scattered all over the room.
This should be kept from her.
The less she knows, the better.
Rut.
Mook.
Well, please don't mind me.
Make yourself at home.
My house is your house.
By the way, where is Lan?
He isn't hungry. We can eat first.
Enjoy the meal.
Thanks.
I'll be right back.
Why are you here?
I'm here to ask you
to join us for dinner.
Whether I eat or not
is my business, not yours.
Hey.
You've been avoiding me.
Do you think you can keep
running away?
Not seeing your face
makes my mind feel at ease.
But I want to see your face.
It gives me an appetite.
Come on. Let's go eat.
Can you stop bothering me?
Hey!
Lan.
I want to be near you.
Do you miss me?
If there are people behind this,
the incident at the factory
wasn't an accident.
Being near me is dangerous.
If you are out of my life,
you will be safe.
No, I don't miss you.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine. I'm a tough woman.
I'm thick-skinned. This is nothing.
Hey, just eat.
Don't worry about the others.
They'll eat when they feel like it.
Why don't you try this? It's good.
Oak, can you reach this?
Let me get it for you.
(Latest Dream Guy: The Next
Vice President At LS Design)
Oh no. Here it comes.
Do we follow him or keep eating?
I say we keep eating.
Lan.
What's all the ruckus?
There is a rumor about you
on the internet.
The latest dream guy
or LS Design's next vice president,
Chalantorn Anantanapat,
the only son of Limpichat,
is rumored to become
the company's vice president soon.
What will Lim's elder child,
Laknara, say about this?
You leaked the news, didn't you?
What news?
The news about
Lan becoming vice president.
Come on, Lak. It's just a rumor.
Don't pay attention to it.
I don't believe you. They wouldn't
write about a baseless rumor.
You leaked the story
to see how our partners
and the board would react.
Very smart.
You're right. I leaked the story.
You want him to be vice president.
What about me?
What will be my position?
For now you're in the same position.
But I'll find you a new one soon.
You're saying it like I'm unsuitable
to take over the company.
Lak,
you're raising your voice at me.
If you can't control your emotions,
get a grip on yourself first.
Danai, get her to calm down.
Alright.
Lak.
I think you should talk to him
when you're calmer.
No. I want to hear
his reasons right now.
Why do you refuse to
recognize my capability?
Lan does nothing and you're ready
to give him everything. It's unfair.
Lak.
I'm not handing over
the company to him.
You have the same
executive power I do.
You can run the company in my place.
Isn't that enough for you?
Listen.
The company doesn't belong to you.
It belongs to all of us.
I just want Lan to be
part of the company. That's all.
It's clear that he doesn't want to
work with us but you don't listen.
He was born lucky.
He's never had to struggle.
You're doing this because
I'm a woman, aren't you?
- That's not true.
- You're lying.
You don't care about me
because I'm a woman.
You never recognize my worth
no matter how hard I try.
Lak, why don't you believe me?
The way you are acting right now
has confirmed my expectations.
You're emotional and unreasonable.
You look down on yourself.
You don't listen to anyone.
If you keep acting like this,
it will be a long time until
I can accept you. Remember that.
Dad.
Danai.
Get her out of here.
Now!
Okay.
Lak, please come with me.
Dad.
- You have to listen to me.
- Come on, Lak.
- You can't do this to me.
- Just come with me, please.
Dear, what happened?
I could hear you from the gate.
Dear, it's Lak.
She yelled at me
for making Lan vice president.
I don't know what's wrong with her.
Dear, nothing's wrong with her.
She just wants to know
why you did that.
I told you to take it
one step at a time, didn't I?
You have to see things
from her perspective.
Has anyone ever seen things
from my perspective?
Has anyone done that?
I have.
I agree with you. I'm here for you.
Come on. Let's calm down.
Please.
It's just a rumor.
I don't think it's unfounded.
If I were to guess,
it's my father who leaked the news.
I won't waste my time complaining
because I won't accept the position.
But it's your father's company.
You should continue his work.
I didn't ask for your opinion.
I will give you my opinion anyway.
No matter how hard
you try to run away,
you will eventually do it
for your family.
This is my life. I can handle it.
I don't need help.
I will give you another chance.
Let me know if you change
your mind about Mook.
Our rule is
don't love the same girl.
I stand by what I've said.
I will never love Praomook.
Good.
I don't want to stab someone
in the back.
And I don't like being
stabbed in the back either.
There's one thing you can do for me.
Lak, calm down.
Shut up, Danai.
If you can't help me,
leave me alone.
- Can you be reasonable?
- I said shut up.
You're partly the reason
why it has come to this.
If you were more capable,
the vice president position
would be either mine or yours.
You're right. It's my fault.
You've done nothing wrong.
But Dad told you.
The company belongs to all of us.
It doesn't belong to one person.
Lan may be irresponsible,
but one day he will change.
I don't want to listen to you.
- Please.
- Get out.
I want to be alone.
- Come on. Calm down.
- Get out.
Get out, Danai, now.
Get out.
I will show you
how wrong you are, Dad.
Help me choose. Leave this house,
or I will leave myself.
From now on, if there's you,
there's no me.
I'm not going anywhere.
I go wherever you go.
No. You must choose.
I'm getting back together with Nuch.
And what she will be? Your mistress?
She isn't my mistress.
She is a woman I once loved.
No.
I might still love her.
Do you think
I will fall for your tricks?
I know you're using her to hurt me.
You're wrong. I don't feel a thing.
I've never felt a thing for you.
I've only been around you
in order to beat you.
So my answer is
I'm not going anywhere.
Then I'll go.
Lan,
where are you going?
Mind your own business.
Lan.
Lan, hold on.
I'm not letting you leave.
You can't control me.
This marriage
isn't a result of love.
It's full of hatred.
It's best for us to
stay away from each other.
I don't need you in my life.
I only need Nuch.
If you think mentioning her name
can hurt me,
or make me want a divorce,
you're mistaken.
I don't feel a thing.
I will be with you wherever you go
until our contract is up.
I don't need you.
I've realized now that my heart
never forgot about her.
Rut,
you told me to stop
running away from Nuch.
I've asked myself
and got my answer.
Nuch is important to me.
So you chose Treenuch.
That's right.
If I pursue Mook,
you will be fine with that, right?
- That's right.
- What?
What's going on?
Lan and Treenuch.
Rut is going to pursue my sister.
Did you two break up
and start liking women now?
The relationship between me and him
is a lie we created
to reject the marriage.
We're just friends.
We're men,
straight men.
From now on,
I will pursue you.
I'm a man of my word.
You can do whatever you want.
You have my permission.
Giving permission like that,
do you think you own me?
This is between me and Rut.
You have no say in this.
You're right.
I have my life. You have yours.
You have no say in who I hang out
or fall in love with.
No way. Rut,
you can't pursue my sister.
Lan, you can't see another woman.
It's wrong.
How is it wrong?
Although this is a mock marriage,
they registered their marriage.
They are husband and wife.
But they don't love each other.
Love isn't the point.
The point is if you pursue her
and she develops feelings for you,
you will become an adulterer by law.
An adulterer means
one who has an affair
with someone else's spouse.
- According to the Civil and...
- Enough.
An example of adultery is
touching someone else's spouse.
I think just touching her
is considered adultery.
Or sleeping with them,
either in a public or private place,
is considered adultery by law.
A mistress is
a woman who has an affair
with a married man.
A wife can sue the mistress
for compensatory damages.
You can also file for divorce.
You will definitely win.
Sounds interesting.
If you want her, you can go ahead.
I will collect evidence
to incriminate you.
I will file for divorce
and sue you for compensation.
It will be more than eight-figures.
Wait, Oak, should I ask for nine?
Let's go for ten.
Shall I get a lawyer?
You're a greedy woman.
Money is more useful than
an unfaithful husband.
If you want to get
back together with her,
you will have to wait.
Because I won't let it happen.
You told me to suffer with you.
Now I'm suffering with you
and you will never get to be happy.
Endure it because
there's nothing else you can do.
Alright. But I've had
enough of you today.
I'm going to see the person I love.
Lan, you're not going anywhere.
- Lan, hey!
- Mook.
- Rut, let go.
- Mook, calm down.
Mook,
you should let him go for now.
You two can talk once you've
calmed down.
If pretending to be gay didn't work,
you don't have to try to hit on me.
If you want to help your friend,
try another way.
I don't like it.
- Wait, Mook. What I said...
- Rut.
We need to talk.
Mook, wait for me.
Where should I go now?
Hey.
You aren't allowed
to pursue my sister.
I'm your boss.
Who are you to order me around?
I'm saying this as her sister.
What you're trying to do
isn't right.
It's immoral and illegal.
I'm just trying to create up
an opportunity for myself.
I'm not trying to
take advantage of her.
Lan doesn't love her.
They'll divorce after a year.
A lot can change in a year.
You shouldn't try to
get between them.
Lan made it clear
that he doesn't love her.
So, I have the right to pursue her.
I can't believe
your logic is so awful.
You're not the man I know.
You're just a part-time employee.
How well can you know me?
You think I'm a good man,
a gentleman, don't you?
I'm sorry to disappoint you.
I'm just a human being.
I guess an inexperienced kid
like you wouldn't understand.
I'm not a kid anymore.
You're under 18.
To me, you're a kid.
You wouldn't understand adult love.
I'd rather be a kid forever than
become an immoral person like you.
When you grow up, you will realize
righteousness doesn't always work.
Sometimes
you have to fight for love.
This is an adult matter.
Mind your own business.
Do you understand, kid?
Nampetch!
The wrong kind of love
won't make you happy.
I won't let you do
whatever you please.
If you want my sister,
you have to go through me.
You brat, you will pay for this.
I'm looking forward to it, Boss.
Petch, what happened?
Boss!
Boss, why are you in the pool?
She isn't my mistress.
She is a woman I once loved.
No.
I might still love her.
This marriage
isn't a result of love.
It's full of hatred.
I don't need you in my life.
I only need Nuch.
So you chose Treenuch.
If I pursue Mook,
you will be fine with that, right?
That's right.
I'm not your property.
You can't hand me over
to anyone, jerk.
Be honest with me.
Are you jealous of Treenuch?
I'm not jealous.
You still love him, don't you?
I don't love him.
I'm mad at him for handing me over
to Rut when he has no right.
He thinks I'm an easy woman
who likes to sleep around.
It's irritating.
I want to purify him and
get rid of his filthy mind.
Now, listen to me, Oak.
What? What did I do?
If you don't stop saying
that I love him,
I will smack you in the mouth.
Don't even think about it?
I'm not thinking about anything.
Anyway, what will you do next?
Will you stay or leave?
I'm stubborn. I will stay.
What about Rut pursuing you?
What will you do about it?
I don't trust him.
They are friends and have
already pretended to date.
Who knows what their next move is.
I agree with you.
You should be prepared.
Don't worry.
No matter how many tricks
they throw at me, I can handle it.
(Latest Dream Guy)
(LS Design's Next Vice President)
Vice president now.
Next is the president.
The single man of your dreams?
No one knows he's already taken.
Soon I will make you single again.
You belong to me and only me.
Why didn't you let me know
you were coming?
- Danai, what's wrong?
- Shut up.
Lan may have a suspicion
that you're dating someone.
Stay away from him.
What about the plan
to get them to divorce?
Let's hold off on it for now.
I'll take it from here.
What was the fight about this time?
You were
rather rough.
It's the same old thing.
It's annoying.
She would be very upset
if she heard you say that.
She doesn't care about me.
She only cares about herself.
It's alright.
You still have me. I care about you.
I told you to stop seeing Lan.
Why didn't you listen to me?
Lak still wants me to
ruin their marriage.
Are you stupid?
He is watching you.
Stay away from him
and stop seeing him.
If Lak finds out
about our relationship,
she will destroy us.
What about the plan
to destroy their marriage?
Don't worry about that.
I will handle it.
Lan, I was thinking about you.
I'm glad you called.
I want to see you.
Can I come to your place?
I want to see you too.
But I'm out running errands.
I don't know when I'll be finished.
I can wait.
I want to talk to you
about something.
I really can't make it today.
Can we talk tomorrow?
I have all day for you.
Alright.
See you later.
I'm glad you want to see me.
I refuse to stay like this forever.
You told me you weren't
seeing anyone.
What is this? You're married.
- Nuch.
- You lied to me.
Wait, Nuch. Let me explain.
No, we're over.
I'm sorry
I didn't tell you about Lak.
I can't lose you.
You're selfish.
I refuse to be anyone's mistress.
Nuch, please. You're not a mistress.
You're number one in your own place.
We're happy together.
If you stay with me,
I will support you with everything.
Be it money
or your career, everything.
What do you say?
Who would be stupid enough
to let go of a vice president?
Danai's car.
I want to wait until it's over.
You can do that if you want.
However, I have the right to
try and make you interested.
I will make you take off this ring
without regretting it.
Can you go back to living abroad?
Go back to do what you love
quickly before I
hate you.
I think you should deal with
the cause of this problem instead.
You mean...