(Praomook)
Are you going to pursue duckling
even though she thinks you're gay?
You won't succeed.
You know that when
I have eyes for someone,
I have to have them.
Do you really like her,
or you think this is a game?
Both.
Lan, watch out!
Does this mean
Mook will suffer in my son's place?
- That's right.
- Is there a way to fix this?
They have to travel.
Then their stars will change.
Go on a honeymoon with me.
No way.
If you don't go with me,
I have to be alone with duckling.
Then I will go. When is it?
- Come with me.
- Why?
We've been followed.
They are on a honeymoon?
Why didn't you tell me this earlier?
Mook probably has had
her way with Lan by now.
Do you think I should follow him?
No, don't follow him.
I heard that
Rut will also be there for work.
My brother probably has a plan.
You can find a way to make him
fall for you after his return.
I think we have to
take this more seriously.
We can't lose to her.
I almost had Lan the other day,
but I was interrupted by her.
She is a formidable opponent.
You can be just as formidable.
I give you free rein.
You have my full support.
Win.
What is it?
I brought you the incident report
from the factory.
I'll leave you two alone.
According to the report,
the incident was caused
by an unkempt workspace
and worker negligence.
The factory manager will
carry out more rigorous inspections.
Is there anything suspicious?
Based on my investigation,
I found nothing suspicious.
You have to be more careful.
Why are you smiling?
Well, am I not allowed to
enjoy this beautiful scenery?
- Hold on.
- What is it?
Let's take some pictures
and send them to your parents.
For what?
Well, they will want to see
how we're doing on our honeymoon.
This is annoying.
- Hey.
- Come on. Smile.
Look at them. They're adorable.
Now we can be sure that
they're actually on a honeymoon.
I agree, dear.
Wait.
Our son is so irritating.
- Why?
- Look at his pretentious face.
He's just like you. You think making
that face makes you look handsome.
Oh, come on.
Do you think there's a chance of us
getting a grandkid after this trip?
I want Mook to take this opportunity
to make our son hers.
Dear, take it easy.
She won't do that.
However,
I believe Lan making a move on her
is more likely to happen
since there is so much potential.
This time
he will forget about
the whole gay charade.
Mook and Lan have history together.
Their bond is deep.
His hatred cannot destroy her love.
Trust me.
Of course. Trusting my wife
is the best thing to do.
Oh.
Look at this.
Wow.
This place is beautiful.
Absolutely. We must be very lucky
to get to stay here.
Thank you.
Well, here's the thing.
One of the pipes is broken.
As a result,
some of the rooms aren't available.
But don't worry.
They've prepared us a place
to stay together.
Well.
As expected of my number one
secretary. Great work.
This is beyond our control.
He didn't mean for this to happen.
She's right.
Keep protecting him.
Do you realize that you won't have
a place to sleep tonight?
Why do you say that?
Poom just told us that
they've prepared a place for us.
We can all sleep in there.
No. You're a woman. You can't sleep
in the same room with men.
I agree with him.
Are you sure it's a good idea?
Well, we can each stay
in our own corner.
It's only for tonight.
I'm sure it's fine.
It's not going to happen.
If your guardian knows that I let
you sleep in a room with three men,
they will be upset.
If by guardian you mean my sister,
I'm sure she'll be okay with it
since she knows you're...
Lan's boyfriend.
Poom can be trusted.
Oak and I know each other.
There won't be a problem.
- Whatever, it's not going to...
- I think we should stop arguing.
For now let's check out
the place they've prepared for us.
Then we can make a decision.
What do you say?
I agree with him, Boss.
Please, Marut.
Wow.
This is huge.
It can accommodate several people.
Indeed.
I think we can all sleep here.
- Right?
You get along well.
Boss,
I've checked with nearby hotels.
They are all fully booked.
With a room this big,
I think we can comfortably
divide space for the four of us.
I agree with Poom.
I will talk to Mook about Nampetch.
It's three to one now, Boss.
Alright.
Poom,
ask the hotel to prepare
space for Oak and Nampetch.
Sure.
I don't care how you feel.
Try to get used to seeing my face.
Because all I care about
is your safety.
She is a terrible photographer.
Lovely pictures, aren't they?
Have you started to
feel things for me?
I don't feel a thing.
Are you sure?
Shall we bathe together then?
You're shameless. Don't you get
embarrassed saying such a thing?
Well, since this is our honeymoon,
we should enjoy our moment together.
I will make this one
memorable for you.
You bathe me.
I bathe you.
Slowly rubbing soap over you,
starting from your arm
to your shoulder.
And then...
Let me wash your body,
so you can relax.
I...
Are you shy?
We're married.
We are pretty much one person.
We should have been intimate
with each other a long time ago.
You're very muscular.
Your heart is racing.
Mine is racing too.
Feel it.
I will make your heart
race even faster.
Finally you're mine.
You will be mine forever.
You lost to me, Lan.
Hey, no!
Stop talking.
I won't walk into your trap.
The only person
I will bathe with is Rut.
Don't you want to try it?
I can make you forget about him.
I won't stop loving him.
No matter how hard you try to
seduce me, I won't feel a thing.
We'll see how long
you can control yourself.
Right, and stop trying to seduce me.
I'm running out of patience.
If you don't stop,
I will tie you to the pillar.
Sounds scary.
Duckling, what are you doing?
I'm making you fall in love with me,
have only me in your mind.
You can say you hate me
as many times as you want.
I don't care what you say to me.
All I care about
is your heart.
I've arrived.
Tomorrow after I'm done with work,
I will come and see you.
Come here as fast as you can.
I don't think I can take it anymore.
What do you mean?
Wait.
Did you and Mook...
No way. That woman can't
make me feel anything.
Duckling has been acting
like my shadow,
trying to test if I'm gay or not.
I'm so sick of her.
I've been wondering
if her friend joined the trip
to observe me.
Be careful.
Mook and her friend
may have planned something.
I'm curious about their plan.
Should I seduce Rut tonight?
That way, we'll find out
if he likes men or not.
Listen, you don't have
to be that committed.
You told me before
that your gaydar didn't ping.
If you seduce him and he kicks you,
judging from his large frame,
he will break your bones
and I won't be able to help you.
Oh, I can picture it in my head.
I was just kidding.
Look, if you want to test Lan,
you can seduce him.
You have my support.
Are you crazy? I can't do that.
Well, your voice is shaking.
You aren't firm about the idea.
You feel something, don't you?
No way.
I spoke very firmly.
You heard it wrong.
Oh, really?
Don't forget that
you have only a year with him.
Your goal is to get back at him
by making him fall for you
and then dump him.
This means you can't love him
or sleep with him.
Otherwise, it will be you
who gets hurt the most.
You can't let your feelings
get the best of you.
I know what I'm doing.
I won't be reckless
with someone I don't love.
The number you've dialed
can't be connected. Try again later.
Where are you?
Why did you turn your phone off?
Call me back.
(Treenuch)
Lan, what are you doing?
Lan is taking a bath.
Mook, how dare you answer his phone.
Am I not allowed to
answer my husband's phone?
I answered his phone because
I'm tired of shameless women.
It's just a mock marriage.
How dare you claim that he is yours.
Don't you feel ashamed
to call him your husband?
It's still considered a marriage.
It's better than
being an ex-girlfriend
who isn't even his friend
nor his acquaintance.
Nothing. A nobody.
If I were you,
I would feel very hurt.
But if I were you,
I would hurt even more.
You confessed your love to him
and he rejected you.
If his parents didn't force him,
he would never marry you.
Stay in your lane.
This is between me and him.
Did I just rile you up?
I will make you lose this
wife position you're so proud of.
Be my guest.
Be careful.
Old flames burn brighter.
I won't interrupt
your honeymoon anymore.
Tell him I miss him
and let's meet again in Bangkok.
(Marriage Certificate)
You're his past. I'm his present.
Marriages can end in divorce.
Stop.
Tonight you will sleep
on the sofa outside.
I will sleep in this room.
You aren't allowed to come in.
We will sleep separately.
What are you afraid of?
I'm afraid you will try to touch me.
I don't want to sleep with you.
Do you think sleeping separately
will make you safe?
No matter where you sleep,
if I want to make you mine,
I can make it happen.
Don't you feel ashamed of
the things you said?
You are so shameless.
Being bold can get you anywhere.
I can't wait to test your sexuality
and find out if you're gay or not.
Do you remember what I told you?
I will use my right.
Don't be distracted tonight.
Because if you get distracted,
I will make you mine.
I'm not scared of your threats.
Not even a little?
Then be careful tonight,
my beloved husband.
Shall we sleep on this bed?
This is my bed. Go somewhere else.
- Get out now.
- No, I want this bed.
- Get out.
- No, let go.
- Let go of me.
- No.
- I will sleep here.
- Duckling!
- This is my bed. Get out!
- No!
- Hey!
- Get out!
I'm taking the bed.
- Come here.
- Oh.
- Get out of the bed.
- Duckling!
I'm not getting out of my bed.
Duckling!
- No, I'm not leaving.
- You won't leave, will you?
- Ah!
- Get up!
Move!
Get off!
Stubborn woman.
Get out.
Duckling.
- Will you surrender?
- No way.
I surrender! I surrender!
I surrender!
You can sleep anywhere you want.
I surrender! I surrender!
- Let go.
- There you go.
Make yourself comfortable.
Hey.
Duckling.
Did she just fall asleep?
Poom.
Are they competing
in a snoring championship?
Duckling!
Were you a gecko in your past life?
You have sticky feet.
You even touch me in your sleep.
One sheep.
Two sheep.
Three sheep.
Four ducklings.
Five ducklings.
Six ducklings.
Where were you all day?
I told you I went to another city.
Why did you turn off your phone?
You didn't even answer my voicemail.
Oh.
My battery died. I didn't realize.
I was busy and didn't check.
I came back as soon as I was done.
Are you sure it's work
and not something else?
Honestly, I was working.
I wasn't fooling around.
I came back as soon as
I had finished with work.
I don't care how late it is.
I don't want to stay at a hotel.
I'd rather fall asleep
with you in my arms.
Don't try to sweet-talk me.
I didn't do anything wrong.
The phone was an accident.
If you're mad at me,
I will make it up to you.
Oh, wait.
Careful.
Sorry.
Rut, are you okay?
Your heart is beating fast.
Are you watching me?
No.
You're attracted to me, aren't you?
No, you're projecting.
Eight ducklings.
Nine ducklings.
Ten ducklings.
Eleven ducklings.
No, Mook. Focus.
See you this evening.
No progress on Rut so far.
I'll keep looking for the chance.
Shall we stop by somewhere
on the way to Lan?
- No, we'll head straight to him.
- Okay.
- Rut.
- Lan.
Why are you so happy to see me?
I'm really happy to see you.
If you were a second late,
I would be eaten by her.
Mook, I miss you so much.
Hey, are you this happy to see me?
Listen. I have so much to tell you
about the conference.
Can I stay with you tonight?
You can't, Petch.
Lan and I are on our honeymoon.
If you want to talk to me,
we can talk during the day.
Now, how will you arrange
our accommodation for tonight?
Since I know you all want to
spend your precious time together,
I've arranged for you
to stay in one room.
You can decide
where you want to sleep.
Rut, I miss you so much.
We'll sleep together tonight.
Don't worry. I haven't touched
duckling at all the last few nights.
Rut.
I haven't touched him either,
so don't feel jealous.
But I want to stay with you tonight.
I have so much to tell you
about our trip.
Alright.
Mook, you should stay with me.
I really miss you.
You should stay with your sister.
I want to spend time with my lover.
But I want to talk to him.
- He will stay with me.
- He is my lover.
- Hey!
Come over here. Come on.
You're behaving like children.
You could have torn him apart.
Are you hurt?
If you can't make a decision,
we will all sleep here.
Hey, Mom.
Mook, what's wrong?
Dad went into cardiac arrest.
The doctor is trying to save him.
Dad.
Dear, please hang in there.
Da, stay calm.
The doctor is trying to save him.
He will be alright.
Oak, Petch and I will fly home
right away. Get us tickets.
Alright, I'll handle it.
Phone.
Oak, let me handle it.
You can take care of your friend.
- Mook.
- I'll pack my bag.
Come on.
Leave me. I'm not ready
to fight with you.
You don't have to do anything.
Just stay still.
- You can stay here. I will...
- Quiet.
Will my dad be okay?
I don't know.
Whatever will happen will happen.
You should be prepared.
I will help you pack up.
I'm flying home with you.
Mom, how is he?
They brought him back.
Did the doctor tell you
why his condition worsened?
There's something wrong
with Dad's brain.
Mook, Petch,
I have something
important to tell you.
We have to make a decision together.
Based on our examination,
it is confirmed that
Pethai's brain has stopped working.
He is being kept alive
by life support.
Clinically, he is considered dead.
Oh, Da.
Do you mean
he can't recover from this?
I'm sorry for your loss.
What I want to inform you is
Pethai is a registered organ donor.
The donation process can only
be continued with your consent.
To be frank,
you have to decide quickly
if you want to keep up the treatment
or respect the patient's wish.
So we have to decide if we want
to let him go or keep him alive.
That's right.
The decision is up to us
whether we wish to give our consent.
What's your opinion on this?
Mom.
I want Dad to stay with us.
This is too early.
I know.
I can't accept this either.
But I don't want to ignore his wish.
- Mom.
- Petch.
Can I have tonight
to make up my mind?
We still have time, don't we?
We still do.
But the doctor wants us
to decide quickly
before all of his organs fail.
Are you still qualified
to be an organ donor?
I'm not that old.
We can be an organ donor
until we're 65 years old.
I'm only 50.
Does Mom know about this?
She does. I just want you to know
in case something happens to me
because it's you, Mom, and Petch
who have to make the decision.
Dad, don't say something like that.
The future is unpredictable.
I just want you to be prepared.
But, if you have to decide some day,
I want you to think of my words.
If something happens to me,
if I have to leave this world,
and any part of me can save
the life of somebody,
who has their own family
just like I have you, Da and Petch,
and I can help them get back to
their family, I will do it.
Although I won't be
with you physically,
I will be alive
in someone else's body.
I want you to think that way.
It's my wish.
I hope you remember my words.
I remember everything you said.
But I'm afraid
that I can't live without you.
Why aren't you
by her side right now?
How could you let her go home alone?
You're useless.
I won't be able to help her anyway.
You could at least be there for her.
Listen to me.
Husband and wife are supposed to
be there for each other.
You stay together during
your joyous moments.
You hold each other's hand
during hardship.
You aren't supposed to do
what you're doing right now.
I'm giving her time
to be with her family.
You're her family too.
Whatever, you have to be
by her side immediately tomorrow.
Alright.
I will do it because you told me to.
Lan.
Do you know that our family
made it through our financial crisis
because we got help from Pethai?
Our families share a real bond.
How can we do nothing
when their family is struggling?
Listen to me.
You will take care of
Mook and her family
on behalf of me and your mother.
Or at least during this time.
Can you do that for me?
Beg me and I will do it.
Alright.
I beg you.
I want you to consent to
the organ donation.
Mook, don't you love him?
How can you let him die?
Dad left us, Petch.
The doctor declared it.
The doctor might have
made a mistake.
Should we move Dad to a new hospital
or find him a new doctor?
There must be a miracle.
Petch, there's no miracle.
The doctor checked several times.
Only once the results were clear
did he let me know.
Dad left us.
That's not true.
Petch.
Stop running away.
You have to be strong
and face reality.
- I don't want to listen to you.
- Petch.
Petch, Dad left us.
Let him go.
This is the last thing
we can do for him.
How did you get here?
I drove here.
You can drive back
if you're going to be annoying.
I'm not in the mood
to argue with you.
I wasn't being annoying.
I just answered your question.
Lan.
I just want to be left in peace.
Didn't you hear what I said?
Why are you still here?
You said you want to be left
in peace, not alone.
Where are you going?
I want to be alone in peace.
Don't go anywhere.
I promise I will be quiet
and won't disturb you.
I want you to add color
and graphic details in this scene.
Let me know when you've finished.
I'll take a look at it again.
Okay. Thanks, Boss.
If you're worried,
you should go to the hospital.
Staying here,
you can't concentrate on work.
I'm not worried.
But you keep looking at
Petch's desk every five seconds.
- I'm not.
- Stop.
Don't argue with me.
I've been watching you.
Are you this dedicated
when it comes to your work?
People's business is my business.
We don't have a lot of work today.
You can leave the office
if you want.
I will get back to work.
If you don't go,
then I'd like to take this day off.
I've finished all my work.
Wait.
Where are you going?
I'm going to see Petch.
I'm worried about her.
She has been through a lot.
As her mentor,
I have to take care of her.
Boss, where are you going?
I'm going to the hospital.
Do I have to tell you everything?
You're so clueless.
- Poom.
- Yes?
I heard that.
Don't worry about us.
We can take care of ourselves.
I will miss you a little though.
Dad, don't worry.
I will do my best
to take care of Mom and my sister.
I can take care of myself.
I won't need you.
Dad, I'm an adult now,
so don't worry about me.
When I make my own game,
I will create a character based on
you, and you will be the big boss.
Nobody will be able to beat you.
Would you like that?
I love you, Dad.
Please rest in peace, Pethai.
Don't worry.
My family
will always be there for yours.
Although Mook and I fight a lot,
when she is in trouble,
I will stay by her side.
It's time to rest.
Rest well.
Don't worry about your family.
No matter what happens,
I will do your job for you.
Pethai.
We're a family.
You don't have to worry.
Lim and I
will take care of everything.
Rest in peace, Pethai.
Thank you, Pethai,
for always being there
for my family.
I will never forget what
you've done for me.
I don't have a father.
My mother didn't have time for me.
But you love me
and always treated me like a son.
I will keep your love for me
in my heart forever.
Goodbye, Dad.
I love you more than
anything in the world.
This is where we part.
Start your journey before me.
And one day I will follow you.
I love you.
Mom.
- Mom.
- Oh dear.
Rut.
When you're with me,
you don't have to
make yourself look tough.
I'm not breaking our rule
that says we won't date
the same woman.
You said it yourself that Mook
doesn't mean anything to you.
Lan.
Where is Mook?
I don't know.
How can you say you don't know?
During this time,
you should be by her side,
consoling her, reassuring her.
And why should I do that?
It's not my place.
You're her husband.
A husband who doesn't love her.
So I don't have a duty to fulfill.
Lan.
Still, you shouldn't be this unkind.
You two grew up together.
Can't you at least be there for her?
Dear, take it easy.
Lan, look.
Mook is mourning.
I want you to be by her side
and console her.
I'm worried about her.
I don't want her to be all alone.
She isn't all alone,
so don't worry about that.
He may do a better job
than a cruel man like me.
I'm not needed here.
Lan! Lan!
Dear.
Who did he mean?
How would I know?
I'm just as clueless as you are.
Rut, I'm sorry for
losing control of myself.
I told you before.
You don't have to be strong
around me.
I just want to be there for you
when you feel vulnerable.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
Although you wish I were Lan.
No, I didn't mean it like that.
Of course.
I understand how you feel.
Time will help you get through this.
I believe you.
I will get through this.
Petch.
Poom.
What should I do?
I don't want to cry.
I don't want Dad to worry.
I want to be strong.
I don't want anyone
to worry about me.
But it's really hard.
I can't hold back the tears.
Crying doesn't make you weak.
It's an emotional expression.
You are allowed to cry.
Rut.
Nampetch.
I know you're upset.
But you have to
pull yourself together.
Crybaby.
There you go.
(Nuch is calling)
Mook will stay
with her mother tonight.
Why are you telling me this?
I don't want to know.
I just want you to know
because you will be alone tonight.
Good. Maybe then I will get
some peace and quiet.
Since I married her,
my life has been in chaos.
She will be away for a few days.
You will get to fully enjoy
some peace and quiet.
Tell me the truth.
Don't you worry about her?
Why should I?
I don't care what happens to her
or how she feels.
I told you before. What happens
to her doesn't concern me.
You're a real jerk.
Rut, are you insulting me?
I'm telling you what I see.
You are mean to her
to keep her away from you.
It's actually a good thing
that you're mean to her.
The more you hate her,
the greater chance I have
of making her fall in love with me.
Did duckling put you under a spell
and cause you to lose your mind?
You've gotten involved with her when
we don't know if she is the culprit.
You're setting yourself up
for disappointment.
Thanks for the warning.
But I'm not scared.
I will uncover the truth from her.
Now, you...
(Nuch is calling)
You should uncover the truth
from Treenuch and stop running away.
- I'm not running away.
- Then what are you doing?
Do you think I don't know
that you readily agreed to the trip
because you wanted to
run away from her?
You should ask yourself
how you feel about her.
So you can stop getting angry
when I hit the nail on the head.
Are you done?
If you're done, shut up.
I want to be alone.
Oh.
I will stop pretending
to be your boyfriend.
Everybody knows you're lying.
Nobody will buy it,
except those who don't know you.
I will begin my own game.
And I'm sure that in this game
I will be the winner.
Sure. Do whatever you want.
I want to be close to you.
Do you miss me?
I will give you another chance.
Let me know if you change
your mind about Mook.
Our rule is
don't love the same girl.
You told me to stop running away.
I've asked myself
and got my answer.
Nuch is important to me.
From now on I will pursue you.
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
Then I will give you another story.
You've been surrounded on all sides.