(Praomook)
What proof do you have
that my sister is behind everything?
that your sister didn't do it?
Nothing.
Then your sister and Rawin
are the suspects.
Someone sent you a threat.
I can't believe
it's actually what I thought.
What did you say?
I'm sorry for
thinking only about myself.
If it isn't too late,
I'd like to come back
to help you out.
If you want everything back,
I will help you.
Life is unpredictable.
You don't know
what tomorrow will bring,
if you will be alive or dead.
What if he targets her instead,
who will be there to help her?
The number you dialed
cannot be reached.
(Nampetch)
(Rut)
Rut, did you miss me?
How is your sister?
I can't get a hold of her.
Keep trying.
She will pick up eventually.
Or maybe she doesn't want to
answer your call.
Nampetch, this is important.
Can I talk to her?
Let me think about it.
Mook!
Anybody, help!
Petch, run away.
- No.
- Don't worry about me.
Come on.
Lan, don't follow him.
I have to catch him.
Call an ambulance.
Ambulance.
Rut.
Rut, my sister was attacked.
I'm calling an ambulance.
- Rut.
- Where is the attacker?
He got away.
I called the police.
They should arrive shortly.
Mook, are you okay?
Petch, are you okay?
I'm okay.
But Mook got hurt badly.
If I was a second late, it might...
Petch, it will be okay.
Oh, they're here.
How was your dinner with the client?
We still have him,
but it may be different next year.
And?
I need to take a shower.
Let's talk about this tomorrow.
(Marriage Certificate)
(Marriage Contract)
(property ownership shall belong
to the payer for 1 year...)
(Praomook)
Lan.
Something came up.
Does it have to do with Mook?
It does.
Once I handle it, we'll talk later.
Hey, what are you doing?
Anybody, help!
Help!
Lan, watch out!
Mom.
I'm going to take Mook with me.
Why?
I'm worried about her mental state.
Staying here will remind her
of what happened.
Oh, poor girl.
Please take care of my daughter.
Let me know if anything happens.
I will do my best to keep her safe.
Take care.
If anything happens, no matter
how serious it may be, tell me.
We will get through it together.
Don't shoulder the burden
on your own.
I know, Mom.
Lan, I remember something.
What is it?
I bit his left arm.
It should've left a mark.
And
when he was choking me,
I...
Hey, that's enough.
You don't have to
think about it anymore.
You're starting to crack.
Don't strain yourself.
If you have something to say,
let's talk tomorrow.
What happened?
Lan, I'm scared.
It will be okay. You're safe now.
It's all in the past.
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
It wasn't your fault.
But...
It was the attacker's fault.
Don't put the blame on yourself.
I'm alive because of you.
You did your best.
Thank you.
I hope you won't betray me.
I should stop myself right here.
Are you worried about
how other people may feel?
I am.
Even though I am right here,
you're thinking about other people.
I'm pathetic.
- I...
- Don't talk anymore.
Leave me.
I can be by myself.
I said leave.
In the end, I lost.
I will never love Praomook.
Good. I don't want to stab someone
in the back.
And I don't like being
stabbed in the back either.
How is Mook?
She fell asleep.
That's good.
It's time to go to bed.
We have a lot
to deal with after this.
Rut.
What?
Do you still like Mook?
I do.
Why do you ask?
I want to know
if you've changed your mind.
When it comes to Mook,
I don't waver easily.
Good.
What about you?
Do you feel the same about her?
I feel the same.
I should stop myself right here.
Are you worried about
how other people may feel?
I am.
Even though I am right here,
you think about other people.
I'm pathetic.
Where are you going?
I'm going to work.
Why?
You just went through something
traumatic. You should rest.
I have to deal with something.
I can't stop you, can I?
Stay safe, my stubborn sister.
Ow.
I will.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
Are you heading to work?
I am. I have to check on something.
I remember that I bit the attacker.
He should be injured.
I also hit him in the back.
Unless he is super tough,
it should still hurt.
Lan is out.
I'm free today.
Let me give you a ride.
Let him take you to work.
If anything happens,
he and Oak will be able to help you.
My sister's safety is top priority.
What's wrong?
Do you have to be this alert?
You too, Rut.
We have to act tough
to scare off the attacker.
You look very scary.
I'm glad to see you in a good mood.
Good morning, Mook.
Good morning, Win.
Good morning, Rut.
Do you have business here,
or you're just dropping her off?
The latter.
Mook, you can go to work.
Rut and I will wait for you
at a nearby cafe.
Call me when you're finished.
I have to discuss
something with you.
Let's talk as we walk.
Sure.
See you later, Rut.
Alright.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Hello.
Have a seat.
I want you to look at this.
(Marriage Contract)
The contract is real, isn't it?
Tell me the truth.
The contract is real.
So you did it
for your own interests.
You don't care about my brother.
I admit that the house is part of
the reason why I married Lan.
You traded yourself for the house.
What are you going to do next?
Will you trade yourself for money
by having his baby
and use that
to live off my father's possessions?
No.
Once the term is over,
I will get a divorce.
What about Lan?
Don't you feel hesitate
about leaving him?
He won't feel anything.
I will probably become
one of his bad memories.
You don't love him?
I don't.
I feel bad for him that he married
a woman who doesn't love him
and only cares about
her own interests.
So this contract is real.
Now that you know the truth,
what will you do next, Lan?
Why did you ask for me?
I have something to show you.
(Marriage Contract)
(mortgage and debt shall be
paid off, on the condition that...)
She married for the house.
She doesn't care about you.
You're her leverage.
(property ownership shall belong
to the payer for 1 year...)
Don't jump to conclusions.
You don't even know if it's real.
If you want the truth,
why don't we ask her?
Now that it's come to this,
if you want to prove that
you aren't using Lan,
divorce him.
You're here to work,
or to see the damage you've done?
Both.
I have an appointment with Lak.
It's probably about the contract.
It would be great
if they get a divorce.
Lak will definitely
have a talk with her.
But I don't think her dad
would let them end the marriage.
As long as Lan hates her after this,
I will make them
get a divorce myself.
For now, we wait.
You did a great job.
Rut, do you think
they seem suspiciously close?
My instincts are telling me
they are more than co-workers.
- I...
- I will handle this myself.
How will you handle it?
You will find out soon enough.
Come with me.
Hello, Lak.
Sure.
I have to go and meet her.
I hope it's good news.
Of course.
- Ow!
- I'm sorry.
- Be careful next time.
- I'm really sorry.
I also hit him in the back.
Unless he is super tough,
it should still hurt.
Lan, let go.
Did you even think of
telling me about the contract?
If Lak hadn't told me,
I guess this would have
remained a secret forever,
or I would've found out
on the day of the divorce.
If you were me,
would you tell anyone?
Marrying for a house.
It's just like what you said to me,
that I sell my body.
You didn't marry for the house.
You did it for your family.
The house is the agreement
made between you and my dad.
He can spend his money
however he wants.
If there's a change, you have to
discuss it with him, not my sister.
Shall I go to him now
and end this whole thing?
It will end
only when the term is over.
You should feel happy to be free.
Won't you regret losing your house?
You were willing
to do anything to keep it.
Why are you letting it go now?
What do you want me to do?
Should I endure it,
letting my feelings get hurt?
What about the attacker?
I can't do it anymore, Lan.
(Lak)
(Marriage Contract)
Find the person who sent me this.
This contract was made
between my father and Praomook.
If the sender managed to
take a picture of the contract,
it could be someone close to them.
I can't believe she would do that.
She almost agreed to get a divorce,
but Lan didn't let her.
I guess he's lost his senses.
He may have a plan.
I don't think he does.
He just wants to protect her.
(The number is registered
under Treenuch's name.)
I may need your help.
End their marriage.
I don't care how.
I can do it.
I'm just scared that
it would upset your father.
I don't want to have
a problem with him.
Don't worry.
I will deal with my father.
You're a capable woman.
More importantly, Lan loves you.
My parents will eventually
accept you as their daughter-in-law.
Talk to Lan.
Find a way to change his mind.
Alright, I will talk to him.
I'm going to take a shower.
I don't like your perfume.
Stop wearing it.
If you don't do that,
I will handle it myself.
(The number is registered
under Treenuch's name.)
Treenuch.
Danai.
I heard about the assault.
What happened?
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't want you to worry.
You didn't want me to worry,
or you didn't want me to know it
wasn't some thug who attacked you.
If it wasn't,
what would you do about it?
I will catch your attacker
and send him to jail. That's it.
You knew.
That's right. Mook told me.
She was very worried,
so she came to tell me
to keep an eye on things.
I sent someone to investigate it,
but I got nothing.
Then Mook was attacked.
I didn't think it would happen.
I don't think he will stop here.
For her safety,
you and Mook have to stay
at our family's condo for now.
The place should be more secured
than Rut's house or hers.
Alright.
I will keep her safe.
I have to talk to you.
Alright.
The security at this place
is tight and transparent.
There is only one entrance and exit,
which should be better than
our house that has several exits.
Right. This place looks secure.
You should stay with her.
For her safety, we need someone
to be on watch 24/7.
Oak can stay with me.
That way, it won't disturb
Rut's and your time.
Then who will stay with your mother?
Just do as I say.
- What do you say, Rut?
- Alright.
I will stay here.
I want you to be careful
of your brother-in-law.
We don't know how he hurt his back.
It's better to be on guard.
Can we check his travel records?
Yes, we can.
I told Poom to check Rawin's.
Check Danai's too.
Alright.
(Nuch)
Hey. I have something
interesting to tell you.
Look at this.
I think Nuch and Danai
seem suspiciously close.
Assuming they were discussing work,
their eyes, body language,
and posture were too relaxed.
They could be more than co-workers.
How close do you think they are?
I don't know.
But I'm sure
they're more than co-workers.
Should we tell Lan about this?
Without solid evidence,
he would be mad if I told him.
It's a lose-lose situation.
What should we do then?
It's best to do nothing.
What? Don't you
want to know the truth?
This is between Lan and Nuch.
Let them handle it on their own.
Did you give up on him?
It's time.
I've given up.
Dear, I have a bad feeling.
I'm worried about both of them.
Da is stressed. She is scared
Mook will be attacked again.
Listen, I told them
to stay at the condo.
I asked security
to always stay alert.
If anything seems wrong,
they will inform me at once.
Dear, I'm not so sure
if we did the right thing
by asking Mook to marry our son.
Don't worry, dear.
There must be a solution to this.
I hope so.
Dad told Lan and Mook
to move to the condo.
For what?
I don't know. I guess he doesn't
want them to stay at Rut's.
So he gave them the condo.
Now that he gave them his condo,
who knows what
he will give them next.
If you can't end their marriage,
we will lose even more.
If you can't be useful,
stop talking.
Just do your job
and don't make any mistakes.
I can handle Mook.
I won't let her
take anything from me.
I won't make mistakes.
Mook.
Yes?
I have something to show you.
What is it?
It's a game
your sister is developing.
What is it about?
"How To Be Romantic?"
This is an otome game.
As expected of her.
Right, as expected of the brat.
I can't believe she created this.
She has a talent in this field.
She is highly creative.
With constant training,
she could create more fun games.
If this game is a success,
I'm going to give her
a percentage of the sales.
Then she will probably brag to you
about how she can make money.
She will brag about both the game
and the money. She likes to brag.
Anyway, thank you
for giving her the opportunity.
Sure.
- Here. Let me show you how to play.
- Alright.
- Well, there are these characters.
- Okay.
It's like a game
where you're romantic virtually,
but it's actually an experiment
in the game.
However, it's like being
romantic in real life.
How do I be romantic?
- Here. You will do missions.
- Okay.
And the number of hearts
will increase after each mission.
- So I'm a girl going after a guy.
- You got it.
Alright.
Hey, Nuch.
I have to discuss work with you.
And I want to see you.
Can you come to my place?
Sure. I will see you there.
Okay.
I'm going out.
Take care of Mook.
You shouldn't go out by yourself.
I will be with Nuch.
It will be fine.
Excuse me.
Lan.
How can you leave me alone with her?
I'm giving you an opening.
You won't feel a thing
if she falls in love with me?
I can't dictate how people feel.
Be honest with me.
You love Mook, don't you?
Ignore my feelings.
Our rule is
don't love the same girl.
I don't love Praomook.
Are you happy?
So far you haven't been
honest with me.
If you think not loving her
will solve everything,
go ahead.
Go be with whoever you want.
I will take care of her.
Remember my hatred.
You will face it
for the rest of your life.
I told you before. Even if
you're the only woman left,
I won't take an interest in you.
I should stop myself right here.
Are you worried about
how other people may feel?
I am.
You told me to stop
running away from Nuch.
So I asked myself and got an answer.
Nuch is important to me.
I don't love Praomook.
If you think not loving her
will solve everything, go ahead.
Go be with whoever you want.
I will take care of her.
When you're with me,
you don't have to act strong.
- Answer me.
- I didn't do it.
- Lan.
- Hey!
Rut!
Do you still like Mook?
Why do you ask?
I want to know
if you've changed your mind.
Can't I take a peek?
Don't be self-conscious.
Nuch.
I should go home.
Okay.
Oh.
What's wrong?
I'm fine. You should go home.
Oh.
Is it your stomach?
Yes.
It's good to have you by my side.
Lan.
Duckling.
It's me, not the person
you're thinking of.
You should wash up.
I will prepare breakfast.
You should watch Treenuch
and Danai's relationship closely.
What Oak and I saw
looked suspicious.
They barely talked
in front of you, right?
From what we saw,
they seemed intimate.
The day Poom brought her medicine,
a cleaner said she lives alone,
but that a guy would
visit her occasionally,
mostly at night.
The cleaner doesn't know who he is.
She saw him sometimes,
but couldn't see his face.
What are you looking for?
I'm looking for a towel.
Here you go.
I will find you a toothbrush.
Do you live here alone?
What do you mean?
I mean, does your family
visit you sometimes?
I live alone.
If you're worried,
you can move in with me.
Sounds interesting.
I will consider it.
What are you doing?
I slapped you.
I want to know how thick your skin
is since you won't leave Lan alone.
You aren't any different
from a prostitute.
He told me about
your pathetic contract.
That's for insulting me.
You!
You have no right to judge whether
the contract is pathetic or not.
It means you're insulting the person
who helped me, which is Lan's dad.
And I'm not a prostitute.
Drop the good daughter-in-law act.
There's no audience here.
No one to feel grateful
for your protectiveness.
Is that all you have to say?
If people knew the reason
behind your marriage,
wouldn't you feel ashamed?
A daughter-in-law who can be
bought with a house.
Interesting, don't you think?
You may be able to endure it
because you're shameless.
But I wonder if Lan's parents can.
Stop with your disgusting thoughts.
If it helps me get Lan,
I won't give up.
I talked to Mook.
I don't know if she will listen.
If she has a conscience,
she should feel ashamed of herself.
If she doesn't get it,
you can keep warning her.
Put more pressure on her.
I know you can.
Okay.
When you're no use to me,
I will get rid of you.
Come in.
I need to talk to you.
What is it?
I want to get a divorce
as soon as possible.
Can you tell me one good reason
for the divorce?
It's to protect Mook.
Okay.
I need to talk to you.
Me too.
Then I will go first.
Let's get a divorce.
Alright.
You can choose the date.
How about today?
You will finally be free from me.
(Praomook Wongnuannang)
(Chalantorn Anantanapat)
(Divorce Certificate)
Did she get anything?
She wouldn't accept anything.
Dad's possessions are intact.
Are you happy?
Very.
All the evidence points to Rawin.
Win, stay calm.
If there is an investigation,
try to stall it.
I will deal with the rest.
Be careful and don't get caught.
If you want to take care of Mook,
tell me the truth.
Do you love her?
Take care of her for me.