[antifan_act, hashtag anti-fan, follow]
[Choi Tae-joon]
[Choi Soo-young]
[Hwang Chan-sung]
[Han Ji-an]
[Kim Min-gue]
[So I Married the Anti-Fan]
[Episode 11]
[There Comes a Time
When You Must Choose a Side]
-Someone's calling you.
-No, I'm not picking up.
Come on, pick it up.
Who's calling at this hour?
[Stranger]
What are you doing? Pick it up.
Okay.
One second.
-What is...
[-Are you Oh In-hyung's guardian?]
[This is the hospital.]
Yes, okay.
What is it? What's going on?
In-hyung fainted in a car alone,
and she's at a hospital.
Really?
That's not good. Let's go.
I'll take you home.
You're going there alone?
There are lots of people at the hospital.
Will you wear your helmet there?
What if people begin a weird rumor?
Let's go.
I'll go with you.
[Dasom Hospital Emergency Medical Center]
One second.
If you go in like this,
you'll cause a huge scene in there.
-But still.
-After she's sent to the ward.
You should call Ji-hyang.
[Dasom Hospital Emergency Medical Center]
We usually call speed dial
when a patient comes in alone.
What a relief.
Sometimes they aren't the guardian.
She's the girl I couldn't protect.
I made a choice to protect everyone.
Yet I couldn't protect anybody
and ended up hurting everyone.
[In-hyung, did you still want Who-joon
to be your guardian?]
[Oh I. Hyung]
[Where did everything go wrong for us?]
She'll wake up soon, so don't worry.
Thanks.
You're up.
How did you find me here?
You fainted in the car by yourself.
Don't you remember?
Right.
So how did you two end up here?
Things happened.
What happened to you?
I need to make a call.
Tell me, In-hyung. What's going on?
I don't even remember how I got there.
I didn't think
the hospital would call you.
I didn't expect to see you
with Geun-young either.
Is Jae-joon troubling you?
What if he is?
If he is,
and so if I want to be back with you,
will you accept me?
I was patient
because I thought you'd be happy. But...
Don't be angry.
I hate myself to death for doing this.
Yes, I'm sure they have things
they want to discuss alone.
-Geun-young.
-You're here.
-Where's Joon?
-He's inside.
Joon, let's go.
-Ji-hyang.
-I'll call Jae-joon.
No, Ji-hyang. I'll call him later.
Okay, then. Since you're up,
we'll get going. Let's go.
She's not well. How can I leave?
So what? Will you stay
and look after her all night?
Then I'll stay.
It's okay, Geun-young.
Don't say that. We can't leave you alone.
-I'll stay.
-No, Geun-young. I'll...
Sorry Geun-young,
but please stay here for tonight.
-He has to be at a shooting.
-Sure. You should go.
-Thanks.
-Ji-hyang.
Let's go.
Sorry.
How can we leave them alone?
Do you have another idea?
She was our only option.
And if the number
that the hospital called you is
a secret number between you two,
disconnect it.
In-hyung is trying hard
not to cause me any damage.
I'll see what happens tomorrow
and call Jae-joon
or let her get discharged alone,
so stop minding her.
Feel free to let me know
if you need anything.
-Okay.
-Good.
We seem to meet rather often.
We do.
I'm sorry.
For what?
Among Who-joon's acquaintances,
I'm someone who knows about you.
That too.
I meant leaking the song.
Sorry?
I wasn't trying
to make people think it was you.
Wait, it was you?
Why? Why did you do that?
I'm not even sure what I wanted from it.
You wouldn't understand, would you?
Then did you expect me to understand?
Have you thought about
how it would hurt other people?
Other people?
Who are you worried about?
Joon? Or Jae-joon?
Everyone. Starting with me,
Ji-hyang, Jae-joon, and Who-joon.
Everyone was put in a tight spot
because of you.
You said you didn't know what you wanted.
Before you find what you want,
you should learn to think and understand
in other people's shoes.
[The person you have reached...]
[I'm sorry.]
[Just Lee Geun-young]
Joon, the other scene ended.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
[I'm sorry.]
[Why do you keep saying sorry to me?]
[You don't even know how I feel.]
[Dasom Hospital]
Your meal is here.
Enjoy.
I know you wouldn't want to eat,
but you should.
Are you still angry at me?
Or do you feel better?
So you're aware that you made me mad.
I think I have a knack for that.
Making people angry.
I think you have a knack
for making people turn around and stare.
Is it because you're pretty?
How can you smile right now?
You have a knack for that too.
I wanted to say I'm very sorry
for what I have done.
I didn't even know
how to apologize properly.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what your story is,
and I haven't lived
such a righteous life either,
but I do know this.
When you want to get what you want,
you first have to become strong.
So you have to eat first.
I'm here as your guardian,
so you have to listen to me
while you're at the hospital.
You have a knack
for making people speechless.
I gave it a thought
after I heard what you said yesterday,
and I got very frustrated with myself.
What do I really want?
That's also for you to find out
on your own.
Who do I think I am to give her advice?
She's really clumsy too.
Why did she take my phone?
[Punk]
[I'm worried about you.]
[Are you sure
you aren't worried about In-hyung?]
[Punk]
[Options, delete]
[Delete message]
Hello?
Who drove?
["Who-joon's Song Leakage Captures
Everyone's Attention Online"]
What will you do about the leakage?
I already sent out a news release
saying it's just the demo version.
We still have time to consider
releasing that song.
Are you sure it wasn't Lee Geun-young?
-Definitely not.
-"Definitely"?
How can you trust an anti-fan?
If you think about it,
she was a woman who went around
meeting reporters saying that
she'll expose Joon's female relationships.
That was a misunderstanding.
I believe they built trust
as they worked on the variety show.
-But still, keep a good eye on her.
-Yes, sir.
I did everything I can to stop Joon
from running amok to this day,
so I can't let him
get involved with a woman.
-Don't let him do anything weird. Okay?
-Yes, sir.
Call some reporters
and patch up this mess.
So where's Joon?
Why are you here? Where is he?
Hello?
Yes. Hello.
Where have you been...
Are you okay?
You must've been worried sick.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
You looked as if you were worried.
Are you all right?
Don't ever do this again.
Do what?
Going around doing this alone?
Or leaking your song?
You knew
I was the one who leaked it, right?
It may seem like an excuse,
but once the song got leaked,
I hoped people would become
a little interested in who I am.
But in the end,
no one showed me any interest.
Don't take it that way.
You sang the song very well.
I guess it wasn't all that bad
since I got your attention.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for you and Geun-young.
I really had no idea
people would take it out on her.
I know.
I told her I was sorry,
then she got angry.
But she still seemed cool.
She had the guts to say what she wants.
I can't do that.
You used to be like that too.
Really?
I don't remember
what I was like before.
I guess only you remember
what I was like back then.
I haven't called Jae-joon.
Get well soon.
I got jealous of Geun-young.
She saved your name as "Punk."
But you saved me as "Stranger."
That's depressing.
I sent you that text before.
She took the wrong phone.
Really? Was it really Who-joon?
Definitely. And that anti-fan.
I thought I saw someone
who looks like her,
but I figured she just looks similar.
Then I saw someone
who looked like Who-joon.
It's tough to tell regular people apart,
but celebrities look very charismatic.
Chief.
I think I got us a big scoop.
[Jae-joon]
Geun-young, why are you here?
Something came up, so I had to come.
What brings you here?
You were with In-hyung?
The hospital called me, actually.
I was the last person to talk to her.
Why didn't you call me?
I was really out of it too.
You should hear me out first.
I don't know what In-hyung said,
but I need to see her now.
So please try to understand.
I don't get why everyone says
I should understand anything.
I don't want to
get between you two either.
So could you just go home and wait?
I'm sorry. I can't do that.
Wait, hey. Let me go in first, then.
I'll have to talk to her first, and...
She might be too surprised.
I got to meet everyone here.
How did you know about this?
The hospital called me first,
I think it's because I was the one
she talked to last.
I told you about that, right?
I didn't know what to do,
so I called Who-joon.
Geun-young, you should've called me first.
I was really flustered too.
And you happened to call me
right at that time.
Right?
You don't have to try so hard, Geun-young.
Things somehow ended up like this.
But I don't think
that's what's important right now.
"Somehow"?
[Stranger]
She's somehow your speed dial one.
This isn't important?
You just found out
your girlfriend is at the hospital.
Don't you get what's important?
Shouldn't you be worried about her first?
That sounds like
you think I don't worry about her.
Do you think you're the only one
who worries about her
and runs over at once?
That's enough, both of you.
What's going on?
People must've talked about you.
Reporters are in the lobby.
Sounds great.
Let's expose everything with this chance.
Do you really want that?
You should all leave.
I'm sure no one cares that I'm here.
In-hyung, just be quiet.
Ji-hyang, for now,
-please let Geun-young leave first.
-Then what?
Then how about this?
I wonder if she left all right.
Stop worrying about others.
You made me worry about her first.
It looks like
she left without any trouble.
Will you be okay?
I can just lie in bed,
eat when I get hungry,
and sleep when I get sleepy.
The easiest task in the world.
Worrying doesn't suit you.
You make me worried.
Hey, Reporter Choi.
Thanks a lot. I'll be there soon.
Okay.
Thanks, Geun-young.
I'll pick you up tomorrow.
Let's go. Time to talk to the reporters.
Okay.
Bye.
-There's Who-joon.
-Hey.
Who-joon, why were you here?
Who was hospitalized?
Ms. Lee Geun-young was just hospitalized.
She was highly stressed due
to the misunderstanding of the song leak.
She's under a lot of stress,
so she needs absolute rest at the moment.
Please go back.
Ms. Lee is the key suspect
for the leak of that song.
Are you saying it wasn't her?
No. I never took the song to the set,
and I never had her listen to it.
There was no reason for her to leak it,
and she had no means to.
We came to apologize to her
for getting criticized
and framed because of our affair.
We lifted the misunderstanding,
so please do not attack Ms. Lee
for this song leak scandal,
because she isn't responsible.
Please excuse us.
-Do you know who did it?
-Who's responsible?
-Share your opinion on this!
-Is there a possibility
-she'll be cut from the show?
-Do you have anything to say?
I thought you disappeared. But you didn't.
You hoped I'd disappear,
so were you startled to see me here?
If I knew you'd let me go,
then I would've disappeared.
No matter how much you try to disappear,
someone hears about you.
No matter how hard I try
to keep you separated,
you somehow end up
getting connected to somebody.
You've been
staying in touch with him like this?
"Stranger."
A number that I'm a stranger to?
We didn't stay in touch.
I just had his number on my phone.
Why? Why would you?
Why would you keep his number?
Right, if you left him as speed dial one,
did you think you would get in touch
with that someone before you die?
Aren't you sick
of having this conversation?
It's not like he cares.
Why? Because his heart
seems to belong to someone else?
Because someone else seems
more important to him?
Are you offended?
That's enough!
What's enough? I've had enough of you!
Yes, we've had enough of this.
Let's terminate the contract,
and let's put an end
to our relationship too.
Put an end to it?
Hey, you only feel sorry for Joon,
don't you?
You were always like that.
You only take what you want from me.
Right, and I gave this another thought.
I can't let you go that easily.
So don't ever do anything rash like that.
As I said before,
no matter what you choose to do,
it'll be the wrong decision.
You!
My gosh, you throw these at me
even when I come in.
What the heck have you been doing?
Did you see the news? I patched it up.
Why were you at that hospital?
Are you In-hyung's guardian?
No, I said it's Geun-young.
You haven't read it.
How dare you try to deceive me?
I thought you'd come to yourself
and work hard once In-hyung is gone.
Will you get a grip
after she disappears from this industry?
Go ahead. And see what I'll do.
It's not like you did anything right.
Stop talking like that.
Stop treating us like objects
that'll disappear once you abandon us.
Right. Aren't you afraid
of being forgotten too?
That's what happens to entertainers.
Get it?
Those of you who whine and say
your life is too tough
and you have no freedom
will miss those days
once they're forgotten by everyone.
So pull yourself together.
One day, we'll realize what it's like
to truly keep oneself together.
That idiot.
Will I really miss everything
once I'm completely forgotten?
[Unknown Caller]
I know it's you, so speak.
I can't believe you called me
on this number.
[I should save your number too.]
You two kept in touch
by using a different number?
Why? Were you hoping
In-hyung would return to you?
Do you feel that unconfident
about your girlfriend?
I picked up what you abandoned,
then you'd pick up what I abandoned.
[If the world found out,
they'd have a good laugh.]
Let me make myself clear once again.
If you'll treat her like that, then...
Then what will you do?
I won't let you drag me around anymore.
I dragged you around?
You two did that to me to this day.
You need to stop this too.
I tried my best to understand you,
but if you'll be like this,
then there's no reason
for me to do that anymore.
I don't care if it's this number
or the other one,
but if I need you, I'll call you first.
[So I Married the Anti-Fan]
[-I think you're going a little too fast.
-Wait. Stop the car.]
[-Stop it. Stop the car!
-Okay, I'll stop.]
[-Stop! Step on the brake!
-I am stepping on the brake.]
Having fun?
I'm all done.
What was that?
You're still here.
Of course not.
It's really late. Let's go.
Let me walk you out.
What is this? Show me the final edit.
Don't you trust me? Let's go.
-How can I trust you?
-Let's go.
How would I trust you?
Goodness.
[Anti-fan hospitalized]
Okay. Let's just consider this
as the best decision for everyone.
But Geun-young, next time,
you need to learn to stay quiet.
Things can go well without you.
I'm bored, sleepy,
and I want to go home. Gosh.
Yes?
-Pizza delivery.
-Pizza?
Right, I never ordered pizza.
Then
did you order me?
How did you get in?
Are the reporters gone?
They all left when I did.
You must be hungry. Have some pizza.
I was so hungry. How did you
come up with such an endearing idea?
You can't just end it there.
You have to pet my head.
But I was craving tteokbokki.
-I...
-I chose the wrong menu, right?
Then should we make a run for it?
Make a run? Really?
Okay. Let's get you changed.
Are you crazy?
Get changed. I won't look.
What? Get out. Get out of the room.
I won't look.
My gosh.
Home sweet home.
You look as if you own this place.
I probably know
more about this place than you.
Except for the second floor.
Do you want to come with me?
-Really?
-It's not a big deal.
Come.
Really?
Are you that thrilled?
-What?
-This changes every single day.
Wait, what?
You kept this room so hidden
just to play games?
Hey, do you know how rare this is?
This is awesome.
This is a huge blow as a reporter.
A huge blow? Take a look.
Can you see those?
-I mean...
-These have years of history.
As a reporter,
this is a huge disappointment.
-Woodcraft?
-I did it myself.
-Really?
-A rabbit.
You're really good.
You were so cute.
Don't I look the same?
This boy grows up into Who-joon.
Little rascal.
Is that your mother?
Yes.
She's really beautiful.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
You've done well today.
You must've been startled. I didn't know
Jae-joon would do that around you.
I'm sure he was flustered too.
Anyway, the three of you were
once so close.
We were once like that.
And we thought it'd last forever.
We thought we'd all make it
and become huge celebrities.
But you made a debut first?
I only made my debut,
but no one knew me at first.
I had no idea
the fake life that Young-suk scripted
would become so deeply loved by everyone.
You three were so close.
What happened?
Everything Young-suk wanted to do
became a big success,
so the agency
began to put all of their focus on me.
Then Jae-joon and In-hyung's debut
slowly got postponed.
They held out for a long time,
then Jae-joon said
he wanted to make an agency himself
and asked me to come with him.
But I
couldn't do that.
Why not?
I know. That's why
I'm asking you for an understanding.
Just a few days. I'll pay the rest
of the hospital fee in a few days.
What? Postpone the operation?
I thought the operation
needs to be done now.
Then do you expect me
to take my sick kid out of the hospital?
Hello? Hey.
He bet everything he had for everyone
even though
he couldn't pay for his kid's hospital.
I couldn't do that to him.
Why didn't you tell Jae-joon?
Then things wouldn't have
come down to this.
You should've told him.
They were already determined to leave.
I thought they'd feel like
I'm pressuring them not to go.
That's why I couldn't.
Do you think he did it on purpose?
Did Jae-joon hate you so much,
then end up with In-hyung...
I doubt it.
I'm sure things were tough for them too.
Then they probably depended on each other.
I suddenly had to go overseas a lot,
so it must've been hard for In-hyung.
What's wrong?
I think I felt too relaxed to be home.
I suddenly got sleepy.
I'll get to bed first.
[What if In-hyung wants to return?]
[I couldn't bring myself to ask you that.]
[When you become anxious,]
[you make me afraid.]
[I don't want to lose anybody anymore.]
[Shooting Star]
Hello? Mr. Seo.
[Geun-young, where are you?]
Right, I actually came home.
[With Joon, right?]
By any chance, is he there?
No, he left after dropping me off.
He's not home, and he can't be reached.
What do you mean, he can't be reached?
Well, I think Joon got abducted.
Abducted?
Mr. Seo.
Did you two have a drink last night?
A little. I'm sure he took the taxi.
I think I saw that on the CCTV footage.
But I can't see the license plate.
And this was his last text message.
[Universal Star, Joon!]
[I got abducted by a fan. The ca...]
The police will find him, right?
I asked them
to keep the investigation private.
If they demand a ransom,
it means he was abducted.
But what's odd is that
his ransom hasn't been demanded.
Please contact us right away
when you hear anything.
We'll ask around a little more.
-Thank you.
-Please find him.
This is bad. I need to cancel
his schedule and keep people quiet.
Are you going to keep it a secret?
Yes, this is too big.
If we don't hear from him by tomorrow,
the search may turn public.
You should go home and get some rest.
I'll look around his house some more.
No, I'll come with you.
Okay. Let's go, then.
I hope we find him soon.
He said it's a fan, so...
Wait, this cap.
Were these caps sponsored?
No, it was sent to his home.
The sender was unknown,
so he wasn't very sure about this.
I think I've seen this cap before.
I've seen this cap among his fans.
What?
Ca. It's "ca."
"Ca"?
Caps. Was he texting you about these caps?
It got cut off at "ca".
[I got abducted by a fan. The ca...]
Do you think this girl abducted him?
The one who was wearing this cap
wasn't a woman. One second.
-Yu-ri!
[-Geun-young.]
Why do you ignore my texts?
You've seen this cap, haven't you?
[Yu-ri]
That's the cap this guy always wears,
this guy among Joon's fans.
[He said he was going to give him one,
and he did.]
Do you know who this guy is?
[He's really famous
as an avid fan among the fans.]
[A male fan for a male star.]
[And not many male fans always show up
at fan events and meetings.]
Why? Is the TV station
looking for a male fan?
Will they get to be on TV?
Can you just tell them I'm a guy?
No, it's not like that. Don't worry.
Do you know his name or phone number?
Well.
[Right, he said
he works part-time as a courier]
[Yu-ri]
before he gets a real job.
[So he said
we should give him Joon's gifts,]
[TG Courier]
[then he'll have those
delivered safely to him.]
Okay, Yu-ri. Thanks a lot.
Don't you think
he might be working in this company?
Let's go.
Grab the cap.
-What did they say?
-He went out to work today.
The police confirmed his house was empty.
We should look around his area.
Let's go.
Do you think he abducted him
for not wearing the cap?
Even so, how can he abduct him
over something like that?
The world is like that now.
Let's just hope nothing bad will happen.
I shouldn't have let him go yesterday.
This wouldn't have happened
if he didn't go out at that hour.
Don't be hard on yourself.
It's not your fault.
You're helping us out greatly.
If it hadn't been for you,
we wouldn't have found that courier.
Excuse me, is this the parcel
you were to receive?
I already got it this afternoon.
Sorry.
Let's try this one.
I don't think he got here yet.
[TG Courier]
Isn't that the company?
That's the one.
What's that?
I don't think it's them.
Let's give it some time.
That's the same company.
[TG Courier]
That man.
It's him.
Hello, are you Ms. Kim Da-hyeon?
-Yes.
-Is this you?
-I think it's him, but...
-I need you to check.
-One second.
-Please check.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
Hey, Joon!
Okay.
Let's go.
You must've been shocked.
First off, the parcel you got is
for you, right?
You have to check your name.
It can't go to someone else.
The one who sent you that parcel
sent me as a part of the delivery.
And he told me to make sure
to tell you this.
He left me something romantic,
saying he only wants to look at one woman,
and that he wants to protect her.
Isn't that romantic?
Should we find out
who this romantic guy is?
-Yes!
Okay, then. Please give him a big hand.
Da-hyeon, will you marry me?
You have to put it on me, Do-yeong.
Do I have to wear it myself?
Right.
My gosh.
You won't find another guy like him.
Da-hyeon, it looks like
you found yourself a great guy
who'll stand by your side
when life gets tough.
It's Who-joon!
♫ I wonder what is love ♫
♫ I wanna know what is love ♫
♫ That sweet flavor ♫
♫ But what is this dark flavor? ♫
♫ I wonder what is love ♫
♫ There's no answer
to this sweet question ♫
♫ But still, I'm falling in love ♫
♫ Oh-oh ♫
♫ Love hid somewhere ♫
♫ But from the moment I met you ♫
♫ My love gets bigger and bigger ♫
♫ So there's no way I can hide it ♫
♫ Whenever I think of you ♫
♫ I begin to wonder if this is love ♫
♫ I think I like you ♫
♫ I do, yeah, I do ♫
♫ I wonder what is love ♫
I thought you'd decline if I just asked,
so I did this without thinking.
She's a huge fan of yours.
We went to your concerts together,
then I ended up becoming a fan too.
I'm a guy who doesn't have much,
but I wanted to give her
a proposal to remember.
I can't believe you helped me.
I'm so sorry, and thank you.
Thank you.
Don't mention it. I hope
you two will be happy for a long time.
Let's go.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
Bye.
He abducted me, then said sorry,
and begged me to help him,
so what can I do? I couldn't help it.
I'm sorry I didn't call.
I was going to do it,
then return home quickly.
Be quiet.
I'm sorry.
Get a good rest.
You too.
It must've been a tough day, Mr. Seo.
Bye.
You must've been worried.
-Why?
-I mean,
it's how you look.
Never mind. Get a good rest.
Let's go, Ji-hyang.
-Bye.
What about my face?
You shocked me so much today
that I probably became three years older.
[The way you looked made me concerned,
so I didn't want to go.]
[Will you be home?]
[Let me make up with Ji-hyang first.]
[Jae-joon]
Hello?
What?
Are you still angry?
Do you really have
nothing else to say to me?
-Tell you what?
-About you and Geun-young.
Joon, you aren't obligated
to share your love life with me.
But you need to tell me
how you feel about her.
I don't know
how much I'm allowed to intervene.
I shouldn't make a mistake.
It's not like you were cautious before.
Not to you. I mean to Geun-young.
Things became awkward between us again.
I guess so.
I shouldn't have asked to see you.
It must be uncomfortable
to be here with me.
I'm sorry. That's not the case.
But it was a bit confusing.
I hope I'm not bothering you.
Do you do this for In-hyung?
You're such a nice guy. I wondered
why In-hyung always looked gloomy.
The Jae-joon I saw at the hospital,
was not the Jae-joon I knew.
I'm mistaken, right?
You weren't completely mistaken.
Do you want some soju?
This might sound funny,
but that's what I thought too.
Joon probably thought
I've been abusing In-hyung.
Then what about him?
Not only is he in my girlfriend's memory,
he even stayed in touch.
Is that something I should let go of?
But they said nothing is going on
between them now.
-You might have overreacted...
-Do you believe them?
Maybe this is why I liked you.
You trust what people say.
I thought you might trust me too.
But
you've changed a lot.
Like everyone else,
you only have your ears opened for Joon.
It's not like that.
Then,
can we continue to be friends?
I'm a very simple-minded person.
You three seem to have years of history,
so I don't want to get into that
without knowing the whole story.
I don't want to make any mistakes either.
I just wanted you to know that.
Okay.
I'm sorry you got involved in this mess.
Anyway, let's go. I'll take you home.
I'm a friend,
but I don't even know where you live.
Why should you know where I live?
No, that's not what I meant.
You need a chauffeur anyway.
Let's have our last glass,
then go home on our own.
-Okay. Right.
-Cheers.
Joon.
You're a universal star.
Try to be careful.
Be careful with what?
I'm going to get some rest at home.
And I'm going to Japan
early tomorrow morning.
Once I get back,
let's go see those men in that group.
Right, yes. Have a safe trip.
-Okay. Go home, then.
-Okay. Bye.
Gosh, my shoelaces came undone.
Okay, Ji-hyang. Bye!
Why are you here?
Ji-hyang will be worried.
I told you to stay home.
Where have you been? I was worried.
Do I have to report back on everything?
Yes, you do. On every single move.
Forget that. Get in the car.
Where are we going?
Just trust me and come.
Okay.
Are you sure you can travel this far?
You should've gotten some rest today.
Why can't I?
I meant to come here for some time,
but I couldn't for a while.
You said you had to make up with Ji-hyang.
You put him through so much all day.
You'll make him worried again.
I came out because of you.
You know,
it's great to get some air out here.
That's not what I meant.
Ji-hyang is going to be worried again.
Are you my mom?
Why do you nag at me so much?
Even my mom wasn't this bad.
I was just worried.
You were worried? How?
Did you cry when you heard I disappeared?
Cried? Why would I cry?
Anyway, I told you to go home.
Where have you been?
I just went out.
What? You're avoiding my question.
Are you my dad?
Why do you want to know everything?
Even my dad didn't pry this much.
You won't let anything go.
Anyway, can you actually catch fish here?
My gosh, you're full of complaints.
You have to wait a while
when you come out to fish.
It's the beauty of waiting.
I really don't get it.
There are millions of things
we need to wait for.
What else do you wait for?
We have lots of things to wait for.
Life is full of things to wait for.
A top star like you wouldn't know.
For example,
you wait for your promotion at work.
You wait to buy a house
after years of saving money.
And you wait for someone
who'd love you with all their heart...
Anyway, so you brought me here
to teach me the art of waiting?
So? Are you waiting for anything?
No.
Don't you know what today is?
What is it?
You make me feel awkward
if you look so hopeful.
It's not a big deal.
Episode three of our show gets aired.
What?
That's something
that I've never waited for.
I can't believe
this day came around again.
But still.
It's better than watching it alone.
You'll be stressed out watching it alone.
Let's watch it together.
I don't need to.
Okay.
[Three, two, one.]
[Now, shall we go, Geun-young?]
-This feels like yesterday.
-I'll be a gentle driver.
[Okay.]
Wait, this is that day.
[Geun-young, wait.
You're going a bit too fast.]
[Urgent]
[Wait. Stop the car.]
[-Wait. Slow down!
-Step on the brake.]
[-Step on the brake!
-The brake!]
[I am stepping on the brake.]
I can't believe this got on camera.
[Their lips got in an accident.]
That was just an accident!
How can they put this on air?
[Kiss]
[Did you get hurt?]
This will turn into huge trouble.
How can you laugh right now?
I'm about to be criticized again.
Well, you wouldn't know how I feel.
My gosh, Mr. Han, you're a loony!
I'm going to call him.
Stop that.
Geun-young.
This one's not an accident.