(The start of the end of
The Penthouse 3 by keymen)
(It's my first time.)
(The unpredictable world of The Penthouse)
(It's crazy.)
(The three secretaries are appearing.)
(Just enough spoiler)
(Just enough suspense)
(Just enough push and pull)
(Revealing all the charms)
(New type of talk show...)
(by the kids of The Penthouse continues.)
(Revealing their real singing skill)
(And)
(The whole story of The
Penthouse 3 slowly reveals.)
(The footage of The Penthouse
3 is revealed for the first time.)
(Please send us lots of love.)
(The Penthouse 3 Hidden Room,
The Start of the End begins now.)
The Penthouse 3 Hidden
Room, The Start of the End.
I'm your host, Jang Do Yeon.
(Jang Do Yeon)
- I'm Jo Jung Sik. - Hello.
In The Penthouse 3 Hidden Room today,
we're going to talk about...
the start and the end...
of The Penthouse.
The Penthouse 3 Hidden
Room, The Start of the End.
First, it's "Back to the Beginning".
There were flashbacks throughout the drama.
We collected all the flashbacks...
and created new footage.
It is The Penthouse Youth Theater.
- Youth Theater. - Let's watch.
(The Penthouse Youth Theater)
(The story of their
youth through flashbacks)
- Back in high school. - Yes.
(Seoul, 1996)
- It goes back to 1996. - Stop! Stop!
You need to project!
(One father and daughter had an
extraordinary passion for music.)
Don't you know how
important this audition is?
It's an opportunity to sing with
the best opera company in Italy.
They only wanted to see Yoon
Hee, the top student in the school,
but I forced your way in.
I'll practice more, Father.
I can do it.
Are you weeping because I nagged a little?
You know I can't stand seeing chicks cry.
Do it again!
(Everything her father said was
absolute law to Cheon Seo Jin.)
The trauma to be the top.
(After the audition)
How did it go?
- Who made it? - This music is playing.
Loser.
You can't beat her even once?
Then...
is Yoon Hee going to Italy?
- My. - I can't allow that.
(Yoon Hee with the skill
and Seo Jin with power)
We arranged it to say
Yoon Hee turned them down.
After what I did to get
you in, you almost lost it.
What a disgrace.
- I'm sorry. - Let's go.
(Seo Jin couldn't meet
her father's expectations.)
She wants her father
to approve her the most.
(The big day)
(The day of Cheong A Art Festival
to get into Seoul National University)
(Yoon Hee, the top student
shows off what she's capable of.)
- She never makes a mistake. - Yes.
She's the center of S.E.S.
(She finishes her performance
with cheer and applause.)
The highlight of the 25th
Cheong A Art Festival.
The grand prize winner
for the best classical singer.
The Bella Voce Award goes to...
- Cheon Seo Jin! - My.
(An incomprehensible result is announced.)
What? The grand prize?
- How could you win when you were...
- It's the prelude to war.
Unstable and your voice cracked?
Did you think you'd always win first place?
This is mine.
- Give it to me. - Let go!
(No one can yield.)
This is where the whole story begins.
That's right.
(There's an intense fight over the trophy.)
When I first watched this
drama, this scene was shocking.
(Yoon Hee can barely
get close to the trophy.)
No!
The trophy looks so dangerous.
Yes. It's got a pointy end.
I will never let you take this.
(That's how their worst
ill-fated relationship begins.)
You pitiful brat.
- What? - The fake winner, Cheon Seo Jin.
You're just a darned thief.
It's scary to watch it again.
(Seo Jin whose pride is hurt ends
up wounding Yoon Hee's neck.)
Look at her face.
- That reminds me of Eun Byeol. - Right.
It keeps reminding me
of Eun Byeol and Ro Na.
(Only if they had met in an environment...)
(where the competition wasn't so fierce.)
- Seo Jin! - Seo Jin!
- What happened? - Seo Jin!
The lyrics sound different.
(They could've been good friends.)
You can get up now.
(The investigation shows
that Seo Jin fabricated it.)
Fathers all know if they're
sleeping or just pretending.
Fathers always say they're not sleeping.
Yoon Hee bled a lot from her neck.
I'm sorry, Father.
- My. - Boy.
Father.
Do you know why I slapped you?
Not because you hurt a brat like her.
It's because you lost to her.
Your father is the director
of the Cheong A Foundation.
And yet, you lost to
a girl with no father...
and made me go and beg the judges...
to give you the Grand Prize.
Her father is turning her into a monster.
I'm sorry, Father. It's my fault.
This can never happen again.
You must be the best.
Or you don't deserve to take
over Cheong A Foundation.
Okay.
I will be the best.
She ended up hurting her neck...
I can't believe this music is playing.
I feel so bad for her.
She won't be able to sing anymore.
She was the top student
for three years straight.
But now, she's hit rock bottom.
It's Chelsia Chan's song.
Does that mean she won't
be able to go to college?
(They end up walking different paths.)
(Meanwhile in Japan)
Is it Japan?
(Na Ae Gyo, Joo Dan Tae's girlfriend)
(Joo Dan Tae, Na Ae Gyo's boyfriend)
Joo Dan Tae doesn't have much yet.
I'll make sure that you
live like Shim Su Ryeon.
For how much longer do I have to wait?
It won't be long.
If I use Shim Su Ryeon's name right,
we'll become so rich that we could
suffocate under our piles of money.
He talks about such a scary plan...
- with such a naive face.
- I'll buy a house in Gangnam,
and build a Joo Dan Tae Village...
on the land where my
mother has passed away on,
and make the whole world kneel before me.
And we'll have children?
Of course.
Just thinking about it makes me so happy.
(They plan to steal other's
life for their happiness.)
(Should they be thankful?)
(Is this what love is?)
It's Oh Yoon Hee's song.
(As the first step of his plan, )
- When she was a k-pop singer. - I like it.
(Joo Dan Tae plans a
marriage with Shim Su Ryeon.)
- I'll get this gift-wrapped. - Okay.
(Joo Dan Tae plans a
marriage with Shim Su Ryeon.)
He's marrying Shim Su Ryeon, not Na Ae Gyo.
You're right.
Su Ryeon, what is it? I'm
surprised you called me first.
I feel happy.
Are you coming back for summer break?
My parents are mentioning
our marriage and...
Let's call off the marriage.
That's cruel.
What did you just say?
- These are all great songs. - I'm...
getting married soon in the States.
(Dan Tae got dumped.)
I'm sorry, Dan Tae.
Hello?
(However, the plan goes wrong.)
With the wrong method...
Yes, he comes up with a scary plan.
Who says you can?
(He plans one scary incident to marry her.)
Who says you can call it off?
Is it possible for a human
to become that wicked?
(Several months later in the USA)
(Su Ryeon's spending a pleasant
time with the man she loves.)
She's pregnant.
(Su Ryeon's spending a pleasant
time with the man she loves.)
It's sad since I know
what's going to happen next.
(There are so many
things I should not love)
(Dan Tae decides to punish Su
Ryeon for choosing someone else.)
(What upsets him the most is...)
How cruel.
(You who don't love me)
(I didn't ask you to stay by my side)
(You didn't have to call off our marriage.)
The flashbacks show the reasons...
- why they've become monsters. - Yes.
(And)
There must've been a problem
with her brain due to premature birth.
(Su Ryeon ended up giving
premature birth due to shooting.)
It's my fault.
(The moment Dan Tae had
been waiting for has arrived.)
It's all my fault.
Don't blame yourself.
I'll take care of your child now.
(While Su Ryeon became
weak due to shock and sadness...)
Now that I'm watching in order,
I can see the change in their looks.
- It's fun to watch the compilation. - Yes.
(Meanwhile, after high school, )
(Yoon Hee got a job right away.)
It feels like an archive.
(Ha Yoon Chul, Yoon Hee's boyfriend)
(She's in love with a
poor medical student.)
I got my salary.
Pay for your lodgings.
- Oh Yoon Hee and Ha Yoon Chul.
- I don't want to.
Stop giving me money.
- What an adorable couple.
- I'm giving it to you to feel good,
so you don't have to feel bad. It's true.
It's not much anyway. Take it.
I'll become a doctor as soon as I can...
and support you.
They haven't met Cheon
Seo Jin yet, have they?
(Even poverty felt romantic to
them because they were in love.)
Cheon Seo Jin sees them now.
She gets jealous.
(Their ill-fated relationship
with Cheon Seo Jin begins again.)
(Seo Jin still feels inferior to Yoon Hee.)
Dad, it's me.
About the next Cheong
A Foundation scholarship.
I want to recommend someone
who is studying medicine.
(Yoon Chul became a scholarship student...)
(with Seo Jin's recommendation.)
Holding onto the end
of the night It's no longer
What's going on? Did you get the
Cheong A Foundation scholarship?
(Yoon Hee doesn't like it.)
Why didn't you tell me?
I couldn't refuse to attend
when they gave me a scholarship.
It doesn't mean anything.
Do you call that an excuse?
You being involved with Cheon Seo Jin...
I hate that more than death!
Will you stop talking about Cheon Seo Jin?
Just stop it.
I'm sick of it now!
Their relationship falls
apart as Seo Jin intended.
The conflict deepens.
- That's what Seo Jin wanted. - Yes.
(Love...)
(and reality)
(The young medical student's woe grows.)
- This scene. - Oh, this scene.
- Cheon Seo Jin's really annoying. - Yes.
Stop drinking.
(Yoon Chul has a drink with
Seo Jin out of frustration.)
He drank a lot.
That's the old Jinro soju.
- I got too excited. - Darn it.
What else am I to do?
Studying must be hard enough.
Why do you want to live with such a burden?
(Yoon Hee sees Yoon
Chul and Seo Jin together.)
Oh, why on earth?
- Why did she have to pass it?
- Especially at that moment.
I will give you...
A pair of wings.
(Seo Jin suddenly confesses
her feelings to Yoon Chul.)
That sounds so sweet to
a self-supporting student.
I know. In fact, she's
the director's daughter.
(With rain and drinks in between)
How cruel.
(Seo Jin steals Yoon Hee's life again.)
Oh, this is the moment.
(You've left)
(And the rain is falling)
(To someone, it's an end.)
(To someone, it's a start.)
Oh, gosh. Why would you
wrap your arm around her?
Seriously.
(Youth and the start of the end)
(Time goes by)
(Over the years)
(A moment to achieve something arrives.)
Today,
(Seo Jin expects an important decision.)
You waited long enough. The foundation...
is yours, Seo Jin.
(She finally becomes the director
she's long been waiting for.)
- Finally. - He finally approves her.
It's what she's been waiting for.
Father.
It was Cheon Seo Jin's goal in life.
A halo.
- And fireworks inside the building. - Yes.
- When you're really happy... - Right.
- You're overwhelmed,
- you can't say anything.
But it's hard to describe it.
(The brightest moment
in her life has arrived.)
- It's hard to believe. - Yes.
Now she feels like eating.
(I'm just happy to think about it.)
Today,
the most wonderful thing happened to me.
Seo Jin and my husband
are having an affair.
(Soon, her affair with
Dan Tae is revealed.)
We must get divorced.
We can't.
Now, the whole Hera Club members know.
We can't stay together.
Chairman Joo Dan Tae.
(Yoon Hee also tries to threaten Seo Jin.)
What are you trying to pull?
Everyone already knows
about me and Dan Tae.
That's right.
But there's one person who doesn't.
(I don't know yet)
- "Dad." - Dad.
He wishes to appoint
someone else as the director.
(Seo Jin's father dismisses Seo
Jin from the director position.)
No. Father.
(Seo Jin runs to stop her father.)
What a good choice of a song.
Let go.
(She went out of her way
to take the best position.)
(Seo Jin could never lose it.)
(She confronts her father
who's become an obstacle.)
(Her father's on the verge
of life after the scuffle.)
- Seo Jin. - Grab him. You must grab him.
(Seo Jin turns her back on her father.)
Greed can be very scary.
(She exchanged her father
for the director position.)
You abandoned me...
first, Father.
(Seo Jin ends up killing her father.)
(Meanwhile, Joo Dan Tae)
She's the one...
he talked about the future with.
(He got this far all for Na Ae Gyo.)
(He ends up killing Na Ae
Gyo with his own hands.)
Who do you think she is?
(She was the goal of Dan Tae's life.)
(Na)
(Ae)
(Gyo)
(She's gone...)
(out of Dan Tae's life for good.)
It's "She's Gone."
(Dan Tae finally realizes the
person he killed was Na Ae Gyo.)
This is like a music video.
So, Na Ae Gyo...
is really dead?
I...
killed...
Na Ae Gyo?
You jerk.
(He cries for the perfect
future he shattered on his own...)
(and the sense of loss.)
(Due to the shadow singer incident, )
(Seo Jin faces voting
to be appointed again.)
(But she barely avoids
losing her position.)
She finally protected it.
- It was hard to believe the result.
- I know.
(What protected Seo Jin
was her father's favour.)
What favour?
My first daughter still
has a long way to go.
She is ambitious but lacks in many ways.
Support her.
So that she can keep her place as Director.
Yet, she killed her father.
Gosh. It's breaking my heart.
Father...
Why did you do that?
(Her father has gone to a
place he can never come back.)
(Seo Jin wanted her
father to approve her...)
(by winning the highest and best position.)
(Joo Dan Tae dreamed of a
happy future with Na Ae Gyo.)
(They both ended up killing the
most precious person in their lives...)
(for them and their lives.)
(And now...)
(Director Cheon Seo Jin)
(They've emptied their offices.)
- Bye, bye. - Bye.
Goodbye, Assemblyman.
Bye.
Goodbye, Kang Ma Ri's bathhouse.
Bye, Ms. Cheon.
(People who went to prison, Ha Yoon Chul)
(Lee Kyu Jin)
(Ko Sang A)
It was such an unexpected conclusion.
(Joo Dan Tae)
(Oh Yoon Hee)
(People who went back home, Shim Su Ryeon)
(People who went missing,
Jin Bun Hong and Eun Byeol)
(New appearances, Yoo Dong Pil)
(Baek Jun Ki)
Not many of them were
able to keep their places.
(Logan Lee had an explosion accident.)
(Find out what they will do in Season 3.)
Their lives are so ironic.
Both Joo Dan Tae and Cheon Seo Jin...
live for someone,
but they end up killing the
person with their own hands.
Like you said, they both
killed someone with their hands.
But there's another thing
they have in common.
Neither of them can do
anything on their own.
All they do is give orders.
The Penthouse would completely
stop without these three people.
You're right. They're at the beck
and call of the main characters.
It wasn't easy to bring all of them here.
I can't believe it. It feels unreal.
You rarely see them in one place.
Exactly.
The three secretaries are here.
- Nice to see you. - Welcome.
This is so exciting. I've
never met them before.
Didn't you shoot any scene
together in Seasons 1 and 2?
- We've never seen them together.
- This is the first time...
we've been on camera together.
The viewers would also think...
this is such a rare opportunity.
Hello, I play...
Secretary Hong, who works for
Logan. My name is Kim Jae Hong.
Hello, I play Secretary Do,
who works for Director Cheon Seo Jin.
My name is Kim Do Hyun.
Hello, I play Secretary Cho,
Joo Dan Tae's right-hand man.
My name is Kim Dong Kyu.
Your eyes are so sparkly.
Your eyes are really shiny.
You look like a little boy with a beard.
It might sound rude,
- but the thing is, - I know.
He looks so different
in real life. I'm shocked.
In real life,
- you look so innocent. - You look so kind.
I'm still in my 20s too.
- You are? - Yes.
(Shocked)
- What's that reaction? - Your beard...
It's because you beat older guys a lot.
I'm very polite in real life.
- You are. - That's right.
Who's the oldest then?
I was born in 1983.
- Secretary Cho was born...
- I was born in 1994.
- I was born in 1992. - 1992.
But their age doesn't really matter.
What matters in the Penthouse is
who has more money and power.
- That's right. - That's what matters.
Who has the most power then?
In the show, I used to
be in the special forces.
It's something I've come up with.
- It's a secret? - It's a secret.
I'm the only one who knows it.
These two have more powers than I do.
I even lose to Oh Yoon Hee and Bae Ro Na.
I get shoved aside by them.
Sometimes, I wonder if Secretary
Do has any muscular strength.
"Muscular strength?"
First things first.
We prepared a video that shows
the different work styles you have.
Let's watch it.
Excuse me! You're Logan
Lee's secretary, right?
I'm Logan Lee's secretary.
(Secretary Hong, User of
cutting-edge technology)
So you really are a special agent.
(Using high-tech devices, )
(he prepares thoroughly in advance.)
Everything is set, sir.
(The one who killed Min Seol A is in here.)
(He successfully threatens the
murder suspects of Min Seol A.)
(He uses even more advanced equipment.)
- That's incredible. - The fingerprint.
- It's your biggest accomplishment.
- It was the decisive move.
(He copied Joo Dan Tae's fingerprint.)
You're very proud of it.
That's just... It still makes me proud.
It's your only accomplishment.
(He always remains quiet.)
Oh Yoon Hee was also there on the night...
when the lighting ceremony took place.
(Secretary Hong relies
on high-tech equipment.)
Send this woman out.
- Secretary Do! - He sent you a bouquet.
- What? - Out of the blue?
The mood changed completely.
- Find out whom he met. - Yes, ma'am.
Find where this person is.
- Any other information? - There's none.
I'll make sure to find her
no matter what it takes.
- Find out by all means. - I will, ma'am.
He's like a sunflower.
My gosh.
Are you okay?
Why don't you call it a day?
You don't seem so well.
It's suddenly became a romance.
You were with me today...
and after that, you
were in the lesson room.
He's so cool.
You must pull yourself together.
(Because of one woman...)
He looks so cool.
This feels completely different.
(He lives another day.)
It's so romantic.
It's amazing.
(Mental and emotional care provider)
(Secretary Do, the man of loyalty)
My goodness.
Secretary Cho, come in. Come in!
- Secretary Cho. - Yes, sir.
(Secretary Cho, the tough guy)
He's the tough guy.
Move your car.
(From moving his boss's car...)
- That's how it all began. - No.
- Did you take care of it? - Yes, sir.
You stay right next to Joo Dan Tae.
(His specialty is violence.)
(He has beaten every man on
the show except for Dan Tae.)
(He is the strongest
fighter in The Penthouse.)
(When it comes to violence, )
(he never disappoints.)
(But apart from that...)
Why are you telling me that now?
She hasn't come back to the cottage.
- What is this? - It's the perfect song.
Are you an idiot?
Our stock plummeted today.
They definitely said it was taken.
You moron.
If you have the time to say
that, get out and look for her!
Who have you been following, you moron?
My gosh.
- Get out! - Yes, sir.
That moron.
He's so mean.
What is this?
I'm sorry, sir.
(Secretary Cho, the violent fighter)
(The story of the hidden heroes begins.)
Even though all three
of you are secretaries,
- your work styles totally differ.
- Absolutely.
It was so interesting to see
them next to one another.
A word that's still
ringing in my ears is...
- a "moron". - A "moron".
What did you think?
It's such a shame.
Why do I always mess up
when he can easily beat me?
- Just when he is about to flip...
- I tell him about my mistake.
You're not so tactful, are you?
It's just that I try to
keep my boss updated.
That's a good interpretation.
It's not easy.
- Are you athletic? - I'm pretty athletic.
You've beaten...
almost every man on the show...
except for Joo Dan Tae.
Yes, I have.
Will we get to see Secretary Cho...
beat Joo Dan Tae in season three?
(Well...)
If not, I'd get upset.
That would be Secretary Cho's last shoot.
But you never know what
will happen in The Penthouse.
Secretary Do's video was
so beautiful and touching.
What did you think?
I'm very satisfied.
- I'd love to get the file. - Really?
If I was Cheon Seo Jin,
I might have developed feelings for him.
In the show,
do you have personal
feelings for Cheon Seo Jin?
Not at all.
I blame the music.
It's not my intention at all.
- It totally gave us the wrong idea.
- Definitely.
- I totally got the wrong idea. - I know.
I'm just fond of Ms. Cheon as a person.
- You admire her. - Yes.
In the video, when Secretary Hong...
copied the fingerprint,
he looked so proud.
As if you really copied it yourself.
With the fingerprint aside,
there's a scene the viewers think is...
Secretary Hong's biggest accomplishment.
- Okay. - Can you guess what it is?
I have many accomplishments for sure.
Do you realize you sound very arrogant?
- He doesn't even try to be humble.
- He looks so arrogant.
I'd guess it's...
my contribution to the romance
between Logan and Shim Su Ryeon.
(Oh...)
- It's something else. - Goodness gracious.
It's when you reported to
Logan about Shim Su Ryeon,
- who was disguised as Na Ae Gyo.
- Oh, I see.
Logan told you you
could stop spying on her.
But then you started showing
him pictures slowly, one by one.
That's right.
One of the pictures was of a
handbag, which seems random.
Some suspected Secretary
Hong is a handbag collector.
But I have something shocking to tell you.
This should be in the preview.
Let us decide that.
- You're telling us how to edit?
- When we were shooting,
the pictures I showed him were...
(Are you...)
(ready...)
(for a shock?)
just green sheets of paper.
(Shock loading)
They were just green sheets of paper.
Seriously?
(So this is how variety shows work.)
The pictures I was showing him
one by one were sheets of paper.
The pictures were edited
in by the CG team...
- That's so interesting. - afterwards.
I had no idea there was
a picture of a handbag...
until I watched the show.
Secretary Hong, do you really
think this will be in the preview?
Almost every character
is in prison right now.
Doesn't that mean the
secretaries have bigger roles now?
All our bosses are in prison.
And we don't even know
if Secretary Hong's boss...
- is still alive. - Exactly.
But I'm sure they'll try
to find a way to get out.
Secretary Hong seems restless.
- He can't stop fidgeting. - I know.
In seasons 1 and 2,
Secretary Hong didn't appear...
- as much as the other two. - That's right.
If Logan Lee really disappears...
What are you talking about?
- He's going to cry.
- That's how season two ended.
- Don't make him cry. - That's why...
if Logan Lee leaves the show...
My gosh. That's...
(His reaction seems so real.)
His reaction feels so genuine.
Please don't say that.
Of course. I really hope we
can see him in season three too.
There's one important question.
Is Secretary Cho...
on Joo Dan Tae's side or
on Yoo Dong Pil's side?
The reason he stays with Joo Dan Tae...
might be related to Yoo Dong Pil.
It seems like many
people are taking guesses...
after the last scene where I greeted
Yoo Dong Pil outside the prison.
I'm very curious too.
I want to know...
Secretary Cho's intention
behind working for Joo Dan Tae...
and if he worked for
him from the beginning.
I'm curious.
There's something going on, right?
That's my guess.
About Joo Dan Tae's
trauma related to blood,
not many people seem to know.
On top of that,
he can't stand dirty shoes.
That's right.
If you pay attention to
that part in season three,
I'd be very happy.
I think it's time to ask this question.
Earlier...
- What did you do? - He made a heart.
Logan.
Instead of just making a heart,
I'll give you a chance...
- to say something properly... - Oh my.
- That sounds good. - to Logan.
If I get to say something to him...
"Please survive", for example.
Just the thought of Logan makes me tear up.
Seriously?
- He's acting. - No.
I was so shocked. He was really tearing up.
- I'm just joking. - He keeps doing this.
Please say something to him.
Logan. Logan?
(To Logan)
I can't figure out...
whether you're alive or dead now.
But I really hope you're alive.
If you come back alive and
I get to work for you again,
you can trust the competent Secretary Hong.
I'll take care of everything for you.
- Hypothetically speaking... - Okay.
If Logan somehow fails to come back alive,
it seems like Su Ryeon
doesn't have a secretary.
- You'd work for her instead? - So...
Ms. Su Ryeon.
I'm a competent man.
- I'm a hard worker.
- He's looking for a job.
He'd even work at Ma Ri Sauna.
(He can even work at Ma Ri Sauna.)
Right? Even if he doesn't get the job...
- With a towel around his head.
- We'd love to see you.
It's a women's bathhouse,
so it won't be easy.
I'm ready to do anything.
You should sell banana-flavoured
milk or something.
- Please stop. - I'm sorry.
I didn't know when to stop. I apologize.
The more I listen to him,
the more it seems like
he's talking to the writer,
- You're right. - Kim Soon Ok.
- Soon Ok, we love you. - We love you.
At the moment, we know nothing
about what's going to happen...
in season three.
We don't know how many episodes...
these three will appear in...
or if we'll get to see them at all.
- Secretary Hong sighed so deeply.
- Exactly.
Nothing is guaranteed.
So we'd like to give you a
chance to promote yourselves.
I'm suddenly feeling nervous.
You can do whatever you want.
- Right. - You can do impressions, dance,
do a monologue...
- A monologue?
- Secretary Hong did mention...
that he has many things to show us.
- I have 59.
- But we can't see all 59 of them.
I wasn't planning on doing all 59 of them.
What's the most popular one?
It's the radio show, "Cultwo Show".
The host is Kim Tae Kyun.
This is how he sounds
when he reads a story.
Okay.
"Hello. I live in Ilsan..."
- "and work for a company."
- He sounds just like him.
"I'm a 39-year-old man..."
Oh, it's a man.
(The details are perfect.)
When it's an older woman, "Hello."
Are you an actor or a comedian?
- I can do anything. - Really?
You're open-minded.
Look how open-minded I am.
He's opening his jacket.
I'm sure you've never seen...
- the next one. - Really?
I'll copy Jung Woo
Sung's facial expression.
Jung Woo Sung's facial expression.
It's just an impression.
I'm not saying I look like him.
The eyes are important.
(Jung Woo Sung loading)
(Complete)
(Oh!)
It's his smile.
- I've seen it.
- He looks exactly like him.
- I know what it is. - My gosh.
Goodness.
- I know what it is. - That's incredible.
- That's hilarious.
- You look exactly like him.
It's incredible, right?
Once you put on that expression,
you look just like Jung Woo Sung.
- Exactly. - This feels weird.
His eyes and nose look
exactly like Jung Woo Sung's.
I just gave it a try,
and many seemed to love it.
You look just like him.
You're funnier than most comedians.
He's so good.
I should work harder.
Would you like to wrap
things up nicely here...
or do you want to try some more?
It's been going well so far.
Hwang Je Seong has already done this.
It's Lee Kyoung Young
singing "Any Song" by ZICO.
There's this gesture he always does.
(He starts with his typical gesture.)
Why are you all so down?
(Hilarious)
What's the problem? Say something
- That's so funny. - He's really good.
- That's hilarious.
- Let me try Lee Kyoung Young...
playing Jung Woo Sung's role...
in "A Moment to Remember".
That sounds so funny.
That's an interesting twist.
If you drink this, we go out together.
You don't want to drink it?
I feel so lonely.
(Hilarious)
- That's it. - My gosh.
- Oh, my. - Nice job.
He's trying harder toward the end.
- I think that's it.
- That sounds good. It was perfect.
(Secretary Hong's
self-promotion ended successfully.)
- It's Secretary Do's turn now. - But...
- Secretary Do... - This is not good.
You must feel a little pressured.
We had actually decided on the order.
What was the original order?
- He was supposed to go last.
It's our mistake. We apologize.
Do better next time.
- Do better next time. - He's scolding us.
My goodness.
Between you two, who wants to go first?
I actually...
was going to do impressions...
- of the cast of The Penthouse.
- That sounds great.
But after seeing what
he did, I don't dare...
- Don't be like that. - Come on.
Why are you all so down?
Stop it.
Then I'll mix it with beatboxing.
- Okay. - That sounds great.
I'll start with Joo Dan Tae,
and move on to Cheon Seo Jin,
and to Ma Doo Ki.
Sure.
I'm so nervous.
(So far so good)
(Beatboxing)
[VIU Ver] SBS 'The Penthouse S03 Special'
"Hidden Room - The Start of the End"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
What on earth did she see?
(His impression of Joo
Dan Tae is a success.)
Oh Yoon Hee?
Is it really you?
(What am I hearing?)
(Back to beatboxing)
Bae Ro Na.
- Oh, my. - He sounds just like him.
You're so cheeky.
But I'm your homeroom teacher.
- That was amazing. - My gosh.
What was that in the middle?
"Oh Yoon Hee?"
- "Is it really you?" - "Is it really you?"
I can imagine him practicing this at home.
- I do. - He practices beatboxing.
Secretary Cho, will you be okay?
You must feel so pressured.
I don't have many things...
- to show you. - Okay.
But I wanted to do my best.
So I prepared "Rollin'",
which is so popular these days.
(Can he be this cute?)
"Rollin'"? That sounds awesome.
(Can he be this sexy?)
(The pressure is driving him crazy.)
I can't imagine Secretary
Cho dancing to "Rollin'".
(How will the boy with a
beard dance to "Rollin'"?)
I'll just do my best.
- Please enjoy it. - Of course.
I can't wait to see it.
(His facial expression
changes immediately.)
What is this?
Look at his face.
What is going on here?
Oh, my.
(He doesn't miss any move.)
(Are you watching?)
(This is the tough guy's ray dance.)
(He throws in some fancy steps.)
- Look at that. - Look at his steps.
(He finishes up with hearts.)
He prepared a lot.
Once the song started...
He changed completely.
He's a great dancer.
What do I do?
We've had so many funny moments today.
So many variety shows
will want Secretary Hong...
- as their guest. - Of course.
- I wish we had more time.
- You'll be seeing Do Yeon a lot.
Why is he doing this?
I'm old.
Don't sound so sad.
Everyone gets old.
(Laughing)
He keeps talking about his age.
You're still so young.
- Okay. - Right?
I wish we could talk to them a bit more.
- It was so fun. - Time went so fast.
Please say something to the viewers.
I'm so happy we got a chance...
to meet our viewers outside the show.
I hope you continue to enjoy our show.
- We'll do our best.
- Thank you for your support.
Show us Jung Woo Sung's smile again.
(Jung Woo Sung's smile one last time)
It's addictive. It's dangerous.
- I can't get enough. - Me neither.
We'll look forward...
to seeing the three of
them in season three.
Hi.
(The Penthouse kids played a
big part in the show's popularity.)
(Here they come!)
(I'll make your dream
come true on your behalf.)
(A natural talent)
(She patiently puts up with bullying.)
(But Bae Ro Na is branded
as a murderer's daughter.)
(Apart from his mean
personality, he is absolutely perfect.)
(He changes when he
meets his first love, Ro Na.)
(Joo Seok Hoon rebels against his father.)
(She inherited her mother's
obsession with first place.)
(Her inadequacy leads
to a mental breakdown.)
(Ha Eun Byeol, who is forever number two, )
(is determined to be number one.)
Welcome to your nightmare.
(The queen of Cheong A Arts
High School can't stand poverty.)
(On the inside, the soft-hearted
girl misses her mom.)
How dare you?
(Joo Seok Kyung, the troublemaker
who is both strong and weak)
You have to eat very balanced meals.
(The immature boy whose
parents are his biggest strength)
(With his credentials gone, Min
Hyuk starts caring about his parents.)
(The hidden story of the
Penthouse kids begins now.)
They're finally here.
If only I could share...
- my optic nerves with our viewers.
- I know.
Isn't it incredible?
- They should see them in real life.
- Exactly.
They look even better in real life.
Each of them...
really glows.
It feels different from
seeing them in the show.
None of you seem to deny it.
No one says, "That's not true."
- I know. - "That's not true."
- They all love themselves so much.
- The secretaries...
are watching.
By the way,
- you may wonder where Jenny is.
- She's missing.
She has an important performance...
at her school, not Cheong
A Arts High School,
but the one in real life.
That's why she couldn't make it.
I'm sure the five of
you can make up for it.
The Penthouse is extremely popular.
Has anything changed
since the show started airing?
Many things have changed.
But since we have to wear masks,
- I can't notice much of it.
- It's the pandemic's fault.
Did you know the show would be such a hit?
This was my first show,
so I couldn't really make any predictions.
When I read the script,
I was just shocked...
by Seok Kyung's personality.
Was this your début show?
Almost.
(It was her first main role.)
What are you going to do now?
(What?)
What do you mean?
- What I mean is...
- Because it became such a hit?
Her début show became such a big hit.
What about you, Min Hyuk?
I knew it was going to be a hit...
as soon as I read the script.
Since the story is so intense,
I thought it could add a little fun...
to the dull everyday life.
He sounds like a professor.
"The dull everyday life..."
- "The dull everyday life..."
- He sounds like a professor.
But he's always like that.
He's extremely calm in real life.
He's very mature.
- Thank you. - He's a genius.
There's something I really want to ask you.
Your parents must be so proud.
The people around them...
talk a lot about the show. It
makes my parents very proud.
I think I should try to be
more careful and humble...
at a time like this.
She smiles a lot in real life.
- She looks completely different.
- In the show, she glares at people.
Even before the cameras started rolling,
she was smiling the whole time.
I wondered if she was seeing things.
(Everyone claps their hands.)
She's so lovely.
You do smile a lot.
The Hidden Room crew analysed...
every scene of the Penthouse kids...
in seasons 1 and 2.
Surprisingly,
one of them...
turned out to be...
extremely materialistic and greedy.
Can you guess who it is?
(Seok Kyung raises her hand.)
Seok Kyung?
- No? I think it's me. - Seok Kyung.
If it's among us.
They think it's Seok Kyung.
- This is so real. - It's not me?
I heard that you didn't
see the script for today.
- That's right. - That's right.
So they don't know what we're going to do?
- They don't. - We don't.
- We have no idea. - We don't know.
All of you are going to
dance to "Rollin'" later.
- No! We didn't hear about that. - No!
(Do Yeon's scheme fails.)
I failed.
Please tell us.
Let's see if it's really Seok Kyung.
The typical materialist turns out to be...
Bae Ro Na.
- What? - Why?
- It's Ro Na. - Are you greedy?
Here's the proof. Let's watch it.
(Ro Na is full of anger.)
- She's very angry. - She's angry.
(Fierce)
(She often rebels against her mom.)
That's right.
It's from season one.
(The only way to make her laugh is...)
(I have presents for you.)
- She's so cute. - She's so cute.
How did you know?
She can't stop smiling.
(Excited)
(She automatically smiles.)
She couldn't be happier.
(She also gets irritated easily.)
She gets irritated easily.
She has mood swings.
(But presents can calm her down.)
That's right.
It's very easy to calm her down.
You're right.
Mom, I'm not dreaming, am I?
I'm proud of you.
(How could you call yourself human?)
You're disgusting! You creep me out!
- Wait a second. - She looks so happy.
You are materialistic.
The editing is so mean.
Even the song sounds so happy.
(Her mom used to creep her out.)
Yes, we're going to live here.
(Bae Ro Na's capitalistic smile)
- That was funny. - It was true.
The editing is so mean.
(It's the result of our analysis.)
Can you relate to your character?
Since this is the third season...
and we've been shooting for a long time,
it's easier to relate to Ro Na...
than my previous characters.
(Nodding)
Seok Hoon seems to be immersed in his role.
(Is he still immersed in his role?)
Say something.
- He's even dressed in black.
- He's dressed in black.
You could've worn a helmet too.
We were told to wear...
- bright, casual clothes. - That's right.
That's why we're wearing
these colourful clothes.
And he showed up in a black suit.
I didn't hear that.
Did you come straight from
the Baeksang Arts Awards?
Exactly.
How do you get into the role?
You must be more cheerful in real life.
I am.
That's it?
I didn't expect that.
- I see. - Okay.
Another reason for the
popularity of The Penthouse...
is the perfect acting.
Their excellent acting
definitely contributed...
to the show's popularity.
But the acting of one of
them was pretty embarrassing.
Can you guess who it is?
Is it me?
I was wondering if it was me.
Could it be literal?
(Seok Kyung lifts her foot.)
It must be me.
- We have proof. - We do.
Let's watch it together.
She used her feet a lot.
3, 2, 1, 5.2, 1, 3, 2.
(That's embarrassing.)
That's so embarrassing.
I'm wiggling my toes.
(I do everything with my feet.)
- She keeps using her feet.
- She's so charismatic.
- Look at that. - She's so cute.
(She moves her foot up and down.)
She looks so cute.
(This is how I act with my foot.)
With the background
music, she looks so cute.
(Watch this.)
(Here comes the ultimate foot acting.)
It must have been so
hard to shoot that scene.
(This time, she acts with her entire body.)
My goodness.
- That scene... - That was really...
It was really hard.
(Stop putting on an
act. You can't fool me.)
Oh, my.
(Seok Kyung's foot
acting gets a thumbs-up.)
It ended with a thumbs-up.
She can even express
emotions using her feet.
- I know. - It's incredible.
Did you try to pay more
attention to your feet?
It was the director's idea.
So it wasn't in the script...
but the director ordered you to do it?
Yes. He'd say, "How
about you put your feet up?"
He wanted me to look more rebellious.
At first, I was wearing socks.
And he wanted me to take them off.
So I put nail polish on my
toes a couple of days before.
The scene where you
fall in the water looks hard.
It was very cold.
After I fell in the water,
Young Dae came in to save me.
He came in floundering.
And I slipped.
- I ended up falling too. - That's right.
She said, "You should go out."
Seok Hoon is finally
getting out of his role.
When season three starts,
I'll pay extra attention
to Seok Kyung's feet.
- Let's see if there's more.
- Did I shoot more?
Can you act with your feet right now?
Please express your emotion right now.
- Well... - Show us how you feel.
No. I don't know what to do.
(Flapping)
I did it.
- I did it. - You did it?
I'm done.
Good job.
- By the way, Do Yeon, - Yes?
We should be careful with
what we do and say today.
- You're right.
- There's a secret agent here.
The secret agent is watching
us even at this moment.
Can you guess who it is?
Can you guess who the secret agent is?
- Not really. - I think this might be hard.
- Of the five of you... - I think...
Maybe not?
- The secret agent? - I'm not sure.
The secret agent is...
- Joo Seok Hoon. - I knew it.
- I got it wrong again.
- Oh, because I'm always watching.
Every time I cause trouble,
he comes running over,
and screams,
"Joo Seok Kyung!"
- You shocked the audio director.
- I'm sorry.
He thought you were quiet.
(Seok Hoon said something
for the first time in 10 minutes.)
I'm sorry.
Let's look at Joo Seok Hoon's
true nature for ourselves,
after he's infiltrated The Penthouse.
(Secret Agent, The Hoon Identity)
(Focused)
(Specialty 1, Boxing)
(Specialty 2, Stakeouts
and shadowing people)
That's right, that happened.
He was following Ro Na.
(Specialty 3, Monitoring the enemy)
- He's right there. - That's right.
- Isn't it like "Where's Willy?"
- This is too funny.
That's so scary.
Watching from above.
(Embarrassed)
(Specialty 4, Wiretapping)
Wiretapping.
- Isn't that when you saw Ro Na?
- Yes, it is.
(He is a team leader who is
smart and makes the right decision.)
Leave the group chat and block this ID.
And don't tell anyone.
That's right.
This part was so dashing.
(He can carry out his mission
perfectly no matter what.)
Min Seol A died in Hera Palace.
(Interrogating the suspect)
Isn't that right?
Are your memories back?
Why do I find that so cute?
(Hostage rescue)
Hostage rescue.
(He figured out the
escape route in advance.)
(He carries out the rescue
secretly and quickly.)
(The last order from headquarters)
Yes, it's me.
Tonight?
He really seems like a secret agent here.
I'll wait for you.
- What's with the song? - No way.
(His last mission)
(The quiet agent who resolutely
carries out his missions)
He's like a cartoon character.
(The Hoon Identity, Season 3, coming soon)
My goodness.
- He wasn't looking for me, I guess.
- The Hoon Identity.
What did you think?
First of all, they edited it so
well, which I was happy to see.
(Could this be?)
It's like he's giving a
speech at an award ceremony.
I think you've still got your
head in the Baeksang Arts Awards?
(We'll hear the rest of your
speech at the SBS Drama Awards.)
I'm sure you noticed this too
as we were watching the clip,
but Seok Hoon acts with his eyes so well.
(It can't be, can it?)
- To Do Yeon, could you... - No, no.
(He's the only one having
trouble laughing now.)
- You don't have to.
- The way you look at Ro Na.
Just do it for us once.
Just pretend it's Ro Na
20 years into the future.
A lot happened to Ro Na,
and she suffered a lot over the years.
1, 2...
(Fidgeting)
Stop fidgeting.
(Even the ones watching
feel nervous about it.)
Now, 1, 2, 3.
(No...)
- Three. - No...
(Interpretation, "This
is too embarrassing.")
- Three. - No...
(Do Yeon is confused.)
Do Yeon...
- Her heart was racing just now.
- No, I'm sorry.
(Do Yeon's heart was racing
within 1 second of gazing.)
I'm sorry, Do Yeon.
- As for Min Hyuk, - Yes?
After watching this clip,
you'll be able to participate...
in season three not as an
actor, but in a different role.
Is it a camera director?
That's right, the cameras.
Let's confirm if they're
right or wrong in the video.
(Min Hyuk is in charge of
filming, anytime, anywhere.)
(That includes dynamic sports filming, )
(with live moving shots, )
(and appropriate close-ups.)
That's right.
(He even follows characters'
movements properly.)
- Even there. - Even in that tight space.
Quickly, do it now.
Filming sideways.
- Drink up, quickly. - Drink it.
(He can turn horizontally
filmed videos into vertical ones.)
That's so true.
They filmed this well.
What?
I'm not the old Min Hyuk.
(Call me Director Lee from now on.)
- Director Lee. - Wow.
Director Lee.
The current camera director
of The Penthouse is nervous.
(Chuckling)
I'm sure he really is, right?
I know I've said it but
I'm not sure about that.
He's breaking out in a
cold sweat, even now.
- So he is nervous after all. - Yes.
I'm really curious about one weird detail.
Do you film with your own
phone, or with a set prop?
As in, is he really filming?
Yes, I'm really curious about that.
I film with a prop.
But you're really filming?
Yes, I think they do that so
they can really use the footage.
I end up focusing more on
filming than I do on acting.
Are your skills getting better?
Yes, because I keep wanting
to make everything look good.
I'll adjust the angles. I
filmed a lot for Jenny, actually.
I'd say, "Your right side looks pretty."
- Wow. - That's what I'd end up doing.
You smell like a pro.
- At the last interview, Min Hyuk...
- I got a lot of criticism.
You said that it was hard
for you as a result, right?
After the last special episode aired...
(After The Penthouse 2 Hidden
Room, The Unfinished Story aired.)
I got a lot of people
showing me their support.
- That means you acted well.
- That's right.
Eun Byeol, did you
experience anything similar?
I had a lot of scenes
where I picked on others,
so I also got a lot of
criticism for that as well.
Since I also tend to flip
out on my own, chaotically,
I think some viewers...
didn't like that side of me.
How do you feel when you see that?
Are you disappointed?
- I'm disappointed, but...
- Are you smiling at negative posts?
Now we just have Eun Byeol left,
but it turns out she has
an incredible alter ego.
Let's find out Eun Byeol's
alter ego in this video.
Alter ego?
(Ha Eun Byeol is dying.)
That's scary.
I look like a zombie.
Oh, gosh.
(In order to save her...)
Oh, no.
(Dr. Ha decides to take a gamble.)
That was shocking.
(He gives Eun Byeol a super serum, but...)
Is she a zombie?
- A zombie. - Eun Byeol!
What's happening? Did something go wrong?
Do something!
(The revived Eun Byeol
experiences strange events.)
(An inexplicable ringing in her ears)
(Strange images)
(Even ghost sightings)
That sounds like it would be so miserable.
It's all mine.
She is sick and tired of ghosts now.
(Eun Byeol decides to become an exorcist.)
So suddenly?
Start over with your breathing.
(Her training began.)
- She's training to be an exorcist? - Yes.
(As her exorcism training
starts to come to a close...)
Contract your abs more.
(She even gains a legendary
weapon in the exorcism world.)
From the exorcism world.
(Exorcist Eun Byeol
maxes out her battle points.)
(She heads to Hera Palace...)
Here we go with the music.
(where ghosts have been spotted.)
There.
But...
(But she's overwhelmed by
the sight of Ro Na's ghost.)
(Scared to death by the
ghost's singing attack.)
Ro Na is right there!
- The attack? - It's a musical attack.
(She tries wielding the legendary weapon.)
Oh, my gosh.
(It's stronger than she thought.)
This was honestly a bit scary.
Oh, no. No!
Eun Byeol!
This is so funny.
- Here. - Wow.
No.
Eun Byeol.
(Ro Na's ghost finally disappears.)
(Eun Byeol won her meaningful
victory with her own courage.)
(The protector of Hera Palace)
I'm amazed they
managed to edit it this way.
Wow.
(She's the exorcist, Ha Eun Byeol.)
She's an exorcist now.
We saw this in the clip too,
but you had an unusually
large number of ghost sightings.
Wasn't that hard to film?
When we film, I see the
real Ro Na, the person,
but when it airs, there are
bats flying around everywhere.
- Are you two separated?
- We start out in the same area,
and Eun Byeol attacks the air,
and then I'll go in with a green screen,
and fly around.
(Why are you laughing?
It is a green screen.)
She's so cute.
Do you practice any individual skills?
- Eun Byeol has a ton of them.
- No, I'm not.
She'll show them to us while we're on set.
- Really? - This is a set too.
(Show us.)
I'll do Krusty Krab from
"Spongebob Squarepants."
(It's already funny
before she even tries it.)
That's so funny. Krusty Krab.
"I love money."
(They totally love it.)
- That was so cute. - She did it.
I've never seen it before
but I get a good sense of it.
That was so cute.
But as a viewer, the thing
I'm most curious about...
is that in the drama, your
singing is cleaned up...
before the show airs, but
what is it like in reality?
Opera?
- Really? - I was curious about it.
Can we hear you sing without the recording?
(Sing without any music here?)
(Frozen for a moment)
The three of you in the middle...
had the most scenes like that.
Let's do it.
Let's decide the order
with rock paper scissors.
You lose if you don't
play, rock, paper, scissors.
(Ro Na goes last.)
You lose if you don't
play, rock, paper, scissors.
(Eun Byeol goes first.)
I thought you were holding the
Cheong A Art Festival trophy.
(It's like the results announced
at Cheong A Art Festival.)
What are you going to sing? The final song?
The song I sang in the
basement in season one.
- That's great. - That's a famous scene.
I'm honoured to hear this.
- That's a lot of pressure.
- Just a moment, please.
I have to warm up my
voice a little bit for this.
Of course, go ahead.
Hee, Hee, Hee.
She's really passionate.
(Making a big effort)
What was it again?
(She forgot the lyrics
because she's nervous.)
(Still, she works hard until the very end.)
That was so impressive.
- That was great. - Brava, brava!
Wow.
You sang so well for us.
She has so much passion.
- Seok Kyung, how about you?
- What shall I sing for you?
A song from season one?
Or season two?
Then from season two.
(She's confident enough to
start without even warming up.)
- This does make you nervous. - It does.
- It does make you nervous.
- It's nervewracking.
(Gesturing to make
sure she stays on the beat)
(Seok Kyung sang this over and
over for the sake of the drama.)
(Shall we enjoy it for a moment?)
I think that's how it went.
Brava.
(Seok Kyung's performance
led to a standing ovation.)
- Brava. - Nice.
I think I forgot the lyrics.
You were so good.
It would've been terrible
if we didn't request this.
You're exactly like
Seok Kyung in the drama.
You're so good at singing this.
Now we have the grand prize winner.
(The winner of the Cheong
A Art Festival, Ro Na)
That's right. She won.
- She got the grand prize.
- With genius-like talent.
In that case,
I'll sing the song...
I practiced with my mother,
when I was applying to Cheong A.
It's a meaningful song too.
(With the emotions of that time, )
(Ro Na sings carefully...)
(with her pure voice.)
(That's a skill worthy of
the grand prize winner.)
(Thank you.)
- That was so great.
- At first, I wondered...
- if this request was all right.
- It was so good.
- It was so refreshing.
- Thank you so much.
Right now, we've been filming...
- for a few hours. - Right.
Do you want to hear something incredible?
- What is it?
- We'll now start on season three...
In season three,
are all five of you going to become adults?
We don't know.
You still don't know?
Really?
You're all trying not to say a word.
Were you all scolded by the writers?
I'm sure we'll all be adults
eventually since we're ageing.
- What was that? - That's just...
exactly what Ha Eun Byeol would say.
That was so incredible.
Tell us how you felt as
soon as you saw the script.
(Gasping)
- So that was it? - Really? That was it.
What about you, Eun Byeol?
(What? Oh, no...)
- Eun Byeol... - That's so interesting.
It makes me want to guess what will happen.
What is it? Why is she reacting like that?
(What does this reaction mean?)
Did you eat something bad?
What about Ro Na, when you saw the script?
Oh, no.
- I see. - I see.
All three reactions were different.
- Min Hyuk? - What a headache.
- A headache. - I see.
Last but not least, Seok Hoon.
For me, as soon as I saw it,
I thought, "Really? Who?"
- Who? - Was that too much?
What is it?
Because you don't know what will happen.
As we watch the show,
we'll know what those
reactions meant after all.
So this is why Min Hyuk said
that, why Seok Hoon said that.
But maybe it'll end and we still
won't know why they said that.
As our expectations for season three...
continue to grow,
there's another aspect of the
show that we should focus on.
There are three more characters
that hold the key to the plot.
Let's meet them through video.
My baby is sleeping so well.
I love Eun Byeol very much.
I think of her as my own daughter,
so if it's for her, I could
make a deal with evil.
(A manic obsession with
Eun Byeol, Jin Bun Hong)
My princess. I'll be home soon. See you.
An ally who's of help to his family,
and an enemy to everyone else.
(His reason for living
is family, Yoo Dong Pil)
I'm excited because it's been so long.
He is Baek Jun Ki, but he also may not be.
A fake that seems real,
the real that seems fake.
(Neither real nor fake, Baek Jun Ki)
(The actors will introduce these
three critical roles personally.)
Hello, I'm actor Park Ho San,
who plays the role of Yoo
Dong Pil in The Penthouse 3.
I think many people
thought of me as a gangster.
I thought so as well, at first,
but I'm actually very detailed.
I think deeply about things,
and aspire to be a force for good...
for my family, and the enemy
to those who oppose my family.
It's understandable, but not justifiable.
That's the role I play.
Hello, I'm actor On Ju Wan,
playing Baek Jun Ki on The Penthouse.
Ki Joon introduced me to the role,
asking me if I'd like to meet
the writer, Kim Soon Ok.
When we first met,
the writer told me she'd like
me to play a hero-like role.
But if I listen to the things
people say about the character,
he's not a hero.
I heard he was a hero, so I
thought he'd vanquish evil,
like the Avengers do,
but what the director tells me,
and what the rumours tell me,
- is that he's a villain.
- He's the worst villain ever.
It's very confusing.
One side calls him a
villain, and the other a hero.
If I were to provide more
hints that are more helpful,
he's like a fake that seems
real, and the real that seems fake.
That means...
he goes back and forth.
Hello, I'm actress Ahn Yeon Hong,
who plays Jin Bun Hong in The Penthouse.
She's a mysterious figure who
doesn't distinguish good from evil.
That's how they explained
the character to me.
(Critical Scene, "Hello, sir.")
Hello, sir.
Secretary Cho is close with me.
He was definitely one of my people before.
I think that's why he came
to see me when I left prison.
How their relationship will
develop, only the writer knows that.
The unique thing about The Penthouse...
is that no one knows what's coming.
It's amazing, and fun,
and also makes you despair.
It makes you feel many things.
It's my first time doing
a drama in this way.
But that's how much
faith we have in the writer,
and because we've
achieved good results so far,
our faith in the writer
has grown even more.
Now, I'm just making sure
I'm faithful to the script.
My poor thing.
Call me Mom from now on.
Call me mom.
Even I grew curious about it,
as I was acting out my role.
As far as I know, Logan was the mastermind,
but why am I changing so much?
That's what I started thinking,
and I wondered if I didn't
have some kind of trauma...
related to children that
have caused this obsession,
this twisted motherly love.
To be honest, I'm very
curious about what will happen.
Can I go have a smoke first?
Sure, go ahead.
(Critical Scene, "Can I
go have a smoke first?")
(An unbelievable coincidence?
Or a secret conspiracy?)
The way I look at it, I still
think there is no relation...
between Baek Jun Ki and the exploding car.
He got out of the car, leaving his bag,
gazes at him once, and
then disappears somewhere.
To be honest,
some people could think I
left the bag in there on purpose,
but if there was a bomb in it,
why didn't airport security catch it?
I don't think I'm the one
who tried to kill Logan.
(Are you sure?)
I can't be sure, with this drama.
I'm sorry, but I just
think he's not related.
(Which character should we
focus on most in season three?)
I think...
Jin Bun Hong.
(Jin Bun Hong)
I think my role is really fun,
and I think it's set up
for a plot twist coming up.
You'll be shocked if you watch.
There's something
shocking that's coming soon.
Because I'm a character
that's been around...
since season one,
I know a lot of people have
expectations while watching.
I do have a certain
number of confirmed scenes.
I'm sure everyone picked themselves, right?
I guess I'll pick myself too.
Jun Ki is a person...
who knows Joo Dan Tae's past.
That's his greatest weapon.
I also think that Dong Pil...
will side with good,
in my opinion.
I think he'll end up being a just person.
(Are you sure?)
I told you I can't be sure.
I don't even know about my own character.
How can I know anything about Dong Pil?
I just think that might happen.
Jin Bun Hong...
I've never seen her in
person, not even on set.
I'm not sure if I can say this,
but as a character, she
doesn't seem totally sane.
The way she speaks reminds
me of the movie, "Misery."
I wonder if that's the
kind of character she is.
Even when he's just standing
around, he looks so dashing.
Just looking at him is so nice.
It's so satisfying.
You should've told me that in advance.
I'm sure she's also beautiful and kind.
But to speak only about
her character, 100 percent,
I'm wondering if...
that might not be the case.
I said that so carefully, but all
of a sudden, after the interview...
Many of the characters in The Penthouse...
are curious about me.
They seem to think of
me as very mysterious.
I can't tell what she's like.
She's truly a mystery.
Do I seem like a psycho?
Jun Ki's goal is to get back what's his.
Will he waver?
That could be money,
and he might waver due to the temptation.
I think that's one point to watch for.
Jin Bun Hong...
doesn't have any ambitions
about the penthouse,
or about money.
But for Eun Byeol, she has a
lot of strong feelings for her only.
She's always on Eun Byeol's side.
I really love Eun Byeol.
I think of her as my own daughter,
so if it's for her, I could make a deal...
with evil.
(But Eun Byeol already has a mom.)
We need to compete for Eun Byeol.
I'd like to meet her soon.
(Onjuwan1211, Who am I and where am I?)
(I hope everyone looks forward
to the first episode on June 4.)
(What does this social media post mean?)
I really didn't know who I am.
I'm playing a villain,
but also filming scenes where I smile.
I'm pretending to be nice too.
It feels like I'm actually
playing three roles at once.
It's driving me insane.
What I was talking about is this.
What if I'm not the person...
who knows about Joo Dan
Tae and his past after all?
What if everything is a plan?
That's how far I got.
I could be Baek Jun Ki, but also not.
You know what I mean, right?
You can see how much
this is driving me insane.
As a character, it's a bit confusing,
so I asked Ki Joon for advice.
I heard some secretive
stuff, which went like this.
What do you think?
He said he didn't know.
(Consultation with Ki Joon is over.)
Even Dan Tae didn't know.
I think Ki Joon just gave up.
I think he's the type to
focus just on the scenes...
he's in each week.
There are still plot lines
that haven't been resolved,
embedded in the plot like time bombs.
When will they explode?
I'm also looking forward to that,
as I continue to prepare for my own role.
Right now, everything I said,
and everything the other
actors have said so far...
can go in one ear and out the other.
That's how chaotic this
drama will be, I think.
That's why you can focus on what happens,
and deduce and predict things on your own,
becoming your own detective.
I believe that way,
you'll really enjoy watching the show.
Which person do you think
deserves the focus of attention?
I just thought of something...
- about Jin Bun Hong. - What is it?
Some people thought
this about the character.
Eun Byeol is being punished
by meeting Jin Bun Hong.
And?
- And? - That's all.
Oh, so it wasn't a question
or a response to the question.
You were just relaying the news.
I was just sharing what I'd heard.
What about Yoo Dong Pil?
I've met with Dong Pil...
from time to time.
- Isn't that a big spoiler?
- Is that meaningful?
That we met?
You're all making each other very anxious.
Why are you doing that to me?
I'm not allowed to say that part?
The scariest phrase for
all of The Penthouse is this.
"Is it a spoiler?"
Is it not?
I'm curious why they met,
and what they did in their meetings.
I saw that scene with Jenny's dad,
and went to film something
else in Yangyang right afterwards.
I should've greeted
him, but it was too scary.
So I couldn't greet him after all.
Is that it? Was that the news?
(Chuckling)
Please watch the show to see.
If we're just going to find out
everything by watching the show,
- what's the point of this special?
- You're right.
- If we just have to watch the
show, - Why bother talking here?
Now...
(The time everyone has been waiting for)
it's time.
It's no exaggeration to say...
our entire show will
culminate in this video.
- None of you have seen it before? - No.
I wonder how it turned out.
I'll introduce it using a
particularly impressive voice.
Never before seen!
You sound like Kim Kyung Sik.
(Giggling)
There is a man right here.
That's true.
- I'll add more gravity. - All right.
Never before seen!
Here is the trailer...
for The Penthouse 3.
(The Penthouse 3)
It's the prison.
This place is just like Hera Palace.
There's a penthouse in this prison too.
A prison penthouse?
It's my dad.
Don't you dare touch my food!
I'll break you all.
Wow.
- Dad... - You have to eat to live.
It's not time to give up yet.
Do what makes you happy.
Logan is dead.
I don't rely on the
judgement of the law anymore.
Everything I tell you from now on,
make sure it never gets back to Su Ryeon.
To Su Ryeon?
- What is it? - So there's a huge secret.
Dad.
That person will reveal Joo Dan Tae's past.
Eun Byeol's guardian is me.
Get rid of them?
If you don't want to live like a pig,
you have to pay for
your sins no matter what.
Why did you do that?
- What was that? - Yes, just now.
What is it?
- Get out of here. - Seok Kyung.
Why are you insisting on dying?
I'm going to kill you all.
We have to make him remember everything.
He's a total crazy fool.
- Where is he now?
- You think I don't know?
Do you still think I'm Shim Su Ryeon?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- Oh, no. - If you do anything,
I'll kill you myself.
(The Penthouse 3 airs on June 4, 10pm)
From now on,
shall we begin in earnest?
So that wasn't Shim Su Ryeon?
I was so shocked when
I read that in the script.
Oh, that line?
What was that?
(Rendered speechless)
I got goosebumps.
- That's going to be so much fun.
- They made it so well.
My heart really felt like it
was squeezing the whole time.
- I can't wait to find out.
- I can't seem to predict...
what's going to happen in the middle.
I'm so curious now. Anyway...
From the time this show will
air, the first episode is in two days.
That's right. June 4, Friday,
is when the first episode
of The Penthouse 3, airs.
- That's right.
- We should all watch it then.
I'm so nervous.
I hope everyone watches
the show when it first airs.
Thank you so much for being with us,
here on The Penthouse 3 Hidden
Room, The Start of the End.
Any feelings you'd like to share?
We've been working
together for a whole year now.
Any regrets we have are
just turned into motivation.
With the desire to have no regrets.
To give our all.
We hope our hard work
pays off even in season three.
It's like you're making a birthday wish...
before blowing out the candles.
"Please, I want this
for my birthday and..."
Please show us a lot
of love for season three.
(Please show The
Penthouse 3 a lot of love!)