(The start of the end
of The Penthouse 3 by keymen)
(It's my first time.)
(The unpredictable world
of The Penthouse)
(It's crazy.)
(The three secretaries
are appearing.)
(Just enough spoiler)
(Just enough suspense)
(Just enough push and pull)
(Revealing all the charms)
(New type of talk show...)
(by the kids of The Penthouse
continues.)
(Revealing their real singing skill)
(And)
(The whole story of The Penthouse 3
slowly reveals.)
(The footage of The Penthouse 3
is revealed for the first time.)
(Please send us lots of love.)
(The Penthouse 3 Special
begins now.)
The Penthouse 3 Hidden Room,
The Start of the End.
I'm your host, Jang Do Yeon.
(Jang Do Yeon)
- I'm Jo Jung Sik.
- Hello.
In The Penthouse 3
Hidden Room today,
we're going to talk about...
the start and the end...
of The Penthouse.
The Penthouse 3 Hidden Room,
The Start of the End.
First, it's "Back to the Beginning".
There were flashbacks
throughout the drama.
We collected all the flashbacks...
and created new footage.
It is The Penthouse Youth Theater.
- Youth Theater.
- Let's watch.
(The Penthouse Youth Theater)
(The story of their youth
through flashbacks)
- Back in high school.
- Yes.
(Seoul, 1996)
- It goes back to 1996.
- Stop! Stop!
You need to project!
(One father and daughter had
an extraordinary passion for music.)
Don't you know how important
this audition is?
It's an opportunity to sing with
the best opera company in Italy.
They only wanted to see Yoon Hee,
the top student in the school,
but I forced your way in.
I'll practice more, Father.
I can do it.
Are you weeping
because I nagged a little?
You know I can't stand
seeing chicks cry.
Do it again!
(Everything her father said was
absolute law to Cheon Seo Jin.)
The trauma to be the top.
(After the audition)
How did it go?
- Who made it?
- This music is playing.
Loser.
You can't beat her even once?
Then...
is Yoon Hee going to Italy?
- My.
- I can't allow that.
(Yoon Hee with the skill
and Seo Jin with power)
We arranged it to say
Yoon Hee turned them down.
After what I did to get you in,
you almost lost it.
What a disgrace.
- I'm sorry.
- Let's go.
(Seo Jin couldn't meet
her father's expectations.)
She wants her father
to approve her the most.
(The big day)
(The day of Cheong A Art Festival to
get into Seoul National University)
(Yoon Hee, the top student shows off
what she's capable of.)
- She never makes a mistake.
- Yes.
She's the center of S.E.S.
(She finishes her performance
with cheer and applause.)
The highlight of the 25th
Cheong A Art Festival.
The grand prize winner
for the best classical singer.
The Bella Voce Award goes to...
- Cheon Seo Jin!
- My.
(An incomprehensible result is
announced.)
What? The grand prize?
- How could you win when you were...
- It's the prelude to war.
unstable and your voice cracked?
Did you think you'd always win
first place?
This is mine.
- Give it to me.
- Let go!
(No one can yield.)
This is where the whole story
begins.
That's right.
(There's an intense fight
over the trophy.)
When I first watched this drama,
this scene was shocking.
(Yoon Hee can barely get
close to the trophy.)
No!
The trophy looks so dangerous.
Yes. It's got a pointy end.
I will never let you take this.
(That's how their worst
ill-fated relationship begins.)
You pitiful brat.
- What?
- The fake winner, Cheon Seo Jin.
You're just a darned thief.
It's scary to watch it again.
(Seo Jin whose pride is hurt
ends up wounding Yoon Hee's neck.)
Look at her face.
- That reminds me of Eun Byeol.
- Right.
It keeps reminding me of
Eun Byeol and Ro Na.
(Only if they had met
in an environment...)
(where the competition
wasn't so fierce.)
- Seo Jin!
- What happened?
The lyrics sound different.
(They could've been good friends.)
You can get up now.
(The investigation shows that
Seo Jin fabricated it.)
Fathers all know if they're sleeping
or just pretending.
Fathers always say
they're not sleeping.
Yoon Hee bled a lot from her neck.
I'm sorry, Father.
- My.
- Boy.
Father.
Do you know why I slapped you?
Not because you hurt
a brat like her.
It's because you lost to her.
Your father is the director
of the Cheong A Foundation.
And yet, you lost to a girl
with no father...
and made me go and beg the judges...
to give you the Grand Prize.
Her father is turning her
into a monster.
I'm sorry, Father. It's my fault.
This can never happen again.
You must be the best.
Or you don't deserve to take over
Cheong A Foundation.
Okay.
I will be the best.
She ended up hurting her neck...
I can't believe
this music is playing.
I feel so bad for her.
She won't be able to sing anymore.
She was the top student
for three years straight.
But now, she's hit rock bottom.
It's Chelsia Chan's song.
Does that mean she won't be
able to go to college?
(They end up walking
different paths.)
(Meanwhile in Japan)
Is it Japan?
(Na Ae Gyo,
Joo Dan Tae's girlfriend)
(Joo Dan Tae, Na Ae Gyo's boyfriend)
Joo Dan Tae doesn't have much yet.
I'll make sure that you live
like Shim Su Ryeon.
For how much longer
do I have to wait?
It won't be long.
If I use Shim Su Ryeon's name right,
we'll become so rich that we could
suffocate under our piles of money.
He talks about such a scary plan...
- with such a naive face.
- I'll buy a house in Gangnam,
and build a Joo Dan Tae Village...
on the land where my mother has
passed away on,
and make the whole world kneel
before me.
And we'll have children?
Of course.
Just thinking about it makes me
so happy.
(They plan to steal other's life
for their happiness.)
(Should they be thankful?)
(Is this what love is?)
It's Oh Yoon Hee's song.
(As the first step of his plan,)
- When she was a k-pop singer.
- I like it.
(Joo Dan Tae plans a marriage
with Shim Su Ryeon.)
- I'll get this gift-wrapped.
- Okay.
(Joo Dan Tae plans a marriage
with Shim Su Ryeon.)
He's marrying Shim Su Ryeon,
not Na Ae Gyo.
You're right.
Su Ryeon, what is it?
I'm surprised you called me first.
I feel happy.
Are you coming back
for summer break?
My parents are mentioning
our marriage and...
Let's call off the marriage.
That's cruel.
What did you just say?
- These are all great songs.
- I'm...
getting married soon in the States.
(Dan Tae got dumped.)
I'm sorry, Dan Tae.
Hello?
(However, the plan goes wrong.)
With the wrong method...
Yes, he comes up with a scary plan.
Who says you can?
(He plans one scary incident
to marry her.)
Who says you can call it off?
(He plans one scary incident
to marry her.)
Is it possible for a human
to become that wicked?
(Several months later in the USA)
(Su Ryeon's spending a pleasant time
with the man she loves.)
She's pregnant.
(Su Ryeon's spending a pleasant time
with the man she loves.)
It's sad since I know
what's going to happen next.
(There are so many things
I should not love)
(Dan Tae decides to punish Su Ryeon
for choosing someone else.)
(What upsets him the most is...)
How cruel.
(You who don't love me)
(I didn't ask you to stay
by my side)
(You didn't have to call off
our marriage.)
The flashbacks show the reasons...
- why they've become monsters.
- Yes.
(And)
There must've been a problem with
her brain due to premature birth.
(Su Ryeon ended up giving premature
birth due to shooting.)
It's my fault.
(The moment Dan Tae had been
waiting for has arrived.)
It's all my fault.
Don't blame yourself.
I'll take care of your child now.
(While Su Ryeon became weak
due to shock and sadness...)
Now that I'm watching in order,
I can see the change in their looks.
- It's fun to watch the compilation.
- Yes.
(Meanwhile, after high school,)
(Yoon Hee got a job right away.)
It feels like an archive.
(Ha Yoon Chul, Yoon Hee's boyfriend)
(She's in love
with a poor medical student.)
I got my salary.
Pay for your lodgings.
- Oh Yoon Hee and Ha Yoon Chul.
- I don't want to.
Stop giving me money.
- What an adorable couple.
- I'm giving it to you to feel good,
so you don't have to feel bad.
It's true.
It's not much anyway. Take it.
I'll become a doctor
as soon as I can...
and support you.
They haven't met Cheon Seo Jin yet,
have they?
(Even poverty felt romantic to them
because they were in love.)
Cheon Seo Jin sees them now.
She gets jealous.
(Their ill-fated relationship with
Cheon Seo Jin begins again.)
(Seo Jin still feels
inferior to Yoon Hee.)
Dad, it's me.
About the next
Cheong A Foundation scholarship.
I want to recommend someone
who is studying medicine.
(Yoon Chul became a scholarship
student...)
(with Seo Jin's recommendation.)
Holding onto the end of the night
It's no longer
What's going on? Did you get
the Cheong A Foundation scholarship?
(Yoon Hee doesn't like it.)
Why didn't you tell me?
I couldn't refuse to attend
when they gave me a scholarship.
It doesn't mean anything.
Do you call that an excuse?
You being involved
with Cheon Seo Jin...
I hate that more than death!
Will you stop
talking about Cheon Seo Jin?
Just stop it.
I'm sick of it now!
Their relationship falls apart
as Seo Jin intended.
The conflict deepens.
- That's what Seo Jin wanted.
- Yes.
(Love...)
(and reality)
(The young medical student's woe
grows.)
- This scene.
- Oh, this scene.
- Cheon Seo Jin's really annoying.
- Yes.
Stop drinking.
(Yoon Chul has a drink with Seo Jin
out of frustration.)
He drank a lot.
That's the old Jinro soju.
- I got too excited.
- Darn it.
What else am I to do?
Studying must be hard enough.
Why do you want to live
with such a burden?
(Yoon Hee sees Yoon Chul
and Seo Jin together.)
Oh, why on earth?
- Why did she have to pass it?
- Especially at that moment.
I will give you...
A pair of wings.
(Seo Jin suddenly confesses
her feelings to Yoon Chul.)
That sounds so sweet to
a self-supporting student.
I know. In fact,
she's the director's daughter.
(With rain and drinks in between)
How cruel.
(Seo Jin steals
Yoon Hee's life again.)
Oh, this is the moment.
(You've left)
(And the rain is falling)
(To someone, it's an end.)
(To someone, it's a start.)
Oh, gosh. Why would you wrap
your arm around her?
Seriously.
(Youth and the start of the end)
(Time goes by)
(Over the years)
(A moment to achieve something
arrives.)
Today,
(Seo Jin expects
an important decision.)
You waited long enough.
The foundation...
is yours, Seo Jin.
(She finally becomes the director
she's long been waiting for.)
- Finally.
- He finally approves her.
It's what she's been waiting for.
Father.
It was Cheon Seo Jin's goal in life.
A halo.
- And fireworks inside the building.
- Yes.
- When you're really happy...
- Right.
- You're overwhelmed,
- you can't say anything.
but it's hard to describe it.
(The brightest moment in her life
has arrived.)
- It's hard to believe.
- Yes.
Now she feels like eating.
(I'm just happy to think about it.)
Today,
the most wonderful thing
happened to me.
Seo Jin and my husband
are having an affair.
(Soon, her affair with Dan Tae
is revealed.)
We must get divorced.
We can't.
Now, the whole
Hera Club members know.
We can't stay together.
Chairman Joo Dan Tae.
(Yoon Hee also
tries to threaten Seo Jin.)
What are you trying to pull?
Everyone already knows
about me and Dan Tae.
That's right.
But there's one person who doesn't.
(I don't know yet)
- "Dad."
- Dad.
He wishes to appoint someone else
as the director.
(Seo Jin's father dismisses Seo Jin
from the director position.)
No. Father.
(Seo Jin runs to stop her father.)
What a good choice of a song.
Let go.
(She went out of her way
to take the best position.)
(Seo Jin could never lose it.)
(She confronts her father
who's become an obstacle.)
(Her father's on the verge of life
after the scuffle.)
- Seo Jin.
- Grab him. You must grab him.
(Seo Jin turns her back
on her father.)
Greed can be very scary.
(She exchanged her father
for the director position.)
You abandoned me...
first, Father.
(Seo Jin ends up
killing her father.)
(Meanwhile, Joo Dan Tae)
She's the one...
he talked about the future with.
(He got this far all for Na Ae Gyo.)
(He ends up killing Na Ae Gyo
with his own hands.)
Who do you think she is?
(She was the goal
of Dan Tae's life.)
(Na)
(Ae)
(Gyo)
(She's gone...)
(out of Dan Tae's life for good.)
It's "She's Gone."
(Dan Tae finally realizes the person
he killed was Na Ae Gyo.)
This is like a music video.
So, Na Ae Gyo...
is really dead?
I...
killed...
Na Ae Gyo?
You jerk.
(He cries for the perfect future
he shattered on his own...)
(and the sense of loss.)
(Due to the shadow singer incident,)
(Seo Jin faces voting
to be appointed again.)
(But she barely avoids
losing her position.)
She finally protected it.
- It was hard to believe the result.
- I know.
(What protected Seo Jin was
her father's favor.)
What favor?
My first daughter
still has a long way to go.
She is ambitious
but lacks in many ways.
Support her.
So that she can keep her place
as Director.
Yet, she killed her father.
Gosh. It's breaking my heart.
Father...
Why did you do that?
(Her father has gone to a place
he can never come back.)
(Seo Jin wanted her father
to approve her...)
(by winning the highest
and best position.)
(Joo Dan Tae dreamed of a happy
future with Na Ae Gyo.)
(They both ended up killing the most
precious person in their lives...)
(for them and their lives.)
(And now...)
(Director Cheon Seo Jin)
(They've emptied their offices.)
- Bye, bye.
- Bye.
Goodbye, Assemblyman.
Bye.
Goodbye, Kang Ma Ri's bathhouse.
Bye, Ms. Cheon.
(People who went to prison,
Ha Yoon Chul)
(Lee Kyu Jin)
(Ko Sang A)
It was such
an unexpected conclusion.
(Joo Dan Tae)
(Oh Yoon Hee)
(People who went back home,
Shim Su Ryeon)
(People who went missing,
Jin Bun Hong and Eun Byeol)
(New appearances, Yoo Dong Pil)
(Baek Jun Ki)
Not many of them were able
to keep their places.
(Logan Lee had
an explosion accident.)
(Find out what they will do
in Season 3.)
Their lives are so ironic.
Both Joo Dan Tae
and Cheon Seo Jin...
live for someone,
but they end up killing the person
with their own hands.
Like you said, they both killed
someone with their hands.
But there's another thing
they have in common.
Neither of them can do anything
on their own.
All they do is give orders.
The Penthouse would completely stop
without these three people.
You're right. They're at the beck
and call of the main characters.
It wasn't easy to bring
all of them here.
I can't believe it. It feels unreal.
You rarely see them in one place.
Exactly.
The three secretaries are here.
- Nice to see you.
- Welcome.
This is so exciting.
I've never met them before.
Didn't you shoot any scene
together in Seasons 1 and 2?
- We've never seen them together.
- This is the first time...
we've been on camera together.
The viewers would also think...
this is such a rare opportunity.
Hello, I play...
Secretary Hong, who works for Logan.
My name is Kim Jae Hong.
Hello, I play Secretary Do,
who works
for Director Cheon Seo Jin.
My name is Kim Do Hyun.
Hello, I play Secretary Cho,
Joo Dan Tae's right-hand man.
My name is Kim Dong Kyu.
Your eyes are so sparkly.
Your eyes are really shiny.
You look like a little boy
with a beard.
It might sound rude,
- but the thing is,
- I know.
he looks so different in real life.
I'm shocked.
In real life,
- you look so innocent.
- You look so kind.
I'm still in my 20s too.
- You are?
- Yes.
(Shocked)
- What's that reaction?
- Your beard...
It's because you beat
older guys a lot.
I'm very polite in real life.
- You are.
- That's right.
Who's the oldest then?
I was born in 1983.
- Secretary Cho was born...
- I was born in 1994.
- I was born in 1992.
- 1992.
But their age doesn't really matter.
What matters in the Penthouse is
who has more money and power.
- That's right.
- That's what matters.
Who has the most power then?
In the show,
I used to be in the special forces.
It's something I've come up with.
- It's a secret?
- It's a secret.
I'm the only one who knows it.
These two have
more powers than I do.
I even lose
to Oh Yoon Hee and Bae Ro Na.
I get shoved aside by them.
Sometimes, I wonder if Secretary Do
has any muscular strength.
"Muscular strength?"
First things first.
We prepared a video that shows
the different work styles you have.
Let's watch it.
Excuse me!
You're Logan Lee's secretary, right?
I'm Logan Lee's secretary.
(Secretary Hong,
User of cutting-edge technology)
So you really are a special agent.
(Using high-tech devices,)
(he prepares thoroughly in advance.)
Everything is set, sir.
(The one who killed Min Seol A
is in here.)
(He successfully threatens
the murder suspects of Min Seol A.)
(He uses even more
advanced equipment.)
- That's incredible.
- The fingerprint.
- It's your biggest accomplishment.
- It was the decisive move.
(He copied
Joo Dan Tae's fingerprint.)
You're very proud of it.
That's just...
It still makes me proud.
It's your only accomplishment.
(He always remains quiet.)
Oh Yoon Hee was also there
on the night...
when the lighting ceremony
took place.
(Secretary Hong relies
on high-tech equipment.)
Send this woman out.
- Secretary Do!
- He sent you a bouquet.
- What?
- Out of the blue?
The mood changed completely.
- Find out whom he met.
- Yes, ma'am.
Find where this person is.
- Any other information?
- There's none.
I'll make sure to find her
no matter what it takes.
- Find out by all means.
- I will, ma'am.
He's like a sunflower.
My gosh.
Are you okay?
Why don't you call it a day?
You don't seem so well.
It's suddenly became a romance.
You were with me today...
and after that,
you were in the lesson room.
He's so cool.
You must pull yourself together.
(Because of one woman...)
He looks so cool.
This feels completely different.
(He lives another day.)
It's so romantic.
It's amazing.
(Mental and emotional care provider)
(Secretary Do, the man of loyalty)
My goodness.
Secretary Cho, come in. Come in!
- Secretary Cho.
- Yes, sir.
(Secretary Cho, the tough guy)
He's the tough guy.
Move your car.
(From moving his boss's car...)
- That's how it all began.
- No.
- Did you take care of it?
- Yes, sir.
You stay right next to Joo Dan Tae.
(His specialty is violence.)
(He has beaten every man
on the show except for Dan Tae.)
(He is the strongest fighter
in The Penthouse.)
(When it comes to violence,)
(he never disappoints.)
(But apart from that...)
Why are you telling me that now?
She hasn't come back to the cottage.
- What is this?
- It's the perfect song.
Are you an idiot?
Our stock plummeted today.
They definitely said it was taken.
You moron.
If you have the time to say that,
get out and look for her!
Who have you been following,
you moron?
My gosh.
- Get out!
- Yes, sir.
That moron.
He's so mean.
What is this?
I'm sorry, sir.
(Secretary Cho, the violent fighter)
(The story of the hidden heroes
begins.)
Even though all three of you
are secretaries,
- your work styles totally differ.
- Absolutely.
It was so interesting
to see them next to one another.
A word that's still ringing
in my ears is...
- a "moron".
- A "moron".
What did you think?
It's such a shame.
Why do I always mess up
when he can easily beat me?
- Just when he is about to flip...
- I tell him about my mistake.
You're not so tactful, are you?
It's just that I try
to keep my boss updated.
That's a good interpretation.
It's not easy.
- Are you athletic?
- I'm pretty athletic.
You've beaten...
almost every man on the show...
except for Joo Dan Tae.
Yes, I have.
Will we get to see Secretary Cho...
beat Joo Dan Tae in season three?
(Well...)
If not, I'd get upset.
That would be Secretary Cho's
last shoot.
But you never know what will happen
in The Penthouse.
Secretary Do's video was
so beautiful and touching.
What did you think?
I'm very satisfied.
- I'd love to get the file.
- Really?
If I was Cheon Seo Jin,
I might have developed feelings
for him.
In the show,
do you have personal feelings
for Cheon Seo Jin?
Not at all.
I blame the music.
It's not my intention at all.
- It totally gave us the wrong idea.
- Definitely.
- I totally got the wrong idea.
- I know.
I'm just fond of Ms. Cheon
as a person.
- You admire her.
- Yes.
In the video, when Secretary Hong...
copied the fingerprint,
he looked so proud.
As if you really copied it yourself.
With the fingerprint aside,
there's a scene
the viewers think is...
Secretary Hong's
biggest accomplishment.
- Okay.
- Can you guess what it is?
I have many accomplishments
for sure.
Do you realize
you sound very arrogant?
- He doesn't even try to be humble.
- He looks so arrogant.
I'd guess it's...
my contribution to the romance
between Logan and Shim Su Ryeon.
(Oh...)
- It's something else.
- Goodness gracious.
It's when you reported to Logan
about Shim Su Ryeon,
- who was disguised as Na Ae Gyo.
- Oh, I see.
Logan told you
you could stop spying on her.
But then you started showing him
pictures slowly, one by one.
That's right.
One of the pictures was
of a handbag, which seems random.
Some suspected Secretary Hong
is a handbag collector.
But I have something shocking
to tell you.
This should be in the preview.
Let us decide that.
- You're telling us how to edit?
- When we were shooting,
the pictures I showed him were...
(Are you...)
(ready...)
(for a shock?)
just green sheets of paper.
(Shock loading)
They were just
green sheets of paper.
Seriously?
(So this is how variety shows work.)
The pictures I was showing him
one by one were sheets of paper.
The pictures were edited in
by the CG team...
- That's so interesting.
- afterward.
I had no idea there was
a picture of a handbag...
until I watched the show.
Secretary Hong, do you really think
this will be in the preview?
Almost every character is
in prison right now.
Doesn't that mean the secretaries
have bigger roles now?
All our bosses are in prison.
And we don't even know
if Secretary Hong's boss...
- is still alive.
- Exactly.
But I'm sure they'll try to find
a way to get out.
Secretary Hong seems restless.
- He can't stop fidgeting.
- I know.
In seasons 1 and 2,
Secretary Hong didn't appear...
- as much as the other two.
- That's right.
If Logan Lee really disappears...
What are you talking about?
- He's going to cry.
- That's how season two ended.
- Don't make him cry.
- That's why...
if Logan Lee leaves the show...
My gosh. That's...
(His reaction seems so real.)
His reaction feels so genuine.
Please don't say that.
Of course. I really hope we can
see him in season three too.
There's one important question.
Is Secretary Cho...
on Joo Dan Tae's side
or on Yoo Dong Pil's side?
The reason he stays
with Joo Dan Tae...
might be related to Yoo Dong Pil.
It seems like many people are
taking guesses...
after the last scene where I greeted
Yoo Dong Pil outside the prison.
I'm very curious too.
I want to know...
Secretary Cho's intention
behind working for Joo Dan Tae...
and if he worked for him
from the beginning.
I'm curious.
There's something going on, right?
That's my guess.
About Joo Dan Tae's trauma
related to blood,
not many people seem to know.
On top of that,
he can't stand dirty shoes.
That's right.
If you pay attention to that part
in season three,
I'd be very happy.
I think it's time
to ask this question.
Earlier...
- What did you do?
- He made a heart.
Logan.
Instead of just making a heart,
I'll give you a chance...
- to say something properly...
- Oh my.
- That sounds good.
- to Logan.
If I get to say something to him...
"Please survive", for example.
Just the thought of Logan
makes me tear up.
Seriously?
- He's acting.
- No.
I was so shocked.
He was really tearing up.
- I'm just joking.
- He keeps doing this.
Please say something to him.
Logan. Logan?
(To Logan)
I can't figure out...
whether you're alive or dead now.
But I really hope you're alive.
If you come back alive
and I get to work for you again,
you can trust
the competent Secretary Hong.
I'll take care of everything
for you.
- Hypothetically speaking...
- Okay.
If Logan somehow fails
to come back alive,
it seems like Su Ryeon
doesn't have a secretary.
- You'd work for her instead?
- So...
Ms. Su Ryeon.
I'm a competent man.
- I'm a hard worker.
- He's looking for a job.
He'd even work at Ma Ri Sauna.
(He can even work at Ma Ri Sauna.)
Right? Even if he doesn't
get the job...
- With a towel around his head.
- We'd love to see you.
It's a women's bathhouse,
so it won't be easy.
I'm ready to do anything.
You should sell
banana-flavored milk or something.
- Please stop.
- I'm sorry.
I didn't know when to stop.
I apologize.
The more I listen to him,
the more it seems like
he's talking to the writer,
- You're right.
- Kim Soon Ok.
- Soon Ok, we love you.
- We love you.
At the moment, we know nothing
about what's going to happen...
in season three.
We don't know how many episodes...
these three will appear in...
or if we'll get to see them at all.
- Secretary Hong sighed so deeply.
- Exactly.
Nothing is guaranteed.
So we'd like to give you a chance
to promote yourselves.
I'm suddenly feeling nervous.
You can do whatever you want.
- Right.
- You can do impressions, dance,
do a monologue...
- A monologue?
- Secretary Hong did mention...
that he has many things to show us.
- I have 59.
- But we can't see all 59 of them.
I wasn't planning on doing
all 59 of them.
What's the most popular one?
It's the radio show, "Cultwo Show".
The host is Kim Tae Kyun.
This is how he sounds
when he reads a story.
Okay.
"Hello. I live in Ilsan..."
- "and work for a company."
- He sounds just like him.
"I'm a 39-year-old man..."
Oh, it's a man.
(The details are perfect.)
When it's an older woman, "Hello."
Are you an actor or a comedian?
- I can do anything.
- Really?
You're open-minded.
Look how open-minded I am.
He's opening his jacket.
I'm sure you've never seen...
- the next one.
- Really?
I'll copy Jung Woo Sung's
facial expression.
Jung Woo Sung's facial expression.
It's just an impression.
I'm not saying I look like him.
The eyes are important.
(Jung Woo Sung loading)
(Complete)
(Oh!)
It's his smile.
- I've seen it.
- He looks exactly like him.
- I know what it is.
- My gosh.
Goodness.
- I know what it is.
- That's incredible.
- That's hilarious.
- You look exactly like him.
It's incredible, right?
Once you put on that expression,
you look just like Jung Woo Sung.
- Exactly.
- This feels weird.
His eyes and nose look
exactly like Jung Woo Sung's.
I just gave it a try,
and many seemed to love it.
You look just like him.
You're funnier than most comedians.
He's so good.
I should work harder.
Would you like to wrap things up
nicely here...
or do you want to try some more?
It's been going well so far.
Hwang Je Seong has already
done this.
It's Lee Kyoung Young singing
"Any Song" by Zico.
There's this gesture he always does.
(He starts
with his typical gesture.)
Why are you all so down?
(Hilarious)
What's the problem? Say something
- That's so funny.
- He's really good.
- That's hilarious.
- Let me try Lee Kyoung Young...
playing Jung Woo Sung's role...
in "A Moment to Remember".
That sounds so funny.
That's an interesting twist.
If you drink this,
we go out together.
You don't want to drink it?
I feel so lonely.
(Hilarious)
- That's it.
- My gosh.
- Oh, my.
- Nice job.
He's trying harder toward the end.
- I think that's it.
- That sounds good. It was perfect.
(Secretary Hong's self-promotion
ended successfully.)
- It's Secretary Do's turn now.
- But...
- Secretary Do...
- This is not good.
You must feel a little pressured.
We had actually decided
on the order.
What was the original order?
- He was supposed to go last.
It's our mistake. We apologize.
Do better next time.
- Do better next time.
- He's scolding us.
My goodness.
Between you two,
who wants to go first?
I actually...
was going to do impressions...
- of the cast of The Penthouse.
- That sounds great.
But after seeing what he did,
I don't dare...
- Don't be like that.
- Come on.
Why are you all so down?
Stop it.
Then I'll mix it with beatboxing.
- Okay.
- That sounds great.
I'll start with Joo Dan Tae,
and move on to Cheon Seo Jin,
and to Ma Doo Ki.
Sure.
I'm so nervous.
(So far so good)
(Beatboxing)
[Kocowa Ver] SBS 'The Penthouse S03 Special'
"Hidden Room - The Start of the End"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
What on earth did she see?
(His impression of Joo Dan Tae
is a success.)
Oh Yoon Hee?
Is it really you?
(What am I hearing?)
(Back to beatboxing)
Bae Ro Na.
- Oh, my.
- He sounds just like him.
You're so cheeky.
But I'm your homeroom teacher.
- That was amazing.
- My gosh.
What was that in the middle?
"Oh Yoon Hee?"
- "Is it really you?"
I can imagine him
practicing this at home.
- I do.
- He practices beatboxing.
Secretary Cho, will you be okay?
You must feel so pressured.
I don't have many things...
- to show you.
- Okay.
But I wanted to do my best.
So I prepared "Rollin'",
which is so popular these days.
(Can he be this cute?)
"Rollin'"? That sounds awesome.
(Can he be this sexy?)
(The pressure is driving him crazy.)
I can't imagine Secretary Cho
dancing to "Rollin'".
(How will the boy with a beard
dance to "Rollin'"?)
I'll just do my best.
- Please enjoy it.
- Of course.
I can't wait to see it.
(His facial expression
changes immediately.)
What is this?
Look at his face.
What is going on here?
Oh, my.
(He doesn't miss any move.)
(Are you watching?)
(This is the tough guy's ray dance.)
(He throws in some fancy steps.)
- Look at that.
- Look at his steps.
(He finishes up with hearts.)
He prepared a lot.
Once the song started...
He changed completely.
He's a great dancer.
What do I do?
We've had so many
funny moments today.
So many variety shows
will want Secretary Hong...
- as their guest.
- Of course.
- I wish we had more time.
- You'll be seeing Do Yeon a lot.
Why is he doing this?
I'm old.
Don't sound so sad.
Everyone gets old.
(Laughing)
He keeps talking about his age.
You're still so young.
- Okay.
- Right?
I wish we could talk to them
a bit more.
- It was so fun.
- Time went so fast.
Please say something to the viewers.
I'm so happy we got a chance...
to meet our viewers
outside the show.
I hope you continue
to enjoy our show.
- We'll do our best.
- Thank you for your support.
Show us Jung Woo Sung's smile again.
(Jung Woo Sung's smile
one last time)
It's addictive. It's dangerous.
- I can't get enough.
- Me neither.
We'll look forward...
to seeing the three of them
in season three.
Hi.
(The Penthouse kids played a big
part in the show's popularity.)
(Here they come!)
(I'll make your dream come true
on your behalf.)
(A natural talent)
(She patiently puts up
with bullying.)
(But Bae Ro Na is branded
as a murderer's daughter.)
(Apart from his mean personality,
he is absolutely perfect.)
(He changes when he meets
his first love, Ro Na.)
(Joo Seok Hoon rebels
against his father.)
(She inherited her mother's
obsession with first place.)
(Her inadequacy leads
to a mental breakdown.)
(Ha Eun Byeol,
who is forever number two,)
(is determined to be number one.)
Welcome to your nightmare.
(The queen of Cheong A Arts
High School can't stand poverty.)
(On the inside, the soft-hearted
girl misses her mom.)
How dare you?
(Joo Seok Kyung, the troublemaker
who is both strong and weak)
You have to eat very balanced meals.
(The immature boy whose parents
are his biggest strength)
(With his credentials gone, Min Hyuk
starts caring about his parents.)
(The hidden story of the Penthouse
kids begins now.)
They're finally here.
If only I could share...
- my optic nerves with our viewers.
- I know.
Isn't it incredible?
- They should see them in real life.
- Exactly.
They look even better in real life.
Each of them...
really glows.
It feels different from seeing them
in the show.
None of you seem to deny it.
No one says, "That's not true."
- I know.
- "That's not true."
- They all love themselves so much.
- The secretaries...
are watching.
By the way,
- you may wonder where Jenny is.
- She's missing.
She has an important performance...
at her school,
not Cheong A Arts High School,
but the one in real life.
That's why she couldn't make it.
I'm sure the five of you
can make up for it.
The Penthouse is extremely popular.
Has anything changed
since the show started airing?
Many things have changed.
But since we have to wear masks,
- I can't notice much of it.
- It's the pandemic's fault.
Did you know
the show would be such a hit?
This was my first show,
so I couldn't really make
any predictions.
When I read the script,
I was just shocked...
by Seok Kyung's personality.
Was this your debut show?
Almost.
(It was her first main role.)
What are you going to do now?
(What?)
What do you mean?
- What I mean is...
- Because it became such a hit?
Her debut show became
such a big hit.
What about you, Min Hyuk?
I knew it was going to be a hit...
as soon as I read the script.
Since the story is so intense,
I thought it could add
a little fun...
to the dull everyday life.
He sounds like a professor.
"The dull everyday life..."
- "The dull everyday life..."
- He sounds like a professor.
But he's always like that.
He's extremely calm in real life.
He's very mature.
- Thank you.
- He's a genius.
There's something
I really want to ask you.
Your parents must be so proud.
The people around them...
talk a lot about the show.
It makes my parents very proud.
I think I should try
to be more careful and humble...
at a time like this.
She smiles a lot in real life.
- She looks completely different.
- In the show, she glares at people.
Even before the cameras
started rolling,
she was smiling the whole time.
I wondered if she was seeing things.
(Everyone claps their hands.)
She's so lovely.
You do smile a lot.
The Hidden Room crew analyzed...
every scene of the Penthouse kids...
in seasons 1 and 2.
Surprisingly,
one of them...
turned out to be...
extremely materialistic and greedy.
Can you guess who it is?
(Seok Kyung raises her hand.)
Seok Kyung?
- No? I think it's me.
- Seok Kyung.
If it's among us.
They think it's Seok Kyung.
- This is so real.
- It's not me?
I heard that you didn't see
the script for today.
- That's right.
So they don't know
what we're going to do?
- They don't.
- We don't.
- We have no idea.
- We don't know.
All of you are going to dance
to "Rollin'" later.
- No! We didn't hear about that.
- No!
(Do Yeon's scheme fails.)
I failed.
Please tell us.
Let's see if it's really Seok Kyung.
The typical materialist
turns out to be...
Bae Ro Na.
- What?
- Why?
- It's Ro Na.
- Are you greedy?
Here's the proof. Let's watch it.
(Ro Na is full of anger.)
- She's very angry.
- She's angry.
(Fierce)
(She often rebels against her mom.)
That's right.
It's from season one.
(The only way
to make her laugh is...)
(I have presents for you.)
- She's so cute.
How did you know?
She can't stop smiling.
(Excited)
(She automatically smiles.)
She couldn't be happier.
(She also gets irritated easily.)
She gets irritated easily.
She has mood swings.
(But presents can calm her down.)
That's right.
It's very easy to calm her down.
You're right.
Mom, I'm not dreaming, am I?
I'm proud of you.
(How could you call yourself human?)
You're disgusting! You creep me out!
- Wait a second.
- She looks so happy.
You are materialistic.
The editing is so mean.
Even the song sounds so happy.
(Her mom used to creep her out.)
Yes, we're going to live here.
(Bae Ro Na's capitalistic smile)
- That was funny.
- It was true.
The editing is so mean.
(It's the result of our analysis.)
Can you relate to your character?
Since this is the third season...
and we've been shooting
for a long time,
it's easier to relate to Ro Na...
than my previous characters.
(Nodding)
Seok Hoon seems to be
immersed in his role.
(Is he still immersed in his role?)
Say something.
- He's even dressed in black.
- He's dressed in black.
You could've worn a helmet too.
We were told to wear...
- bright, casual clothes.
- That's right.
That's why we're wearing
these colorful clothes.
And he showed up in a black suit.
I didn't hear that.
Did you come straight from
the Baeksang Arts Awards?
Exactly.
How do you get into the role?
You must be more cheerful
in real life.
I am.
That's it?
I didn't expect that.
- I see.
- Okay.
Another reason for
the popularity of The Penthouse...
is the perfect acting.
Their excellent acting
definitely contributed...
to the show's popularity.
But the acting of one of them
was pretty embarrassing.
Can you guess who it is?
Is it me?
I was wondering if it was me.
Could it be literal?
(Seok Kyung lifts her foot.)
It must be me.
- We have proof.
- We do.
Let's watch it together.
She used her feet a lot.
3, 2, 1, 5. 2, 1, 3, 2.
(That's embarrassing.)
That's so embarrassing.
I'm wiggling my toes.
(I do everything with my feet.)
- She keeps using her feet.
- She's so charismatic.
- Look at that.
- She's so cute.
(She moves her foot up and down.)
She looks so cute.
(This is how I act with my foot.)
With the background music,
she looks so cute.
(Watch this.)
(Here comes the ultimate
foot acting.)
It must have been so hard
to shoot that scene.
(This time, she acts
with her entire body.)
My goodness.
- That scene...
- That was really...
It was really hard.
(Stop putting on an act.
You can't fool me.)
Oh, my.
(Seok Kyung's foot acting
gets a thumbs-up.)
It ended with a thumbs-up.
She can even express emotions
using her feet.
- I know.
- It's incredible.
Did you try to pay more attention
to your feet?
It was the director's idea.
So it wasn't in the script...
but the director ordered you
to do it?
Yes. He'd say, "How about
you put your feet up?"
He wanted me to look
more rebellious.
At first, I was wearing socks.
And he wanted me to take them off.
So I put nail polish on my toes
a couple of days before.
The scene where you fall
in the water looks hard.
It was very cold.
After I fell in the water,
Young Dae came in to save me.
He came in floundering.
And I slipped.
- I ended up falling too.
- That's right.
She said, "You should go out."
Seok Hoon is finally getting
out of his role.
When season three starts,
I'll pay extra attention
to Seok Kyung's feet.
- Let's see if there's more.
- Did I shoot more?
Can you act with your feet
right now?
Please express your emotion
right now.
- Well...
- Show us how you feel.
No. I don't know what to do.
(Flapping)
I did it.
- I did it.
- You did it?
I'm done.
Good job.
- By the way, Do Yeon,
- Yes?
we should be careful
with what we do and say today.
- You're right.
- There's a secret agent here.
The secret agent is watching us
even at this moment.
Can you guess who it is?
- Not really.
- I think this might be hard.
- Of the five of you...
- I think...
Maybe not?
- The secret agent?
- I'm not sure.
The secret agent is...
- Joo Seok Hoon.
- I knew it.
- I got it wrong again.
- Oh, because I'm always watching.
Every time I cause trouble,
he comes running over,
and screams,
"Joo Seok Kyung!"
- You shocked the audio director.
- I'm sorry.
He thought you were quiet.
(Seok Hoon said something
for the first time in 10 minutes.)
I'm sorry.
Let's look at Joo Seok Hoon's
true nature for ourselves,
after he's infiltrated
The Penthouse.
(Secret Agent, The Hoon Identity)
(Focused)
(Specialty 1, Boxing)
(Specialty 2, Stakeouts
and shadowing people)
That's right, that happened.
He was following Ro Na.
(Specialty 3, Monitoring the enemy)
- He's right there.
- That's right.
- Isn't it like "Where's Willy?"
- This is too funny.
That's so scary.
Watching from above.
(Embarrassed)
(Specialty 4, Wiretapping)
Wiretapping.
- Isn't that when you saw Ro Na?
- Yes, it is.
(He is a team leader who is smart
and makes the right decision.)
Leave the group chat
and block this ID.
And don't tell anyone.
That's right.
This part was so dashing.
(He can carry out his mission
perfectly no matter what.)
Min Seol A died in Hera Palace.
(Interrogating the suspect)
Isn't that right?
Are your memories back?
Why do I find that so cute?
(Hostage rescue)
Hostage rescue.
(He figured out the escape route
in advance.)
(He carries out the rescue
secretly and quickly.)
(The last order from headquarters)
Yes, it's me.
Tonight?
He really seems like
a secret agent here.
I'll wait for you.
- What's with the song?
- No way.
(His last mission)
(The quiet agent who resolutely
carries out his missions)
He's like a cartoon character.
(The Hoon Identity, Season 3,
coming soon)
My goodness.
- He wasn't looking for me, I guess.
- The Hoon Identity.
What did you think?
First of all, they edited it
so well, which I was happy to see.
(Could this be?)
It's like he's giving a speech
at an award ceremony.
I think you've still got your head
in the Baeksang Arts Awards?
(We'll hear the rest of your speech
at the SBS Drama Awards.)
I'm sure you noticed this too
as we were watching the clip,
but Seok Hoon acts with his eyes
so well.
(It can't be, can it?)
- To Do Yeon, could you...
- No, no.
(He's the only one
having trouble laughing now.)
- You don't have to.
- The way you look at Ro Na.
Just do it for us once.
Just pretend it's Ro Na
20 years into the future.
A lot happened to Ro Na,
and she suffered a lot
over the years.
1, 2...
(Fidgeting)
Stop fidgeting.
(Even the ones watching feel
nervous about it.)
Now, 1, 2, 3.
(No...)
- Three.
- No...
(Interpretation,
"This is too embarrassing.")
- Three.
- No...
(Do Yeon is confused.)
Do Yeon...
- Her heart was racing just now.
- No, I'm sorry.
(Do Yeon's heart was racing
within 1 second of gazing.)
I'm sorry, Do Yeon.
- As for Min Hyuk,
- Yes?
after watching this clip,
you'll be able to participate...
in season three not as an actor,
but in a different role.
Is it a camera director?
That's right, the cameras.
Let's confirm if they're right
or wrong in the video.
(Min Hyuk is in charge of filming,
anytime, anywhere.)
(That includes
dynamic sports filming,)
(with live moving shots,)
(and appropriate close-ups.)
That's right.
(He even follows characters'
movements properly.)
- Even there.
- Even in that tight space.
Quickly, do it now.
Filming sideways.
- Drink up, quickly.
- Drink it.
(He can turn horizontally filmed
videos into vertical ones.)
That's so true.
They filmed this well.
What?
I'm not the old Min Hyuk.
(Call me Director Lee from now on.)
- Director Lee.
- Wow.
Director Lee.
The current camera director
of The Penthouse is nervous.
(Chuckling)
I'm sure he really is, right?
I know I've said it but
I'm not sure about that.
He's breaking out
in a cold sweat, even now.
- So he is nervous after all.
- Yes.
I'm really curious about one
weird detail.
Do you film with your own phone,
or with a set prop?
As in, is he really filming?
Yes, I'm really curious about that.
I film with a prop.
But you're really filming?
Yes, I think they do that
so they can really use the footage.
I end up focusing more on filming
than I do on acting.
Are your skills getting better?
Yes, because I keep wanting
to make everything look good.
I'll adjust the angles.
I filmed a lot for Jenny, actually.
I'd say,
"Your right side looks pretty."
- Wow.
- That's what I'd end up doing.
You smell like a pro.
- At the last interview, Min Hyuk...
- I got a lot of criticism.
You said that it was hard for you
as a result, right?
After the last
special episode aired...
(After The Penthouse 2 Hidden Room,
The Unfinished Story aired.)
I got a lot of people
showing me their support.
- That means you acted well.
- That's right.
Eun Byeol, did you experience
anything similar?
I had a lot of scenes
where I picked on others,
so I also got a lot of criticism
for that as well.
Since I also tend to flip out
on my own, chaotically,
I think some viewers...
didn't like that side of me.
How do you feel when you see that?
Are you disappointed?
- I'm disappointed, but...
- Are you smiling at negative posts?
Now we just have Eun Byeol left,
but it turns out she has
an incredible alter ego.
Let's find out Eun Byeol's
alter ego in this video.
Alter ego?
(Ha Eun Byeol is dying.)
That's scary.
I look like a zombie.
Oh, gosh.
(In order to save her...)
Oh, no.
(Dr. Ha decides to take a gamble.)
That was shocking.
(He gives Eun Byeol
a super serum, but...)
Is she a zombie?
- A zombie.
- Eun Byeol!
What's happening?
Did something go wrong?
Do something!
(The revived Eun Byeol
experiences strange events.)
(An inexplicable ringing
in her ears)
(Strange images)
(Even ghost sightings)
That sounds like it would be
so miserable.
It's all mine.
She is sick and tired of ghosts now.
(Eun Byeol decides to become
an exorcist.)
So suddenly?
Start over with your breathing.
(Her training began.)
- She's training to be an exorcist?
- Yes.
(As her exorcism training
starts to come to a close...)
Contract your abs more.
(She even gains a legendary weapon
in the exorcism world.)
From the exorcism world.
(Exorcist Eun Byeol maxes out
her battle points.)
(She heads to Hera Palace...)
Here we go with the music.
(where ghosts have been spotted.)
There.
But...
(But she's overwhelmed
by the sight of Ro Na's ghost.)
(Scared to death
by the ghost's singing attack.)
Ro Na is right there!
- The attack?
- It's a musical attack.
(She tries wielding
the legendary weapon.)
Oh, my gosh.
(It's stronger than she thought.)
This was honestly a bit scary.
Oh, no. No!
Eun Byeol!
This is so funny.
- Here.
- Wow.
No.
Eun Byeol.
(Ro Na's ghost finally disappears.)
(Eun Byeol won her meaningful
victory with her own courage.)
(The protector of Hera Palace)
I'm amazed they managed
to edit it this way.
Wow.
(She's the exorcist, Ha Eun Byeol.)
She's an exorcist now.
We saw this in the clip too,
but you had an unusually large
number of ghost sightings.
Wasn't that hard to film?
When we film, I see the real Ro Na,
the person,
but when it airs, there are
bats flying around everywhere.
- Are you two separated?
- We start out in the same area,
and Eun Byeol attacks the air,
and then I'll go in
with a green screen,
and fly around.
(Why are you laughing?
It is a green screen.)
She's so cute.
Do you practice
any individual skills?
- Eun Byeol has a ton of them.
- No, I'm not.
She'll show them to us
while we're on set.
- Really?
- This is a set too.
(Show us.)
I'll do Krusty Krab
from "Spongebob Squarepants."
(It's already funny
before she even tries it.)
That's so funny. Krusty Krab.
"I love money."
(They totally love it.)
- That was so cute.
- She did it.
I've never seen it before
but I get a good sense of it.
That was so cute.
But as a viewer, the thing
I'm most curious about...
is that in the drama,
your singing is cleaned up...
before the show airs,
but what is it like in reality?
Opera?
- Really?
- I was curious about it.
Can we hear you sing without
the recording?
(Sing without any music here?)
(Frozen for a moment)
The three of you in the middle...
had the most scenes like that.
Let's do it.
Let's decide the order with
rock paper scissors.
You lose if you don't play,
rock, paper, scissors.
(Ro Na goes last.)
You lose if you don't play,
rock, paper, scissors.
(Eun Byeol goes first.)
I thought you were holding
the Cheong A Art Festival trophy.
(It's like the results announced
at Cheong A Art Festival.)
What are you going to sing?
The final song?
The song I sang
in the basement in season one.
- That's great.
- That's a famous scene.
I'm honored to hear this.
- That's a lot of pressure.
- Just a moment, please.
I have to warm up my voice
a little bit for this.
Of course, go ahead.
Hee, hee, hee.
She's really passionate.
(Making a big effort)
What was it again?
(She forgot the lyrics
because she's nervous.)
(Still, she works hard
until the very end.)
That was so impressive.
- That was great.
- Brava, brava!
Wow.
You sang so well for us.
She has so much passion.
- Seok Kyung, how about you?
- What shall I sing for you?
A song from season one?
Or season two?
Then from season two.
(She's confident enough to start
without even warming up.)
- This does make you nervous.
- It does.
- It does make you nervous.
- It's nervewracking.
(Gesturing to make sure
she stays on the beat)
(Seok Kyung sang this over and over
for the sake of the drama.)
(Shall we enjoy it for a moment?)
I think that's how it went.
Brava.
(Seok Kyung's performance led to
a standing ovation.)
- Brava.
- Nice.
I think I forgot the lyrics.
You were so good.
It would've been terrible
if we didn't request this.
You're exactly like Seok Kyung
in the drama.
You're so good at singing this.
Now we have the grand prize winner.
(The winner of
the Cheong A Art Festival, Ro Na)
That's right. She won.
- She got the grand prize.
- With genius-like talent.
In that case,
I'll sing the song...
I practiced with my mother,
when I was applying to Cheong A.
It's a meaningful song too.
(With the emotions of that time,)
(Ro Na sings carefully...)
(with her pure voice.)
(That's a skill worthy
of the grand prize winner.)
(Thank you.)
- That was so great.
- At first, I wondered...
- if this request was all right.
- It was so good.
- It was so refreshing.
- Thank you so much.
Right now, we've been filming...
- for a few hours.
- Right.
Do you want to hear something
incredible?
- What is it?
- We'll now start on season three...
In season three,
are all five of you
going to become adults?
We don't know.
You still don't know?
Really?
You're all trying not to say a word.
Were you all scolded by the writers?
I'm sure we'll all be adults
eventually since we're aging.
- What was that?
- That's just...
exactly what Ha Eun Byeol would say.
That was so incredible.
Tell us how you felt
as soon as you saw the script.
(Gasping)
- So that was it?
- Really? That was it.
What about you, Eun Byeol?
(What? Oh, no...)
- Eun Byeol...
- That's so interesting.
It makes me want to guess
what will happen.
What is it?
Why is she reacting like that?
(What does this reaction mean?)
Did you eat something bad?
What about Ro Na,
when you saw the script?
Oh, no.
- I see.
All three reactions were different.
- Min Hyuk?
- What a headache.
- A headache.
- I see.
Last but not least, Seok Hoon.
For me, as soon as I saw it,
I thought, "Really? Who?"
- Who?
- Was that too much?
What is it?
Because you don't know
what will happen.
As we watch the show,
we'll know what those reactions
meant after all.
So this is why Min Hyuk said that,
why Seok Hoon said that.
But maybe it'll end and we still
won't know why they said that.
As our expectations
for season three...
continue to grow,
there's another aspect of the show
that we should focus on.
There are three more characters
that hold the key to the plot.
Let's meet them through video.
My baby is sleeping so well.
I love Eun Byeol very much.
I think of her as my own daughter,
so if it's for her,
I could make a deal with evil.
(A manic obsession with Eun Byeol,
Jin Bun Hong)
My princess.
I'll be home soon. See you.
An ally who's of help to his family,
and an enemy to everyone else.
(His reason for living is family,
Yoo Dong Pil)
I'm excited
because it's been so long.
He is Baek Jun Ki,
but he also may not be.
A fake that seems real,
the real that seems fake.
(Neither real nor fake, Baek Jun Ki)
(The actors will introduce these
three critical roles personally.)
Hello, I'm actor Park Ho San,
who plays the role of Yoo Dong Pil
in The Penthouse 3.
I think many people thought of me
as a gangster.
I thought so as well, at first,
but I'm actually very detailed.
I think deeply about things,
and aspire to be a force for good...
for my family, and the enemy
to those who oppose my family.
It's understandable,
but not justifiable.
That's the role I play.
Hello, I'm actor On Ju Wan,
playing Baek Jun Ki
on The Penthouse.
Ki Joon introduced me to the role,
asking me if I'd like to meet
the writer, Kim Soon Ok.
When we first met,
the writer told me she'd like
me to play a hero-like role.
But if I listen to the things
people say about the character,
he's not a hero.
I heard he was a hero,
so I thought he'd vanquish evil,
like the Avengers do,
but what the director tells me,
and what the rumors tell me,
- is that he's a villain.
- He's the worst villain ever.
It's very confusing.
One side calls him a villain,
and the other a hero.
If I were to provide more hints
that are more helpful,
he's like a fake that seems real,
and the real that seems fake.
That means...
he goes back and forth.
Hello, I'm actress Ahn Yeon Hong,
who plays Jin Bun Hong
in The Penthouse.
She's a mysterious figure who
doesn't distinguish good from evil.
That's how they explained
the character to me.
(Critical Scene, "Hello, sir.")
Hello, sir.
Secretary Cho is close with me.
He was definitely
one of my people before.
I think that's why he came
to see me when I left prison.
How their relationship will develop,
only the writer knows that.
The unique thing about
The Penthouse...
is that no one knows what's coming.
It's amazing, and fun,
and also makes you despair.
It makes you feel many things.
It's my first time doing
a drama in this way.
But that's how much faith
we have in the writer,
and because we've achieved
good results so far,
our faith in the writer has grown
even more.
Now, I'm just making sure
I'm faithful to the script.
My poor thing.
Call me Mom from now on.
Call me mom.
Even I grew curious about it,
as I was acting out my role.
As far as I know,
Logan was the mastermind,
but why am I changing so much?
That's what I started thinking,
and I wondered if I didn't have
some kind of trauma...
related to children that have caused
this obsession,
this twisted motherly love.
To be honest, I'm very curious
about what will happen.
Can I go have a smoke first?
Sure, go ahead.
(Critical Scene,
"Can I go have a smoke first?")
(An unbelievable coincidence?
Or a secret conspiracy?)
The way I look at it, I still think
there is no relation...
between Baek Jun Ki
and the exploding car.
He got out of the car,
leaving his bag,
gazes at him once,
and then disappears somewhere.
To be honest,
some people could think
I left the bag in there on purpose,
but if there was a bomb in it,
why didn't airport security
catch it?
I don't think I'm the one
who tried to kill Logan.
(Are you sure?)
I can't be sure, with this drama.
I'm sorry, but I just think
he's not related.
(Which character should we
focus on most in season three?)
I think...
Jin Bun Hong.
(Jin Bun Hong)
I think my role is really fun,
and I think it's set up for
a plot twist coming up.
You'll be shocked if you watch.
There's something shocking
that's coming soon.
Because I'm a character
that's been around...
since season one,
I know a lot of people have
expectations while watching.
I do have a certain number
of confirmed scenes.
I'm sure everyone picked
themselves, right?
I guess I'll pick myself too.
Jun Ki is a person...
who knows Joo Dan Tae's past.
That's his greatest weapon.
I also think that Dong Pil...
will side with good,
in my opinion.
I think he'll end up being
a just person.
(Are you sure?)
I told you I can't be sure.
I don't even know about
my own character.
How can I know anything
about Dong Pil?
I just think that might happen.
Jin Bun Hong...
I've never seen her in person,
not even on set.
I'm not sure if I can say this,
but as a character,
she doesn't seem totally sane.
The way she speaks
reminds me of the movie, "Misery."
I wonder if that's the kind
of character she is.
Even when he's just standing around,
he looks so dashing.
Just looking at him is so nice.
It's so satisfying.
You should've told me that
in advance.
I'm sure she's also beautiful
and kind.
But to speak only about
her character, 100 percent,
I'm wondering if...
that might not be the case.
I said that so carefully, but all of
a sudden, after the interview...
Many of the characters in
The Penthouse...
are curious about me.
They seem to think of me
as very mysterious.
I can't tell what she's like.
She's truly a mystery.
Do I seem like a psycho?
Jun Ki's goal is
to get back what's his.
Will he waver?
That could be money,
and he might waver
due to the temptation.
I think that's one point
to watch for.
Jin Bun Hong...
doesn't have any ambitions
about the penthouse,
or about money.
But for Eun Byeol, she has a lot
of strong feelings for her only.
She's always on Eun Byeol's side.
I really love Eun Byeol.
I think of her as my own daughter,
so if it's for her,
I could make a deal...
with evil.
(But Eun Byeol already has a mom.)
We need to compete for Eun Byeol.
I'd like to meet her soon.
(Onjuwan1211,
Who am I and where am I?)
(I hope everyone looks forward
to the first episode on June 4.)
(What does this social media post
mean?)
I really didn't know who I am.
I'm playing a villain,
but also filming scenes
where I smile.
I'm pretending to be nice too.
It feels like I'm actually playing
three roles at once.
It's driving me insane.
What I was talking about is this.
What if I'm not the person...
who knows about Joo Dan Tae
and his past after all?
What if everything is a plan?
That's how far I got.
I could be Baek Jun Ki,
but also not.
You know what I mean, right?
You can see how much
this is driving me insane.
As a character,
it's a bit confusing,
so I asked Ki Joon for advice.
I heard some secretive stuff,
which went like this.
What do you think?
He said he didn't know.
(Consultation with Ki Joon is over.)
Even Dan Tae didn't know.
I think Ki Joon just gave up.
I think he's the type to focus
just on the scenes...
he's in each week.
There are still plotlines
that haven't been resolved,
embedded in the plot
like time bombs.
When will they explode?
I'm also looking forward to that,
as I continue to prepare
for my own role.
Right now, everything I said,
and everything the other actors
have said so far...
can go in one ear and out the other.
That's how chaotic
this drama will be, I think.
That's why you can focus
on what happens,
and deduce and predict things
on your own,
becoming your own detective.
I believe that way,
you'll really enjoy
watching the show.
Which person do you think
deserves the focus of attention?
I just thought of something...
- about Jin Bun Hong.
- What is it?
Some people thought this
about the character.
Eun Byeol is being punished
by meeting Jin Bun Hong.
And?
- And?
- That's all.
Oh, so it wasn't a question
or a response to the question.
You were just relaying the news.
I was just sharing what I'd heard.
What about Yoo Dong Pil?
I've met with Dong Pil...
from time to time.
- Isn't that a big spoiler?
- Is that meaningful?
That we met?
You're all making each other
very anxious.
Why are you doing that to me?
I'm not allowed to say that part?
The scariest phrase
for all of The Penthouse is this.
"Is it a spoiler?"
Is it not?
I'm curious why they met,
and what they did in their meetings.
I saw that scene with Jenny's dad,
and went to film something else
in Yangyang right afterward.
I should've greeted him,
but it was too scary.
So I couldn't greet him after all.
Is that it? Was that the news?
(Chuckling)
Please watch the show to see.
If we're just going to find out
everything by watching the show,
- what's the point of this special?
- You're right.
- If we just have to watch the show,
- Why bother talking here?
Now...
(The time everyone has been
waiting for)
it's time.
It's no exaggeration to say...
our entire show will culminate
in this video.
- None of you have seen it before?
- No.
I wonder how it turned out.
I'll introduce it using
a particularly impressive voice.
Never before seen!
You sound like Kim Kyung Sik.
(Giggling)
There is a man right here.
That's true.
- I'll add more gravity.
- All right.
Never before seen!
Here is the trailer...
for The Penthouse 3.
(The Penthouse 3)
It's the prison.
This place is just like Hera Palace.
There's a penthouse
in this prison too.
A prison penthouse?
It's my dad.
Don't you dare touch my food!
I'll break you all.
Wow.
- Dad...
- You have to eat to live.
It's not time to give up yet.
Do what makes you happy.
Logan is dead.
I don't rely on the judgment
of the law anymore.
Everything I tell you from now on,
make sure it never gets back
to Su Ryeon.
To Su Ryeon?
- What is it?
- So there's a huge secret.
Dad.
That person will reveal
Joo Dan Tae's past.
Eun Byeol's guardian is me.
Get rid of them?
If you don't want
to live like a pig,
you have to pay for your sins
no matter what.
Why did you do that?
- What was that?
- Yes, just now.
What is it?
- Get out of here.
- Seok Kyung.
Why are you insisting on dying?
I'm going to kill you all.
We have to make him
remember everything.
He's a total crazy fool.
- Where is he now?
- You think I don't know?
Do you still think
I'm Shim Su Ryeon?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- Oh, no.
- If you do anything,
I'll kill you myself.
(The Penthouse 3 airs
on June 4, 10 p.m.)
From now on,
shall we begin in earnest?
So that wasn't Shim Su Ryeon?
I was so shocked when I read that
in the script.
Oh, that line?
What was that?
(Rendered speechless)
I got goosebumps.
- That's going to be so much fun.
- They made it so well.
My heart really felt like it was
squeezing the whole time.
- I can't wait to find out.
- I can't seem to predict...
what's going to happen
in the middle.
I'm so curious now. Anyway...
From the time this show will air,
the first episode is in two days.
That's right. June 4, Friday,
is when the first episode of
The Penthouse 3, airs.
- That's right.
- We should all watch it then.
I'm so nervous.
I hope everyone watches
the show when it first airs.
Thank you so much for being with us,
here on The Penthouse 3 Hidden Room,
The Start of the End.
Any feelings you'd like to share?
We've been working together
for a whole year now.
Any regrets we have are just
turned into motivation.
With the desire to have no regrets.
To give our all.
We hope our hard work pays off
even in season three.
It's like you're making
a birthday wish...
before blowing out the candles.
"Please, I want this
for my birthday and..."
Please show us a lot of love
for season three.
(Please show The Penthouse 3
a lot of love!)