♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 31=
(Initial Practicing Method)
You gave me so many books.
Which one
can speed up my practice?
There’re thousands of books here.
I can’t remember all.
Here should be a book
Supreme Ancient Scripture.
You may find a way in it.
Your good friend Qingyan...
She’s turning 18, right?
Yeah.
Not only Dragon King is expecting,
I’m excepting, too.
Me, too.
Why do you expect?
Oh, right, you and Dragon King
are good friends.
You should feel happy and look
forward to it for him.
Yes, that’s right.
Qingqing,
your Datura Weaver Ribbon
seems to be lack of power.
Take it off
and let me give it more power.
Immortal, you’re so nice.
My pleasure.
Alright, here you are.
How is it? Does it look better?
Thank you, Immortal.
And,
thanks for your books.
See you!
Master’s birthday is coming up.
What should we give him as the gift
this time?
I heard the Garuda Flower
on the Sorong Volcano
is extremely precious.
It’s the sacred flower
of the immortal world.
Sorong Volcano is shrouded
in dark clouds
without sunlight for years.
Demons never like to go near it.
There are three trails
leading to the three peaks of it.
The sacred flower of the immortal world,
Garuda Flower, can be found there.
How do you know so much about it?
When I was helping Master
clean up his study,
I read these in an ancient book.
No wonder Master always
praises Qingyan for being gifted.
(Sorong Volcano)
This place is really scary.
That’s here.
One of the three trails
can lead us to the Garuda Flower.
Here is it.
I’ll go the right one.
Qingfeng, the middle one.
Qingyan, the left one.
Yes, Senior.
Remember. Whether we get it or not,
we have to return to the Hall
before tomorrow morning.
Yes.
See you.
(Sorong Volcano)
According to the ancient book,
the Garuda is an ancient
Dragon-eating Golden Eagle.
Its body fluid turned into flowers,
which are Garuda Flowers.
Eagles like to be on the cliff.
Then the Garuda Flower must also
grow on the cliff.
It’s Garuda Flower!
I can.
I can make it.
Master will definitely be happy!
Luckily, there are these leaves.
Why is this mountain so high?
How can I get up there?
I’d better go the other way.
Are you sure you’re going
to let her take the Garuda Flower away?
It’s just a flower.
But, what if Priest Xuanyang gets it
and makes a weapon of it?
It will be able to hurt
both demons and immortals.
Then, you’ll be in danger.
He can do nothing to me even if
he plants a courtyard of it.
Good.
But now, with her power,
she can feel my Dragon Breath.
If I want to protect her closely,
I’m afraid she would be scared.
She has met you once.
If she really likes you,
she won’t care about it.
But I care.
I hope our second meeting
can be beautiful,
not scary.
You’re thinking too much.
This fan can temporarily shield
immortal or demon breath.
I can lend it to you for now.
Soul-devouring Fan?
One of Luofeng Pavilion’s tokens.
So, I can only lend it
to you temporarily.
Remember to return it.
Don’t worry.
I can find a way out.
Why is there a firefly here?
Little firefly,
are you taking me out?
(Sorong Volcano)
I really walked out!
Little firefly, thank you!
Who are you?
It’s me.
Yuchi?! Is it really you?
Liuying, you are having a dream.
I’m Qingyan, not Liuying.
Yes,
now you are Qingyan.
Yuchi, you finally come to see me.
Although it’s in my dream,
I’m still so happy!
It will be my
18th birthday in a few days.
At that time, you need to tell me
the stories a long time ago.
Then,
since it’s in my dream,
can you
grant me all my requests?
I want you to carry me home.
Yuchi,
I feel that these fireflies
used to be always with me.
♪Does my heart ripple with memories♪
♪Only to remember you♪
It’s so beautiful!
Yuchi,
it feels so peaceful
on your shoulder.
I hope I can always
lean on you like this.
Sure.
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
Are you tired?
It’s in your dream.
There is no tiredness in dreams.
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
It’s really a nice dream.
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
Why am I at the gate now?
Wasn’t I at Sorong Volcano?
Was that
not a dream?
It was really Yuchi who took me back!
Yuchi!
Yuchi! Was that you?
My 18th birthday is coming!
You promised me to come to see me!
Then, I’m going back now!
Don’t forget your promise!
You’re really my smartest apprentice!
Qingyan,
Garuda Flower is just
what I need right now.
Master, I went together with
my seniors.
It’s just that I got more lucks.
You’re all my good apprentices.
Do you know why
I need this flower?
Could it be
that you’re worried
about the dragon demon’s attack?
That’s right.
With this flower,
I can rest assured.
Master,
the one who hurt people
down the mountain was a cat demon,
and recently there was one
of her accomplices.
That cat demon is very powerful.
Qinglu got wounded
while trying to catch her.
I arrived in time,
but she still fled away.
But she was also badly injured.
Master,
I don’t think she can go too far.
Let’s go and catch her now.
Lately, I can feel many
demons around Kunlun.
Maybe it’s not a coincidence,
but because of Qingyan.
The unique soul of Qingyan
is like a tempting ripe fruit
to the demons.
Cat or fox demons are no big deal.
What I’m worried about
is the dragon demon which has been
around Kunlun for years.
I have refined the Garuda Flower
into this Golden Eagle Dagger.
Master!
Senior is going to catch the cat demon
which hurt Qinglu.
I want to go with him.
-No!
Why?
Qingyan,
just listen to me.
I’ll take your seniors to catch
the cat demon down the mountain.
Take this Golden Eagle Dagger with you.
Make sure to carry it with you.
Take care of yourself.
Thank you, Master.
Qingqing. Qingqing.
Qingqing!
What’s wrong?
Is there any demon?
Are you alright?
Did you get hurt?
I’m fine. Don’t worry.
That’s good.
You haven’t used Three-call Spell
for a long time,
and you called me over
in the middle of the night.
I thought you were in danger.
My master and seniors are out today.
So I came here to meet you.
So, you’re just missing me!
Why don’t you
bring me anything to eat today?
How could I not?
Look!
These are the apricot and peach
preserves my senior made for me.
They are delicious! Have a try!
Your senior is so nice!
Does it taste good?
Yes! Great!
And,
my master gave me another treasure.
Let me show you.
Look!
Golden Eagle Dagger!
Take… Take it away now!
Take it away!
-Take it away!
-What’s wrong?
You…
Your dagger has
the power of Garuda Flower,
which can absorb
the power of demons.
You just opened it a bit but
it already got me a serious headache.
It’s so dangerous!
No wonder Master asked me
to take it with me.
Turns out that it can protect me
from demons.
Alright.
Qingyan,
just like humans,
there are also good demons
and bad demons.
You have to be clear about this.
Of course, I know it.
By the way,
I made a unique skill recently.
Let me show you.
So beautiful!
But, what is the
purpose of this skill?
It’s… It’s beautiful!
Yes, it is.
I made it to miss Yuchi
in my dream.
The fireflies are beautiful.
But it can only be used to tease girls.
Master,
we made Seventy-two Heavenly Formation
and finally caught
the evil cat demon.
Very good.
From today on,
you all take turns on guard duty.
This cat demon is very cunning.
Don’t take it lightly.
Yes.
Say it!
Why did you hurt people?
What’s your intention?
You killed my sister Chengcheng
and you ask me what I’m up to?
I’m just avenging my sister!
She deserves to die
for hurting my junior brother!
I was already generous
for not destroying her soul.
I’ll give you a chance.
If you tell me where the fox demon is,
I’ll spare your life.
Or, you can wait for your power
to be burned dry by the True Fire
and your cultivation
to be completely destroyed!
I have nothing to say to you!
Senior.
Don’t stop the True Fire unless she
tells the hiding place of the fox demon.
Yes.
Liuying!
Liuying! It’s me!
I’m Marble!
You saved me 200 years ago!
Don’t you remember?
Liuying?
Liuying, you are having a dream.
I never saved you.
It’s fine if you don’t remember.
I remember.
You are Liuying.
You saved me 200 years ago.
You’re my benefactor.
Even my name, Marble,
is made by you.
It hurts?
The fire burned up my power
and now it keeps
drilling into my body.
It hurts so much.
Then you can just tell
the hiding places of other demons.
My master will let you go after that.
I want to tell you.
But I really don’t know it.
Liuying,
you saved me 200 years ago.
Can you save me again?
Just stop the True Fire for a moment
and let me take a breath. Only a breath.
Master said that
we couldn’t stop the fire.
He was afraid that I would escape.
But, the fire
has already burnt up my power.
I can’t escape even if I want to.
Please! I beg you!
Her power does feel weak now.
And her painful appearance
doesn’t look like she is pretending.
I’ll never be soft-hearted to demons
like you who harmed people.
What about the dragon demon
with you before?
You also killed him?
Dragon demon?
What dragon demon?
You also forgot him?
He was so nice to you.
Who was nice to me?
What are you talking about?
How could you forget him?
As long as you let me take a breath,
I can tell you his name.
Tell me.
Come here.
His name is…
What?
How could you still use your power?
It’s not my power.
It’s you human’s knockout drops.
Very often,
humans are more vicious than demons.
Master,
Qingyan is just knocked out by the drug.
She is fine.
Cat demon!
Master, Senior, I’m sorry!
It’s my fault
for trusting that cat demon
and letting her out.
But I’ll definitely find her back.
Qingyan,
you made such a big mistake this time.
Do you know how many people were injured
by that cat demon?
Not only did we not catch other demons,
but even she escaped.
Since you have awakened,
you will be punished to go
to Introspection Wall
behind the mountains
to reflect on your mistakes.
Master.
No,
I have to get that cat demon back.
It’s easier to let her go
than to catch her again.
I can find her.
I cast Tracing Spell on her.
As long as I follow the firefly,
I can find her.
Firefly? Tracing Spell?
What are you talking about?
I never heard of it.
Behave.
Master is really angry this time.
Don’t go against his words.
You’d better go
to the Introspection Wall first.
I’ll go help him
to catch the cat demon again.
I let the demon go.
I should find her back myself.
What do you want? Who are you?
Thanks for your help.
May I know who you are?
Sorry for being rude.
You don’t need to know who I am.
Then, how should I repay your favor?
You don’t need to.
I’ll help you again.
May I ask why you want to help me?
Your enemy is also my enemy.
That’s the reason.
Enemy?
Your sister is killed by people
from Kunlun.
Don’t you want to avenge her?
I want.
I’ll definitely avenge her.
But,
Priest Xuanyang’s power…
I can help you to do it.
But you have to help me
get close to Gu Qingyan.
Qingyan?
Master,
I would say nothing
if it’s anything else.
But, Qingyan saved me
hundreds of years ago.
I can’t do such a vicious thing.
Don’t worry.
I’m not trying to hurt her.
I just want one thing from her.
As long as Qingyan is not harmed
and I can avenge my sister,
I’ll do whatever I can.
Good.
Very good.
Bold wolf demon!
Smells so good! It’s the Yin Soul!
You come to me yourself!
Garuda Flower?
You deceitful cat demon!
I’ll take you back!
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪