♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 32=
Bold wolf demon!
Smells so good! It’s the Yin Soul!
You come to me yourself!
Garuda Flower?!
You deceitful cat demon!
I’ll take you back!
Yuchi!
Leave it to me.
Yuchi! Let me help you!
Yuchi, you got hurt!
It’s fine.
Let me walk you home.
You got poisoned by the wolf.
You need to sit in meditation
and adjust breath to recover.
Let me help you with my herbs.
Ouch! It hurts!
You look like the one who got hurt.
It’s fine. Don’t worry.
How could I not?
The wolf poison is strong.
I’ll recover in days.
Don’t move!
You know what?
If you dare to escape again,
I will not spare you.
Rest assured.
I’m clear about grudges and kindness.
Since you have saved my life,
I won’t run away again.
You don’t need to tie me up.
It’s you!
It’s been more than 200 years.
I can’t believe you are still with her.
She is the cat Liuying saved.
Wait.
You don’t have inner core.
You’re just an ordinary person.
How could you still be together?
200 years?
Are you taking me as that Liuying again?
I’m Qingyan.
How could I…
Shut up!
Maybe I really mistook you for her.
Yuchi, are you alright?
I’m fine.
Your injury can no longer be delayed.
I’ll go collect some herbs.
Wait.
It’s such a tiring work.
Just let the cat do it.
Yes, I can go do it.
You?
Can you recognize the herbs?
You just want to escape!
I won’t!
But it’s good if I can have someone
to help me.
You! What did you do to me?
I sealed your power up.
If you dare to escape again,
I will not spare you!
Yuchi, have a rest.
I’ll be back soon.
Thanks.
Let’s go.
If you get Qingyan tired,
wait and see how I will punish you.
Luckily, there are many herbs
in the mountain.
Kitty!
So cute!
Seems that
they have been hungry for long.
Newborn kittens should not
leave their mother for too long.
They will die.
I’ll go find their mother.
So, you’re hungry?
Don’t worry.
Your mom is coming back soon.
Why are you back so soon?
Where is their mom?
She died.
Just under the tree over there.
She went to find food,
but died by the trap
set by animal hunters.
What about these kittens now?
Humans only keep hurting us.
Actually, there are both
good people and bad people.
My sister, Chengcheng,
lost her mom when she was
as little as them.
Luckily, I picked her up
and made her the name Chengcheng.
From that on,
we have relied on each other
and become sisters.
However,
she was still killed by
you people from Kunlun.
Don’t be sad.
I hope you can meet her again
after she goes through the tribulation
to her next life.
I know I have to go back
to Kunlun with you.
But, Qingyan,
please give me some time,
so I can help them
find another mom cat
who can take care of them.
Can I?
Alright.
Thank you, Qingyan!
Then let’s pretend that
I have never met you.
Take good care of them.
A mere wolf demon can actually hurt you?
Why is your power so weak that you can’t
get rid of the wolf poison yourself?
Did Qingyan use Golden Eagle Dagger?
Qingyan has found
that you are the Dragon King?
Did you take the Soul-devouring Fan
with you?
Lend it to me for two days.
To cover your Dragon Breath again?
I’m by Qingyan’s side.
Xuanyang will come
to kill me with Dragon-slaying Sword.
Thanks.
The Golden Eagle Dagger you said
must be dangerous.
What if she hurts you?
She won’t!
Qingyan knows that I’m bird demon.
But we are now good friends.
She won’t hurt me.
But he has already got hurt.
No, you can’t stay by Qingyan’s side.
Go back with me.
No! I won’t! I don’t want to!
No!
I’m here to see Qingyan.
You have so much work to do
in Luofeng Pavilion.
You’d better go back now.
Who is she?
No way. I have to find the answer.
I just pushed him lightly.
He just really left again.
(Luofeng Pavilion)
The Lonely Star was absent
without leave,
being punished by removing the position
of the Heavenly General,
taking out a rib and making a lute
to accompany him to reflect on his sin.
He drank the Lethe Tea willingly
to forget all the past
and was stationed at Luofeng Pavilion
for 3,000 years.
(Punishment of the Lonely Star)
It’s weird.
The details of this case are missing!
Immortal, did you find the
missing passage of the Punishment
of the Lonely Star?
Why did I leave
Terrace of Goddess Nuwa back then?
I have searched for a long time,
but I really can’t find it.
But,
I heard that some
of the Immortal Swallows
know about it.
I can help you ask about it.
Thank you.
My pleasure.
(Chronology)
(Punishment of the Lonely Star)
(Left Terrace when Immortal Qingqing
was trapped by Evil Spirits…)
Qingqing!
What brings you here?
I didn’t even call you.
How do you know I’m here?
I heard there were
bad wolf demons nearby,
so I came to have a check.
But surprisingly,
I feel your breath here.
So, here I am!
But, there is only
someone I don’t know inside.
He is Yuchi I mentioned to you before.
Come on, let’s talk inside.
Yuchi.
This is my friend, Qingqing.
She is not an ordinary human.
She is a bird demon.
We are secret friends.
Hi, Ms. Qingqing.
I’ll go make you the medicine.
Hot! It’s too hot!
-Too hot!
-Come here.
Give me that.
What’s this? It’s so dark
and smells so bad.
It’s the medicine made of herbs.
Herbs?
Let me try.
What’s this?
It’s too bitter!
I need water!
Why do you humans
drink such a terrible thing?
Yuchi, take it.
It can help you with the wolf poison.
Yes, right.
Yuchi, drink it now.
Alright.
Be careful of the heat.
Qingyan!
What’s wrong?
Qingyan,
there… there are a bunch
of wolf demons at the gate,
saying to eat you!
You… You should leave now!
Eat me?
Ridiculous! With Dragon…
With me here, who dares?
You are the one that day…
Yes.
I’m the prettiest bird demon
in the world!
Why are you here?
Of course I should be here.
Qingyan is my friend.
Anyway, let’s leave now.
Calm down.
Where are those demons from?
Come on, let’s go have a check.
Come on. Let’s go together.
These are…
All those demons?
They were obviously
burnt to ashes by the Dragon Fire.
To protect Qingyan,
Dragon King left none of them alive.
Looks like they can’t eat us now.
It’s fine.
Let’s go back now.
Come on.
I left Yuchi
alone there!
I need to be back now!
Thank you for coming to inform us.
Liuying is my benefactor.
I will do anything to help
my benefactor out of trouble.
Liuying?
Your benefactor?
Yuchi!
Luckily you’re fine.
Why does his face feel hot?
He is having a fever!
Is it because of the wolf poison?
What to do now?
Master said that
fever might hurt the brain.
Senior said skin scraping
could bring down a fever.
Wait for me!
Skin scraping?
What’s that?
I need to take off my clothes?
What… What is she doing?
Why is he still so hot?
Senior said
covering more and sweating more
could also cure the fever.
Yuchi,
let me get you another quilt.
Is this how humans
treat themselves when they are sick?
You’re sweating now!
Hot.
It’s really hot.
You’re getting better.
I’m not!
My heart is beating faster
and I feel hotter now.
Why are you sweating this much?
Come on!
We are both Liuying’s old friends!
Yes!
I didn’t expect to meet you here!
Come on!
Another toast! Cheers!
Cheers!
This is to you for Qingyan.
Loyal friend!
Cheers!
Look at you.
You’re really a loyal friend.
Qingyan has already let you go,
but you came back again tonight
to help her.
Wait! One more toast!
Of course.
I will do anything to help
my benefactor out of trouble.
You’re so loyal!
I’ll definitely make friends with you!
Let’s finish this pot!
Cheers!
-Nice!
-Great!
So happy!
It’s such a happy night!
Yes!
Let’s continue tomorrow!
Tonight we just had a good time.
Tomorrow, we should have
-the best time ever!
-Best ever!
The best time ever!
Qingqing.
Xue Qianxun?
Your best time ever?
Where did you get drunk
like a drunk cat?
Just in the woods over there.
And, I’m not a drunk cat.
She is
the drunk cat.
Do you know how long I have been
waiting for you here?
You didn’t tell me you’d come.
Let’s go inside the room.
How dare you be drunk like this!
Don’t do this again.
Why didn’t you take the sachet
I gave you with you?
Sachet?
It’s here.
I took it off when I changed my clothes.
This sachet must not leave you.
Remember?
I know.
You…
You cast Tracing Spell on it.
No wonder you can find me
immediately no matter where I go.
You are so active and nosy.
No one knows what kind of trouble
you might get into.
I… I… I…
I have Three-call Spell.
I will call you if I’m in danger.
What if you pass out?
Anyway, only when I can find you
at any time
can I feel at ease.
At ease?
Alright.
I will take it with me
wherever I go, alright?
I’ll take it with me when I eat, walk,
sleep, and do everything.
I’ll take it as you
and hold it all the time.
Qingyan
is sleeping in Dragon King’s room.
Then, let’s go to sleep, too!
♪Pure white sunshine♪
♪Clouds hide the moss♪
♪There comes the deer’s call♪
I…
We birds
are not so finicky like humans.
There are no unnecessary formalities
between males and females.
And, we birds
can not only hug,
♪Will you only hesitate♪
if we like,
we can also kiss.
♪The heart beats fast and deafening♪
♪Wait until the red sunset♪
♪Embraces the delicate breeze♪
♪Thousands kinds of beautiful flowers♪
♪Are not as good as your grace♪
♪Like a thick wine flows into the sea♪
♪And into your heart♪
After so long,
now you are not picky about beds.
But you still only recognize me.
You haven’t changed at all.
You! Why are you in my bed?
I…
Don’t get close!
Get out of it!
What did you do to me?
I…
You what?
How could you not
get my consent before…?
You have to be responsible for me!
Coming!
-Qingqing, good morning!
-Marble?
It’s early in the morning.
What’s the matter?
You said you liked my
hair clasp last night, didn’t you?
I bought you the same one in the market!
Yeah, right, last night.
You still remember it?
You’re so nice.
We are friends. Don’t say that.
Qingqing, why is your face
so blushed?
It’s a mosquito bite!
Let me help you comb your hair.
It’s brighter in the yard.
Let’s go to the yard.
You really decide to let me go?
You came back to tell me
there was a danger.
That means you are a kind one.
I’ll let you go this time.
But you have to be good in the future.
We can have another good talk next time.
About the past of 200 years ago.
Then,
see you.
Your sister is killed
by people from Kunlun.
Don’t you want to avenge her?
As long as Qingyan is not harmed
and I can avenge my sister,
I’ll do whatever I can.
Qingyan!
I’ve called you three times.
Why are you still in bed?
Qingyan?
Qingyan!
What’s wrong with Qingyan?
I don’t know why.
I can’t wake her up anyway.
It’s an ancient spell,
the Nightmare Spell.
One year in the dream is one day
in the real world.
In seven days, her soul
will be slowly absorbed by the one
who cast the spell.
Qingyan!
Qingyan is sleeping so peacefully.
The spell caster
must know her past very well
so that she can’t distinguish
between dream and reality,
staying in the beautiful dream
and not willing to wake up.
But she doesn’t know
she is in a dream?
No, she doesn’t.
We have to find the spell caster
within seven days
and kill him.
But we have no any single clue now.
Where should we find him?
You can enter the dream world
through your spiritual awareness.
The caster presents the dream
as if it were real,
but there will inevitably be flaws.
You can find out
who the caster is from the flaws.
But…
But I can’t wake up
from the dream either.
You can only tell us who the caster is
and we go kill him.
But we can’t hear
your voice in the dream world.
You have to sit still and concentrate
in order to connect to reality,
provide clues with your movements,
and you can hear our response.
What if
we fail to kill the caster
within seven days?
You’ll be trapped in her dream.
Your soul will fall into the nightmare.
That’s so dangerous!
Let’s do it.
It’s Liuying’s room.
The spell caster knows
the things of Qingyan’s past life?
This place looks so real.
He must have used hair
or skin of people familiar
with Xiahou’s Mansion
to make this.
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪