♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
Wu.
Will you marry me?
Since you made a choice,
then...
I will gift this comb to you.
I will.
How could I miss out
on Grand Sword Master's tutoring?
This sword is called
Hepta Kill.
Brothers.
Show your martial souls!
[Episode 159]
Qian Dao Liu.
There is one more person of the Martial Soul Hall
that can intimidate the entire Hao Tian.
The person my father mentioned
is not Bibi Dong,
but Qian Dao Liu.
Senior Chen Xin's father's
soul power was already at level 97,
but he still couldn't defeat
Qian Dao Liu, who was at level 99.
There should be
such a big difference between the two levels.
Unless the two people have soul skills
that are fundamentally different,
a level 96 Grand Soul Land Master
can suppress all other Grand Soul Land Master
at level 95 or lower.
In terms of the gap between level 100 and 99,
there is a 100% increase in soul power alone.
This is the difference between top masters.
All of the little freaks are geniuses.
As their skills get stronger,
they've gotten more confident as well.
They must understand
how big of a difference there is
between themselves and the true masters.
How big is the gap
between me and them?
The younger generation is indeed strong.
I was only able to defeat them
after using my Ninth Soul Skill.
Xiang.
I'm at level 59 now.
What are you gloating about?
Aren't you still the weakest
among the Seven Devils?
With my talent,
I definitely won't end up the weakest.
If you don't believe me,
let's make a bet
and see who improves more quickly
during our trip on the Haishen Island.
Fine.
I'm not scared of that.
If I win,
I get to kiss you.
If you win,
I'll let you kiss me.
You pervert!
Fatty.
Why do you keep making Xiang mad?
Maybe this is what it means
to be a quarrelsome couple.
Are you done with the sealed-off training?
Everyone seems to be in a good state.
It seems as if you've all learned something new
after fighting with Grand Sword Master.
Very good.
Remember this feeling.
Pressure is motivation.
But remember.
Never overdo it.
Thank you for your guidance, Teacher.
San.
Teacher.
Chief Ning sent someone to bring you to the palace.
His Majesty's breathing is rapid
and unstable.
Chief Tang.
Xue Beng has something to tell you.
Your Highness.
What are you doing?
Chief Tang.
Back then, I angered you multiple times
in order to save myself,
but you rescued my father from danger.
Please accept my appreciation,
or else I will never feel at peace.
Your Majesty.
Chief Tang.
I hope that you will agree to be Xue Beng's master
and take care of him in the future.
Teacher.
Tang San, Chief of Tang's clan, at attention.
I am here.
You are now appointed as Crown Prince's teacher.
You don't need to bow when you see the royal family.
Within the realm of the empire,
you will be ranked three levels higher
than all other officials.
You are granted to be duke with an alien surname,
titled Lan Hao.
Greetings, King of Lan Hao!
Thank you, Your Majesty, for your reward.
King of Lan Hao.
Open it and take a look.
From now on, this is the symbol of your status.
This item is called
the Vast Sea and Universe Shield.
It is kind of a soul guiding tool
with many magical uses.
You will see when you go back
and infuse your soul power into it.
This...
His Majesty should award you
such a precious treasure.
This shows how much he values you and Tang's clan.
Just accept it.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
This item is projecting glistening light
and water-like ripples,
dizzying those who see it.
What kind of a treasure is this?
If I use my spirit power to explore it...
What is this vast and powerful surge
of energy?
After all these years,
I've finally found someone
capable of handling this immense power.
[Soul Land]
Wu.
Don't worry.
Mu Bai just tried to inject his soul power.
Yet this thing didn't change a bit.
It probably won't hurt Brother San.
Even the Jiubao Amber Pagoda
is in awe of this treasure.
You will see when you go back
and infuse your soul power into it.
Infuse the soul power?
Brother San.
You're finally awake!
A whole night has passed.
San.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine.
This gift from Tian Dou Empire
is too precious.
Let's go.
Let me show you.
If the Peerless Flexible Armor is a magical item,
then this Vast Sea and Universe Shield
is the most magical of them all.
This is its first skill,
called Vast Sea Protection.
It can protect us and make us invisible.
Not only can it hide our physical bodies
but also our breathing,
which is its biggest use.
Its second skill is called
Universal Freezing Protection.
It can freeze anyone with spirit power
three times weaker than mine.
Even though it can't hurt the opponent,
it can buy us time.
Besides,
there is another
group attack skill called Roaring Seas
and a solo attack skill
called Demon Destruction.
I need to do more tests to explore its full power.
With it,
at least, we won't need to
leave someone on guard out in the wild anymore.
Let's go.
[Shrek School]
It's alright.
Take care.
Teacher.
Teacher, we're leaving.
Bye, Grandpa.
Be safe on the way.
Hope everything goes well.
See you!
Go!
They will go towards the west
to Tian Dou Empire's western-most sea
and then switch into boats to reach Haishen Island.
After this departure,
who knows when we'll see them again?
This journey won't be easy.
It's so far away
and we have to get to the sea.
Xiang.
Don't cry.
I promised your grandpa
to take good care of you.
I know clearly what you're up to!
Fatty.
Don't be upset.
Xiang just left home.
She must be unhappy.
I came to comfort her
exactly because I knew she was upset,
but she's annoyed with me.
[Tian Dou Empire]
[Haagendazs Empire]
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 159 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1494 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2403]
[Total scene: 59212]
[Total CGI: 27799]
[Total plan of action scene: 12408]
[Total scene model: nearly 556]
[Total character model: nearly 1002]
[Total props model: 13383]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
♪ I'm faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods ♪
♪ Who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching ♪
♪ Any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven't told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
Something's wrong.
There's no one here.
It was brightly lit the entire way,
but there's no sound at all.
This is...
a wolf?
They are blood-thirsty.
Once attacked, they'll be relentless till death.
They're extremely hard to deal with.
Stop!
Xiang!
San.
What should we do?
Do you want to die?
Oh, no!