♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 29=
Dragon King must have taken Chenyue
back to Dragon Pool to get married.
No!
I have to prepare the dowry for Chenyue!
It’s not the human world here.
There is no need for
betrothal gifts and dowry.
Your immortals’ marriage is so boring!
No. Other things can be unnecessary,
but the red wedding dress and
the love token are indispensable.
They have already had love tokens.
Then, they need red wedding dress!
I need to go to tell them!
I’m going!
But the red wedding dress and
the love token are indispensable.
Greetings.
My Lord, what brings you
to my place?
Can’t I come for nothing?
You can, of course.
I’ll just look around.
Enjoy yourself.
(Documents for the Three Realms)
(Treasure Brochure)
My Lord, are you
looking for some treasure?
You get me wrong.
But now that you mentioned the treasure,
I’d like to have a look.
Xue Qianxun...
Why doesn’t he admit
he’s coming to look for treasure?
Enjoy it, please.
I have a treasure brochure.
Would you like to have a look?
(Treasure Brochure)
(Ancient Weapon, Supreme Sword)
Ancient Weapon?
Supreme Sword.
Garuda’s Bone?
They’re all killing weapons.
Is there something elegant?
The Eternity Jade Brush is good.
Qingqing uses no pen,
but an eyebrow pencil.
She won’t like this Jade Brush.
Keep it to yourself
for writing the Book of Fate.
Looks like
you don’t have any treasure
that is elegant or gorgeous.
Are you looking for some treasure
for a girl?
What a ridiculous thought!
You’re not?
I’m thinking too much, then.
Keep pretending.
What’s in the box?
It’s...
It’s a treasure I just found.
What?
I can’t see it?
No.
The Datura Weaver Ribbon
has gorgeous and complicated patterns.
I don’t think you’ll like it.
Datura Weaver Ribbon?
How does it function?
It’s made
by Weaver Fairy.
It feels as soft as breeze.
Mostly importantly,
it can cover all kinds of scars
and then disappear.
Its fragrance calms people down, too.
It took me many efforts to find it.
It’s useless to you.
Come and check the Supreme Sword.
No.
I want the Ribbon.
Come on.
Xue Qianxun.
I haven’t enjoyed it yet.
I know your rule.
I must exchange one treasure
with another.
Xue Qianxun!
Why isn’t he in?
What the hell!
It looks so beautiful.
What’s...? What’s this?
The patter of the headband...
And the color...
How old-fashioned it is!
He’s always dressed plainly.
But the headband for a girl
looks so ugly.
For a girl?
I’m the girl staying with him,
aren’t I?
He’s giving me a present?
-Give me a present...
-Qingqing?
I come to discuss with you
about the present for Chenyue.
When I didn’t see you,
I got in directly.
This box looks pretty.
It does?
Yes.
It also looks expensive.
Is it a present for someone?
I didn’t mean to give it to you now.
But it seems that
you like it a lot.
What do you think?
Is it nice?
Yes!
The pattern looks...
beautiful.
The color is...
yellow.
You’re always dressed nicely
and your present for someone
also looks nice.
I’m glad you like it.
This is my love token for you.
Love token?
He gave me a love token?
God, what a surprise!
The color is quite...
Luckily, I’m the prettiest bird.
Close your eyes.
My Meteor mark...
It’s gone.
It’s really gone!
What’s this?
It must be valuable.
I got it accidentally.
Immortal-trapping Net?
I made it myself.
I’ll exchange it
for the Datura Weaver Ribbon.
Are you serious?
The Immortal-trapping Net
cost large power.
It took you three hundred years
to make one.
Aren’t you suffering great losses?
Come on.
Take away the Three Pearl Leaf Tea, too.
Thank you, then.
It doesn’t matter.
I like whatever you give me.
Thank you.
I’m going to help Chenyue
with her wedding.
So beautiful!
Is it you...
Not me.
It’s God’s will.
With the Star Halo as a proof
and the Dragon Pool as the present,
Chenyue,
will you marry me,
and never leave me?
I will.
You’ve given me so many things,
but I have nothing to reward you.
I want nothing,
but you.
I see.
Take my hair and I’ll be with you
now and forever.
Now and forever.
Why did you squeeze me?
Don’t squeeze me.
They nearly kissed.
Go on. Go on.
-Yes.
-Go on with that.
We’re leaving immediately.
We’re leaving.
Congratulations, Dragon King.
-Congratulations, Dragon King.
-Congratulations on your marriage.
Has the Star Halo satisfied you?
Thank you, Immortal of Rain.
Thank you, everybody.
Dragon King, you get married at last.
We’ll no longer worry
you’ll break into the palace again.
He’s right, Dragon King.
We also helped a lot
with your marriage.
Propose more toasts to us.
No problem.
General, when you get married,
you should follow the mortal way.
It’ll be more interesting
when you wear the red wedding dress,
drink cross-cupped wine
and bow in the wedding.
Dragon King, you’ve already prepared it.
This wedding robe looks so gorgeous.
With so many layers,
it looks terrific.
It was prepared a century ago.
Liuying is me.
I’m Liuying.
Right?
Sure.
This wedding dress looks more beautiful
than the one Consort Yu wore.
Dragon King cares a lot about you.
You’re Liuying.
But you’ve lived a military life.
You must have a different taste.
I guess you’ll like this better.
Yes. Yes.
General looks the best
in this kind of dress.
♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if the moon shone for you♪
♪Bright or dim♪
♪Fate is like a rain of flowers♪
♪Withering in the sentimental world♪
♪In a flash I picked your teardrop♪
♪Does my heart ripple with memories♪
♪Only to remember you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
Congratulations, Dragon King.
Thank you, everybody.
We’ve watched you for over a century.
At last, you get married.
Here’s a Karma Stone,
as our wedding present.
Karma Stone?
You broke Matchmaker’s stone?
Nonsense. We didn’t dare to.
You have no idea.
This is quite popular lately.
Use the power
around the real Karma Stone.
Lethe Ice and pottery clay
are mixed
and made into the small Karma Stone.
When the couple’s names
are craved on it,
they’ll always be together
and have unforgettable good luck.
Is that so?
You really know how to live it up.
It’s a great present.
Thank you.
(Longyan)
How beautiful!
You haven’t changed at all.
They’re for you two.
You take this one with his name on.
And you take this one with her name on.
You own him and he owns you.
(Longyan & Chenyue)
Time for the cross-cupped wine.
After that,
you can go back to your bedroom.
Wait!
Wait. Wait.
Dragon King,
I must remind you.
Your wedding should be in the future,
instead of now.
She’s the soul bred in the world.
Without experiencing in the human world,
how long do you think she can exist?
She lives
as long as I live.
I know you’re going to protect her soul
with your own power
and make her live forever.
But don’t forget.
She’s still the Yin soul
all demons want.
Are you sure you won’t leave her
for even a second?
What do you think
I should do?
When she lives in the human world
and learns arts of immortality,
with your help,
she can become immortal
with a human body.
By then, she can stay with you frankly
and you can never leave each other.
Dragon King, he makes sense.
But...
I agree.
I don’t want to live
under your protection forever.
You can’t defend me
for thousands of years
and never leave me alone.
I don’t want to be your burden.
I want to face everything
with you.
By then,
let’s get married.
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
Is it really so hard to enjoy a wedding?
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
Will I
totally forget you?
I’ll find you immediately
and protect you.
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
This time,
I’ll watch her
drink the Lethe Tea.
Don’t worry.
I promise she’ll drink it.
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
If I can’t remember you in my next life,
♪It lingers around♪
you must remind me early
of our promise.
♪If I no longer miss you♪
I will.
I’ll seize you tightly.
Hope you’ll be well prepared.
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪The destiny lasts for years♪
♪I’ll pay it back with lives♪
♪I give you my youth♪
♪For the exchange of my wish♪
♪This is our destiny♪
Qingyan.
Don’t help her.
Let her stand up alone.
You two just came to our sect.
Besides practicing arts of immortality
and martial arts,
you must remember our rules clearly.
Every member of our sect
must follow the rules
and never go against them,
no matter when or where.
Understand?
Yes!
Come.
Read after me.
Respect masters, punish the evil
and praise the good!
Enforce justice and kill demons!
Very good.
What about you?
Enforce justice and kill...
Kill demons.
Thank you, Qingfeng.
Kill...
Qingyan,
why can’t you even remember
such simple rules?
Master, why must we kill demons?
It’s our duty to kill demons
so that they won’t hurt the human world.
It’s also the natural rule.
What about kind demons?
Can’t we stay with them in peace?
All demons are evil.
Every demon comes to the human world
with a purpose.
I hear that
swallows delivering messages
to Queen Mother of the west
are also demons. But they’re not evil.
Swallows?
They’re domesticated.
They’re different, of course.
We can’t domesticate them
if we kill them.
Anyway,
our duty is to follow the natural rule
and protect common people.
Every member of our sect
must kill all demons they see.
Understand?
I do.
I don’t.
If you don’t,
go out and have a time-out!
Why did Qingyan get punished again?
Don’t go there.
If we get close to her again,
she’ll be more severely guarded.
Then we can’t even peek at her.
But...
No buts!
Look.
Look at her.
Does she look like she’s being punished?
She’s quite enjoying herself.
Master,
I sensed the dragon demon again.
Take some men
to check the circle I set.
Let nothing go wrong.
Master,
why does the dragon demon
approach our sect
again and again?
If the Yin soul is used by demons,
it’ll play a dreadful role.
Demons will have extra power
of one hundred thousand years.
This is why
I brought Qingyan back to us.
I don’t want any ambitious demon
to have the Yin soul.
You mean
the dragon demon comes for Qingyan?
I’m not sure yet.
But he’s indeed getting closer.
Luckily, the Yin soul easily dissipates.
But it’s hard to be taken away.
It must be raised by abundant power,
strengthened by spirit
and protected by aura.
The longer, the purer.
Qingyan is still a little girl.
We don’t need to worry now.
Whoever wants it
won’t take rash action, either.
But the dragon demon...
Don’t bother.
If he takes any unusual action,
I’ll kill him
with my Dragon-slaying Sword.
What are you doing?
I understand how you feel.
It’s hard to wait when failing
to see the destination.
It’s the hardest to wait
when seeing the destination.
You’ve waited for such a long time.
Can’t you wait patiently
for another dozen of years?
Don’t rush to approach Qingyan.
Your strong dragon breath
will hinder her soul development.
Qingyan has a special soul.
She needs the spirit
from the Kunlun Mountains.
After she reached the Foundation Phase
at the age of 18,
she won’t be interfered by your breath.
Then with the help of elixir,
she can enjoy a long life forever
and become an immortal.
Figured umbrellas.
Fun, isn’t it?
Yes.
Thank you.
Father, look. That’s so fun.
Be careful.
Cosmetics.
Sachets.
Sachets. Pendants.
(Qi’s Jewelry, Yuxing Inn)
Figured umbrellas.
Sachets. Pendants.
Qingyan,
why did you follow me sneakily?
I want to come with you
and visit the fair in town.
I’m not coming to visit the fair.
Demons have appeared lately.
Master asked me to come down
and check on them.
Come with me.
(Qi’s Jewelry, Yuxing Inn)
Qingyan,
I’m getting in and ask for some info.
Stay here and don’t leave.
If you get lost,
I won’t go look for you.
Roasted chestnuts!
I can’t go. I can’t go.
She asked me to stay here
and not to leave.
I can’t go. I can’t go.
Sweet and delicious roasted chestnuts!
Sweet roasted chestnuts!
Roasted chestnuts!
Little girl,
you want some roasted chestnuts?
I want to...
Have a look at the dragon tassel.
You want this?
Come closer.
Then you can look more clearly.
Come over.
Girl,
you have such a special soul.
If I eat your soul,
my power will be greatly enhanced.
Big brother.
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪