♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 30=
You’re awake?
Big brother, where are we?
On the way back to Kunlun Mountains.
Thank you for saving my life today.
You’re welcome.
What’s your name, please?
I’m Yuchi Longyan.
Yuchi,
have we met before?
Why did you ask?
No reason. I just find you familiar.
Yes.
We met a long time ago.
Why can’t I remember?
It doesn’t matter.
This is for you.
How lovely!
Do you like it?
Yes.
Thank you, Yuchi.
You’re welcome.
When can I
see you again?
Not until you grow up.
I have to wait that long?
Yeah.
When I’m 18,
come and tell me
the old story,
will you?
I will.
I’m leaving, Yuchi.
Be careful.
Why did you leave Qingyan alone
outside of the inn?
Gather our men and go look for her!
You must get her back!
Yes.
Master.
Kneel!
How dare you!
You remember to come back?
Who allowed you to leave?
I’m sorry, Master.
I was standing outside the inn,
but I met a demon.
A demon?
How did you get away?
The demon was about to eat me.
Luckily, Yuchi saved me.
Yuchi?
Which sect is he from?
I didn’t ask.
You didn’t know who he was,
and you let him walk you back?
What if he’s a bad man?
If he were a bad man,
he wouldn’t have saved me.
You...
Anyway,
you must be cautious against strangers.
I see.
Stand up.
When practicing in our sect,
you must learn to calm down first.
If you don’t calm yourself down,
how can you learn arts of immortality?
From now on,
you must play the Mind-clearing Song
two hours a day
until you can remove
distracting thoughts
and are no longer fun-loving.
Yes, Master.
Why must you kill me?
Cat demon, how dared you
disturb the human world
and seduce Mr. Xu!
My husband and I have true love
for each other.
Please let us go.
But Master said that
demons and humans were different races.
They mustn’t get married.
But my husband and I love each other.
Why can’t we get married?
No one can tear us apart.
Qingyan, kill her!
Stop her from talking nonsense.
Darling!
Chengcheng.
Darling, leave! It’s dangerous here.
Chengcheng hasn’t done anything evil.
She...
She’s my dear wife.
Please let her go.
Do you know she’s a demon,
instead of a human?
I don’t care what she is.
I just know she’s my wife.
She has totally muddled your mind!
Senior,
looks like they have true love
for each other.
Can you let her go?
Demons and humans are different races.
Don’t you remember what Master said?
Let’s go.
Stop!
Darling!
I... I didn’t mean to kill him.
I had meant to kill the cat demon.
Chengcheng...
You killed him.
I’ll make you pay with your lives!
Chengcheng!
Darling!
Demon, how dare you hurt my junior!
-Darling, I’m here.
-Senior!
Chengcheng, you...
Leave.
My husband and I love each other.
What wrong have we done?
I beg you.
Please bury me
with my husband.
Darling,
wait for me.
I’m coming to you.
She...
She exploded her inner core.
She really died for love?
Humans, immortals and demons
turn out to be void.
All realms and destinies
end up in Luofeng.
People in Kunlun Sect
are quite merciless.
Mortals usually think
all the other races are vicious,
not to mention the demons.
What about immortals and demons?
Even if the Three Realms collapse
and the world reveres,
I won’t leave you.
When I see Qingyan feeling sad,
how I wish I could make her happy!
She isn’t Feng Chenyue anymore.
She’s Qingyan, who is always determined
to kill demons.
You must be very careful
and don’t get close to her.
Understand?
Let’s go.
Humans, immortals and demons
turn out to be void.
All realms and destinies
end up in Luofeng.
Let’s take Qingwu back
and have Master cure him.
Qingfeng,
bury the man.
Senior, but the cat demon said...
How can a demon be buried with a human?
If Mr. Xu hadn’t been obsessed with her,
he wouldn’t have died.
Please bury me
with my husband.
A smell of demon?
Pay with your lives for my sister!
Where’s my sachet?
I didn’t go anywhere else today.
It’s really here.
The cat demon is your sister?
Qingyan’s voice.
Why is there another demon?
Stop!
You’re a demon, too.
Why don’t you help me?
I am helping you!
If you hurt her, you’ll be dead.
You’re scared that
Kunlun Sect will take revenge?
I’m not scared.
I must avenge my sister.
You...
You’re the cat demon’s sister?
Did you see her kill your sister?
I...
Because of demons like you
who mistake people indiscriminately
and hurt humans,
mortals have a deep understanding of us.
Why does she look so familiar?
How did you hurt your paw?
Let’s go up the mountain
and I’ll pick some herbs for you.
I’ll cure you.
It’s her.
If you dare to hurt her again,
I’ll call for helpers.
Then you can’t easily get away.
Are... are you alright?
I’m fine. She can’t hurt me.
Qing...
I’m Qingqing.
I’m the prettiest bird demon.
Qingqing?
I’m Qingyan.
Thank you for helping me.
I thought you...
You thought all demons hurt humans
who couldn’t tell right from wrong?
I had thought like that.
But you surprised me.
Many more things will surprise you.
Nothing.
Tell me.
Why are you coming here
in the middle of night?
I’m here to fulfil her last wish.
You fulfilled their last wish.
(Mr. Xu’s Tomb)
They’ll be grateful in the heaven.
I hope that
they can still be together
in their next life.
I must go back soon.
Qingqing,
can we be good friends?
You and me?
But I’m a bird demon.
Don’t you worry about your master?
Master said that
all demons were evil.
But I think
all creatures can be kind and evil.
Yes, yes. You’re much smarter than him.
Don’t criticize my master.
All right.
Let’s...
Let’s be good friends secretly.
All right.
There’s a circle
around the Kunlun Mountains.
What should I do if I want to see you?
Let me teach you the Three-call Spell.
Follow me.
Put your palms together.
Turn.
Clever girl.
Call my name three times.
Qingqing. Qingqing. Qingqing!
When you want to see me,
use the Three-call Spell.
I promise I’ll turn up.
I’ll often summon you, then.
Qingyan,
where are you going?
I...
What are you hiding?
Osmanthus cake?
Give me a piece.
Qingfeng,
may I ask you something?
Do you think
there are kind demons?
According to Master,
all demons are evil.
But think about it.
There’re kind and evil humans.
There must also be kind and evil demons.
You make some sense.
But what Master says
matters more.
But...
What are you doing here,
instead of practicing?
Master.
When I was practicing,
I felt hungry.
I asked Qingyan
to get me something to eat.
Lately, demons are raging in town
and have hurt many people.
I guess the dragon demon did it.
It has been living nearby for years.
When I track him down,
I’ll take men to kill him.
You two should also practice hard
so that you can kill demons
as soon as possible.
Yes, Master.
Why does my heart hurt
when he mentions the dragon?
Is it delicious?
Yes.
You still remember
I like osmanthus cake?
Remember? What do you mean?
How do you know
I like osmanthus cake?
I guessed.
Because I like it.
I think you like it, too.
So, I’m right about it.
It tastes great.
Enjoy more.
Let me wipe your mouth.
Qingyan!
Qingqing,
my master is coming. Leave immediately.
Qingyan!
Master, you’re looking for me?
Didn’t I ask you to practice?
Why are you here?
The...
The scenery is great here.
Qingyan,
when you were here,
did you feel anything unusual
or did you see anyone?
No.
That’s weird.
The dragon demon’s smell is near.
Even the Dragon-slaying Sword
can sense it.
Master,
I didn’t see any dragon demon.
Qingyan, I know you’re a kind girl.
But under the circumstances,
I have to tell you something.
You have a special soul
that demons eagerly want.
That’s why
I always tell you that
all demons come to you
with a purpose.
I...
I have a special soul?
So, you must stay away from demons,
especially the dragon demon.
What’s wrong?
Nothing, Master.
You must be very careful.
Thank you for your concern, Master.
Since I took you back,
the dragon demon
has been lingering around.
Dragons have strong bloodline.
If they go the right way,
they’ll be Immortal of Dragon.
If they stay in the human world,
they’ll be evil dragons.
You must keep it in mind.
Yes, Master.
Go on with your practice.
Six day. Seven days. Eight days.
Nine days. Ten days.
Qingyan.
Qingfeng.
You’re turning 18 in a couple of days.
Senior Sister is learning
to steam the peach-shaped cake for you.
Look.
Smells great.
Have some, too.
I don’t like sweet food.
Enjoy it yourself.
Bring my gratitude to her.
How many days did I count?
Yuchi.
On my 18th birthday,
will I see you?
Qingqing. Qingqing.
Qingqing!
Qingyan, osmanthus cake for me again?
Not osmanthus cake.
Look. Peach-shaped cake.
Peach-shaped cake?
I remember
it’s not your 18th birthday yet.
It’s in a couple of days.
But Senior Sister cares for me.
She made the cake for me in advance.
It’s so nice of her.
Is there anything wrong
with the cake?
No. No.
Then why are you staring at me?
I want to ask you
if it tastes delicious.
Yes. Sure, it does.
Qingqing,
I have something to ask you.
What?
Look at this.
Looks so beautiful.
Is it for me? It’s so sweet of you.
No, no.
It’s not for me?
Well, the style
doesn’t suit me.
Its color suits men more.
Do you really think
it’s suitable for a man?
If I want to give it to someone,
shall I embroider some flowers on it?
As played in the drama,
if an unmarried girl
gives a man something she embroidered,
it’ll be a love token!
Love token?
Who will you give it to?
Who is he and what’s his name?
Who’s there in his family?
The man I told you last time...
Yuchi.
Him?
He’ll like whatever you give him.
Really?
Yes.
Am I really going to give him
a love token?
Isn’t it too soon?
He won’t realize anything, will he?
What’s on your mind?
Nothing.
Then why are you giggling?
I’m not.
You are.
You are. You are!
I’m not.
Qingqing, I heard that
a dragon demon had appeared nearby.
Then?
Master told me that
no dragons became Immortal of Dragon.
They’re all...
All what?
What’s wrong?
I don’t know why,
but every time I mention a dragon,
my heart hurts.
Did your master tell you that
all dragon demons
were overbearing and cruel?
The dragon demon is overbearing.
But he isn’t cruel,
especially to...
Dragons...
Dragons are nice.
Really?
Yes.
Xue Qianxun, your Three Pearl Leaf Tea.
Drink it.
What’s behind your back?
This is for you.
It’s...?
It’s the feather you took off.
It’s for me?
You gave me a present.
I...
I want to give you a present, too.
The Datura Weaver Ribbon you gave me
is so precious.
My feather is far less valuable.
The Datura Weaver Ribbon
is an external thing.
But the feather is from your body.
It’s precious for sure.
Qingqing,
how are you going
with Heaven Secret Art?
Oh, dear.
Why did he ask about my practice
at such a romantic moment?
What kind of immortal
am I in love with?
The tea is quite bitter.
I’ll go get you some sweetmeats.
Do you know
why I ask you to keep practicing?
Because I’m too weak.
You don’t want others to think
I’m not good enough for you.
Nonsense!
As long as I like you,
you’re good enough for me.
You will die,
unless you become an immortal.
Bird demons have a short life.
But I...
I want to be with you
for thousands of years.
Qingqing,
when you become an immortal,
I want you to marry me.
What are you talking about?
I haven’t promised to marry you so soon.
Qingqing and I in my memories
seem different from what we are now.
(Initial Practicing Method)
You gave me so many books.
Which one
can speed up my practice?
There’re thousands of books here.
I can’t remember all.
Here should be a book
Supreme Ancient Scripture.
You may find a way in it.
Your good friend Qingyan...
She’s turning 18, right?
Yeah.
Not only Dragon King is expecting,
I’m excepting it, too.
Me, too.
Why do you expect it?
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪