=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 20=
(Pleasure House)
I’ve admired this place for long.
I must get in.
If you don’t like it,
go back and wait for me in the inn.
After I have enough fun,
I’ll go back to you.
Wait.
What?
Do you need me
to walk you back to the inn?
No.
I just don’t understand.
It’s a place
for men.
Come in.
What fun can you have?
Or do you
simply want to get rid of me
by getting into this place?
You’re poorly informed.
There’re female demons in it,
as well as male demons.
What?
When males can come,
females can’t?
Well, Lord Fengran,
please kindly enlighten me tonight.
After you.
There you are.
I’ve been missing you.
Come in.
That is Xuanjing Palace,
where Demon Lord Ziyue is.
It’s heavily guarded.
We can’t force in.
You quit muscling things out now?
When did I ever muscle anything out?
You’re impulsive
and have a bad memory.
Yesterday, you had a fight.
Whenever I rectify injustices,
Jingjian will call it heroic.
Why do you sound the opposite?
Well, please use your brain
and find us a safe plan.
Perhaps,
we can muddle through
disguising as guards.
The guards are from one garrison.
What do you say the possibility of them
not knowing each other?
Right.
That was ill-considered.
You should muscle this out.
Hey! Qin!
What can I do for Your Highness?
Qin,
take the badge back.
By returning the badge
to command all troops,
I meant to resign.
From now on, Xuanjing Palace and I
are no longer related.
Are you going to
force me to stay by your rank?
You resigned knowing that
I don’t want you to leave.
Qin,
is there no way
for us to reconcile?
Li.
Li, why did you come out?
Didn’t I tell you?
Your spirit is weak
and could catch cold.
Qin!
Don’t go, please.
Isn’t this Prince Sen Yu?
It’s the demons’ rules
that the strength has the say.
Since you don’t let me go,
then fight me.
If I win,
no one from Xuanjing Palace
can stop me from leaving.
Qin,
don’t be ridiculous.
Sir, sunflower seeds hot from stove.
Speaking of snacks,
nothing produces the same lingering taste
as walnut-flavored
sunflower seeds from Dibei City.
If immortals in Heavenly Palace
see you like this, they’d shed
tears of disappointment.
What’s the problem with it?
Too worldly.
I eat grains.
That makes me an ordinary man.
Besides,
only True Gods and Goddesses
can be abstinent from food.
In these poor
immortals’ eyes,
you’re a cool god free of worldliness.
They shed their tears for nothing.
I hate my cool face
for those unnecessary attention.
Alright.
I know you’re not pretending.
The man down there
is the second demon prince, Sen Yu.
The girl is Chang Qin, the fox princess.
They were a demon couple
engaged for marriage
thousands of years ago.
Then why are they fighting?
The story began from the war
between immortals and demons.
Sen Yu was severely wounded
and saved by a fox.
The fox
gave her demon core to him.
Thus, she could never
transform to human.
Sen Yu took her back to Xuanjing Palace
and promised to look after her
for her lifetime.
The fox princess
is proud.
She would not swallow the insults.
In anger, she broke their engagement
and insisted on leaving the third heaven
and back to her kind.
It’s common that affection disappears.
Why such a fuss?
That’s very hypocritical.
Sen Yu is a man.
Don’t all men in the world
want everything to be perfect for you?
Not the man you’re looking at now.
Forget about what I said.
Lord Qingmu.
Call me Qingmu.
Qingmu,
why do you possess Demon Power?
It’s fine if you don’t want to tell.
To us from Qingchi Palace,
immortals and demons are equal.
And I will not disdain you for that,
or tell your secret to the immortals.
No secrets
between you and me.
The Demon Power has been there
since the earliest of my memory.
It doesn’t show usually.
But when I perform great power,
it would spiral out of control.
Immortal and demon powers coexisting?
It’s never been heard of.
Yes.
So I want to find Boxuan fast
and ask about my past.
It’s odd.
They should be neck and neck
in strength.
How did Sen Yu make such great progress?
Chang Qin must have regressed.
She’s too weak to power this move.
Are you hurt?
Qin,
you know
Li has always been fragile,
- so I have to...
- I have no interest
in your business.
Without my order,
no one would let you leave.
Your Highness.
This female demon is troublesome.
If she’s not well,
she should stay in
and get herself a physician,
instead of coming out here.
What did you say?
She is troublesome.
The last part.
I know a way to get us in.
What is this?
You let her come out
knowing that she’s weak.
I asked you
to find a physician yesterday.
Where is the physician?
Pardon me, Your Highness.
I’m a physician.
What are you doing?
I got this.
Your Highness,
I’m Beichi, a fox
who excels in treating diseases
for foxes.
I can see you’re greatly concerned
of Miss Li.
Why don’t you give me a chance?
You’re from Mount Jingyou?
Which clan?
I’m one of the black foxes.
Elder Chang Mei is my master.
This is my apprentice, Nanmu,
a roan fox
who just transformed to human.
Elder Chang Mei’s disciple
must excel in medicine.
Come.
Take a look at Li.
Fortunately that Fengran
told me all sorts of bizarre stories,
so I know Sen Yu and Chang Qin,
and the gossips about the families
in the Three Realms.
The Spirit Reviver is of no use to me.
It’s the fox’s lucky day.
You’re truly skilled.
I’m impressed of
Elder Chang Mei’s disciple.
Why don’t you
come with me to Xuanjing Palace
as a guest?
Is it good?
My master asked me to travel around.
I can’t be a trouble to you.
Yes, Master Beichi.
Elder Pinghui of the flood dragon clan
is waiting for us to treat him.
We can’t stay.
Young master,
you can cure flood dragons’ diseases?
Marvelous!
Come to Xuanjing Palace.
You’ll be my honored guest.
Alright.
I gave Elder Pinghui some magic pills.
I suppose he’s recovered.
Miss Li has been suffering for long.
Her affliction is more pressing.
Let’s stay a few days in Xuanjing Palace
and look after Miss Li.
Great!
This way, please.
My apprentice,
take my medicine chest
and follow me.
There are restrictions everywhere.
Demon Lord Ziyue is an eminent figure.
I wonder where he lives.
Master Beichi,
how is Li?
Don’t worry, Your Highness.
I’m about to give her treatment.
Houchi, Houchi.
The fox lost her demon core.
Her power is drained
and her soul fragile.
Even the Heavenly Emperor
can’t cure her.
Can you?
My power is not strong enough,
but I learned all sorts of skills.
If anything goes wrong,
make an excuse and run.
I’ll take the blame.
Look at yourself.
Don’t give us out.
Take care of yourself.
Young master,
how did it go?
Don’t worry, Your Highness.
Li!
Li.
Your Highness.
You can transform to human.
I...
Miss Li lost her demon core.
It’s difficult to transform.
Acupuncture can only
keep her form for a few days.
But don’t worry, Your Highness.
Miss Li’s affliction is hard
to be cured,
but I know it well.
In three days with acupuncture,
Miss Li can gather power in her body
and cultivate without a core.
Then she can transform to human.
Is it true?
Thank you, Master Beichi.
Servants!
Take the young master to change
and ready the feast.
I’d like to extend my gratitude.
No, no, no.
My master doesn’t drink.
That’s not necessary.
You have no manners as an apprentice.
I’m talking to your master.
How dare you interrupt me?
You’re right.
I’ve been admiring
Xuanjing Palace since I came.
There are so many questions to ask.
Master.
Please make sure my apprentice
is taken to somewhere he can rest,
in case he makes any trouble.
Of course, young master.
You demons
do know how to enjoy life.
Well,
thank you for saving Li.
This is to you.
It’s what I do.
Don’t mention it.
Your love to Miss Li is deep.
I’m impressed.
I lived in Mount Jingyou all year long
and never knew a place
with such grandeur as Xuanjing Palace.
The purple moon hanging above
close to the front gate
is brighter than anywhere else.
You may not know.
Demon Lord Ziyue
is currently in Xuanjing Palace.
The purple moon you saw
is the incarnation of his power.
Surely the moon here
is unusually bright.
When did Demon Lord Ziyue
come to Xuanjing Palace?
Almost ten thousand years ago.
Ten thousand years ago?
Your Highness,
I greatly admire Demon Lord Ziyue.
Do I have the honor to meet him?
I’m afraid you’ll be disappointed.
Demon Lord Ziyue is withdrawn.
He wears a mask all day long
and keeps away from others
by the Purple Moon Spring in the back.
Even I seldom see him.
Withdrawn, wears a mask,
came here ten thousand years ago.
Sounds like Boxuan.
I beg your pardon.
Nothing.
Well,
Your Highness,
another toast to you.
Are you feeling well?
Take it easy.
It’s a pity
that the donkey, Qingmu isn’t here
and couldn’t see the grandeur.
What’s wrong with me?
Why am I thinking of him?
Are you drunk already?
Cheers!
(Pleasure House)
Sir, it’s been a long time.
Come in.
Your Highness, bottom up.
Your Highness,
let me fill it up.
Your Highness, another cup.
No,
I can’t drink anymore.
I’m a little dizzy.
I understand.
But you must
drink this up.
You won’t turn me down, right?
Your Highness.
No.
I really can’t drink anymore.
Come on, drink.
Here is more.
Young man,
when I was shouting orders
at Abyssal Ridge Swamp,
you were still a kid.
Hey,
weren’t you drunk?
Where are you going,
Lord Fengran?
I...
Didn’t we agree
to get loaded together?
I...
Come on now.
Let’s drink.
Put it away. Let go of your hand.
Magic Rope?
You tied me up with the rope?
Jingjian, loose the rope.
Jingjian, Jingjian!
Free me, Jingjian!
I’m worried about her safety,
however she
is fraternizing with the demons
like they’re a family.
It’s late.
Why hasn’t she come back?
Miss, be careful.
Miss, watch your steps.
The wine in Xuanjing Palace
is fabulous.
Careful.
It makes people drunk faster than mine.
Master Beichi, you’re back.
Lord Qingmu,
you should go to your lover
in the Heavenly Palace.
The Heavenly Palace?
Why are you in my dream?
You’re drunk, master.
The Heavenly Palace? Lover?
Those stories in novels are not real.
Actually,
you do have a handsome face.
If Jingzhao didn’t have a crush on you,
I would have...
I would have been nicer to you.
You’re drunk, master.
Let me take you in.
I’m not drunk.
You are.
Well...
Master Beichi...
Don’t interrupt them.
The apprentice is so good-looking.
We should leave them alone.
I want five more bottles of wine.
You’re a girl,
and you drank too much.
What if your identity is exposed?
If you run into a pervert,
your reputation will be ruined.
If you want to drink again,
take me with you.
Do you hear me?
What are you doing?
Shanggu has changed.
She won’t travel around
and play with you.
What are you doing here?
Shanggu has been upset
since she came back
from the Nether World.
I want to cheer her up.
Shanggu is so ungrateful.
You should have seen this coming
when you brought Master Bai Jue back.
Hold on.
You address Bai Jue by master.
But why do you address me as oi or hey?
Sometimes you call me by my full name.
Do you need a title to add
to your majesty?
Well, no.
I’m a talented and carefree man
who’s close to everything.
I don’t need these titles.
Then why did you ask?
We keep distance from Bai Jue
because we’re in awe of him.
But you’re different.
We grew up together.
In my heart,
you’re not an august True God,
but someone to share my thoughts with.
You’re so sweet.
My temperament
is way more friendly than the Ice Cube.
Are those for Shanggu?
It’s been a while.
They’re no longer fresh.
Come with me to pick
the most beautiful herb
in the Three Realms.
Really?
Come on.
It’s desolate here.
Fending off wind with magic
weakens the place’s power.
But we’ve walked a mile,
and we didn’t see one flower.
Are you fooling me around?
You have no idea.
The south of the demon land
is abundant with blooms.
But the most precious one
is Purple Woolly growing
on cliffs in the north.
Purple Woolly?
Yes.
It’s a prickly herb
that’s not easy to pick.
It implies the most beautiful blessings.
As for its character,
it’s aloof and condescending.
I’m eager to see it.
Lead the way.
I’ll pick some for Shanggu.
Aren’t you tired after walking
a mile away?
I can go another mile.
We’re almost there.
Help!
Anybody?
Let’s take a look.
Help! Anybody?
Help!
Thank you, miss.
I’m Sen Jian, a tiger.
I wanted to pick this herb
on this spring day,
but I fell off the cliff.
Know how much you can chew
before you bite.
Don’t take such risks again.
Do you hear me?
I’ll keep it in mind.
Well,
we’ll have to go empty-handed.
What do you mean?
Is the herb
in his hands the one?
Forget it.
Shanggu has seen
all kinds of good stuff.
She’ll know
we care about her.
Let’s go back.
Goddess,
my mother told me,
we must do something in return
for others’ kindness.
Do you have any wishes yet to realize?
Give the herb to me then.
Are there any other things I can do?
I’ll complete it for you,
even it’s something dangerous.
But the herb...
I think you’re just saying
about doing something in return.
Let me explain.
My mother has been bed-ridden for years.
I can’t do anything for her
but to pick this herb
for blessing.
And I’m serious about
paying back.
Could you please tell me your name?
When I become a lord someday,
I’ll repay your favor.
You’re quite
an ambitious young tiger.
Goddess!
That boy is honest.
He has potential.
Do you want me to make him
your Divine Beast?
No.
I don’t want him to feel restrained.
Besides,
if I take him,
maybe I’ll be the one
who feel restrained.
And
I don’t want to be followed around
and called goddess.
I know you don’t.
Don’t worry.
That boy is a loving son.
I’ll ask Zihan to look after him.
You’re so wise.
I admire that.
Are you teasing me?
Well,
I’m going to the peach woods
and empty your wine jars
buried down the trees.
Don’t you dare?
I kept those for Shanggu.
Master, are you missing Goddess Yuemi?
Don’t blame yourself.
What happened then...
Don’t.
I’ll never do enough
to atone for my crime.
Miss her?
I don’t deserve to.
I just found
the moon so beautiful tonight
that I should
have a drink.
By the way, Master,
the scouts you sent out days ago
brought back a message.
They found a goddess
who resembles
Her Grace a lot at Mount Lookout.
However,
the only comparison is a portrait.
They can’t be sure.
Have they looked into her background?
Rumors say she’s from Qingchi Palace.
Mount Lookout is in Bai Jue’s domain.
And Qingchi Palace is in Gu Jun’s.
Interesting.
Her Grace is blessed.
Even with the tribulation,
she will come through.
Perhaps we’ll find her in a few days.
Zihan,
thank you
for the last sixty thousand years.
I asked you to look for Shanggu
because of my stubborn belief.
Shanggu is the Chief God.
Even if her soul dispersed,
there have to be something left,
some traces.
Right.
As long as you maintain the belief,
Her Grace will come back to you.
Master,
I truly,
truly believe Her Grace is still alive.
Alright.
You’re right.
What do you mean?
Have you sensed her power?
No.
I met a girl who also
resembles Shanggu a lot today.
Moreover,
her companion is a man
who looks a lot like Bai Jue.
And now
they’re also in the Demon Realm.
Are you sure?
It coincides with your message.
The eclipse eases at night.
Shanggu,
will we meet again?
Houchi.
No.
No!
(Pleasure House)
Jingjian, you get up.
What’s going on?
What else do you want?
Get out!
Forgive me.
I told you last night
I can’t drink much.
You urged me to drink.
In the end, we were both drunk.
I did that to...
To make me drunk
and get rid of me?
Yes, so what?
You knew I didn’t like you around me,
yet you had to stick with me.
You enjoy the leisure,
but I don’t have time for this.
To keep me with you,
you tied me up with the Magic Rope.
Now I see,
you immortals
from Heavenly Palace are all snakes.
Forgive me.
I was so drunk last night.
I don’t remember
tying you up with the Magic Rope.
I can swear
in the name of Heavenly Palace...
Save it.
Untie the rope.
The rope is my father’s halidom.
I can’t untie it.
What?
Show yourself!
Let me explain.
This halidom of my father’s
is forged by the essence
of plants in the East Wasteland,
the spirit of iron in the West Heaven,
the breath of flames in the South
and the core of ice in the North Sea,
by means of magic arts.
No one can break
or untie it.
Once tied,
it links two hearts for eternity.
Jingjian.
I shouldn’t have
drunk that much last night.
The demon maids are so thoughtful.
It’s you.
Where is Qingmu?
The demons love meat,
while the buns are vegan.
Did
Qingmu make them for me?
Clever man.
Is he serious?
About the master and apprentice thing?
It feels so good to have an apprentice.
He wants me to wait here?
What is he up to?
When I finish breakfast,
go out with me for a walk.
Well, I’ll go on my own.
I don’t know if she likes the buns,
but I’m sure
she’ll like the peach ratafia.
Houchi.
Hou...
Where is she?
She left me out
and flied solo again.
Master,
that girl is one of the black foxes.
Her name is Beichi,
Elder Chang Mei’s disciple.
Did you see her face?
Without your order,
I did not appear in front of her.
I showed the portrait
to a maid.
She also said
Beichi resembles Her Grace a lot.
Beichi?
What about the man?
He’s her apprentice.
Apprentice?
A roan fox,
named Nanmu.
Beichi, Nanmu?
Must be their aliases.
Beichi went alone to Sen Yu’s banquet
last night.
Her apprentice had porridge
in his bedroom.
They’re playing a duet.
They must have known each other
for long.
Master,
are they after something in the palace
under the disguise of physicians?
After what?
They can’t be after me.
Master,
I don’t mean to put a damper,
but...
But you haven’t sensed
a tiny bit of their power till now?
Yes.
If they are Her Grace
and Master Bai Jue,
power should well up in Xuanjing Palace
right now.
Not to mention you,
even I
couldn’t sense any of their power.
But it can’t be a coincidence.
Do you have a plan?
Either they are or not,
we’ll prove it today.
Cheers!
I missed a hearty drink.
Let me be clear.
Sen Yu killed my brother.
You insist on going to Xuanjing Palace
with me.
If anything goes wrong,
don’t blame me.
Rest assured.
I’ll handle everything properly.
I’m curious
how you’re going to do that.
This truly is a great sword.
Sure.
I stole half of
my family treasures
to get this sword forged
by a master blacksmith.
It sure is one of the best.
Wouldn’t your brother take you back
to Mount Jingyou for stealing?
I left a letter for my brother.
I told him I’m getting married
and I’m not going back.
Qin,
you...
you accept my proposal?
Qin,
when I come back from the war,
we’ll get married.
Qin,
how did we
end up like this?
Your Highness,
are you thinking about Chang Qin again?
The fox physician is good at her trade.
You’ll be cured in a few days.
Then you can start cultivation
and regain a demon core.
Years of suffering is finally
coming to an end.
Your Highness,
do you really want me to go?
Why?
I remember what you did for me.
And I’ll repay your favors.
It’s heavily guarded.
My power is too weak
to push in.
But if I throw this chance away,
I might not
have another one to get to
Purple Moon Spring.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪