=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 19=
Crispy on the outside
and soft on the inside.
It tastes best now.
Just now,
I was sorry.
I saw you activate your bracelet.
Is it the amulet from Boxuan?
You want to ask about him again?
I just want to figure out
who I really am.
You...
You’re North Sea Lord Qingmu,
the man Princess Jingzhao loves.
Everybody knows that.
In the name
North Sea Lord Qingmu,
the first three words were from
the Heavenly Emperor.
I named myself with the last word.
Except this,
I don’t even know as much as you do.
A thousand years ago,
I woke up in the North Sea
and didn’t remember who I was.
I had nothing with me,
but one bracelet.
Then I wandered
throughout the Three Realms,
trying to figure out who I was.
You and your bracelet
can be my only clue.
So, I want to go with you
and look for Lord Boxuan.
Maybe he knows who I am.
Thank you for helping me
at the Skyreach Pillar.
Also for helping me out
of the Barrier for Demons
and the Vine Demon.
Boxuan is from Qingchi Palace.
He treats me like his own sister.
Ten thousand years ago,
he said he would leave for experience
and go through the Tribulation.
Then he’s never come back.
I went to Mount Lookout to look for him.
But no one was living
in the bamboo house.
Only this fan was left there.
Demon Lord Ziyue’s magic weapon?
So, you went to the Demon Realm
because you thought
Boxuan had something to do with Ziyue?
What?
You look like Boxuan in figure.
But you’re totally different in temper.
Never heard of it.
Did Boxuan date a female lord
in Qingchi Palace
ten thousand years ago?
If you’re his son,
you should call me Aunt.
Maybe you’re his brother?
Or you’re someone close to him.
Boxuan never gave anyone anything
without a reason.
When I was young, I was too childish
that I only played with him
instead of asking about his identity.
If I had cared a bit more,
we would have some more clues now.
Houchi,
where’re you going?
I’m a Goddess in the Heavenly Realm.
Why do you think
you can call me by my name?
Who are you taking me to,
Goddess Houchi?
Taking you?
I’ve told you who Boxuan is.
If you want to see him,
go find him personally.
What about you?
Me?
What does it concern you?
I hate anyone
related to the Heavenly Palace.
The Heavenly Emperor conferred it on me.
I’m not related with Heavenly Palace.
You made fun of me,
and also helped me.
I’ve told you all I know
about Boxuan.
We’re even.
♪Time disturb my feelings♪
♪Like you do♪
♪Hold tightly with your warm hand♪
♪Look up at the meteor
across the darkness♪
♪Your tall figure♪
♪Is even clear in the haze♪
♪I save some time♪
♪To exchange it for you♪
♪Every second sounds so sweet♪
♪Until I meet you♪
♪I make every attempt♪
♪To have the next life♪
♪When we meet again♪
♪I’ll travel around with you
without hesitation♪
♪Listen♪
♪We feel each other♪
♪And get close♪
♪For a little talk♪
♪If it’s such a good time
and such a beautiful scenery♪
♪Hope♪
♪Go with me♪
Greetings, Heavenly Father.
There you are.
I summoned you,
because I want you to visit
the third heaven of the Demon Realm.
You mean...?
When many Gods fell,
the remaining ones couldn’t support
the functioning of the God Realm.
Master Zhiyang had no choice,
but to shut the God Realm
and sent us there
to disseminate the cultivation
to Immortals and Demons.
He hoped that the cultivation of Gods
could be abundant again.
At that time, he mentioned that
when it was time to strike,
we could go look for
Four Weapons of True Gods
lost in the lower realm
and reopen the gate between
the Bronze Bridge and the God Realm
to reactivate the God Realm.
After looking for them over many years,
I’ve got nothing,
but the clue for the Twin Spear
left by True God Zhiyang.
Lately, I recalled that
after the battle
between Gods and Devils,
Purple Moon Whip suddenly disappeared
from the Hidden Pavilion.
I can’t help suspecting
if some demons took it away
in the chaos.
You mean
the Purple Moon Whip may be hidden
in the Demon Realm?
Sen Jian is merely a Demigod,
but he fought us for ten thousand years.
There must be a reason.
I want you to go to the Demon Realm
and try to figure out
if the Demon King
has the Purple Moon Whip.
If he has it,
and wants to reactivate
the God Realm with me,
I’ll promise to give him
ten blessed spots in the Immortal Realm.
When we get some spiritual veins
after the God Realm is reactivated,
I’d like to share
with them equally, too.
But Heavenly Father,
demons are never on good terms with us.
Tianqi was one of the Four True Gods.
Gu Jun was also evolved
from a flood dragon.
When the God Realm was in its prime,
there was no difference
between immortals and demons.
You’re right.
Without the ceasefire between us,
the Three Realms couldn’t be in peace.
This is the Magic Rope.
It’ll help you out of danger.
Among my children,
you’re the steadiest one.
Only by sending you
can I present my sincerity.
Rest assured, Heavenly Father.
I won’t let you down.
Go ahead.
After so many years,
you still haven’t given up
on reactivating the God Realm?
True God Zhiyang entrusted us
with the God Realm.
Now it’s split.
Immortals and demons
are totally incompatible.
How I’ve disappointed him!
It was Sen Jian who disobeyed
Master Zhiyang’s order
and betrayed us.
Even if we want a ceasefire,
I don’t think he’s of one mind with us.
Don’t forget.
Master Bai Jue killed
Demon God Tianqi.
Wu Huan,
it’s been sixty thousand years
since that happened.
There’s little spiritual aura
in the lower realm.
Let alone Gods,
there’s hardly a lord
in a thousand years.
We have trouble cultivating ourselves.
So do the demons.
We can’t achieve the best
unless we reactive the God Realm
and let the two species cultivate in it.
Sen Jian has remained Demigod
for ten thousand years
and can’t make more progress.
I don’t think he’ll reject me.
Hope so.
I’ll take this.
All right.
That’s Lord Qingmu.
It’s him? It’s really him.
He looks so handsome,
just as he is in the rumor.
Yeah.
I never expected to see him personally.
Was that Lord Qingmu?
Yes.
You were right.
He looks great.
- Yeah, he does.
- Yeah.
He looks good in the robe.
He does.
Are you sure
you’re looking for Boxuan with me?
Sure.
All right.
But I can’t take you for no good reason.
You should at least do something
for our searching trip.
I’m the most powerful in this place.
I don’t mean letting you fight.
What else do you want me for?
Do you know
what we need most
in searching for someone?
Clues?
No.
Sacred Beads.
You want me
to earn Sacred Beads for you?
There’s a lonely place
over there.
In one hour,
let’s meet there.
Where are you going?
Are you going to abandon me again?
See you in one hour.
I thought you would run away again.
No.
I promised to take you.
I need you to earn Sacred Beads.
I’ve got a plan.
We can earn as many as we want.
Go.
You don’t know it, do you?
Even the view of your back
can be sold for 20 top-grade Sacred Beads
in the Immortal Realm.
Half of female lords of the Three Realms
have a crush on you.
When you keep such a high profile,
I’m afraid before you earn
any Sacred Beads,
all demons will know you have come.
But we shouldn’t take
such paths, either.
We can earn Sacred Beads here.
How?
Wait for me.
It’s Lord Qingmu.
It’s really him.
- Lord Qingmu!
- You!
- Wait for me!
Wait for me!
You!
Look at me.
- Stop running!
Wait for me.
Lord.
- Lord Qingmu!
Don’t touch me. I’m not Qingmu.
Lord Qingmu, don’t go.
Stay away!
Wait.
Female demons are indeed generous.
Greetings, Heavenly Mother.
There you are.
Take your seat.
You’ve come in time.
These are secret arts
from the Feng Clan.
Pick some and learn them.
But...
I haven’t finished the Gold Dragon Spell
Heavenly Father gave me.
The secret arts...
Why don’t you
ask my second brother to learn them?
He’s more hard-working than you.
He completed them
three hundred years ago.
He’s the Phoenix.
He must learn, of course.
I have something to ask you.
That day,
your father was angry with Jingyang
and I couldn’t ask you.
In Daze Mansion,
did Houchi really hurt Ziyuan
at one stroke,
set up the restriction
and get the thunder strike?
It was her!
She used the thunder strike on me
and humiliated me.
Heavenly Mother,
do you still care for her?
If you want to know it,
ask her in Qingchi Palace.
Why bother to ask me?
I’m asking because I care for you.
Did she...
Did she really stop
my Phoenix Feather Fan
and set up the restriction on Ziyuan?
She did, so what?
Maybe,
Houchi used some
shady arts.
Or why did she suddenly
become so powerful
with her weak spiritual vein?
It’s really weird.
I’ll figure it out.
I won’t let you suffer in vain.
Isn’t it
your favorite Feather Umbrella?
Feather Umbrella is as powerful
as Phoenix Feather Fan.
But it can help cultivators
to absorb all spiritual aura.
It’s very beneficial for cultivation.
I’m giving it to you.
Hope you’ll cultivate yourself carefully
and become a Goddess soon.
Thank you, Heavenly Mother.
I won’t let you down.
Lord Qingmu,
still angry with me?
We did that to look for Boxuan,
didn’t we?
You promised me, too.
I felt sorry for you.
Who could know you were so impatient?
When they flirted with you,
you couldn’t bear.
Think about it.
No one will believe
you’re North Sea Lord Qingmu.
Now I believe that
you’re not a playboy.
You’re definitely not.
Are you hungry?
Shall we go have a meal?
Don’t get angry.
Besides,
we’ve made a lot of Sacred Beads.
It’s enough for looking for Boxuan.
You have no idea
how handsome you look in this robe.
Then why do you hate me so much?
It’s not your fault.
Simply because Jingzhao loves you.
But I don’t love her.
Let’s go have a meal.
I’m hungry.
I’m not used to eating this.
Enjoy more yourself.
All right.
Thank you.
This way, please.
All right.
Come on. Try some.
Tastes great.
This is not an ordinary restaurant.
Lord Turtle lives in the back hall.
He knows everything in the Demon Realm.
Fengran asked me to come to him
in case I need any news.
So, I came up with that stupid idea.
Sorry for that.
Now that you did it to look for Boxuan,
I should sacrifice some.
Let’s go to the back hall later.
Have some more to eat.
Come on.
Cheers.
This tastes good, too.
Who are you?
We have something to ask Lord Turtle.
Have you brought Sacred Beads?
Sure.
Let her in.
He’s with me.
One bag of Sacred Beads for one person.
How did he see us?
Just get in here.
It may be dangerous in there.
Let me go.
I’ll go.
I know more about Boxuan.
I know what I’m going to ask him.
Be careful, then.
Wait for me in the front hall.
You’re Fengran’s friend?
Tell me.
What do you come for?
I hear you know everything
about the Three Realms.
I want to ask you for someone.
Who?
Demon Lord Ziyue.
Don’t be nervous.
I mean no harm.
Demon Lord Ziyue is powerful.
If I really wanted to hurt him,
I wouldn’t come alone.
Isn’t the immortal out there
your partner?
He didn’t come in.
Why is there no sound?
He still didn’t say
where Demon Lord Ziyue was.
Our rule is that
one person asks one question.
Your immortal friend
sent his little friend.
Isn’t he breaking my rule?
It’s a paper figure
with Spiritual Strength.
It doesn’t count.
I decide my own rules.
No matter how powerful
Qingchi Palace is,
you can’t make decisions for me.
Have you heard of it?
The other day,
young Goddess of Qingchi Palace
defeated Lord Ziyuan with one stroke.
It’s just exaggeration of immortals.
I hear that Houchi was born
with no spiritual vein.
Maybe she’s an illegitimate daughter
with a common mother.
Cheers. Cheers.
You’re saying bestial words!
Royal families of Tiger Demons
are decent.
But you’re a shame!
What?
Want to defend
the illegitimate daughter
from Qingchi Palace?
Let me teach you a lesson.
Men,
fight him!
You know who I am?
Because of Fengran.
I have no more Sacred Beads for you.
Please do me a favor.
For the sake that Fengran helped me,
I could tell you
about Demon Lord Ziyue.
But you must promise me one thing
in the name of Qingchi Palace
to make up for the missing Sacred Beads.
You’re blackmailing me.
If you don’t want it,
you may leave.
I won’t give back your Sacred Beads.
I can’t promise you
what you want.
My Heavenly Father told me that
we would be impartial
and we would live all alone.
We wouldn’t fight for power,
or interfere with the Heavenly Realm.
You can refuse to tell me
where Demon Lord Ziyue is,
regardless of your friendship
with Fengran.
But I can’t break our promise,
regardless of my father’s instruction.
Take the Sacred Beads as a present.
Good day.
Wait.
It’s eloquent of you.
If I don’t tell you,
I’ll be a disloyal and dishonest man.
Take the news you want
and leave here immediately
with your partner.
If you do any harm to the demons,
don’t blame me for being rude.
We’re in the Demon Realm.
There’s huge enmity
between immortals and demons.
How could you do this?
Those drunkards just humiliated you.
I couldn’t help,
but taught them a lesson.
But don’t worry.
I didn’t use any immortal power
and I won’t get exposed.
What’s the paper figure?
I raised him with Spiritual Strength
when I was in the North Sea.
He’s my friend.
Do you know I nearly failed
to get any news
simply because of him?
I was just worried about...
Did you really get no news
about Demon Lord Ziyue?
To me,
Boxuan matters most.
I won’t be negligent
in looking for him.
Lord Qingmu,
we don’t go the same way.
From this day on,
let’s go our own ways
and don’t see each other again.
Kick me out again with another excuse?
All right, then.
I won’t go with you, either.
Whoever wants cultivation
in the third heaven
must pay a top-grade Sacred Bead.
Lend me one Sacred Bead.
- Here it is.
- Thank you.
Next.
So many people are here.
Yeah.
I’ve been here for a while.
Next.
I’m late again.
Looks like I can’t get the token.
Everyone wants cultivation
in the third heaven.
But only ten tokens
are issued every day.
Totally not enough.
I hear Black and White Evils
are guarding the pass today.
Even if we got the token,
we couldn’t defeat them.
Or shall we let it go?
We’d better be alive first.
Let’s wait for a while.
All right, then.
When they know we guard the pass today,
they still dare to break through
the Life and Death Gate?
How reckless they are!
Who are you?
I’m Jingjian from the Heavenly Palace.
Under the command
of the Heavenly Emperor,
I’m here to visit the Demon King.
It’s brave of you, Second Prince.
You dared to come to the third heaven
without any subordinate.
In a fight,
messengers are never killed.
If you want a fight,
let’s fight on the battlefield.
Demons like you
won’t fight me in the third heaven,
will you?
You’re indeed the God of War
among immortals.
His Majesty is in seclusion.
I’ll take you to see Prince Sen Yu
in Xuanjing Palace.
Thank you.
Here’s the last token!
The last?
It goes to the highest bidder.
Me. Give it to me!
I have Sacred Beads.
No rush. No rush.
Those back there.
Give it to me!
No rush.
Give it to me.
- Don’t squeeze.
- Give it to me!
I have a lot of Sacred Beads.
- As many as I do?
- Me! Me!
The token is mine.
So many Sacred Beads?
Here.
Such a big bag of Sacred Beads?
Do you have so many?
No.
Stop!
How dare you deceive me with camouflage!
Give the token back to me!
It’s mine. Mine!
Stop!
Stop snatching!
- Stop!
- It’s mine.
Leave some to me.
Stop snatching!
How dare anyone make trouble
in front of the Life and Death Gate!
Somebody.
Take Prince Jingjian to Xuanjing Palace.
Yes.
- It’s mine!
- Stop, all of you!
Who’s making trouble here?
I’m Qingchi from North Qilian Mountains.
I work for Demon Lord Ziyue.
Under his command,
I come here for something important.
Take me in immediately.
What north or south Qilian Mountains?
Never heard of it.
Don’t try to deceive me!
Ignorant men!
Even if you don’t recognize me,
can’t you recognize the token
of Demon Lord Ziyue?
It’s indeed his token.
Take me in immediately.
If you hold up his emergency,
you might be killed.
She sounds so arrogant.
Maybe she’s not lying.
Shall we let her in?
It’s sensible of you.
If there’s a chance,
I’ll put in a good word for you.
Wait.
Ordered by the Demon King,
I guard the gate to the third heaven.
Nobody unidentified can be allowed in
without challenging
the Life and Death Gate.
It’s my duty.
Sorry for the offense.
Wait.
Now that we both work for Lord Ziyue,
we don’t need to injure our harmony.
Let’s not have a life and death fight.
Whoever leaves the ring first
will lose.
Deal.
I’ll fight you alone,
and restrain one of my hands.
When I fight you with only one hand,
I can still defeat you!
But Black...
It’ll be fine.
Where’s she?
What’s going on?
Fly out!
Freeze!
You lost.
You cheated!
When you lost, you lost.
All right.
I won.
I won’t play.
You!
The fight in front of
the Life and Death Gate
is the supreme battle
in the Demon Realm.
But you used such a foul trick.
Shame on you!
What foul trick?
He simply underestimated me.
I kicked him out with my own strength.
What lame arguments!
We demons only care for strength,
but not rules.
Someone as mean as you
can’t ever enter the third heaven.
Don’t be nervous, Your Highness.
Someone must be breaking through
the Life and Death Gate.
Who are you?
How dared you break our rule!
A challenger.
Lord Qingmu,
if the White finds out...
How could you get in?
You sound arrogant.
Didn’t you just say
you only cared for strength,
but not rules?
In this case,
I’ll break your rule, then.
He used the sword
even as strongly as me.
Never heard of such a demon.
Demons turn out to be more powerful
than I’ve imagined.
Heavenly Father is right.
If we want to reactivate the God Realm,
we mustn’t be enemies with demons.
Come, please.
You cut off my Purple Fire?
I’ll see who you are.
Is that you?
Are you really back?
I’ll see who isn’t convinced yet
in the third heaven.
Why is there Demon Power on Qingmu?
Bai Jue?
You have the strongest Demon Power
I’ve ever seen.
Come in, please.
Let’s go.
Your Highness.
What’s wrong with you?
Can’t you see I’m busy?
Your Highness,
Prince Jingjian from the Heavenly Palace
asked to see you.
What?
When a prince comes,
I must see him immediately?
Immortals are all evil.
Ignore him for one day.
Let’s see him tomorrow.
Leave me.
Yes.
Prince Sen Yu sounds so irascible.
He must be handling something difficult.
Well,
I’ll come tomorrow.
I hear the third heaven
is the most bustling at night.
I want to take a walk there.
May I?
Sure.
Enjoy yourself.
Lord Turtle said that
Houchi got some clues
about the third heaven.
But the third heaven is so big.
Where can she be?
Fengran?
Lords in Qingchi Palace never came out
over tens of thousands of years.
But now they’re visiting
the Demon Realm.
Is there any reason for that?
Lord Fengran,
how are you doing lately?
It’s you?
Why are you here?
Under the command
of the Heavenly Emperor,
I have something to discuss about
with the Demon King.
Lord Fengran, what brings you here
to the third heaven?
If you need anything,
I’d like to help.
Now that you have business to do,
I’ll leave you alone.
Wait.
What?
I’m sorry to say that,
but I seldom leave the Heavenly Palace
and I’m not familiar
with the Demon Realm.
Now that we’ve met,
why don’t we go together
so that we can take care of each other?
What does it concern me
whether you’re familiar with this place?
Why can you...?
Or,
you’re up to something
that you don’t want us to know?
He looks like a weak scholar,
but he’s quite cunning.
If I go with him,
he can spy on me.
If I don’t,
it proves we collude with demons.
Now that you trust me,
we can take a walk together.
The third heaven is more prosperous
than any other place.
Let me show you around
and have a good time.
Your wish is my command.
He just helped me
to get into the third heaven.
But he ignored me upon coming in.
Forget it.
He saved me, anyway.
And he’s younger.
I’d like to make him happy.
Thank you for helping me just now.
I’ll keep that in mind.
When I find Boxuan
and get back to Qingchi Palace,
I’ll reward you heavily.
Waiter,
get us some wine.
All right. A minute.
You will?
Now you’d like to go
with me?
Here’s the wine for you.
Since we met,
we’ve never had schemes.
I was in such a fit of anger
that I said something
without careful thought.
In your heart,
am I always someone
who is arrogant, impulsive,
and childish?
Not that dramatic.
Come on.
Enjoy the wine when we talk.
Anyway,
you care for nothing,
but looking for Boxuan.
Like you said, let’s go our own ways.
I won’t enjoy your wine.
Don’t push it.
I hear that Houchi was born
with no spiritual vein.
Maybe she’s an illegitimate daughter
with a common mother.
- Cheers. Cheers.
- Enjoy the wine. Cheers.
You’re saying bestial words!
Royal families of Tiger Demons
are decent.
But you’re a shame!
What?
Want to defend the illegitimate daughter
from Qingchi Palace?
Let me teach you a lesson.
Men,
fight him!
What are you laughing at?
I’m not worried about her.
I simply want to find Boxuan soon.
Stop laughing.
Catch up.
Stop it,
or I’ll turn you into waste paper.
Why did you do this?
What?
We’re not families or friends.
If you come for Boxuan,
you could have tricked me
or threatened me.
But you saved me many times.
You even fought to defend
the reputation of Qingchi Palace.
Lord Qingmu,
why did you do this?
What do you mean why?
A man does what he wants.
When I want to defend you, I defend you.
When I want to save you, I save you.
There’s no specific reason.
But I don’t like to owe others.
And I don’t care how people think of me.
I’m used to the curses on me.
You don’t need to...
But I care.
I can’t stand seeing you be criticized.
I can’t stand seeing you be bullied.
I can’t stand seeing you pretend
nothing happened
while you actually feel sad.
Whenever I’m with you,
I defend you.
Because...
Because I want you to be my friend.
From this day on,
shall we go together
and be honest to each other?
Childish.
You’re simply a bit older than me.
Why can you say I’m childish?
Finish the wine
and let’s go look for Boxuan.
Come on in.
You haven’t come for a while.
I’m right here for you, aren’t I?
Lord Fengran,
where are we?
You’ve stayed in the Heavenly Palace
for so long
(Pleasure House)
that you don’t even know this place.
There’re the most beautiful demons
and the best spirit in it.
What?
You don’t like it?
I...
I’ve admired this place for long.
I must get in.
If you don’t like it,
go back and wait for me in the inn.
After I have enough fun,
I’ll go back to you.
Wait.
What?
Do you need me
to walk you back to the inn?
No.
I just don’t understand.
It’s a place for men.
What fun can you have?
Or do you simply want to get rid of me
by getting into this place?
You’re poorly informed.
There’re female demons in it,
as well as male demons.
What?
When males can come,
females can’t?
Well, Lord Fengran,
please kindly enlighten me tonight.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪