♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
=The Eternal Love S3=
=Episode 18=
By the grace of heaven's will,
Her Majesty hereby proclaims that
Qian Prefecture has been struck
by a great drought,
thus, granary will be opened
for the people in need.
The climate is unpredictable.
People are the foundation of a nation.
Everyone
must show sympathy for the living.
Starting tomorrow,
men from noble families of the city
must enter the palace to pray for one month.
The end.
Long live Her Majesty!
Superstitions.
Message from Her Majesty.
Eldest Princess is newly wedded.
Prince Consort Mo Yan Chen is
exempted from the prayer.
I'm grateful for Her Majesty's grace.
Hold on.
You said all men from noble families
in Dongyue must join.
Is my husband Mo Lian Cheng included?
Certainly.
But...
My husband has been ill recently.
It would be bad if his conditions
displease Her Majesty.
Tan Er.
Are you trying to cause Official Xiao trouble
or are you disobeying the imperial order?
I don't care.
I must see Her Majesty.
It's a message from Her Majesty.
Mo Lian Cheng
must join the prayer.
No.
I must put on everything I can.
We...
We need money everywhere we go.
I need Yu Hao and Jing Xin to help me out.
I must bring all my jewelry with me.
I'll carry whatever I can take.
Cheng Cheng.
Help me out now.
Tan Er.
Even if you run away now,
where can you go?
I couldn't care so much.
We must leave first.
Her Majesty
is clearly doing this because of us.
This is your fault!
This is all thanks to your amnesia.
Look at what happens now.
I can't enter the palace for one month
unless I am summoned.
You will be trapped inside the palace
for one month.
Her ill intention
is too apparent.
Don't worry about it.
I can
take good care of myself.
You mentioned it before.
We are only here
because of the Soul-guarding Bead.
It's likely we'll need it for our return.
Moreover,
the Soul-guarding Bead
is the treasure of the Qu family.
Her Majesty holds the most power in that family.
My guess is,
the bead
might be inside the palace.
I am entering the palace,
so I can ask around.
Maybe we can leave this place sooner.
But you haven't regained all of your memories.
You don't know martial arts either.
I'm worried.
I may not have my memories,
but ignorance gives me courage.
That makes the operation easier.
Her Majesty is now
obsessed with you.
What if she...
A man must always
protect himself out there.
Don't worry.
It's only one month.
Right!
Take this dagger with you.
Use it for protection.
Tan Er.
While I am away,
beware of Her Majesty
and Eldest Princess.
I am now a princess too.
My status is different now.
Don't worry.
I will miss you a lot.
(Jingyi Pavilion)
Her Majesty asked for you,
Prince Consort Lian Cheng.
Please come with me.
I haven't finished copying the scripture.
Her Majesty's order must be followed at once.
Tan?
Tan, wake up.
No.
Tan, wake up!
Tan!
Wake up!
You're finally awake.
Tan.
What happened?
You were shouting loudly.
I was so worried.
I'm glad it was just a dream.
No.
He's been in the palace for days.
Why haven't I heard from him?
Jing Xin.
Ask around in the palace.
Yes. I'll go now.
Rest well.
I'll order the kitchen to make some
food to calm your mind.
Cheng Cheng...
(Why is Her Majesty dressing like this?)
As usual, I'll address you
as Young Master Mo.
Is that all right?
Yes, Your Majesty.
I'm in a mood for pitch-pot today.
Are you willing
to play with me?
I'm afraid
this isn't appropriate.
When did you ever worry about what's appropriate?
Let's have a wager.
Whoever loses
must answer the winner a question.
You have my word.
Each of us gets three arrows.
The player with the best scores wins.
Why do you think?
Your Majesty can decide.
Young Master Mo.
One point for me
and one point for you.
When did you learn how to play pitch-pot?
I...
never knew.
Is there anything you can't do?
I'm flattered.
Whether it's chores or managing a household,
I know nothing.
This is intriguing.
You share similarities
with someone I used to know.
He didn't know these either.
I appreciate the compliment.
Bearing any resemblance with
Your Majesty's friend
is an honor.
The difference is
he was never reverent and respectful
to me like you.
He and I
shared everything together.
We went through ups and downs together.
We went on adventures
and explored the unknown.
The joyous moments we had
are now...
a distant memory.
Your Majesty is the ruler of the nation.
It's my duty
to show my respect for Your Majesty.
As for
Your Majesty's old friend,
I wouldn't dare...
to make any comments.
Young Master Mo,
you are now well-versed in rites
and manner.
But during the sparring test,
what made you say such impulsive words?
I was ignorant of the consequences.
Your Majesty's punishment was wise.
I've learned from my mistake.
Perhaps...
after I met Second Princess,
I've come to know love.
That changed me.
You've changed so much
over time.
I lost.
I was lucky.
Tell me.
What do you want to know?
Rumors say that
the royal Qu family of Dongyue
has a priceless bead.
It can change destiny
and reshape reality.
Has Your Majesty
ever heard of it?
I've never heard of it.
Where did you learn
such rumor?
That was foolish of me.
I thought
the novel's story was real.
I apologize.
The weather is hot today.
I'm sweating very badly.
May I have Your Majesty's permission
to get changed?
Go ahead.
I take my leave.
He was playing pitch-pot with Her Majesty!
I'm jealous!
I'm sure he has reasons to do so.
After all, it was Her Majesty who invited him.
He can't disobey her order.
This is driving me crazy!
Jing Xin.
Bring me my 40-meter long
great spear!
Your Highness.
So I do have one?
Good.
Jing Xin.
We should carry this spear
and break into the palace!
Tan.
No matter what you want to do,
I'm willing to do it with you.
But this...
Can we reconsider it?
I could be spotted even I dress like this.
If you went in there...
What's wrong with me?
Are you looking down on me?
I'm stating the truth.
How dare you!
How dare you make fun of me!
Stand still!
Don't you dare!
Don't you mock me again!
Sorry!
Please, have mercy!
I won't do it again.
That's more like it.
We must figure out a way
to sneak into the palace.
I got it.
You must
play along with my performance.
Go get it ready for me.
Sure.
Tan.
Be careful when you do it.
Got it. Got it.
I am the queen of real estate.
This is a walk in the park for me.
Start gathering the people.
Bring them here
to save me in time.
Let's do it.
Slowly.
Hold tight.
Cheng Cheng.
I'm risking my life for you.
Stay steady.
I'll get some help.
Go on.
Oh, no!
Help! Help!
Her Highness is hanging herself
to commit suicide!
Save...
This is bad!
Her Highness is hanging herself...
Your Highness!
Your Highness! Are you all right?
Are you all right?
Are you hurt?
Your Highness! Are you hurt?
Is Your Highness hurt?
Jing Xin.
You fail at everything.
You almost got me killed.
Is it my fault?
Her Highness is safe now.
Dismiss. You may go now.
Dismiss.
Okay.
Let's go.
Tan.
I will not take part in this kind of plan again.
It's too dangerous.
If something bad happened to you,
I would be blamed for it even if I die!
I had to make the play convincing
so that I can fool others.
Don't worry.
I can handle it.
Are you sure?
Are you sure you're alright?
Let me see it.
Your Majesty.
Second Princess tried to commit suicide
in her residence.
She said she's let Your Majesty down
and if she can't enter the palace,
her life is pointless.
It's making waves.
Young Master Mo, are you not worried at all?
Her Highness and I have made a promise
that we will take care of ourselves
and reunite after the prayer is over.
It seems like Your Majesty and Official Xiao
have work to discuss.
I shall
take my leave now.
Your Majesty.
Our next move...
Mo Lian Cheng has changed drastically.
Something is amiss.
Also,
he seems to know
I have the Soul-guarding Bead.
How is that possible?
Unless he is Young Master Lian Cheng.
But after I sounded him out,
it did not feel like him.
Whatever the case is,
tighten the security around my bedroom first.
Yes.
I'll get it done.
Why haven't we heard anything from the palace?
Does Her Majesty not care if I'm dead or not?
Then why did she send me the tonic?
Tan.
Keep it down when you say that.
What if...
What if Her Majesty
has seen through your plot?
No way.
Let's go.
There must be a way
for me to get into the palace!
Hold on.
You...
When you walk around the place,
be mindful of your behaviors.
You can't be so intimate with a guard.
That is not appropriate.
This guard
can't do anything.
Let's go.
Please let me in.
Take this money.
I really can't do it.
My superior forbid you from entering.
Please don't make things difficult for me.
Why can't you let me in?
I'm a princess.
Do you know how much money I'm holding?
Take it.
Your Highness.
If you have to...
I can...
No! Stop!
Forget it.
I'm grateful for your consideration.
I have an idea.
You can
let Her Highness enter alone.
I can't do that.
She will be on her own.
The palace is huge.
Even if she sneaked in,
no one would notice.
What happened?
Lady.
Your veil looks gorgeous.
I really can't let her in.
Halt!
Foreign officials cannot
ride on carriages inside the palace.
Officials must step out
of the carriage and be examined.
How dare you!
General Pugu will be late to present
himself to Her Majesty!
Will you take responsibility?
Tell them
that I will not
step out of the carriage.
Move aside.
I apologize, General.
Her Majesty has an order for us.
You may stay in the carriage
and be exempted from the examination.
Our rookie
doesn't know the rules.
Please stay in your seat.
But other members of your convoy
must be examined
to prevent impostors from sneaking in.
(Crap.)
Isn't this the classic story
of saving a damsel in distress?
I love it.
What?
You just have to make me get off the carriage?
You've misunderstood, General.
I was merely...
I know every member of my convoy.
You don't need to worry.
Yes.
You're safe.
You may go now.
Pal.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
What if I was an assassin?
Judging by your aura,
you don't know martial arts.
That's very nice of you.
No sweat.
It was no big deal.
You may go now.
Sure.
I'll see you
when I see you.
Cheng Cheng is copying the scriptures.
I don't get to see him.
Her Majesty
is meeting the officials.
She's not here either.
Great.
This is my chance
to find out whether Mo Lian Cheng
had any intimate experience
with Her Majesty.
So far,
it's looking good.
I haven't found a single hair.
This bed looks comfortable.
I should get one for myself.
What is happening to me?
Could it be...
that I skipped my meal
so my blood sugar level is too low?
I'm all right now?
Why didn't you make any noise when you walk?
You almost gave me a heart attack!
Your Highness disobeyed the order
and broke into Her Majesty's bedroom.
What is your agenda?
I can go wherever I want.
It's none of your business.
I miss Her Majesty.
So I came to see her.
I know she is busy right now.
I'll come back again.
I must have seen it right just now.
But Second Princess
doesn't seem to know the truth.
I am Pugu Yun Xiu.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Has your ruler told you
whom you will be marrying
after you've arrived?
As told by my lord,
Your Majesty always made
the best decision.
My fate
is Your Majesty's to decide.
However,
I've come here as a sinner.
This might come as offensive for Your Majesty.
If Your Majesty is unwilling,
I can explain everything to my lord.
Not at all, General.
The Pugus is a noble family in Xiyue.
You belittle your status
by admitting to being a sinner.
Victory and defeat are both common in battle.
I quite admire
your talents and skills.
I appreciate the compliments.
I am worried.
But I am aware that my actions
are usually out of line.
I'm afraid
any woman who marries me
will be frustrated.
Perhaps...
I understand.
You refuse to have a peace-making marriage.
You wish to break the treaty
between the two nations.
I wouldn't dare.
I never want to break the treaty.
I upset Your Majesty.
I deserve punishments.
I believe
Xiyue's goodwill in the negotiation.
I have no children to call my own.
But one of my nieces,
Second Princess Qu Tan Er still
hasn't officially selected
the main prince consort.
I've heard of that.
Her Highness has a kind heart.
She is gentle and intelligent.
Very well.
You shall be her main prince consort.
Be ready.
Two days from now,
you will have the wedding.
Your Majesty.
I can only dream of marrying Her Highness.
Moreover,
this might be too sudden.
I'm afraid if I make any mistake,
I might embarrass Her Highness.
I will send you more manpower to get it done.
All you need to do
is to wait for the wedding.
That settles it.
(I can't disobey the empress's order.)
(There is nothing I can do now.)
I shall
obey the order.
General Mo.
It's been a long time.
How are you lately?
General Pugu.
I'm fine.
I hope you won't cause any trouble
for this peace-making marriage.
General Mo.
It was a misunderstanding.
I...
I only believe what I see.
Pugu Yun Xiu.
You are in the Kingdom of Dongyue.
If you cause any trouble,
it will take more than a marriage to resolve it.
General Mo.
I don't want any further misunderstanding.
Back then...
I'm not interested.
So long, General Pugu.
Judging by that look,
you never found anything?
Indeed!
Jing Xin.
What should I do?
An imperial order has arrived!
Is she going to punish me for
sneaking into the palace?
Jing Xin.
How severe is the offense?
Your whole family might be executed.
An imperial order for Second Princess.
As decreed by Her Majesty,
Second Princess Qu Tan Er of Dongyue
is graceful with her beauty, wise with
her knowledge and manner.
However, she hasn't selected
a main prince consort yet.
Yun Xiu from a noble family in Xiyue
is courteous and respectful.
He is now of age to get married.
Second Princess and Yun Xiu are
a match made in heaven.
He will be betrothed to Second Princess and
granted letters and robes by Her Majesty.
The wedding will be completed two days from now.
The will of the people decides the nation's fate
and thus the royal family's fortune.
May the couple work to contribute
to the nation and live up to
Her Majesty's expectation.
The end.
Second Princess Tan Er, accept
the imperial order.
I accept the imperial order.
Congratulations on obtaining
the main prince consort.
I'll take my leave now.
Yun Xiu?
The man who is here for a peace-making marriage?
The man with a beard?
How could it be such a coincidence?
Could it be he knew it already?
So he saved my neck to please me?
Is that so?
I'm not a trash can!
Why should I take in everyone?
I quit!
Young Master.
What about we probe for a few more days?
I will be leaving the palace soon.
As of now,
the only place I haven't searched
is Her Majesty's bedroom,
which is heavily guarded.
I must start searching now.
I will go with you then.
If you stay,
you won't draw any suspicion.
The continent of Dongyue covers various states.
Women have more power in all states.
All the states wages war on each other.
The farmland sees no harvest.
People are starving and suffering.
In the southwestern region of Dongyue,
the Mo family sets up canteens and schools
and welcomes refugees of
the neighboring states
to go to the southwestern region.
Until formidable women from the Qu family
rise to emerge as a new force
and join hands...
with the Mo family
to unite Dongyue under one reign
with their force.
The name of the regime is Xihe.
The Qu family enforces new laws
to terminate all forms of fiefdom.
A new system that employs officers
is implemented instead.
An empress becomes the ruler.
Their idea diverges from that of the Mo family's
which is to return the power to the people.
And then
the head
of the Mo family dies from a heart attack.
The Mo family...
falls from their grace.
One, two, three.
Sit on my shoulders.
Again.
Come on.
One, two, three!
Can you make it?
I can't hold it!
Are you all right?
This wall is too tall.
Jing Xin!
This is your fault.
You asked me to come and discuss it with
Cheng Cheng in the middle of the night.
If it was daytime,
I could just sneak into the palace.
You can't go over the wall because
you don't know martial arts.
Otherwise,
we could have just jumped over the wall.
Are you really so powerful?
Of course.
Then go ahead.
Fine.
Hold this.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Official Xiao.
Did you install
a GPS tracker on me?
Why do I keep seeing you everywhere I go?
It's late now. Shouldn't you be in bed?
Are you here to scare us?
I know why Your Highness
is trying to break into the palace.
But sadly,
your effort is in vain yet again.
How do you know?
I came here
to discuss an urgent matter with Her Majesty.
Take me to her.
Prince Consort trespassed into the forbidden
ground and was trapped there.
He might be in grave danger.
There are many deadly contraptions there.
Prince Consort is carrying injuries.
Without my help,
he might lose his life.
If Your Highness
could return to your residence and
await the wedding,
I will go to his rescue personally.
Why should I trust you?
Keep bluffing.
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪A flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter what
hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have to
travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter what
hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have to
travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪