♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
=The Eternal Love S3=
=Episode 17=
(Mo Residence)
Father.
Lian Cheng and Qu Tan Er know
you're about to get married,
and they've been visiting every day,
are you really not going to see them?
No matter what they do,
it's all fake.
It's better if everyone lives
their own lives, unbothered.
Yan Chen,
I had been strict with you before,
but it was all for the Mo family.
I hope you're sincere and genuine
about your marriage this time.
If you're reluctant in any way,
you don't have to.
Father.
I was too naive before,
being tied down by love and romance.
After marrying Eldest Princess,
I will strictly follow your teachings.
Have you made up your mind?
Father, I'm willing to follow you
to do all that I can for the Mo family.
So I haven't been wrong about you.
Although you're kind and gentle,
you have great ambition.
Like father, like son.
My Lord. Young Master.
The bridal sedan chair
has arrived at the front doors.
It's time for us to leave.
Father,
I'm leaving.
Go.
So Qu Mei Er gets to marry Mo Yan Chen eventually,
her wish has finally been fulfilled.
Eldest Princess is indeed
passionately devoted.
Wishing those who are passionately devoted
get their feelings returned,
and those with genuine feelings
could be blessed.
Their marriage
isn't just about love.
Mo Yuan Long must have a hand in it.
Exactly, Your Majesty.
Now that Mo Yuan Long has two pillars of support,
I wonder how he will lay things out.
It's time to drop the bait.
The Spring Hunt
has always been an occasion during
which all noblewoman and soldiers
show their skills and abilities.
If this year,
it is changed to an open competition
between the two princesses,
where the winner gets abundantly rewarded,
when the time comes,
those who are restless will
definitely make their moves.
I knew
these wedding robes
would suit you the best.
All these years, I have
failed to return Your Highness's feelings.
Can you call me Mei Er?
Mei Er.
Finally, I've got you.
Only when cold nights and heavy storms come
do I find out
that only you're willing
to give out everything for me.
Unfortunately,
so much unfairness exists in the world.
Being a man,
my fate is not up to me.
I will forever protect you and cherish you.
I won't let anyone harm you.
By Her Majesty's will,
now that all is peaceful,
although
you no longer need to be
fighting at the battlefields,
soldiers
cannot slack off,
and training
cannot be neglected.
Eldest Princess, Second Princess,
as successors to Dongyue's throne,
you should not lose to the generals
in terms of physical strengths and abilities.
A new way to die?
Hurry up.
After a discussion with the officials,
this year's Spring Hunt
will be a competition for both of you,
Eldest Princess and Second Princess.
There will be two categories,
the first is Into-the-clouds Archery.
The second is a showdown with weapons.
It will take place
at the royal training grounds ten days from today.
The winner will be granted
the position of the Commander
of the Capital Guards.
I will not let Her Majesty down.
I will do my best.
I just want to
be a laid-back girl in peace,
why does my life have to be
so bloody and tiring every day?
Commander of the Capital Guards?
Whatever.
I don't want to be in command anyway.
How do I get through
all these tests and exams?
Since Eldest Brother has
chosen to remarry Qu Mei Er,
it is highly possible
that he has joined forces with Father.
If Qu Mei Er earns this position,
Father
could fall into the empress's trap.
Are you saying
that Her Majesty is trying to
draw a snake out of its nest?
Look at you, being so worried.
As long as I win the competition,
there won't be any issues.
But the problem is
that you and Qu Mei Er are
six of one, half a dozen of the other.
It's difficult to tell who will win.
This isn't a competition between the disciples,
but one between the masters.
So do you mean that
when I don't have my memories,
I cannot be compared
to that omnipotent Cheng Cheng?
I didn't say that.
When can you quit this habit
of being jealous of yourself?
Starting tomorrow,
preparations need to be made.
In my opinion, when you don't have your memories,
it should be six of one, half a dozen of the other.
Prince Consort.
Princess has been attacked, Prince Consort.
Princess has been attacked.
Princess, hang in there.
It's bad.
Jing Xin.
Quickly, tell me what happened.
Tell you what?
Show that you care about me, Mo Lian Cheng.
Okay, okay.
Princess,
hang in there.
Today...
it's sunny today, with birds
singing, flowers blooming.
Her Highness was in a great mood
and wanted to go to the bookshop to buy
some secret martial arts manuals.
On our way there,
we passed by...
we passed by a narrow alley.
Seven or eight assassins came out of nowhere
and surrounded Princess.
I unsheathed my blade
and fought them
to death.
Unfortunately,
Princess and I
were outnumbered.
So,
Princess
was almost torn into pieces on the streets,
and almost
died on the spot.
Jing Xin is such a drama queen,
adding fuel into the fire.
Jing Xin, you are highly skilled then,
there's not even
a speck of dirt on you.
Thank... thank you for your praise, Young Master.
Princess.
Since
Princess is so badly injured,
then help Her Highness
back to rest.
Don't!
It's better to have Her Highness
rest in the Snow Court.
I'll leave now.
I feel terrible.
This sweet and sour scent
comes from top-grade plum juice.
I can't think about that much.
Let me turn this place upside-down.
Mo Lian Cheng!
Aside from laughing at me, what else can you do?
If you're so smart,
why don't you
compete
and fight for the military command?!
Putting all the pressure on me,
how can you call yourself a man?
Oh, no.
Was that too much?
Why isn't he angry yet?
Is my firepower still too low?
Look.
Isn't it said
that loving someone
means loving everything about that person?
In sickness and in health, for richer and poorer,
in success and in failure.
Why do you only allow me to succeed but not fail?
What you've said before
are all lies!
Oh, no.
Was that too hurtful?
What if I can't get him to forgive me?
When did I ask that of you?
It's you
who wanted to win the competition for me.
Is he praising me
for caring about him?
I know
you weren't serious about what you've just said.
You just
wanted me to worry,
to get angry,
as well as
to recover my memories.
Then tell me,
how can I help stimulate you?
How are you so certain
that the me without memories
cannot teach you martial arts?
Is it that in your heart,
your husband is such a man?
You've really
become similar to me.
This confidence of yours
is just like mine.
Even though I'm not that good at martial arts,
it should be more than enough
to beat Qu Mei Er.
Okay.
What are you doing?
You haven't hit the target in three shots,
you don't deserve a horse.
Even the horse is saying I'm not worthy,
I should just give up.
Actually,
the accuracy of your shooting is there,
you're just lacking
the acuity for finding the target quickly.
There is no shortcut to that skill.
Practicing hard is the only way.
I can keep practicing,
but I want a reward.
I don't want much,
a kiss is enough.
If you don't agree, I won't practice anymore.
Pay attention to the target.
Satisfied?
Satisfied.
Now,
you've developed the acuity for finding targets.
But during the competition,
the venue will be larger and
the targets will be higher,
which means the shooting range will be wider.
So,
you cannot slack off during the training.
Can't you encourage me?
You always put pressure on me.
So what if the shooting range is wider?
I can still do it.
Your Highness,
keep on practicing.
A narrower shooting range
means
higher accuracy.
Then, if I know the direction of the serve
and run to the closest shooting position,
wouldn't it all come together?
I don't want to practice anymore,
let me take a break.
Have you
run out of energy
or is it that you just don't
want to practice anymore?
If you want to become one with your sword,
you have to first fuse the qi of the sword
into your blood.
What on earth are you talking about?
In my opinion,
I'm just not compatible
with this sword skill.
That's ridiculous.
How about
I teach you a set of sword skill?
Let me show you what it really means
to be one with your sword.
What sword skill?
The Flirting Sword Skill.
Every move
requires to be flirting.
Come on.
What odd sword skill was that?
You know too little,
there's so much more.
What?
The Lovey-dovey Sabre Skill.
The Blazing Passion Palm.
When the time comes,
I'll teach you everything.
Let me remind you.
In order to win the competition,
Qui Mei Er
has been training under Mo Feng Yang
at the Mo Residence every day.
If you keep slacking off,
you'll suffer a crushing defeat.
You really can't take a hint.
Fine, I'll practice.
Why bring up Qu Mei Er?
It's bad luck.
Don't come closer.
We have to be an arm's-length apart.
You finally recovered your memories last night.
What if you come close to me,
feel that happy sweetness,
and lose your memories again?
You're really full of yourself.
Does every single person who touches you
have to fall for you?
At least it's true for you.
Otherwise,
why have you been so attached to me every night?
I'm telling you,
stop provoking me with your dissatisfaction,
otherwise,
you'll suffer the consequences.
Originally,
I had given up on trying
to recover your memories.
But who knew
just casually mentioning my dissatisfaction
would really work?
You...
Alright, I'll stop.
You're about to go into battle.
Relax, face your opponent with a clear head.
No matter what the results are,
you'll always be
the most extraordinary Princess in my heart.
What are you doing?
Cannot surpass
an arm's-length apart.
One two one. One two one.
Halt.
May Second Princess be
ever-victorious, ever-triumphant,
ever-invincible, ever-glorious!
Ever-victorious, ever-triumphant,
Ever-victorious...
The first round, Into-the-clouds Archery.
When the drumming stops, service will begin.
The one who hits more cloud balls
will win.
Launch.
East, west, centre, west, west, east.
Take this.
The rules state that six balls
are served at once.
Follow these directions when you serve.
East, west, centre, west, west, east.
If you have to serve twelve at once,
serve in the reverse order after the first six.
Don't worry,
no one will notice.
Launch.
Second Princess Qu Tan Er
has hit six.
Eldest Princess Qu Mei Er
has hit three
and missed three.
Second Princess wins.
Did you secretly hire an expert?
Otherwise, how could you have
improved so much in just ten days?
I don't need to hire any experts,
my Prince Consort has been helping me train.
That's more than enough.
Mo Lian Cheng?
Impossible.
He's merely a man.
He probably can't even hold up
a bow and arrow properly.
Why can't men hold up bows and arrows?
Men are born weak.
Second Princess, why do you have
to make irrational arguments?
Eldest Princess, you think that
men are born weak,
but I cannot possibly agree.
How about this?
In the next round,
let my Prince Consort Mo Lian Cheng
face off with a female general,
in order to
prove whether it is really as you said
that men are born
weaker than women.
Your Majesty,
this is against the order
and principles of society.
This...
wouldn't this become a joke?
What?
Is everyone here worried
a mere man such me
would defeat a female general?
I agree
on this match.
Prince Consort is very courageous.
I would not like to go too far.
How about I compete with you
without weapons?
Thank you for your compassion.
Please.
How dare you look down on my Cheng Cheng?
Wait to have your butt whipped.
Good job, Mo Lian Cheng.
Cheng Cheng.
Prince Consort, you have kept
your skills well-hidden,
I want to know
whether I will also be defeated by you.
Cheng Cheng.
Prince Consort, in your opinion,
who should be declared
the winner of that match?
The results are obvious to all.
Your Majesty won.
Second Princess, do you disagree?
Prince Consort was defeated by Your Majesty,
I accept defeat.
Official Xiao,
what were today's results?
Bring him in.
Second Princess,
(First: east, west, centre, west, west, east
Reversed: east, west, west, centre, west, east)
care to explain?
My apologies, Second Princess.
I've admitted everything.
I...
My skills are lacking
and my intentions were dishonest.
I coerced the soldier
to serve the balls in the set directions.
It's all my fault,
may Your Majesty have mercy on him.
You are quick to admit your wrong-doing.
Flog him 80 times,
and oust him from the Palace.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'll take care of your family.
Since Second Princess
has lost both rounds,
the position of the Commander
of the Capital Guards
will be Eldest Princess's.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I will not betray Your Majesty's trust.
Defying rules, cheating in public,
disregarding the morals of men,
and violating cardinal guides and virtues.
Second Princess Qu Tan Er,
you are grounded
and are forbidden from entering the Palace.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
handing military command over to
Eldest Princess this time
will definitely remind Qu Tan Er
to thoroughly understand
the importance of the big picture
and be more obedient
to Your Majesty from now on.
With a ghastly appearance like this,
how could I blame him for not recognizing me?
Your Majesty,
are you speaking of Young Master Lian Cheng?
Today,
when I was fighting him,
my memories from before
all came back to me.
I am certain that
Mo Lian Cheng
is the Young Master Lian Cheng
I have been looking for.
Your Majesty.
Perhaps you are tired,
you must not over-exert yourself.
I cannot wait any longer,
I want him back by my side now.
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪A flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter
what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter
what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪