Let's each do what we're good at.
[English subtitles are available]
Do I fascinate you?
Am I an animal at the zoo?
Get out.
Could you please get lost?
I just don't get you.
You'd never be able to.
Then enlighten me.
I want to understand you.
Why should I even bother?
Why should I
when I'm neck-deep in my own worries?
It's past midnight
and the bed isn't refundable.
Insisting that you take off at this hour
won't change a thing.
Get at least a good night's sleep.
I see money is what you understand.
My words carry no weight, but money does.
I'll get lost then.
It's time for your shot.
Could you make sure
the pain is unbearable?
Don't skip your meals
and ventilate the room often.
[Episode 5]
[The moment I saw your tears I realized]
what I did was wrong.
[I realized if the girl I like is in pain,
it hurts me too.]
[If the girl I like is in pain...
If the girl I like is in pain...]
[Storytelling Marketing]
[The girl I like...]
No way. I memorized what he said.
Instead of memorizing lecture notes...
Darn it.
[Don't tell me
he confessed his love to you.]
Please don't say that's true.
Of course not.
Don't you worry and go to bed.
No one-sided love is allowed.
You're one to let it go on
for at least 14 years.
Let me do that math.
She'll only have experienced
unrequited love twice at 36.
-Really?
-Your hair looks great.
Maybe it's because it's black.
My gosh. You're so handsome!
No way. Not a chance!
Darn, I'm done sleeping.
So-bin!
What's the excuse for drinking
this time around?
He won't take my calls.
That's why I can't sleep.
-Who?
-This darn idiot.
-A guy?
What?
He's like a thorn embedded in my chest.
-A thorn!
What's gotten into you two tonight?
Are you already drunk?
You're not one to talk about guys.
Mostly exercising and drinking.
Who is this guy?
He's a thorn that's stuck in deep,
so it hurts.
Why love someone
who'd only give you heartache?
You should've kept it casual.
Why love someone
who you need to make excuses to see?
Who? You?
Me?
Wait. Is this room cursed?
Why is everyone
suffering from unrequited love?
No, not me.
I'm done with one-sided love.
I'd rather die a relationship virgin
than love someone
who doesn't love me back.
As if you can control that.
This isn't something
you can write a declaration for.
Whatever. Let's just drink.
But I'll gain weight.
The calories will be split three ways.
Rather than gaining the whole 3kg,
we'll gain 1kg each.
Sounds good.
It'll be 3kg each and a total of 9kg.
Unbelievable.
Let's be loyal friends
and gain weight together.
Cheers.
That's a big bite.
It's good.
[Why should I even bother?]
Why should I
when I'm neck-deep in my own worries?
[Search]
[Food to eat to recover from malnutrition]
[Nam Soo-hyun]
I can work, sir.
A youngster who used to work with us
died last month.
He was studying for the state exam.
I'm fine, sir.
That night--
You work nights after
taking classes during the day, right?
-Yes.
-Then study hard
and find a less demanding job.
It's all for your sake.
[Job search: Night shifts]
Do you have any night shifts available?
Hello? I'm calling about
the school cafeteria job.
Right, I see.
Hey, Mom.
It's the weekend. Are you well?
I sent some money to Uncle.
Don't worry about
Koo-hyun's rent at the gosiwon.
It's all right.
Mom.
What if I dropped out of school?
No, it's not like that.
All right, sure.
[Nam Soo-hyun]
[Contacts]
[Yeo Jun-wan]
[Get me the company files.]
[I'm sure you heard,
but Father declined my request.]
[Yeo Jun-wan]
[I'm not asking as your family.]
[I don't have one anyway.]
[You pay my credit card bills]
[Yeo Jun-wan]
[to buy me out of this family.]
[Consider this as an advance.]
Jun, where are you headed?
Let's grab something to eat.
Hi.
-Hello.
-Jun!
Next time.
I'll hear your answer next time.
I'm scared.
-Let's go!
-Sure.
One, two, three!
-I should at least give him an answer.
-Jun, one more.
One, two, three.
Gosh, you look amazing!
-Do you like tteokbokki?
-One, two, three.
Take the shot.
Let's go for some tteokbokki.
-What do you say?
-Let's go.
[He told me about ten things
I should remember.]
[I have a good memory,
so let me demonstrate.]
[One, don’t demand her to be girly.]
Two, don't...
Two, don’t let her drink
more than three shots.
She hits random people, you see.
[Don't order coke or juice at a cafe]
[and order coffee.]
When she hits you,
pretend that it hurts when it doesn’t
[and bear the pain when it does.]
[If she complains about her sore feet,]
[swap shoes with her.]
[She likes to write...]
Yeo Jun,
let's talk in private.
[Myungil University]
What's this about?
I won't stop or repeat myself,
so listen carefully.
My So-bin has acrophobia, agoraphobia,
and is scared of cockroaches.
She's scared of just about anything.
She also likes mint chocolate flavor.
Pineapples on pizza? Loves them.
But she hates the crust,
so eat it instead.
When eating sundae,
she only enjoys the liver.
With tteokbokki, she likes
cheap fish cakes with
flour-based rice cakes.
Spicy food? Loves them.
She drinks to enjoy hangover dishes.
Tteokbokki, sundaeguk,
gamjatang, yukgaejang...
Wait. With maratang,
she goes for a mid-spicy level
with dried tofu and napa cabbage.
Did you get all that?
Did you listen carefully?
You'll ace the test on Kim So-bin.
Yes, I even wrote a thesis on her.
And? So what if you know a lot about her?
So what if you're old friends? Who cares?
-My So-bin--
-Stop calling her that.
I call her that because she's my So-bin,
not your So-bin.
I still haven't approved
your relationship.
If something stirs inside me
that makes me approve,
then I'll call her your So-bin.
Fine, she can be yours.
Right. What?
She'll be "honey" and "sweetie" to me.
Honey? Sweetie?
Gosh, are you insane?
Why can't I call my girlfriend that?
Why can't I?
Well, it's just that
I have a lot to tell you about her.
So why don't we
be good friends?
Hand it over.
It's proper manners to greet someone
before addressing business.
How about a hug?
A bow?
Let's hear it.
[2020 Second-half Sales Report:
Mijin Foods]
What desperate reason
did you need this for
that made you come to me for a favor?
And don't say it's for a school project.
It's for a friend.
A friend?
I promised to get this material.
You've got yourself a friend?
What's it to you anyway?
I mentioned this on the phone,
but the family is gathering next week.
Don't come.
No one's waiting for you anyway.
I had my DNA tested. Did you know that?
Because I thought my parents
weren't my parents?
No.
Because there's no chance
you're my brother.
Unfortunately,
you're my biological brother.
Give me your word if you want this file.
-Don't come home.
-No.
I'll be there.
When do I ever listen to you anyway?
Pay me all the money you want.
I'll still be at the house.
Did you meet the visitor
you were expecting?
Yes.
Then please hurry.
The uni president awaits you.
I'll be right there.
It must've been an important visitor
for you to push
your meeting with the president.
Yeo Jun-wan and...
Yeo Jun.
What about you? Any siblings?
No, I'm an only child.
Why didn't you say hi earlier?
You saw me, right?
Well, you stand out wherever you go.
Am I that blinding?
Do I shine bright like a diamond?
That means you can find me anywhere.
Right.
I looked at you to say something.
I'll answer what I didn't the other day.
Just a second.
Let me brace myself first.
Go ahead.
Thank you for telling me
about how you feel.
But...
I still stand by what I said
about not knowing you
and being scared of you.
Do you want to get to know me, though?
You do.
A little.
Well,
it's only because I'm a curious person.
Not because I like you.
Let me be clear with that.
Why bother?
I'm good with it not being clear.
Also, unresolved curiosity
will give you constipation.
Okay, fine.
Every day, I'll let you know
something about me.
Remember them as I list them,
but don't fall too hard for me.
That'll never happen.
I'm not like that anymore.
I'm a new person now.
This is my declaration,
so don't you forget it.
Well, two negatives make a positive.
Okay, fine. Fall for me slightly then,
although that's hard to do.
What about you?
Are you curious about me?
It was your first time
being open about your feelings.
Why did I have to be your first, though?
I'm not trying
to put a meaning to it, but--
Yes. I'm curious about you.
Either be formal with me or don't
for crying out loud.
You're confusing me.
I'd rather you be consistent.
I'm off then.
Unbelievable. You just dug your own grave.
[Nam Soo-hyun]
[You're not passed out
on the street, are you?]
[Get some rest at home.]
Nam Soo-hyun, seriously?
What if you pass out again?
Soo-hyun passed out?
You really don't listen, do you?
I can't believe you paid
a week's worth in advance.
As if I can spend a week lying down.
What's wrong with using me
to take it easy for a week?
Others are fine spending my gold card.
Anyway, take this.
It's the material I promised.
[2020 Second-half Sales Report:
Mijin Foods]
Here.
What's this?
Did we agree on a payment?
It's what I owe you.
Did you work all night
in the state you're in?
You got the money this fast?
Did you take out a loan?
Loans aren't issued to people like me.
Did you go to a loan shark then?
Will you be buried alive
if you don't pay it back?
That's enough.
Then...
it was so that I wouldn't have
a reason to be clingy.
Did you sell your organs?
Let me see if you still have them all.
Why won't you look at me?
Don't tell me you sold an eye.
Six day's worth of hospital stay
was canceled on your credit card.
You can check.
I now owe you nothing.
-But you do.
-What?
As if anyone would steal that.
I gave the watch a secondhand price,
but tell me the price
if it had a sentimental value.
I didn't know of that.
You owe me emotionally.
How will you pay me back
for trampling on my heartfelt generosity?
That was the price for being clingy.
You still won't get rid of me, though.
Don't you get cocky. You'll soon miss me!
You'll want to see me!
[Professor, thank you
for going over my dissertation.]
[I won the participation award
all thanks to you.]
[You weren't at your office,
so I'm sending you a text instead.]
[Check outside your door.]
[Kim So-bin]
Professor,
I'll head in for the day.
Sure. Good job today.
-Have me back at any time.
-Sure.
Just a second.
What's this? I don't see a name.
Oh, it's mine.
Please utilize it however you want.
You want me to cite this?
Do I seem like a joke to you?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
You're dismissed.
Yes, ma'am.
Is she really dating Yeo Jun?
Jun must be insane.
Hey, that's Yeo Jun's girlfriend.
Hi.
Hey, So-bin.
I heard you're going out with Jun.
Is that true?
What? Who said that?
So it's true.
Well--
So-bin, you hit the jackpot.
Yeo Jun of all people?
I hear that computer engineering student
is also from a rich family
of a rural city.
A fair face may hide a foul heart.
That's a bit cruel coming from someone
who doesn't have all the facts.
I know. If only I had known.
I would've made a move on Jun sooner
had I known he'd date someone like you.
You see, I thought he had high standards
and was intimidated.
My bad. We'll see how long you last.
Let's go.
Ta-da.
Wait. Where did she go?
I'm totally embodying Leon today.
It's her loss.
You should watch the world
from this side too.
I'll show you off in a minute.
I see she's finally done.
[The Effects of Family Conflict
on Work Ability]
Hey, you're here.
You shouldn't be here
without my permission.
You don't ask
before entering my office either.
I know you steal my red ginseng candy
all the time.
Whatever. Now, leave.
I'm mistaken, right?
Regarding what?
And what on earth is that?
That's from So-bin...
Looks like you've finished
your dissertation.
Right. So? Are you asking me to a meal?
No thanks.
I saw that you copied
a student's dissertation.
Yes, I took a line that wasn't so bad.
What about it?
Someone even took my work
and copied all of it.
Darn that Professor Choi.
Because of that Professor Choi,
you took time off school
and fell off the grid.
I look for you everywhere.
That's how wronged you felt,
but here you are doing the same thing.
Are you becoming Professor Choi?
Or is this your way of payback
to Kim So-bin?
Kim So-bin?
Why would you mention her of all people?
Because it's her work.
I went over it for her
although that only involved me reading it.
Is that how low you think of me?
Let's not cross the line, Soo-kyung.
Park Si-jae.
I could say the same to you
and keep your mouth shut.
Got it?
So-bin!
You called me first, so I came running.
Did you tell the others
that we're dating?
I thought this was a secret relationship.
If you want, we can go public.
Only you and I know about this
and Chan-ki wouldn't have spilled.
That's a weird thing to say.
You keep taking his side
and accusing me instead.
Well, I mean--
That's not love. It's a habit.
Whether it's real between us or not,
don't take his side in my presence.
No matter what it is about,
I don't like being the center of gossip.
-You may be used to it but--
-I don't like it either.
Us dating...
is a lie anyway.
Hey, Jun. It's time for class!
[Myungil University]
-Here she comes.
-Is that her?
She's Yeo Jun's girlfriend?
Jun's way out of her league.
Tell me about it. Unbelievable.
-She's Jun's girlfriend.
-Talk about a mismatch.
-I'd be more compatible.
-No, me.
Yeo Jun has a girlfriend?
Yes, she flirted with him endlessly.
[Myungil University]
Her mom had an affair
and is leaving her family.
No, her dad had an affair
[and replaced her mom
with his girlfriend.]
[She has a half-sibling.]
So-bin will be taken to an orphanage.
-♫ She's an orphan ♫
Just apologize to Soo-hyun and come back.
"Apologize"?
You're telling me to apologize to him?
Don't tell me you're siding with Soo-hyun.
It's just Soo-hyun and So-bin.
Side with us, and we outnumber them.
Jun, are you really going out with So-bin?
Is that why you can't side with us?
I don't like being the center of gossip.
No, it's not that.
I knew it. Why would you?
This is why you shouldn't be too nice
to all sorts of losers.
"Losers"?
-Are you one of them?
-What?
Hey, Yeo Jun. That was so rude.
I'm off.
[Startup Project]
Don't be so difficult. Just side with us!
You won't get anywhere without us.
Are you confident
that you can beat Soo-hyun?
We'll be doomed if they do a better job.
That won't happen if they can't present.
This is Nam Soo-hyun's?
He dropped it.
Look.
[What I owe to Yeo Jun]
[Total: 1.2 million won]
I knew it. He figured out how nice Jun is
and totally took advantage of him.
He's like a leech.
Were they close behind our backs?
Jun should've come to us
and told us about this.
Where are you?
Hey.
So-bin!
Sorry, I'm sorry about that.
Are you all right?
Don't touch me.
Did something happen?
Did someone say something mean to you
for dating me?
Can you leave me alone?
I want to be alone.
What's wrong? Are you not feeling well?
I don't want to talk about it.
You won't get it anyway.
That is up to me.
You can at least tell me.
I don't want to. Why should I?
Has getting involved with me
made your life difficult?
Yes.
That said,
I don't want to have anything
to do with you.
Do you really mean it?
Yes.
I'm curious about you.
I'm not curious about you at all.
So don't be curious about me.
So you really mean it.
We were fine
when we didn't know each other.
Let's just go back to that.
[You can't even stay out of trouble?]
Don't ruin your brother's reputation!
-I'm sorry, Mother.
-You're such a troublemaker.
You make people around you so miserable.
If you behave yourself,
we'll have no problems at all.
Live like you're dead.
Don't create a roadblock for your brother!
I won't repeat myself. Quit and leave.
-Professor.
-I have nothing else to say to you.
Get out.
[Department of Business Administration,
Professor Song Soo-kyung]
We meet again.
This is where
the convenience store thug works.
I guess that wasn't enough.
My friends were afraid you'd actually die,
so they went super easy on you.
Hey, Jun.
Did Nam Soo-hyun extort money from you?
I see.
I'm sure he's done it to other fools.
Don't worry.
We're collecting evidence
to help you get your revenge.
That's right. Hurry over.
Let's get some fresh air.
Is she going to beat up someone else?
What does she like about UP?
How did he seduce her?
Poor losers like him are always fearless
because they're desperate.
They don't know
when not to cross the line.
Guys, let's just drink.
Cheers.
Hello.
I'm sorry. I'll take care of their bill
and take them home.
Why would you pay for their drinks?
Sorry?
I'll wake them up and deal with it.
Just go home.
Aren't you Yeo Jun in first year?
Yes, do you go to my school?
I'm Wang Young-ran, a senior in PE major.
Are you and Soo-hyun close?
No, we're not close.
I want to befriend him, but it's hard.
I just wanted to ask
if you've talked to him.
Soo-hyun and I are friends,
but I can't get hold of him.
You're Soo-hyun's friend?
What did you do to become his friend?
He wants to cut me off
whenever I try to do anything.
He's a difficult one.
But if I don't do anything,
he'll never even glance at me.
Right?
If I were asked to write just one line
on my resume,
I'd write "Nam Soo-hyun's only friend."
Nothing else.
That was an overshare, wasn't it?
Then I'll be "Nam Soo-hyun's friend
whom he adores like his little brother."
That's what I'll be.
Hey, come on.
Hey, let's go for another drink.
Today's the only day I'm available.
You always say you're not available.
-Are you a politician or something?
-Politics sure is important.
Professor Song will have my back soon.
What? Why?
-And you've got my back.
-That's right.
-You little...
-You too.
[Nam Soo-hyun]
-Come on.
-Do you want me to have your back too?
Oh, did you dial my number by mistake?
-Let's go.
-Did I call him?
[Do you want to have dinner?]
Sorry? What?
[I'm curious.]
[Do you really hate me that much?]
[Yes. Don't follow me.]
[I don't have time to waste with you.]
-Can I call you again?
-No, don't.
[You might call me first, you know.]
[That won't ever happen.]
It's for the coffee. Bye.
[I want to cross the line.]
I'm not curious about you at all.
[So don't be curious about me.]
[Do I]
[have the right
to be curious about someone?]
-What is this?
-I already paid for it. Eat up.
So, you were asking
if I wanted to have dinner alone,
not with you?
Excuse me.
Yes, do you need something?
How am I supposed to eat this?
Look, there's a bug here.
I'm sorry. I'll let the chef know
and get you a new one...
And I asked for butter earlier.
When will I get it?
I'm sorry. I'll bring it right out.
Come here.
What did you do wrong?
Oh, he asked for butter earlier.
Then you should've taken care of it
right away.
-I'm sorry.
-Do you want to get fired?
No, I'll be careful and work harder.
This is your final warning.
I'll be watching you.
I'm sorry.
And why are you always late?
-You need to get here on time.
-I'm sorry.
Gosh.
Did I keep you waiting long?
Don't come close. I smell like food.
Why did you call me here?
I think I know why,
but I want to make sure.
How was the food? Did you like it?
Don't act all sweet.
Why did you call me here?
So I could buy you dinner, okay?
Did you want to make me understand
why you're such a jerk to me?
Whenever I open my wallet,
I'm reminded of yours.
When I see your place, I think of mine.
I feel like I could walk out of my job
and go for drinks
or just chill at a cafe somewhere.
I think to myself, "It seems so easy.
Why can't I do that?"
You see,
I'm fine with not being able
to do stuff like that.
But I think of my brother
whenever I see you, and it hurts me.
You could've kept it short.
You're basically saying
you can't stand seeing me around.
"Don't be curious about me
or try to befriend me."
Did you call me here so I'd just get lost?
Yes, so you'd see my situation
and come to your senses.
I had no idea. I was all excited
on my way here, like an idiot.
Why not pick a better place
if you wanted me to experience
what it's like to be poor?
This place is too boring.
Did you have to work this hard
to pay me back?
I gave up my place.
Oh, you did?
Just to pay me back?
So I'd leave you alone and get lost?
Here, this is what I make in a day.
It's less than how much your dinner costs.
So what?
When I pestered my dad in tears
to buy me a game console
and asked him why my family was so poor,
he didn't say anything.
Then he quietly showed me
how much our total debt was,
his salary, our living expenses,
and the cost of raising me.
He thought that was a faster way
to make me understand.
You and I
can't be friends.
There's no need for us to be friends.
I heard you loud and clear.
You always mean what you say.
I prefer this rather than
being left with hope.
Thanks for the expensive dinner.
[Sauna]
Jun!
Choose your side.
Good luck, you two.
Hey, Jun.
I'll join you. Where else would I go?
I knew you'd join us!
Don't tell me you were torn.
That hurts my feelings.
I almost doubted you
and thought you were ditching us.
Let's go.
Jun, let's eat at your place.
-Gosh, you...
-My mom's there now.
-She can join us.
-Yes, let's go to your place.
Where do I begin?
Nam Soo-hyun works part-time
at the cafeteria.
The cafeteria?
What happened to his backer?
Let's go there and...
Hey.
What we did at the convenience store
is enough.
Let's not do the same thing again.
It's too childish.
Jun, let's do the assignment
at your place.
-Great idea, for a change.
-Right?
Jun.
-Yes.
-Let's do the assignment at your place.
My mother is supposed to come by that day.
Your mother?
This is my first time hearing you
talk about your mom.
Did we mention what day it'd be?
-I'm hungry.
-Let's go have some tteokbokki.
You know I don't eat tteokbokki.
[-I'm safe here.]
-I love tteokbokki.
Actually, I like it too.
[-No one's curious about me,]
-I can eat it all day.
Do you want to join us?
[and I'm not curious about them.]
-The tteokbokki place over there is good.
-No, thanks.
[No pain.]
Hey, you talk to her.
[-And no joy.]
-Let's go.
You're allergic to rice cakes.
[-I'm safe here.]
-I'll take my allergy meds.
You guys go ahead.
[Department of Business Administration,
Professor Song Soo-kyung]
Can I ask you something?
You probably know the answer.
I want to ask someone about something
but can't muster up the courage.
Will you gain something
by asking this question?
Think about that first.
I know I can't get the truth
just by asking,
but it'll at least make
the other person think.
And they'll either choose to
tell the truth, lie or stay silent.
Whether you find out the truth
or realize the other person
is lying to you
won't it be better than doing nothing?
What do you want to know?
I want to know
why I was fired.
You got fired for a reason.
Why do you want to know?
I don't want to hate myself.
Even if I do,
I want to know which part
I have to hate and fix.
I didn't like you from the start.
I hate people who are incompetent, greedy
and who just use other people.
When I decided you were incompetent,
that's all I saw.
Then that'll be a huge stress for you too.
All I'm going to do is point out
how incompetent you are.
-But you...
-I'm sorry if I was rude.
And thank you for your answer.
[Myungil University]
[2020 Second-half Sales Report:
Mijin Foods]
-This...
-Yeo Jun gave it to me.
So he gave this to you
and sat over there.
So...
he had a change of heart.
I have to get to work.
Let's just do what we talked about.
Okay.
Maybe we should get
new members for our group?
Give me lots of meat
and I don't want any onions.
I'm allergic to onions.
Are you ignoring a customer's needs?
He just doesn't care.
He doesn't care if you die
after eating the onions.
Are you here to see me?
You must be busy working
so we'll take care of the team project
and give you credit. No need to thank us.
I'm doing my team project with So-bin
and we're not giving you credit.
Do what you want.
We'll see who wins in the end.
Chun-guk, where's Jun?
Oh, Jun is afraid of Soo-hyun.
-He keeps stealing money from Jun.
-Oh, I see.
He's stealing money from his juniors.
That makes me feel
so ashamed as your senior.
Is he a loan shark?
He lends him money and makes him
pay it back with hefty interest.
Does he have double personality
or something?
Is he a psychopath?
-Why you little...
-Don't you have a brain?
-What?
-I was wondering if you ever use it.
Or it may just be there for decoration.
Why you little...
No, I can't take it anymore.
Hey, you. Come over here!
-That's enough.
-You want a piece of me?
[You didn't go home, right?]
[Park Hye-ji]
[We're at the school cafeteria. Hurry up.]
[Jung-ho, Chun-guk, Hye-ji]
[Chun-guk]
[UP and Jung-ho had a fight.]
You fight with a friend while working?
This place isn't a playground!
-I'm so sorry.
-Pay back the money
for the ingredients you ruined.
You can deduct it from my pay...
What are you talking about?
You're fired!
Kids today are so shameless.
I was going to take it easy on you
since you go to school here.
But making money is no joke.
Gosh.
Please! Please give me another chance.
I'll do better.
Let go of me.
-Please just give me another chance.
-Let go!
-I'll do better.
-You're fired!
Get out of my sight!
My gosh...
Hey. He gave me an excuse to
fire him at the perfect timing.
Yes. I fired him.
He wanted me to let him sleep
in the lounge,
but I really didn't want to.
Why didn't you tell me beforehand?
It's not that hard to hire a student.
Hold on.
Nevermind.
Yeo Jun!
When did you get here?
Oh, I guess the group meeting ended.
I shouldn't have
called you there.
I'm sorry.
Why? I had a nice meal.
I pitied you.
I saw how anxious you were.
I think I was relieved.
Life was fair after all.
Just because you're unhappy
doesn't mean I'm happy.
I was wrong.
You don't even have a place to go to
and you're pitying me?
Don't be so arrogant.
I was so ignorant.
Then again, we need to be on the same
level to have an actual conversation.
I was curious,
but it isn't fun.
I don't want to do it anymore.
Habits are hard to fix.
People live the way they used to.
Even if you try to change, you go back
to the place your mind
and heart remembers.
It's the same for me.
No matter how hard I try, I go back.
-What are you talking about?
-I know you don't mean it.
What do you know?
Just get over yourself and go away.
[I'm afraid to leave my safe zone.]
[I'm scared.]
[At a Distance, Spring is Green]
-Hey...
-Not interested.
You didn't have to do a good job
or be of help.
-At least you kept your promise.
-I won't be fooled.
[I have a question for them.]
[Nam Soo-hyun, stay where you are.]
[Kim So-bin, come up front
and give us your answer.]
What did you say? I can't hear you!
[I'm so sorry.]
[I know we were fine
when we didn't know each other,]
[but I don't want to
go back to that life.]
Don't push it.
And if I do?
Prepare yourself.
[I won't stop once I start.]
[A composite sketch.
I'm looking for someone.]
[-Don't you remember me?
-Enjoy.]
[I'm not going to be
friends with you anymore.]
-Give me five.
-Yes!
My gosh.
[I made a friend
for the first time in my life.]