[antifan_act, hashtag anti-fan, follow]
[Choi Tae-joon]
[Choi Soo-young]
[Hwang Chan-sung]
[Han Ji-an]
[Kim Min-gue]
[So I Married the Anti-Fan]
[Episode 13]
[A Dangerous Invitation]
-Go back inside.
-Let me see you go.
Okay, then.
Let me get charged.
-You should go.
-I'll really go now.
You'll be late.
Gosh.
[How dare you two fool me?]
Are you mad
that I didn't tell you it was In-hyung,
or is it because it turned out to be her?
What? Both, you punk. Happy now?
We were going to have that song
sung by an obscure rookie anyway.
So it didn't matter if In-hyung did it.
["Who-joon's Junior Auditions!"]
She's now a well-known rookie.
["Former Trainee from Who-joon's Agency
Draws Attention"]
"She was in the same agency as Who-joon.
She used to practice with him."
Do you have any idea
how that can damage your reputation?
Sounds great. It's not a lie.
And it's not like I lasted
because I'm completely blameless.
You're good at covering up these things.
Yes, but there is this crazy jerk
who's running around
knowing everything that came out
isn't a lie.
I should've
nipped Jae-joon off at the bud.
Mr. Bae, both Jae-joon and In-hyung
used to be your trainees.
And they even came before me.
Hey, kid. Have you been
helping them to this day
because you felt bad? Behind my back?
Just tell the media that you felt generous
and let In-hyung sing that song.
You aren't the type
who's afraid of making up a lie.
Please excuse me.
Don't deal with every reporter
you come across.
Before more people find out
how In-hyung sang that song,
release a new song and cover it up.
Yes, sir.
Bye.
-Ji-hyang.
-Yes, sir.
-Stay on top of everything, will you?
Goodbye.
-Is he gone?
-Yes.
Anyway, why did In-hyung say
she didn't have an agency?
That probably made Jae-joon angrier.
I'm sure Mr. Bae was flustered too.
Jae-joon must've called
and snapped at him.
I'm sure.
Can you find out what's going on?
Okay. And Joon, about that ring.
The men are having a meeting soon.
Really? Can you make a visit just in case?
Oh, and I found
-that ring.
-What?
How?
There's this person
who keeps finding it for me.
-Hello?
-Is everything well?
[You just left.
Nothing could've happened.]
I was just asking.
Anyway, why do you sound so down?
What's wrong with my voice?
I can almost see you through your voice.
Something must feel eerie.
Yes. Because I left you there.
Why? Did you melt
because that was too sweet?
Sleep tight, Geun-young.
Sleep tight.
My gosh.
What was that?
He must be crazy. My gosh.
Did you look into the ring again?
I asked around,
but it's not easy to find any information.
But there was someone
who had a photo among his friends,
so I decided to take that.
If we know what he looks like...
We have to find that man.
Do you understand?
Yes, I'll get back to you.
You may go.
That ring.
I'm sure it's very important to him.
Mom.
Do you know, Mom?
[YAMA]
Do you know what this means?
You could've picked up at least once.
[Spigen Entertainment]
["A Former Trainee with Who-joon
Draws Attention"]
Director Kim, you can't do this.
The term was that
we only find real rookies.
Come on,
we're all professionals here, Mr. Choi.
You can use this chance
to make her famous,
then sign a contract with her again.
It's a win-win situation.
[GBC]
[What's wrong?
Is she done with your agency for good?]
Listen. SP Group made an investment,
and we're telling you
to only pick real rookies.
I mean, doesn't SP
simply want the show to go well?
This was a business agreement.
Your investor is telling you to drop this.
Don't you know who's paying for that show?
Mr. Choi, our show is now
trending at number one on the internet.
[Also, if Oh In-hyung
doesn't have any potential,]
[people will vote her off anyway.]
I will not condone
any pressure of this sort.
Goodbye, then. I'm on set.
Hello? Hey.
You used to be a trainee with Who-joon
in the same agency.
[Spigen Entertainment Audition Project]
How did you feel
as you watched him become a big celebrity?
Well, Joon had always been
one of the best trainees,
so I always knew he'd do well.
To be frank, if I were you,
I don't think
I would've just been happy for him.
I'm sure you probably weren't jealous,
but you're a human too, In-hyung.
I mean, a close friend became a big star,
while you just...
Well.
[Spigen Entertainment Audition Project]
I wouldn't say I was jealous.
But back then,
I was the only one who remained
as a trainee for a long time.
-I'm sorry.
-It's all right.
Is that why you kept
your friendship with him a secret?
Some people out there say you
kept your friendship with him a secret.
I'm sure it's because you two
now live in different worlds.
Yes.
Once his career took off
and our world became so different,
things turned a little awkward between us.
Cut. That was great.
Director, thank you so much
for letting me pass.
[Spigen Entertainment Audition Project]
Don't thank me. It's all on you.
I think it'd be great
if we can get an interview from Who-joon.
-Right?
-Yes.
Can you make it happen?
I mean, if you can't, it's fine.
But it'll be better for everyone
to keep this hot issue burning.
Exactly.
Okay, then. I'll ask.
-Ask him and let us know.
-Okay.
Great work today.
-Great work today.
-Great work.
-You've done so well today.
-I'll take that.
-Okay.
You said you'll recruit
Who-joon or whatever,
but were you just bluffing?
It's underway.
Really?
If you came to ask me that,
then go back and wait.
Anyway, about Oh In-hyung,
the girl who went out on that audition.
Mind your own.
I told them to only let rookies in,
but the director wouldn't listen.
Do you think I came here
without knowing the entire story?
That troublesome old rookie is
finally getting her break,
but how dare you let her say
she'll cancel the contract?
Darn it, my neck hurts.
You were the one who told me to drop her.
Her value went up.
And that TV director
gave her a break at once,
something you couldn't do over six years.
Do I have to step in to sign a contract
with this nobody?
This is nobody's business,
so don't do anything and mind your own.
I'll manage.
Do you realize that no one in this family
expects you to manage anything smoothly?
This will be your last chance.
And lastly,
let me give you a piece of advice.
You can't afford
to cut anybody's slack right now.
That jerk.
[Group Chat: 3 people]
[Why don't we all meet up
for chicken today?]
I'm all for it.
[What are you up to?]
[Mr. Joon: What are you doing?
You won't even text me.]
Hey, what do you think
about the rhythm here?
I like it.
[Just Lee Geun-young:
I thought you'd be busy.]
You like this? The beat is off right here.
[I can stay in touch with you
no matter how busy I am.]
[Mr. Joon:
But I think I'll be late today.]
[You aren't the only one who's busy.
I have plans too.]
What are you doing?
Hey, one second.
Hello?
Wait, where are you going?
[My gosh, this guy seems
more obsessed than I thought.]
[Did you call me to ask that?]
My gosh, this woman is
much of a player than I thought.
Then you weren't going to tell me
who you'll be with?
[Shooting Star Entertainment Company]
I'm meeting everyone at the chicken place
where Mi-jung works at. Are we good?
Really? It'd be great if I could come.
[But the recording will take a while.]
Next time. We can go together next time.
Okay. Don't drink too much, okay?
And don't go home too late.
And don't smile so much
in front of others.
Goodness, I thought you were
unbelievably busy today.
Stop nagging at me and get back to work.
Gosh, this is so unfair.
I was just worried. It wasn't nagging.
[You make me sad.]
Joon, get back inside.
I'll call you later.
[Ms. Lee Geun-young]
[The person you have reached
is not available. Transferring to...]
Ms. Lee, there's no way
you two can avoid me and be happy.
You're now taking his side too?
It's really hard
to see Geun-young these days.
It's as if she's a celebrity.
I wouldn't call her that.
But are you dating someone?
What? Hey, I don't have time for that.
What brings Shin-hyuk here at this hour?
Hey, Shin-hyuk.
Did your study group end already?
Yes, it was a very tough day.
Geun-young, is Who-joon busy?
Yes, I'm sure.
What would she know?
They're just on the show together.
A celebrity like him
lives a different life from us.
Isn't that so, Geun-young?
Come on. He lives such an awesome life.
He only seemed cool.
Right, isn't "So I Married the Anti-Fan"
on air today?
What? Don't turn it on.
Let's watch it.
It's embarrassing.
Is that when you went to Japan?
[Looking cool in an ad shooting!]
[Perfect chemistry with the model]
Did you go to Japan
because of his TV ad shoot?
This and that.
Isn't that model the same girl
who got her break in the audition show?
Why couldn't she make it before?
She's so pretty.
You probably saw her in real life.
So? Is she pretty?
Yes, she's pretty.
She looks the same in real life.
[Who-joon's sweet and cute moment!]
If she was there as his partner,
I guess they're really close.
They used to be in the same agency.
The same agency? Who is she anyway?
Her name is Oh In-hyung,
a singer signed with JJ's agency.
She debuted as a member of Florence
six years ago, but failed.
She recently went on an audition,
where her history of practicing
with Who-joon as a trainee came out,
which drew many people's attention.
Shin-hyuk, that was amazing.
When did you memorize all that?
Why can't you use your good memory
when you take your exams?
Goodness.
Mi-jung, while we're on the subject,
-should I try to be an entertainer?
-What now?
I think I have the potential
to be an entertainer.
The potential?
Baby, forget the potential.
Why don't you gain some credentials?
-Hey, credentials sound great.
-It sounds great.
Yes, let's make a toast
for his credentials.
-Cheers.
I don't want to work hard
and study for some exam all the time.
I want to live a cool life like Who-joon.
Sweetie, that's enough.
Stop joking around in front of my friends.
I'm not joking.
Why would I joke about this?
Then what? What about
all the time I invested in you?
"Invested"?
-Invested.
-No, I...
I'm sorry. I should probably go.
Wait, I...
[Perfect chemistry with the model]
[Who-joon's sweet and cute moment!]
In-hyung, you're putting on wings
called Who-joon to fly up?
[CEO Bae Young-suk]
And there was another guy
who couldn't stand to see that.
You must be extremely worried, Mr. Bae.
[What the heck are you getting at?]
Wait, you didn't know
about the TV ad either?
It's not like
I'm happy about this, Mr. Bae.
I think it might do you better
if you heard me out first.
If you think I'm trying to pull something,
I'll just do things my way.
Shin-hyuk was serious,
so we shouldn't have taken it as a joke.
Well, it'd be great
to live as a prosecutor's girlfriend,
but a star's girlfriend sounds good too.
Doesn't it, Geun-young?
What? Me? I wouldn't know.
You should probably call him.
Look at the time...
[You're drinking a lot again, aren't you?
Time to go home.]
[Mr. Joon]
[I'll be outside.]
Look at the time.
You're leaving already?
It's way too late.
I guess it's pretty tough
to live with your senior.
It's not that.
I forgot that I have a shooting tomorrow.
Okay. You should go. It's late.
I'll get going.
Work things out with Shin-hyuk.
Okay. Should I grab a cab for you?
No, I can catch one out there.
-Stay. It's cold.
-Bye.
Bye.
You aren't too drunk.
When did you get here?
Did I keep you waiting?
Is your day over? You didn't have to come.
Did you eat anything?
How did you keep
all these questions to yourself all day?
How can I not come
if you were out drinking at night?
There are lots of people here.
What if someone sees you?
Tell them to look. Let's go.
Okay.
So? Did you have fun
hanging out with your friends without me?
I thought you'd drink a lot.
Right, remember Shin-hyuk?
Mi-jung's boyfriend.
He suddenly said he wants to be
an entertainer, so they got into a fight.
What? He said
he wants to be my lawyer before.
Exactly, that's what everyone thought,
but he suddenly said he wants to be
an entertainer, so Mi-jung blew up.
Wait, is that something to be angry about?
What's so bad about entertainers?
But someone with Shin-hyuk's looks
couldn't be an entertainer...
Well, you never know what will happen.
He might become a big star.
You never know what will happen.
Who knew we'd be in this relationship?
What's our relationship?
What?
Well, you know.
Two people who sit together
in the night and stuff.
There are so many stars.
There are.
So? Do you want me to get you one?
-Gosh, that's awful.
-People in this relationship go,
"I'll get you a star!"
My gosh, I hate it.
Cut it out. That's so cheesy.
But whenever I look up
and see stars that sparkle,
there's someone I'm always reminded of.
What? You aren't staring at me
because you didn't get who it is, right?
Who is it? Who's this jerk?
Did you want to be like those stars
that shine brightly?
I wouldn't say I wanted to shine.
I had to.
I took the opportunity
that could've gone to someone else.
I think I made one too many mistakes
trying to shine brightly like the stars.
Have you heard?
You have to make up at least seven lies
in order to make one lie work.
Once I started lying,
it just never stopped.
A guy who studied in America.
A guy born from an affluent family.
And my birthday also became December 31st,
to make it seem like
it's a fate for me to win awards.
Did I ever tell you my birthday was faked?
My real birthday is February 27th. 0227.
That's the passcode to the penthouse.
You're right.
I put it there in case I forget.
In case I lose touch with who I really am.
But that's not important.
The truth is, I'm a hillbilly from Alaska
who doesn't know who my dad is.
Are you still looking for him?
All I know about him is
that ring you found for me last time.
Ji-hyang said he'll visit the group
who made that ring.
Then you might find him.
Maybe.
But I'm kind of scared too.
What if I fail to protect him,
just as I failed with Mom and In-hyung?
Don't be afraid.
I'm sure your mother knows
you didn't give up on protecting her.
And In-hyung too.
That's why I now have someone
I truly want to protect.
Are you staring because you don't know?
Anyway, I had a question.
Why do you like me?
I gave that a thought.
When you're here with me,
I don't feel anxious at all.
I'm completely in peace.
I'm kidding.
How can you like someone for a reason?
I just like you.
Goodness, it has been so long.
You must've been in a hurry, Mr. Bae.
You're still the same.
What are you trying to pull?
I'm not pulling anything.
Didn't I say I have an offer?
I know you.
Stop trying to deceive me,
and say what you have to say, kid.
"Kid"?
You kicked me out saying
I'm not one of yours.
What?
Hey, you're the one
who didn't want to stay home.
You're the one who felt belittled and left
when Joon started to get his break.
You need to wake up too.
Don't let that big boy Joon fool you,
making you go around
cleaning up after his mess.
You don't like
how he's still clinging onto his history.
Don't you simply want him
to do as you say and bring in money?
Think about it.
How many people do you think know
about Joon and In-hyung's history
in this industry?
It's just you and me.
So? Are you going to expose that or what?
You thought I was that simple
after years of working in this field?
Hear me out.
What will you and I get
from exposing their relationship?
If it gets out, it'll only drop the value
on Joon and In-hyung's reputation.
Let's merge our agencies.
Once they belong in the same agency,
all the rumors surrounding them
will come to a halt,
and you can keep my mouth shut too.
Man, you crazy kid.
Is this the so-called "offer"?
And do you think Joon's ancient history
could bring damage in any way?
Stop being petty over the love life
he had before his debut
and save yourself from the humiliation.
Make sure you keep In-hyung under control.
Bye.
Mr. Bae, you shouldn't talk like that.
Why do you think
that's the only information I have?
All right, we're here.
-Get a good rest.
-Thanks.
And about this house.
I'm going to move out.
I was in a tight situation at first,
but I got paid by the show too.
-Wait, you can't.
-What?
You can't.
You'll make me anxious. Just stay.
Why would that make you anxious?
I feel more anxious to stay here.
I'll just shop for a place for now.
No, stop getting a weird idea,
and see you tomorrow on set.
You're staying, okay?
I'll think about it.
Drive safely.
No, don't get off.
I'm scared you might run into someone.
Bye.
Get a good rest.
Why did he come back?
You did your laundry.
Well, I didn't want you
to take this the wrong way.
I had some circumstances,
so I asked him to let me stay.
Do you remember what I asked of you
when I ran into you at the office?
I asked you to take caution
and make sure you don't cause him damage.
Yes, so
do you think I caused him any damage?
I understand that
a young man could date someone.
But if he's a big celebrity,
that isn't always the case.
Even the most insignificant relationship
could cause him big damage.
Insignificant.
You're being a bit too harsh.
Am I?
If I can be harsher, I'll do that.
Then what did you think it'd be like
to date a top star?
Do you want to see Joon crash down
at once?
Well, Joon is like that.
He can't stand to see someone
who's troubled,
just as he did for In-hyung.
Let me give you a piece of advice.
Why don't you date someone in your league?
I'll give you the benefit of doubt
and consider everything you said
as your concern about Who-joon.
You've known him much longer than I did,
but you trust him way less than I do.
Don't you think we're the ones
who can choose what this relationship is?
Do you think you two have
any choice in this?
Okay, fine.
Let's say Joon chooses you
and gives up on everything.
Do you think you two will be happy?
What about Joon? The public will
turn their back on him at once.
He'll have to deal with that,
and can you deal with him
when he's in that spot?
It seems like you know more about him now,
so I'll trust that you will make
the wisest decision and leave.
If I were you, I'd move out
as soon as tomorrow's shooting is over.
Do you know how dangerous it is
for you to live here?
Let me know if you need to find a place.
Goodbye.
My gosh.
Why are you sitting there like that?
What about you?
The studio said you left ages ago.
Don't be so worried. I went for a drive.
What is it?
Is something going on?
Joon, about that ring.
I went to the meeting,
but no one was in touch with him.
After they graduated,
they heard he was getting married.
Then they lost touch with him
once he moved abroad.
Do you think that was my mom?
That could be the case.
So I'm going to ask around a bit more.
I'm sure he had a close friend
among his alumni.
And right.
I got an old photo of him from them.
Right.
I was going to move out anyway.
I'll move out right away
as soon as tomorrow's shooting is over.
[Balance: 23,121,544 won]
With my severance pay
and the pay from the show,
I could probably find a studio, right?
[For lease]
[Mr. Joon]
I'll trust that you will make
the wisest decision and leave.
[Mr. Joon]
Okay.
Later.
I'll tell him later.
This is the last time I sit out here.
I won't have to hide anymore,
so it's for the better.
Goodbye, be well.
It's also my first time
feeling at home at an emergency exit.
-Hello.
-You're here.
-Hey.
Baby, is something going on?
You don't look so well.
Nothing's going on.
Look at this.
Let's see.
What's wrong?
-Hello.
-Hey.
-What are you doing?
-My goodness.
You were thinking of me.
My gosh. People might hear you.
No one is around.
Gosh.
Did you see this?
Articles are flooding out on Oh In-hyung.
See? My gut feelings were right.
I told you that
she'll be the hottest issue.
What do you think will happen to us?
My gosh, you need to stop that.
I know you like it.
-What?
-Come on.
Stop it. My gosh.
What's wrong?
Hey, since when were you standing there?
Well, the...
The cast is on standby.
Let's get started, then.
Watch it.
I'm sorry.
Could you open the door?
Hold out a little longer, Geun-young.
You'll miss everything once it all passes.
Are you drunk?
You always pop my bubble
whenever I say something nice.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
We're all ready. Please get set.
What should we do today?
Do you want to do anything?
Well, there's nothing much
we can do at home now.
Should we go on a trip
before it gets colder?
Then let's leave.
-Right now?
-Yes.
-Isn't that how people travel?
-Some do.
-Is it okay with you?
-Okay.
-I guess.
-Okay, then.
Ms. No and Geun-young can discuss
where you want to go.
Who-joon, may I have a word with you?
Please.
He seriously has a knack
for throwing people off, right?
He does.
What is it?
You haven't heard, have you?
Hear what?
Today will be the last shooting.
What? All of a sudden?
Is there a problem?
It's not a problem, per se.
Who-joon's schedule is full too.
Things were worked out
between the higher-ups.
It's shocking, but what can we do?
Does Ms. Lee know?
What I want to tell you is...
Where do you want to go?
Geun-young?
-Yes?
-What's wrong?
Do you want to do something here?
No.
Right? You'll be coming here
until you get sick of it anyway.
Why don't we go see the winter beach
and get some fresh air?
Okay.
Excuse me.
You're right.
I'll be coming here
until I get sick of this place.
[Geun-young.]
[Did I surprise you?]
[Gosh, a video message?]
[I get really awkward
when I do these things.]
[But I'm sending you this message
because I have to tell you something.]
[-I'm disappointed to say this...]
-I had no idea.
["So I Married the Anti-Fan."]
[Throughout the shooting,]
[I feel like I gave you a tough time.]
[I'm sorry.]
[However,]
[I'll never forget every single moment
I shared with you on the set.]
[I don't know where to begin
or where to end this,]
[but what I do know is this.]
[You met me as an anti-fan,
but at this moment,]
[I've become your fan.]
[I'll never forget every moment
I spent with you, Geun-young.]
Thank you,
and I mean it, Geun-young.
Why are you crying?
It's all right. Okay?
Why? Why do we suddenly have to stop?
I get that,
but why did you deceive me too?
It's not that I deceived you.
I couldn't tell you.
Why not? You know better than anyone
how I must've felt when I got into this.
It's because I knew everything.
How can I tell you it's the last time?
But still, you should've told me.
I'm sorry.
Next time, you'll be the first to know.
-Forget it.
-Are you mad?
Completely.
You're so cute.
What's wrong with you?
Let's go.
Come on, let's go. I promise.
Well. Mr. Han. Mr. Han?
[Shooting Star Entertainment Company]
-What?
-You know what.
That's enough TV show for now.
You won't have enough time
to prepare your album and concert.
I already talked to the TV station,
so that's that.
You could've discussed this with me
at least once.
Hello?
Darn it.
Joon, let's talk to him again
after the shooting.
Okay.
Report on everything
outside of his schedule.
Find out where he goes and who he sees.
Get on his tail.
We nip the bud before it blooms,
and tie up somebody
before they trample you.
Why did you cry
as if we're really breaking up?
That was embarrassing.
We can't break up anymore.
It'll break you.
I was really surprised. I had no idea.
Don't be so sad. It's for the better.
-Let's go on a date without cameras.
-Let's get going.
Let's go.
We'll start the camera now.
You can follow the car in the front.
Okay.
Okay, let's go, Ms. Lee.
Buckle up.
We can't get into another accident.
[Let's go.]
[Spigen Entertainment Audition Project]
Don't be so wary of me.
I'm not here to do anything.
You sent me the cancellation of contract,
but I've been doing my best for you.
What kind of "best" are you doing?
You aren't the type who would sit around
while my name goes out in the media
next to Joon's name.
I don't care what your best is,
but drop everything.
Why do you think I would want
to cut off your hard-earned wings?
And the industry has been
making a connection between you two
without my help anyway.
They're making me want to speak up.
What are you talking about?
Don't you get it?
If you're going to do anything weird,
just drop it.
Hear me out to the end.
That's why
I'm going to turn the time back.
You, me, Joon,
all at Shooting Star together once again.
Once we do that,
all three of us can get what we want.
Think about it.
Joon is finally of some help.
We can't just let go of this chance.
Both you and me.
Come on, you want that too, right?
Give it a thought and let me know.
I'll help you.
I don't need your help.
It's not like I didn't learn anything
while I stayed with you.
I learned a lot from everything you did.
I realized how pathetic it is
to put up a struggle
when you can't be half as good as someone.
Can you leave?
I have to compete with young
and talented kids, so I got no time.
Really?
It really was like that.
So what do you want after?
-Let's get ramyeon.
-Okay.
You drove when we first got started,
but I drive on our last episode.
That day still makes me shudder.
It's our last day.
Let's not mind anybody else
and enjoy our day.
Okay?
-Okay.
-Great work.
Take this.
-This is nice.
-It's nice.
Aren't you glad we came out?
Now that we're facing the end,
could you two please be nice to each other
and try to look like a real couple?
Did we seem that distant?
I'm sure you're closer than before,
but you two aren't
in such a loving relationship.
Right?
Then what do we do now?
Well, what do couples do
when they're at the beach?
Let's figure something out.
Are you saying In-hyung is suing me?
Do you have to take things this far
to cut me off?
Were you that sick and tired of me?
This doesn't seem too special.
I guess couples feel happy
just to walk with one another.
I'm sure.
If it doesn't seem too special,
can they do something
and make this special?
I mean, no matter
how awful their relationship is,
if they're here now,
can't they be like a real couple?
You know, holding hands,
-then put arms around...
-Excuse me, you two! Can you hold hands?
-They did.
It's okay.
I don't think I ever got to enjoy
the little things in life.
As I kept my eyes on you,
I realized fame and living a fancy life
isn't always a good thing.
I've always been confident that
I never had any regrets in that aspect.
Come to think about it,
I do have some regrets.
Everyone regrets.
Nobody is perfect.
That's why
I'm not going to do that anymore.
Someone told me not to be afraid,
that this too shall pass.
I'm hungry. Aren't you?
I've been hungry for a while.
You are, right?
Mr. Han, did you hear that?
How can you not feed us
while we're working?
Let's eat something.
Yes, I totally got that. Cut!
Cut!
-Let's go.
-Hurry up.
Do you have a jacket?
-You can use this.
-I'm fine.
-Put it on.
-No.
You'll catch a cold. Let's go.
-I'm fine, really.
-Keep it on.
I'm not a celebrity or anything.
You can't catch a cold.
[CEO Cho Hae-yoon]
Come in.
The CEO of Spigen Entertainment is here.
Let him in.
Yes, sir.
What brings you to my office?
I had to discuss something,
and you wouldn't have come
even if I asked.
Please take a seat.
Is it Ms. Oh In-hyung's lawsuit?
What should I do?
Will you settle this?
Or should we continue?
It's obviously a breach of contract,
so is there a way to make her pay
a huge compensation?
As I mentioned before,
the contract doesn't state that.
I'm only your legal attorney,
not your troubleshooter.
Have you always been that uptight?
Sorry?
Let's put the lawsuit off for now.
It's not like I'm in a hurry.
-Okay.
-Oh, right.
What if someone gets sued for exposing
someone's history without evidence?
What happens in this case?
That happens from time to time
in the entertainment business.
Who's in question?
-You?
-No, not me.
I'll find some precedents.
[CEO Cho Hae-yoon]
What do those Roman numerals mean?
Pardon?
Oh, it's nothing.
It's just a personal keepsake.
Oh, I see.
-Here's your fish cake.
-Thank you.
Don't they seem a bit odd today?
I know it's the last time,
but why does she look at him so ardently?
Is it so heartbreaking
to see him order tteokbokki?
Why? Why are you staring at me?
Nothing, you look really pretty
when you work hard.
-What's with you?
-Is it just me?
-Enjoy.
-Thank you.
All right.
Wait.
-Stop it.
-Come on.
[Old-fashioned tteokbokki, Fish cake]
-So? Is it good?
-It's good.
There's a great tteokbokki place
in Dangjin, actually.
The tteokbokki there is amazing.
We should go there sometime.
Dangjin? I haven't heard
of a place like that.
If you went there, it'd be famous by now.
What's amazing is this.
The owner lady there has no idea who I am.
No way, how can anyone not know
who you are?
I mean it. That's not important to her.
She's only invested in tteokbokki.
She's a master.
It must be a really good place.
Why aren't you eating?
Seeing you eat makes me feel full.
Here. Let me feed you too. Open up.
-This fish cake is delicious.
-Take a big manly bite.
-The fish cake is really good.
-Really?
-Let's eat together.
-Open up.
-You're eating so well.
Is Dangjin famous for tteokbokki?
I don't know.
But something is
definitely weird with them.
It's better than
seeing them bicker to the end.
[You're eating so well.]
I need information on this guy too.
A lawyer named Cho Hae-yoon.
I'll send you his business card.
And he's in his 50s.
But there was someone
who had a photo among his friends,
so I decided to take that.
What about the photo of the ring owner?
Did you get it?
All right.
[Thank you.]
This is it?
You aren't going to put anything else?
There are lots of unsaid words
in "Thank you."
-I'm very grateful.
-Come on.
-Give it to me. Give it.
-No. Why?
-It's a shame, really.
-You'll do something weird.
-Nothing weird. Just trust me.
-No way.
Give it to me. You'll hurt your hand.
Instead of leaving it like this,
do something like, you know, this.
[Thank you.]
-I knew you'd do this.
-Isn't this sweet?
-No way.
-Just leave it like this.
Will you give me an autograph?
Okay, sure. I'll probably spend
all my life signing autographs.
I guess the beach is
also pretty nice in winter.
Today is
the last time we spend together.
It feels weird.
-Doesn't it?
-It does.
Don't forget
all the time we spent together.
How could I? I had such a tough time.
You're right.
Thank you. I mean it.
Are you cold?
No, don't try to give me your coat.
I really don't like that.
I got cold and just wanted to button up.
You're so full of yourself.
Right, I knew it.
I shouldn't have taken it the wrong way.
Here. You aren't cold now, are you?
I'm okay, really.
They finally seem like a real couple.
Looking nice.
Cut. That's all. Great job, everyone.
-Great work!
-Mr. Seo?
What's next on Who-joon's schedule?
Everything is really over.
Great work to the end.
It's not the end.
It's just the beginning.