We often say that
when you recall a game,
you are actually
recalling your youthful years.
I didn't tell you that before,
because it has been a year since we broke up.
It's such a long time for me.
Of course,
these are just memories.
After all,
who is still playing "Contra" today?
=Falling into Your Smile=
=Episode 04=
FNC.
I think you do not need further introduction.
It's our old rival.
Since they officially entered
the Chinese market last season,
we have played six games against them.
We won four and lost two.
The reasons for losing two games…
Cheng,
do I need to repeat them myself?
No, you don't.
I need you to take it seriously this year,
because they have a Korean aid
bought from the team
winning the world final last year,
that is, TAT,
the former boss of Cheng.
This guy is named Kun.
(Name: Li Hengshuo, another name: Kun)
I've watched
the nine games FNC
played as of Kun's participation.
They won six and lost three.
Their winning rate is up to 70 percent.
Kun's dominance in the jungle
is slightly better than K.
He is also very good at identifying
the enemy's weaknesses
and creating advantages for his teammates.
FNC's tactic for this season
is very clear.
Their junglers
will carry the whole team.
(Club data)
So when you are playing against them,
I hope each of you
can pay attention to
the resources in your own jungle.
We have Cheng and Chubby in the bottom lane.
So don't worry too much.
Kun also will not focus on
their vulnerable lane.
The top and middle lanes
are Kun's main targets.
Therefore, our junglers must cooperate well
in the top and middle lanes.
K.
Tong Yao.
We're about to play the game.
Is it useful to take notes now?
Tong Yao.
Besides Tamamo-no-Mae,
what other shikigamis
are you good at playing?
Besides Tamamo-no-Mae?
Can you play any other roles
besides Tamamo-no-Mae?
Well, we're doomed.
Once they ban her from playing Tamamo-no-Mae,
we will lose our midsolo.
Don't talk nonsense.
I'm good at playing a lot of shikigamis.
Menreiki, Susabi, Enenra…
I can play any role.
Good.
In the training game,
the enemy will definitely
ban your role of Tamamo-no-Mae.
Just get mentally prepared.
First, we can ban the enemy's junglers
from picking Yamakaze, Yoto Hime and Yasha.
I guess they will give the other two bans to
the shooter.
We must take Mannendake first.
Do not let Kun get it.
If Hakuro is not banned,
the enemy would choose to
combine Hakuro with Ichimokuren
in the bottom lane.
Then Cheng can continue to pick Youko.
Chubby can choose Kuro Douji or Umibozu.
There will not be many options left
for the enemy's junglers.
According to Kun's previous performance,
he would probably choose Ubume.
Their topsolo would pick
Ryomen or Shuten.
To make up for their loss in the jungle,
they are more likely to pick Shuten.
Tong Yao,
which shikigami will you choose?
Ootengu.
Okay, Ootengu.
Great, Ming.
You have foreseen that.
Tong Yao,
this is the first training game
since you joined ZGDX.
You can never take it lightly.
Okay.
I will not be a disgrace to the team.
You're very confident.
We must win this game.
Come on, everybody.
Tong Yao.
Come on!
I'll go and prepare
some food for everyone.
The script is done.
The rest is up to you.
(Ibaraki Douji, Mannendake, Ootengu, Youko,
Kuro Douji VS Shuten, Ubume, Hakuro, Ichimokuren)
(Start fight)
Line up along the river.
Cat, watch out.
The enemy's junglers
would come to steal Kirin.
They have entered our jungle.
I'll go to fight their bottom Kirin.
Stop.
Go straight to your top Kirin.
They probably won't show up.
Cat, get closer to the jungle just in case.
Okay.
Cheng,
how do you know they didn't come?
Ubume is weak in the early stage.
Besides,
the position he just took
was found by Cat obviously.
But he still chose to continue.
So I guess,
Kun should be waiting for K
at their bottom Kirin.
(Jungle controller!)
(Kun  Li Hengshuo
Jungle  Sweet of Team)
Why is this guy not here yet?
Tong Yao,
their jungler is here.
(Seal: Initiate)
Nice!
As they didn't add caster minions,
the jungler must be absent.
Do not risk until the enemy comes in sight.
What if you get caught in their trap?
I'm sure
their jungler is not so smart.
She is too fierce. I'm scared.
Don't be afraid.
It's not too late to kneel down.
You still have time to type in?
Maybe you can even browse the Weibo.
Okay, the bottom Kirin's time is up.
It's time to get refreshed.
Ignore it.
K, go to the top lane.
Wait for their topsolo with Cat.
Okay.
Chubby, let's go back to the base.
Let Kun think
there is no jungler in our bottom lane.
The enemy's supporter
and bottom laner have gone home.
Got it!
Kun is here.
Wait in the grass nearby.
After Cat stalks them here,
it will be a sure catch.
The enemy's midsolo is missing.
Be careful.
Middle and bottom laners, come to me.
Okay.
They took the bait.
Cat, K, kill their topsolo.
K, follow.
I'm coming.
(Defeat Assist)
Cat, stalk.
I'm coming.
Cat is stalking us.
No, it's a scam! Leave.
Come on.
(Seal: Double Assist)
(Unassailable Support Assist)
- Nice!
- Good! Bravo!
Cheng,
you can be a director.
We have a good script.
K, Chubby,
steal their Orochi with me.
Got it.
I'm dead. Be careful, Cheng!
(Defeat Assist)
K, watch out!
Leave! Hurry!
I'm leaving.
I'll wait for you to come back.
Don't go, K.
I can fight.
Tong Yao is starting again.
(Defeat)
K, be careful. I'm coming.
- Nice!
We won!
What's wrong?
Wonderful! Bravo!
Tong Yao, you played Ootengu so well!
A newborn calf is not afraid of the tiger.
You even dare go down to
the snake pit just now.
But I did a good job too.
No one would fight in this way.
Tong Yao,
I never thought
you could play the shikigamis so well.
- Great!
- You're too impulsive.
I thought we could fight them.
To kill you guys,
they had nearly run out of their skills
and got weak then.
If we hadn't seized the chance,
our skills would have been wasted.
It's too risky!
You taught me that!
How dare you talk back?
Confidence is good.
It's fear that brings trouble.
Tong Yao did very well, right?
Right!
Just move forward and fight.
You are indulging her.
I ordered milk tea for you guys.
Treat yourselves!
Milk tea.
Let's take a break.
Let's go.
Go. Tong Yao, let's go.
Go.
Let's go.
(Win)
Cheng,
aren't you going?
No.
FNC is also very powerful.
It's just a game.
We will win the next game soon.
(Dinner Live Broadcast Kun)
But,
the girl from ZGDX
did excellently as midsolo.
I really admire her operations.
I'm looking forward to meeting her
in the competition.
ZGDX's tactics surprised me today.
Stop watching it,
or you will be really cocky.
After graduating from primary school,
I've never heard any compliments from others.
Let me hear more.
She must be a pretty girl.
- Don't listen to his nonsense.
- Right?
You can receive compliments from me.
Good-looking girls
- …are all very dangerous.
- Go ahead.
I remember my mom said that to me.
- Although this team is very good.
- Go ahead.
But next time I won't fall for it!
What do you mean?
Captain,
I did a great job today.
Don't you want to praise me?
Good job.
Will you give me any reward?
Don't I have any strengths
that deserve your…?
Here is a small red flower for you,
a reward from your captain.
Keep going.
I will paint it on your forehead next time.
Lu Sicheng, you must have not
graduated from kindergarten yet.
Stupid Lu Sicheng.
This ugly flower cannot be wiped off.
You wanted a reward and I gave it to you.
But now you are trying to wipe it off.
Why are you so fussy?
By the way, little girls are not allowed
to speak dirty words.
You do not like the little red flower?
Next time I will paint a turtle for you.
Bah.
And I will paint it on your forehead.
Let me tell you something.
Today's training game was really amazing!
Tong Yao's operation is so wonderful!
She does deserve to be called
"Mulan in E-sports".
Chubby, talk something about Smiling.
My girl. Wonderful!
I also like this girl.
Suddenly I feel letting her have Cheng for a while
(Dinner Live Broadcast Chubby)
doesn't seem to matter.
The middle and bottom laners
should work well together.
What's going on with the midsolo,
Cheng and Yang?
My Smiling is great.
Can you explain
- Did I tell you…?
- …the "White Snake in E-sports"?
Explain it.
Jian Yang was my boyfriend
when I was a student.
Then we broke up.
Smiling appeared.
Can you see the words we typed in?
She is really at the base.
Why did you break up?
Young people in love break up easily.
Isn't it normal?
There is no special reason.
Where is Jian Yang now?
He is at CK's training base
in Shenzhen, China,
- and also in my blacklist.
- Naive!
Is that you who carried the team
to victory today?
In today's training game against FNC,
we would have had a big advantage.
I even went back to the city
and added some blood
under the nose of the enemy's midsolo.
Chubby, Cheng and K
worked together
to push the tower in the top lane.
After that, Cheng had a bright idea and said,
"How about going to steal their Orochi?"
So they went to do
that kind of sneaky thing.
But it turned out that
they shouldn't have done
too many things like that.
After all, everything is visible
in the bright sunshine.
Five people came up all at once
from the opposite side,
surrounding and beating them.
The big snake is also attacking wildly.
It was hard for them to survive, right?
I didn't carry the team. Really.
But the enemy was so eager to kill them
that they nearly ran out of their skills.
So I just reaped
the rewards of their hard work in the end.
Who stole the snake?
Dare you say it again?
Good. Team bully's anger!
Domineering Captain Cheng
fell in love with me.
What's going on with you two?
Focus on the live broadcasting!
Stop your public display of affection.
Why don't you behave decently?
Why should we do that?
We are just teammates, okay?
We did not go shopping hand in hand.
The only time Cheng and I
appeared on the street together
was when I first joined the team.
That day, as I didn't know the way,
Cheng accompanied me
to the supermarket to buy daily necessities.
We did not go shopping hand in hand.
And my taste is not so bad.
Yeah, his taste is not…
What are you talking about?
It's not what you think.
I just joined the team not long ago.
If we are together, you will soon know it.
Will we receive your wedding candies?
Yes, perhaps!
Shameless!
Hello, Base Explosion,
what the hell is "shameless"?
Room Administrator, time to work!
Ban this guy's speech quickly!
What are you waiting for?
He is waiting for your wedding candies.
Aren't you wearing headphones?
I didn't turn them on.
Then who are you acting for?
I just want to keep my ears warm.
Bravo. Smiling, come on!
Looking forward to your excellent
performance in the National League!
Let's go to dinner together!
We should celebrate our big victory
in tonight's training game!
Okay!
What will we eat?
I'm starving.
AZ Hot Pot.
Cheng, is it okay?
Okay. Go.
My treat!
Okay, it's your treat.
K, do you want to go with us?
Let's go.
I'm not going.
I can't eat spicy food recently.
Leave him alone.
He is just that kind of person.
Only games attract him.
My God, the beef is amazing.
Rui, help me get two more plates.
Come on, come on.
The beef is amazing,
so is the beef tongue.
I'll give you mine too.
How come you guys are eating so fast?
It's tender. Order two more plates.
Take your time.
I'll get nothing if I take my time.
568 yuan for a plate of scallops?!
Were they gotten out of the sea of stars?
Stop. Save some for me.
Tong Yao, you're screwed.
White gourd.
White gourd must be cheaper.
78 yuan!
Are you kidding me?
This is a robbery!
Why should I volunteer to pay the bill?
Nice.
Tong Yao.
What are you waiting for?
Get cracking.
I'm not hungry.
Is it because it's too expensive?
I saw that Cheng
gave his credit card
to the manager just now.
He paid the bill.
Excuse me.
Bring me two bowls of shark fin soup.
One is for drinking,
and the other is for rinsing my mouth.
Shorty.
Eat more meat,
so that you can grow taller.
Why is there no one here?
Take a careful look.
Look.
I think it's right here.
Let's go then.
Tong Yao.
There's something
I've been wanting to ask you.
You didn't want to come
when I invited you at first, right?
You still didn't say yes
after you arrived at the hotel.
How did you agree later somehow?
I was quite surprised.
To tell you the truth,
I thought Rui was a liar at first.
You thought?
He is a liar.
Me?
Have you ever seen such an honest liar?
Tong Yao, we have to make it clear.
Did I behave like a liar
when I was inviting you?
First you sent me messages in English,
and then in pinyin.
That was very strange.
And then I thought,
"Isn't there always a substitute
for Ming from ZGDX?
Where has he gone?
Why do they want me?"
Then I found you even more suspicious.
Besides, my parents didn't agree at first.
My mom and dad
didn't agree either at first.
My parents also didn't quite agree.
It's normal.
Every one of us,
except K
who has never mentioned his parents,
has parents who are clearly
against it.
So I hesitated at first.
So
what changed your mind?
That day, I went to see
the game between you and CK.
When I heard what Ming said on the stage,
I finally made up my mind:
"I want to be a professional player too.
I will stand on the world stage
with you guys
to win the world championship."
And then I can pat my chest,
telling those who
doubted about my ability that
"I, Tong Yao, made it."
I'm a little bit cocky.
Good for you.
Salute Tong Yao's dream.
Come on.
Let's make a toast together.
Okay.
Come on.
Salute the dream.
Cheers.
Hello.
Anyone there?
Are they out?
How can we enter uninvited?
The door is open, isn't it?
Change your shoes.
It's not necessary. Come on in.
Is anyone there?
Hello? Is anyone there?
Who are you, ma'am?
Hello?
Son.
Your mom is doing it again.
I will become a real coward
if I keep coaxing her.
What a henpecked husband. I'm sorry.
For what?
That's a Chinese traditional virtue,
isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
Chubby is right.
It's a virtue.
How can an upper-class gentleman
be henpecked?
Everything he does is out of love
for his wife and children.
When you have spouses in the future,
remember what you said today.
If you forget,
I can remind you.
You're not going back again, are you?
Don't care about that.
They will be fine in a couple of days.
Let's go.
What's Cheng's family background?
You don't know?
I just know he's rich.
There's more to it.
Have you heard of the Lu's Group?
He is exactly the eldest son
of the group president.
Their family has nothing but money.
According to the typical script,
shouldn't he inherit the company?
Why do I have a feeling that his parents
both support his e-sports career?
I heard that they weren't on board either
at the beginning.
I don't know what happened.
Anyway, when I came here,
his family had already been
a shareholder of the team.
He bought the team?
What are you gossiping about?
Nothing.
Boss, I'm going to leave now.
Chubby.
We weren't gossiping.
We were just talking about
how your parents
supported your e-sports career.
Why are you so interested in that?
Don't your parents
support your e-sports career?
My dad's fine with it.
My mom is like…
If only my dad is the head of our family.
But my dad is just
as henpecked as your dad.
It's actually good.
That's good.
You can't expect your man to be henpecked.
Why?
One world, one dream.
Because you're suggestible.
Let's go, Shorty.
Wait for me.
You're long-legged, so what?
Lu Sicheng.
Why are you all standing here?
Dad.
Mom.
You...
You drank?
No, I didn't.
Mom.
Chrysanthemum tea.
It can clear away internal heat
and toxic materials and protect your liver.
Have a sip.
Knock it off.
Are we here to drink tea?
Yes, yes.
You…
No, no.
What the hell is wrong with you?
You're a girl.
Why did you drink alcohol?
Didn't you say
you came here to play
some kind of professional games?
You promised me when you left that
this was a proper job.
Look at yourself.
You're even hiccupping from wine.
The proper job you said
is to go out drinking at night?
Did they instigate you to do so?
Do you know who they are
and what their backgrounds are
before you just hang out
with them every day?
That Chessman?
Who's him?
Mom.
It's no longer fashionable
to pry into someone's background.
Don't interrupt me.
Let's get serious.
You've been here for only a few days.
And you've already
made such a mess.
Now rumor has it on the internet
that you and that Chessman
have put on a so-called
"White Snake" show.
Every time I call you,
I can't say a few words before you hang up.
How can your dad and I not be worried?
What's the difference between
these computers and ordinary ones?
There is a big difference.
For example, the monitor
is customized according
to personal habits and preferences.
Am I right, Tong?
And so is the computer case.
What's the difference?
It's water-cooled inside.
Tong.
Your mom is right.
What does water-cooling mean?
Water-cooling means heat dissipation.
Mom.
I'm doing fine here.
What could happen to me?
So you didn't even read
the news I sent you?
Dad.
Your mom has a good point.
You have to listen to her.
Look, Mr. and Mrs. Tong.
These are the comments on us
on the internet.
Sorry.
Sorry for all the trouble.
Never mind, Tong Yao.
Look, we're
taking good care of your parents.
(Boast for victory
Self-mockery for loss)
Well.
Don't look at that. You can ignore that.
Just look at this. Look at this.
Not bad. Good.
This is an accident.
Really.
I promise I'll send them away
as soon as possible.
Don't panic.
- Tong Yao.
- Mrs. Tong, look.
You didn't drink much tonight.
Why can't you stop burping?
Come on.
Have a slice of dried mango to relieve it.
I'm burping not because of the wine.
- It's because I'm scared.
- This is about me.
- I'm scared.
- Of course, it's about you.
I understand.
It's normal for parents to pay a visit.
I think
we should help Tong Yao through this.
We can smile together
and extend our greetings to make
a good impression on her parents.
Mr. Tong, this way.
These are all our trophies.
Forget it.
Cheng, you can just keep your distance then.
Thank you.
- There are so many.
- How's that, Tong Yao?
See this?
- Thank you.
- It's about me.
If you can send them away
as soon as possible,
I'll buy you a month's supply of snacks.
This is the training base of ZGDX,
not an acting training class.
We don't have the time
to cooperate with you in your show.
If there's too much trouble,
why don't you ask your parents
to take you back?
K.
Yao.
What are you guys talking about?
What should we take back?
It's nothing, Mrs. Tong.
Mom.
It's getting late.
If you want to criticize me,
you'll have to wait until you
get up tomorrow morning, right?
Let's go.
Let's go to bed.
I'm not sleepy yet.
- You're leaving?
- Mom, you are sleepy.
Dad, come on.
Should I go too?
Come on, come on.
See you tomorrow, Mr. Tong.
Okay.
Let's go. Okay.
Mr. Tong, here's a bag of dried mango.
- It's for me?
- Yes.
It's for you.
I'll take it then.
Sorry for the trouble, bye-bye.
Okay, bye-bye.
Bye-bye. Bye.
Tong Yao, take care of your parents.
I'll take care of them.
Yao.
If you're not happy here,
go home with us tomorrow.
Mom.
How can you tell I'm not happy?
You...
Tong.
I don't want to go.
Yao.
Mom.
Dad.
I know you're worried about me.
But I'm doing great here.
Really great.
Although I felt a little out of it at first,
I really
want to be a professional e-sports player.
So I have to overcome
all these difficulties.
I know you worry about me.
You want to arrange a regular job for me.
But I'm pretty sure
that's not the kind of job I want.
If you don't like the job at the bank,
we can find another one for you.
Mom.
I know you both want me to be better.
But
if I go to the place for an internship
as you arranged,
get a job I don't like,
marry a man I neither like
nor dislike,
and then have kids
and live a stable life until retirement,
my epitaph will read,
"Here lies an ordinary person
who lived a stable life
but were never happy."
Such a life is totally meaningless.
Dad, Mom.
I'm an adult now.
So I'm not kidding
or just trying.
I'm serious about learning
how to become
an excellent professional e-sports player.
Maybe one day,
your daughter
can stand on the stage of a world competition
and win a world championship.
You must be dreaming, champion.
Maybe.
Dad.
Say something.
Well.
Your mom is right.
You…
You have a point too.
What I just said is true.
The National League
is only three months away.
I hope
you can let me stay here until that time.
If I really can't get used to the life here,
or I really don't fit in here,
I will go home then.
Dad.
Let's just act the same way as before
to make a gentleman's agreement
and an equal treaty
between father and daughter.
How's that?
Fine.
Let's make a gentleman's agreement
and an equal treaty.
I knew my dad was
the most open-minded and sensible.
Thank you, Dad.
Of course.
My mom is more open-minded and sensible.
Enough. Don't show off your cleverness.
I'm telling you something serious.
You didn't point out to me
that Chessman
who was mentioned on the internet.
Does he have a crush on you?
His nickname is Chessman.
It doesn't sound like a good man.
You should be careful.
Mom.
How many times have I told you?
It's a misunderstanding.
You'd better spend less time
surfing the internet.
Misunderstanding?
What misunderstanding?
You've always
thought your mom doesn't know anything.
Right?
Let me tell you.
I'm a teacher.
I'm surrounded by young people.
Dad.
Your mom has a point.
Cheng.
Rui just cleaned out a room.
Let me lead your parents downstairs to sleep.
Thank you, Cheng.
By the way, Mom and Dad.
Let me introduce someone to you.
This is our team captain
Lu Sicheng. You can call him Cheng.
He's a nice guy.
Hello, Mr. and Mrs. Tong.
We cleaned out a room in a hurry.
You'll have to make do with it tonight.
Thank you so much.
We came here uninvited.
Sorry for the trouble.
I'm sorry.
By the way,
I forgot to tell you something just now.
People also call me
Chessman.
Good.
Very good.
Chessman.
Let me take it, Mr. Tong.
Thank you.
It's okay.
Mr. and Mrs. Tong, this way, please.
Go.
Have an early rest.
Close the door.
Okay.
See you tomorrow morning.
Tong Yao, go for it.
♪Whose reasoning and expectations♪
♪Don't seem to be my inner monologue♪
♪To be myself or to run away♪
♪Should I just sway with the wind?♪
♪You're the one
who came through the sea of stars♪
♪Those corners open unexpectedly♪
♪It seems someone will really understand♪
♪my helplessness♪
♪The loneliness that
comes with the gradual leave♪
♪I'm beginning to believe♪
♪the existence of a tacit understanding♪
♪That fate can be changed♪
♪Because persistence♪
♪has never been pale♪
♪The successes and failures
we have gone through♪
♪The crowd of people cheering tomorrow♪
♪Your look fuels my passion♪
♪Welcome the sunshine♪
♪Let's welcome the sunshine♪
♪Do you still remember♪
♪that I watched the shooting stars
pass by with you♪
♪How many times I seem to have heard♪
♪the wish I made that night♪
♪We all made a promise♪
♪Youth is about no regrets♪
♪If I have a dream in my heart♪
♪I'll follow the light♪
♪The moment we ignite with passion♪
♪Will light up the night♪
♪How foolish the stubbornness
that no one understands♪
♪How strong the desire to return to glory♪
♪Remember that moment at the top♪
♪Let's welcome the sunshine together♪