What?
A girl?
A girl is joining the ZGDX team,
eating, living and playing with my Cheng?
Seriously?
It really is a girl.
Oh, my god!
A girl plays professionally?
Is ZGDX going crazy?
They were so shorthanded
that they went to find one at random?
Some unknown anchor
is to take the place of Ming?
A female to boot...
This operation of ZGDX
will surely cause a loss of fans.
Where is the base located?
I'm going to pounce on them.
(Girls playing pro is hilarious.)
The No. 1 player,
Tamamo-no-Mae of the Chinese server?
Are they bluffing?
(Female anchors can make money
by their faces why bother actually working?)
This chick Tong Yao
must be targeting my Cheng.
(I want to play pro too.)
ZGDX is crazy about being famous.
That woman is old enough to be your mother.
Why can't she play?
=Falling Into Your Smile=
=Episode 2=
Hello?
Yao, just look at
what these people said on the Internet.
So harsh.
Whatever.
I have been through enough to survive this.
Just ignore them.
I'm starving.
Didn't eat anything all the way.
I'm just angry for you.
I dare say,
none of the people who said those things
could beat you in a game.
But do not argue with them.
Be careful of being targeted as
my fans' leader.
What about being a fans' leader?
You're gonna let someone else
be your fans' leader?
My dear Tong Yao.
(Ai Jia)
Let me know when you arrive at the base.
I'll pick you up.
My wife blocked me.
Could you talk some sense into her for me?
Our team is right next to your ZGDX.
You really aren't gonna let me
be your fans' leader?
It's not that.
Ai Jia just sent me a message.
He said their base is right next to ZGDX.
He's gonna come down and pick me up.
What is he up to by being so attentive?
He wanted me to persuade you
to remove him from the blacklist.
Don't even think about it!
I'm one of my words.
Don't even bother.
If you dare to help him.
You'll join him on the blacklist.
I wouldn't dare.
Anyway, do you think my teammates
will welcome me joining?
Of course.
You are all equals.
Why pick on you?
It's not the age for sexism.
Your joining ZGDX
will only make them all wake up laughing.
Well then.
Will they welcome Biscuit too?
Have you ever heard of the story of
the golden and silver axes?
Don't be too greedy.
All right.
Just enjoy your e-sports life.
Bye bye.
The No. 1 player Tamamo-no-Mae of
Chinese serveris joining the ZGDX team.
This is the beginning of a break
with the traditional pattern.
Following the North American arena
admitting female professional players
into the final for the first time,
The Chinese arena's ZGDX
followed closely behind.
The e-sports industry farm
also retweeted this one.
Who is this Tong Yao?
What makes her qualified to succeed Ming?
The ZGDX has taken a lot of time and effort
to impress and convince Tong Yao
to join the ZGDX team
as the first female professional player
in the Chinese arena
since the start of the Battle of Heiannkyou,
and promised her a starting position.
Look, K.
The ZGDX actually found a woman
to play the first.
We're so screwed.
Tong Yao indicated,
(Chinese server's No. 1's player
Tamamo-no-Mae is joining the ZGDX team.)
that professional gaming
has nothing to do with gender.
She didn't quite understand why
it has always been boys
who were at the top of gaming.
She also stated outright
that if you really want to do something,
girls wouldn't do it badly either.
Have you finished yet?
Is she your relative or something?
Too much talking.
She is not your enemy either.
Why being so mean?
Shut up. It gives me a headache.
Cheng.
Captain.
My CV boss.
The girl is our new midsolo.
You have to pay some concerns.
Maybe she'll be here tomorrow.
I heard she'll bring
a furry little animal with her too.
It's probably my takeout.
Captain, please open the door for me.
K. What are you doing?
Use my other account to comment.
I don't like her either.
Lu Sicheng,
why is it you who opened the door?
- Thanks.
- I...
I am Tong Yao.
I'm so hungry.
Cheng, you aren't playing another game?
It's too dumb to play
with the general players.
I can't bear to let them
use me to score points.
They've died more times than I've killed.
Cheng is very grumpy today.
Cheng.
Just suck it up.
The data will be reviewed
the day after tomorrow.
If you don't want your pay docked,
there are at least a hundred points
more to go.
Plus three advanced competitions.
Cheng is hovering at the line.
Stop struggling.
A rank is dropped.
Twenty percent of the monthly salary
will be deducted.
Ever since this rule came out,
Cheng has never received
his full salary.
Let's not be headstrong, Cheng.
Being headstrong costs you money, man.
Our Cheng is rich, that is no big deal.
This isn't right, Cheng.
This isn't the takeout I ordered.
(One notification from Weibo)
(Maiden salt fish smiling)
I came to ZGDX
to enroll and knocked on the door.
It was Cheng who opened the door.
Then he took my takeout,
said thanks and then shut the door.
So now I'm standing
in front of the door once again,
with my Biscuit.
Hahaha!
Cheng took Tong Yao as a delivery girl.
Delete that tweet.
No.
I won't.
For the last time, delete that tweet.
You apologize first.
I have never seen Cheng being
picked on in my life.
Give the new girl my thumbs up.
Yeah, impressive.
Everyone is so diligent today.
You finished the meeting before I got here?
Rui, I'm here to enroll.
Hey, you came!
Let me give you a formal introduction.
This is Tong Yao.
Rumor has it that she reached
the top of the Chinese Server at the age of 19.
At 21, she ranked as the head of Kyoto
in the South Korean Server.
Standing on the shoulders
of ninety-nine percent of boys,
She is a talented Mid-lane girl.
Save the press lines please.
That's too much, Rui.
Anyway.
Tong Yao has officially replaced Ming
as our new midsolo from today on.
Welcome.
Although you probably know them all,
I'll do the introduction anyway.
This is our topsolo, Cat.
He is straight as an iron rod,
and can beat the crispy guys
on the other side who
tremble with fear in game.
Welcome.
It's just that his arc of reflection
is a little long.
Just ignore it.
Who did you say has a long reflecting arc?
Sorry. I've been exercising
a little too much lately.
It's okay.
This one is our support.
Just call him Chubby.
He's our nanny in the team.
A pure and harmless fat game nerd.
You can say I'm a nerd.
But calling me fat is going too far.
I just have more weight.
Hello, Miss Tong.
Don't come to me if there's any problem.
When free, we can play games together.
No problem.
And that is K,
Our jungler.
Despite his looks,
he is actually living in his own head.
With him,
Ming could walk unscrupulously
in front of the opposing midsolo.
That's because Ming was there.
If it was someone else,
things are not necessary.
Next one,
I don't think
he needs any more introductions,
our shooter.
I heard you just shut her out.
I thought she was a delivery girl.
A delivery girl would dress like that?
And hold a cat?
Why not?
So I closed the door.
I'm sorry I didn't get all dressed up.
He's so mean,
being judgmental
about other people's clothing.
Do you have something to say?
I didn't say anything.
Your face tells me
that you have something to say.
Being judgmental
about other people's minds too.
What kind of
horrible character setting is this?
Anyway, let me introduce.
This is my cat. Its name is Biscuit.
So?
So can I call you Cheng?
Your cat's name is Biscuit.
What does that have to do with my name?
Those are two different questions.
Keep an eye on your furry little animal.
I've asked Rui.
No one in the base is allergic to cat hair.
That's why I brought it with me.
Actually there's one.
Who?
My son.
(Si Cheng Sicheng)
Cheng, that's not allergic.
It is called the food chain.
You can't suppress the nature of a kitten.
What if her cat eats my son?
Buy another one.
It's not like you can't afford it.
If you try to not lose
so many points and get fined,
you'd have enough money
for your children and grandchildren.
Cheng, relax.
I'll keep my eyes on Biscuit
and make sure
you'll have a house full of children.
Okay, okay, okay.
Any more and Cheng will lose his temper.
Come on, Miss Tong.
Let me show you your room.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
You take it from here, Chubby.
OK.
What are you laughing at?
What you just said about
having a house full of children.
Not funny?
Take a look, Miss Tong.
How's this?
This was all carefully arranged by me.
The room Rui had decorated before
was a straight man's way of fashion.
What do you think of this one?
I specifically picked out the girl's specials
from the Internet for you.
Girl's specials?
Have you got the wrong idea about girls? Bro?
Miss Tong.
Look at this.
I searched hundreds of stores
to find this.
It's a four-piece suit
with both pink ruffles and lace.
- Nice huh?
-This lace and this pink.
(Four-piece cotton bedding with pink ruffles
and lace in Korean style.)
Did Peppa Pig eat it and spit it out?
And this.
Look at this one.
(Cute romantic maiden style feathered lamp)
How fluffy!
It's blinding me.
And look at this.
Flamingo special tender style for girls.
How beautiful they are!
(Simulated flamingo decoration)
Miss Tong.
How is it? Is it nice?
Yeah.
Told you so.
You're the first girl
ever to play professionally
and join our team.
It's our honor.
So we have to take good care of you.
Give you special attention.
Okay.
I think he's tired, too.
Just take your time cleaning up.
Go to bed early.
I'll leave you alone.
By the way,
there's a team manual
on the table for you.
(ZGDX I Team Manual)
But it doesn't matter if you don't read it.
Tomorrow Rui
will walk you through the routine.
Bye bye.
Miss Tong.
Welcome to ZGDX.
Go get it!
Bye bye.
First day on the team.
Cold Cheng.
Passionate Companions.
Amazing bedroom.
Ha, ha, ha.
Actually, I'm glad to be here.
Tong Yao, go!
(The Happy Family)
Dad, Mom, I'm at the base.
Sending love.
(Dad, Mom, I'm at the base. Sending Love.)
(Mom has changed the group name
to "The Unhappy Family")
(The Unhappy Family)
Can the door be locked?
Take a picture for me to have a look.
It can.
This is a formal training base.
Take a picture of the door lock.
(Dad waiting for a response from Dad)
Yao, how's your room?
Dad.
We're fine here.
Look,
this is the room my teammates
decorated for me.
Although,
But,
It's kind of thoughtful.
This door looks pretty solid.
But I think this window
is a little insecure.
Come on, dad.
What's not safe about this window?
You might as well seal it all up.
Your daughter's here for games,
not some kind of secret job.
Look at you,
I was worried about you,
concerned about your safety.
I haven't finished my sentence
and you've already started talking.
You have the same personality
as your mother.
Don't get me involved.
Her impulsive temper is not like mine.
Dad.
Mom's still mad?
She's been angry all day.
She didn't even cook for me.
Don't talk nonsense.
Didn't you eat your porridge?
Has the ghost been eating it?
Isn't that porridge left over from yesterday?
Are the leftovers from yesterday
no longer food?
And then,
why was there porridge left yesterday?
Let me ask you.
wasn't it because of your little girl.
Your precious little girl
who left without hesitation.
All right, she's already gone.
What's the point of bringing it up again?
Why can't I?
I'm her mother.
Why can't I bring it up?
I'd say it's all your fault.
Why did you let her go?
And leave the bank job behind?
She got the internship already.
We even made all the arrangements.
People asked me,
What's your daughter's job?
Playing video games.
Why does a college graduate
play video games for a living?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Why are you talking about this
on the phone call?
She is young and not settled down yet.
It's not unusual for her
to want to play a little bit.
If she really wants to try,
just let her try.
Maybe in two or three months
she will come home.
Is that right, Yao?
- Dad...
- Besides,
Our family is not short of
- a few months' salaries from her.
- Mom.
Are you out of your mind?
It's so hard to find a decent job these days!
It's not like you don't know that.
Besides, Yao,
You're a fresh graduate.
Do you know
how much this first job means to her?
Playing video games.
Is playing video games even a real job?
Does it have the five social insurances
and the one housing fund?
Yeah.
Yes, it has.
You see,
It has insurance.
It has.
- I'm not as good as you.
- Mom.
Well.
I don't know how to educate kids, okay?
Come on.
What are you doing?
What are you doing with the phone?
I'll talk to Yao a little more.
What do you have to say?
I'll say what's important.
It's all because of you.
What's so important, huh?
You always speak contrary to me.
You're always out of tune with me.
Yao has been coddled by you since childhood.
Biscuit.
The formal training starts tomorrow.
Are you looking forward to it?
Get up at eight thirty.
(The ZGDX's daily schedule)
Nine o 'clock physical training.
No joking around
and negative coping during training.
(The ZGDX's training rules)
Offenders will be fined 1,000 yuan.
(Training summary must be made
and submitted to team coach at the end of each day.)
(Failing to submit once,
a warning will be issued, twice, ¥1000 fine)
(Three times, one month's salary.)
(The ZGDX's Training Rules)
(The ZGDX I Team Manual)
Good morning.
How come there's no breakfast?
Who are you?
Little girl.
I just arrived yesterday.
Little girl, listen to me.
Don't mind my droning.
I advise you,
just pack up and go.
There is one rule for this team.
Girlfriends are not allowed here.
Last time someone brought his girlfriend,
the result was,
he was docked half a month's wages.
Girlfriend?
No, no, madam.
You're mistaken.
I'm nobody's girlfriend.
I am the new member of the team.
A member?
A woman?
A woman.
Madam.
Are you going to cook breakfast?
These are the materials for lunch.
Lunch?
Don't we have to get up
at 8:30 in the morning?
At half past eight?
These kids are working hard.
They trained late last night.
I'll be glad to see them up by 12:30 today.
There are no mornings
for those who play e-sports.
I'd advise you
to get some rest, too.
They'll play games with you in the afternoon.
Madam.
Are you the only one
cleaning such a big base?
I usually do the cooking and the cleaning.
As for the professional jobs
of cleaning appliances,
they're going to go online
and find people to do it.
Girls are playing e-sports now.
Congratulations to ZGDX for winning
the 2019 Onmyoji Arena Pro League
Spring Playoffs Championship.
At the same time,
Let us also congratulate Lu Sicheng
on being crowned the MVP of the competition.
(If you win, they praise,
if you lose, they blame.)
Good morning.
Your superman shorts are quite nice.
What's for breakfast?
The same old things.
Good morning.
Good morning, Cheng,
- Oh my God.
- Why's he running away?
That's stimulating.
What do you think?
Too stimulating.
Where's everyone?
Come here.
Ming, you're back.
What did the doctor say?
Nothing.
Hello, Tong Yao.
Hello, Ming.
Is your hand any better?
Much better.
Cut the crap and get to the point.
Although Ming has retired,
he won't be leaving us.
From today,
he is officially
the team coach of ZGDX.
I knew it.
Ming couldn't bear to leave us.
I am back,
and I never left.
Ming.
I still miss the days
when you played middle lane.
Now our midsolo is Tong Yao.
I will try my best.
The National League is coming up.
I'll work with Ming
to supervise your training.
Alternating work with rest,
maintaining a regular routine.
Starting tomorrow.
No one is allowed to sleep in.
Early to bed and early to rise.
You better wake up early
to watch the TV series.
I...
I didn't know
we can't watch TV shows at the base.
There's no such requirement.
You can do whatever you want on your breaks.
Right? K.
Funny.
K.
I'll go talk to him.
Don't mind him.
Ming has been
the midsolo all the time.
He's also been on the team the longest.
So his retirement
was a sad thing for all of us.
Especially to K.
He was recruited by Ming.
So he only trusts Ming.
Ever since Ming's retirement,
It's like he's been menstruating.
And he also acts odd.
All right, go train.
Come with me, Miss Tong.
Okay.
Let's go. Perfect.
You.
Come.
How did you feel on your first day?
Not bad.
It's just that Chubby's Superman
and Cheng's bathrobe costumes
blinded my eyes.
I didn't expect them
to act so freely while I was away.
You can read the team manual a little more.
It contains the detailed rules
and regulations of our team.
Also, the club has rules
that each team member
must broadcast live 45 hours per month.
You're going to
meet your live performance KPI.
Here is the contract. Please have a look.
By the way,
Which platform
did you broadcast live from before?
You didn't sign a contract, did you?
It's Xingfan.
But I haven't signed a contract yet.
Oh right,
I've never shown my face on air before.
So I just want to ask,
can I wear a face mask for live streaming?
Wear a face mask? Why?
Wearing a face mask
for live broadcasting feels safer.
You're full of lies.
All right, then wear a face mask.
But in the later competitions
and the seasonal photo shoot,
if you always wear a face mask,
I'm sure someone will ask,
Is this girl here to play games
or to play some
mysterious urban girl drama?
Sooner or later your face will be seen.
What's there to hide from?
And then,
This is work.
You have to have the courage
to face your fans.
Okay.
(Party B: Tong Yao)
It's done.
Here, this is for you.
Let's get down there.
Okay.
Let's go.
Let me tell you.
In fact, our team is very developed.
You don't know, do you?
In addition to season results,
our team is also very popular.
You see, the facilities and equipment here
are first-rated.
Enough.
Rui.
You should arrange someone to take her
to the supermarket later.
Indeed!
It's her first day here today.
She'll need to
get some groceries or something.
I would've forgotten
if you hadn't mentioned it.
I'll really have to arrange it.
Cheng, how about you take her?
I think I just said
you can assign someone.
Yes, I assigned you.
I'm very busy.
Too busy losing points?
You've been demoted to Shaoyun, my friend.
That's why I'm busy.
There will be a monthly assessment
in two days.
Two days to upgrade
from Shaoyun to Lord of Kyoto?
Cheng, you think you are some god?
(Breaking of the ward,
practice in private room, no onlookers)
Let's go.
- Bye-bye, Rui.
- Come home early.
Come on, let's play together.
Wait for me, Cheng.
May I call you Cheng?
You could even call me Dad if you want.
I advise you to be a man.
Didn't you call me that long ago? Shorty.
Hurry up.
Wait for me.
Who are you calling Shorty?
We met by chance.
Just relax and be kind, man.
Why are you so hostile?
Because I didn't expect
my future teammate would be a minor.
I'm 22. I've graduated from college.
Your height tells me you're lying.
Deleted that tweet.
No.
You shut me out in the first place.
And you called me shorty.
The tweet is on top.
Tong Yao.
Ai Jia.
(Cute boyfriend, Ai Jia
Midsolo, the composed midsolo)
(The boy next door, Liang Sheng,
Support, the YQCB team captain)
Tong Yao,
you didn't even tell me when you arrived.
It was your ex-girlfriend
who ordered me not to contact you.
You two know each other?
We went to the same university.
He's three years older than me.
His mother was my teacher.
His ex-girlfriend is my best friend.
Did I ask you that much?
Cheng.
Is this
the Miss Tong Yao who tweeted about
being locked out yesterday?
Tong Yao is the only girl
among the professional players.
Cheng.
Can you stop that painful face of yours?
Anyway, Miss Tong.
My name is Liang Sheng.
The captain of YQCB.
Our team is right next door.
You're welcome to have meals with us.
That's great.
Do not corrupt us with food.
One Chubby is enough.
By the way,
Let's do a battle before the National League.
No problem.
Wait until our new guys are in place.
I'll arrange with Rui.
Seems that you have recruited some new aids?
What position?
Shooter.
Wait for the official announcement. Big news!
Who is it?
I don't know.
Tong Yao.
Just put in a good word for me
with your best friend.
At least pull me off the blacklist.
Or tell me why she broke up with me.
I can only tell you,
your ex-girlfriend has turned down
three offers from abroad to come home.
And you only focused on
how many tips
you get for doing the live streaming.
Shorty, get in the car.
Oh my god.
Do all the pros drive this?
What?
You're used to Uber
and don't know how to open the door yourself?
No, no. I'll do it myself.
Cheng, all I need is a pair of slippers,
some daily toiletries.
You can go to any mall around here.
Or what? Take you to the furniture store?
Really?
You missed me?
You want me to pin you down
by the water cooler,
and make you watch me bring home
one trophy after another?
In your dreams.
The other day at the spring finals,
Rui said you were there too.
Yeah.
You were staying at the same hotel as us.
The forty-sixth floor.
Yes.
No.
That stubborn shorty
the other day was really you.
No.
You stubbornly refuse
to admit that you were short.
And stubbornly
refuse to admit that it was you.
No, Cheng, listen to me.
I wasn't too short to reach it that day.
I was carrying too many things in my hands.
That's why I was being .
stubborn.
I'm starting to hate you.
Do you think I care?
So feisty.
Hurry up.
Cheng, which one looks better?
The blue one.
I thought I just said blue.
Straight guys' aesthetics
are a reference of exclusion.
Like Chubby's.
What else do you want to buy?
Buy it all at once.
Don't act like an acrobat.
You were almost hanging on that shelf.
It's not my fault.
Only one last pair of pink.
I just managed to get it off.
- But you...
- You were the one
who put the water away
in the supermarket that day.
What are you talking about?
How did you know that?
You were the water thief.
What water thief?
Did it have your name on it?
I saw it first, so I hid it.
You call that 'hiding it'?
Why can't I?
Hiding things away in the supermarket,
are you a kid?
I was afraid someone else would take it.
Those two days,
I thought I was being besieged
by a pack of zombie shorties.
I didn't know it was all the same person.
What zombie shorty!?
Captain, watch what you say.
Are long legs a big deal? You walk so fast.
Beauty camera, what is it for?
It's for the live streaming.
Has Rui talked to you today
about the live streaming KPI?
You didn't bargain with him?
Using the excuse that girls
need to sleep and wake up early
to make him give you
ten hours less on the air every month?
Forty-five hours and thirty-five hours.
What's the difference?
You'll know the difference
when you need to
catch up at the end of the month.
What do you mean?
It's like your kindergarten homework
for the summer.
And you saved it for the last day.
Who're you saying goes to kindergarten?
Can you talk nice?
A warning from senior.
Such a good deed,
I would only do once in my life.
(Welcome to the Win House, A section.)
It's him?
Is it Cheng? Cheng!
What are you rushing for?
Your fans are taking pictures.
What's wrong with taking pictures?
How can I meet people today
without much makeup on?
And I haven't posted a picture online yet.
You think your fans
would be kind enough
to use the beauty camera on me?
They're coming this way.
Cover me up. Don't expose me.
It'd work vertically, but horizontally?
Not sure.
Cheng, I'm so glad to see you here.
Can you sign for me, please?
Cheng, how's Ming's hand?
I read from the official that
his hand has been being treated.
Is it true?
Cheng, you are really tall.
Taller than you were
on the scene of the competition.
Crap!
Am I going to be exposed?
Cheng.
- Is this your girlfriend?
- She saw me.
- What should I do?
- No.
Why would I find a girlfriend
who looks like my daughter?
She's a team worker.
She accompanied me out shopping.
She is so cute.
Childlike is the correct word.
Miss, could you take a picture
for me and Cheng?
I want it, too. I want it, too.
Thank you, Cheng.
It's my turn, take a picture for me please.
- Thank you, Miss.
- You're welcome.
Bye, Cheng. Bye.
Yeah, I didn't expect to see him in person.
Bye bye.
Let's go.
He's so cool.
What the hell is that
look on your face about?
Cheng.
Do you think I'll have
as many fans as you do in the future?
Will they like me so much that
they'd fight to take pictures with me?
That's if you can get to the finals.
If the team signed you
only to get its grade dropped,
there will be a lot more people than this
to blame you for it.
They'll ask you every day
if you choked to death on your water.
How come the wind outside
didn't blow you away.
They will fight to hang you on the wall.
Just like K did.
Do you care?
Shall I be honest?
Play well if you care.
In the world of e-sports,
only the strong can be recognized.
You've just came into the business.
There's going to be a lot of skepticism.
But if you can prove it by strength
that you can replace Ming.
No one will say a word more about you.
However, Cheng,
how come no one ever seems to question you?
Because I am strong.
In e-sports, weakness is the original sin.
Let's go.
(Exit)
(Exit for vehicles)
K, go to the middle lane.
This way, go this way.
The corner.
What are you doing?
You're back.
Cheng seems to be getting along
with his new teammate very well.
Very well?
It's like taking your kindergarten daughter
to the supermarket
to buy snacks for a spring outing.
Tong Yao.
This is where you're going to sit.
Isn't this where you sat before?
It's not appropriate.
It's okay.
The midsolo all sit in this position.
Look,
this is the latest e-sports chair
that I changed for you
according to Chubby's instructions.
It's all professional.
It can be adjusted at will according to
your personal habits.
Have a try.
I guarantee you won't feel tired
even after a day of playing.
Miss Tong, go get it!
What's the use of just shouting "go get it"?
The team's warm-up match
is coming up in a few days.
Whether she can stay or not
depends on her first performance.
Tong Yao, don't be nervous.
Cheng is always
so strict.
What is this thing?
It's a pink decoration that suits a girl.
Take it off.
It affects my vision when it's around.
I'll blame you if my rank drops.
I chose it carefully.
Tong Yao likes it. I won't take it off.
You like it?
The lace does block the vision a bit.
Miss Tong.
Don't let the power bully you.
Speak your heart out loud.
Not all girls like pink.
I'm just not that girly.
Didn't you just buy a pair of pink slippers?
Cheng, be a kind person.
This is that horrible straight-guy aesthetic.
Shut up.
What's wrong?
Stay out of it.
Miss Tong, want to play together?
♪Whose reasoning and expectations♪
♪Don't seem to be my inner monologue♪
♪To be myself or to run away♪
♪Should I just sway with the wind?♪
♪You're the one
who came through the sea of stars♪
♪Those corners open unexpectedly♪
♪It seems someone will really understand♪
♪my helplessness♪
♪The loneliness that
comes with the gradual leave♪
♪I'm beginning to believe♪
♪the existence of a tacit understanding♪
♪That fate can be changed♪
♪Because persistence♪
♪has never been pale♪
♪The successes and failures
we have gone through♪
♪The crowd of people cheering tomorrow♪
♪Your look fuels my passion♪
♪Welcome the sunshine♪
♪Let's welcome the sunshine♪
♪Do you still remember♪
♪that I watched the shooting stars
pass by with you♪
♪How many times I seem to have heard♪
♪the wish I made that night♪
♪We all made a promise♪
♪Youth is about no regrets♪
♪If I have a dream in my heart♪
♪I'll follow the light♪
♪The moment we ignite with passion♪
♪Will light up the night♪
♪How foolish the stubbornness
that no one understands♪
♪How strong the desire to return to glory♪
♪Remember that moment at the top♪
♪Let's welcome the sunshine together♪