No one and nothing
can be invisible online.
I was just curious about
why you didn't tell me
you were playing professional e-sport games?
Isn't it a better choice for you
to come to our team
than go to the ZGDX Team?
Bro.
It's my own decision to play as a pro.
It has nothing to do with you.
Block me.
Cheng.
Is she your girlfriend?
Especially when I've got you.
(Smiling?@ZGDX e-sport club)
(Seems like some big news.)
Smiling.
It must be her.
Although it's only her back,
she looks cute.
This girl knows Jian Yang?
How long has she been here?
She's already started to come
and go alone with Cheng.
Miss Smiling.
We can't wait
to see your first performance.
(Release)
=Falling Into Your Smile=
=Episode 03=
Hey girl, wanna play a duo?
I'll have a look.
Outplayed.
Your hands move like lightning.
That's awesome.
Stop running,
wait for me.
Fight with them, I am coming.
She dares to attack
when enemies are all there.
So much damage.
(Kill, support)
Tong Yao,
stop ambushing the enemy support,
I can't hold it.
A wave attack, hold there.
I will be there in a minute.
No, there are three enemies there.
It's fine, let's attack.
Now press Q and jump them.
I…
Chubby, jump!
Chubby is dead.
Come on, noob.
(Kill, support)
Nice.
Her hands are moving really fast.
Engage, Chubby.
A wave, a wave, a wave.
You have more health, hold him.
Great, nice.
What a game.
Awesome!
Tong Yao, what you did was monstrous.
I feel like I was tricked.
Are you sure we are playing a duo?
I feel like I am being left all alone.
Chubby.
You are the support,
and you gotta carry the damage.
Or else how am I going to carry the game?
Tong Yao,
I did not know that
you would become
a totally different person during the game.
No wonder other people
call you the "Mulan in E-sports".
Tong Yao, you got the MVP.
Awesome!
Easy, let me carry you for the next round.
Great!
K,
the new midsolo girl
is so awesome.
One girl took the stats and kills
for the whole team,
great,
great solo,
why bother carrying the others?
Never mind, never mind.
Good game,
seriously.
Let's go, let's play.
All right.
I'll be the shooter.
Then I am out, I am out.
I know you are going to
bring up the old times.
K might be wrong in dealing with her.
But he's got a point.
I understand.
She's been too aggressive
in terms of her playing.
Lack of teamwork.
No professionalism.
I know,
(Seal · Three Holy Artifacts)
you told me
before the tryout match.
(Seal · Four Gods Echoing)
(Invincible Victor)
(Seal · Matrix of Five Phases)
Are you all right?
I told you to let me play it for you.
Why not?
It's ok.
What do you think?
Too aggressive.
Lack of team spirit.
No professionalism.
Professionalism can be cultivated.
She's the best
among all of the candidates.
Why are we hiring a newbie?
We have been through that conversation.
You are our midsolo.
You have the say about
who's going to be in your place.
You never asked me
why I chose Tong Yao.
Half of our team
was chosen by you.
Not to mention,
she's taking your place as a midsolo.
I have faith in your judgment.
She is the one I
hand-picked from hundreds of candidates.
She has a strong desire to win
and doesn't give up easily.
She's fearless.
Kind of like you.
I can't play the game
with my hand the way it is now.
But the reason I choose
to retire at this moment
is not entirely because of my injured hand.
There have been many new talents
for this year's Spring Playoffs.
If we want make it to the Finals.
We need fresh blood like Tong Yao.
You are brilliant, Tong Yao.
Nice, good one.
That's risky.
The National League is about to begin.
That's why I need you
to train Tong Yao with me.
You are right.
She has to learn
how to become a professional player
instead of just a gamer.
Come up with a training program
for her as soon as possible.
Starting from tomorrow.
Okay.
Hi dad.
Son.
Do you know how far your mum went?
I just said something a bit annoying
and she just walked out again.
Okay, I got it.
I'll be home tomorrow.
No, son.
You gotta help me figure it out.
How to talk to your mum.
I.
It's okay, just go home.
Don't worry,
I will start to train her beginning tomorrow.
(Tactics, War Gods Directory, Basics for Middle Laners)
Tong Yao, let's begin our training.
Today I am going to start from
being a professional e-sport player.
The ultimate goal of participating in a game
is not to achieve individual victory,
but a team one.
During the process.
You need to get rid of lots of
your attitudes of charging ahead alone.
And the first thing you need to get used to
is to see yourself
as a screw within your team.
Okay.
I am ready to be a backup.
We will officially begin when you are ready.
First take a look at this.
(Basics for
Decisive Onmyoji Arena Pro League)
(ARM Practice)
APM practice, last hit practice.
(Creep Score)
Get to know the game's background
and shikigami characteristics.
These are the very basics.
Are you sure you've got the right one?
For a professional player,
you are still a newbie.
You need to understand that
playing e-sports and playing video games
are two different things.
That's why you need some good training.
Let's roll.
♪I have a dream♪
♪I want to follow the light♪
♪Even if I fall down a million times♪
♪No matter how rough the journey will be♪
♪Covered with thorns
and stepping on blazing sand♪
Keep on with the last hit.
♪The reversal of plots
and the precipice of time♪
♪At least when we all know
that's where we're going♪
♪If I have a dream♪
♪I'm going to follow the light♪
♪The moment we ignite with passion♪
♪We'll eventually light up the night♪
♪How foolish the stubbornness
that no one understands♪
♪How strong the desire to return to glory♪
♪Remember that moment at the top♪
♪Let's welcome the sunshine together♪
♪If I have a dream♪
♪I'll follow the light♪
♪The moment we ignite with passion♪
♪We'll eventually light up the night♪
♪How foolish the stubbornness that
no one understands♪
♪How strong the desire to return to glory♪
♪Remember that moment at the top♪
♪Let's welcome the sunshine together♪
Another round.
(Aoandou)
So tired.
As tired as a dog.
(Jin Yang)
Hi.
Hi, Yao.
You are up so early.
No, not up.
I haven't gotten any sleep.
I am exhausted.
I just sent you a picture.
Check out your WeChat.
(Mother of Amao)
That's why Ai Jia's been saying
he couldn't find you anywhere.
Turns out you are enjoying your own retreat.
What happened to the promise of
favoring your besties?
My advice, be a human, please.
Well, I am on my break-up trip, aren't I?
Hawaii is so great.
Next time I will bring you along.
I can't.
You don't care.
Will you feel good
hearing me crying out loud for you?
What's up?
Why can't you make it?
It's so hard to become
a professional e-sport player.
I got trained like a dog.
12 hours a day every day.
And it's all about the basics.
My hands are wasted.
I doubt they are doing this on purpose.
Crap.
What?
I feel like I am talking to Ai Jia.
Goodbye.
Who is it?
Tong Yao, are you awake?
Time to eat dinner.
I just went to bed, no dinner for me.
It's getting dark.
Ming called you to have a duo with K.
Do you want to?
K?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. K.
Coming.
On my way, soon.
Ming arranged this.
I am ready.
(Onmyoji Dayun,
Qualification Game, Mist, Unselectable)
(Multiple Individuals Team matching,
Onmyoji Dayun)
Holy!
What's up?
Who did you get?
This Sunflower.
Why does it sound so familiar?
Yao, what a coincidence.
Make it a good one.
I will cover you.
Yang.
(So tired, as tired as a dog)
As tired as a dog.
No way.
What?
I am against Cheng.
Why do I keep hitting the jackpot
without buying any lottery tickets today?
First Cheng and then Jian Yang.
What role is Cheng?
The enemy is doing Jungle.
Then we're finished.
He's going to stay in your middle lane.
What am I going to do?
I was one round away
from claiming the Lord of Kyoto.
Why would I meet Cheng?
On my.
And also Jian Yang.
Calm down.
The Shikigami Cheng chose
is a mid-level Shikigami.
As long as we make sure
Yang is in the middle lane,
we can still have a chance to win.
Don't panic.
Let me teach you a move.
Later.
Are you done?
Or just AFK?
Listen to my advice.
Cheng is definitely going to throw the game.
Is now the time?
Yeah, take my word for it.
Cheng.
I am one round away
from claiming the Lord of Kyoto.
So,
please don't screw me.
You have my respect.
It seems to be working.
The minions are now under the turret
and Cheng is yet to be found.
Of course.
(Seal · Initial Ritual)
(Kill, Support)
Go back to the base, I will protect you.
(Lightning Speed)
What's going on?
Well.
Cheng.
Are you taking me with you while dying,
and being buried together?
How kind you are, Cheng.
Tong Yao, Tong Yao.
Psychological attack.
Are you sure?
Just do what I told you.
Hurry.
When are you coming back, Cheng?
The cat,
Biscuit,
is trying to catch fish.
I can't help with that.
Hurry back and deal with it.
You are losing your sons.
It's my fault, Cheng.
It was all Chubby's idea.
Your sons are all good.
It's a big family
with many sons and grandsons.
I am also very obedient.
Cheng, we miss you a lot.
When are you coming back?
As we are missing you so much.
Don't come to middle lane.
Enjoy the view on the bottom lane.
What the hell?
Nobody cares.
What's so funny about that?
Does it make any sense, talking to yourself?
If you want to win, I will carry you.
Tong Yao, is that what you want?
Hello.
I told you to stop calling, didn't I?
K.
Don't worry, Tong Yao.
I guess it's K's family calling.
He becomes like that
as soon as he picks up
his family's phone calls.
Not against you.
(Long Legs and Deadpan face)
Why did you stop playing?
I will be back tomorrow.
Watch yourself and the cat.
Bye.
Who is it? What's up?
Cheng.
Cheng, what did he say?
He says he will return tomorrow.
(ZGDX: first show of its midsolo, a show of
the e-sport version of "The White Snake Legend")
(E-sport White Snake Legend)
(Smiling: Being buried together?)
(Smiling: I can't help with that...
Hurry up and come back to handle it...)
(Smiling: You are gonna lose your sons!)
(Smiling: Go back to the base,
I will protect you)
(Sunflower: If you want to win,
I will carry you......)
Check out the e-sports industry farm.
ZGDX double play flirting interaction.
Yang from CK is shown a cold shoulder.
It could be called
The e-sport Legend of the White Snake.
How long has this girl been here for?
Flirting with Cheng?
What a shame.
Reply to the post and curse her.
No way.
What is Cheng doing?
And what's wrong with Yang?
What a dramatic love triangle.
According to reliable sources,
She is Yang's first love.
Is Yang Xiao Qing?
Have you seen a Xu Xian
like Lu Sicheng before, poster?
I can't believe Yang is that kind of person.
Yang seemed to be jealous.
I wouldn't have thought him
as someone who would say those words.
Like "come on, I can carry you".
It's so flattering, ok?
That's why generally,
a professional team
doesn't have female players.
It's too easy to develop office romance.
It's not like I am against it.
Everything seems to be fine
when they are together.
But what if they have a quarrel?
How are they still going to
fight alongside one another?
What are these?
Are they talking about Yao?
Is she not off playing games?
How is she involved in a relationship?
Who are these people?
Why are they so mean?
(Oh my god, Yang seemed to be so jealous)
(Is she heading for the apex of her life?)
No.
Hello?
Hi mum.
Yao.
Would you explain to us
what's going on?
Why is there the Legend of the White Snake?
Are you there to play games
or to date with someone?
Mum.
I have told you millions of times.
What more can I say?
There's literally nothing going on.
I have just been here a few days.
How could I be seeing anyone?
Besides, we have a 12-hour daily training.
I need some time and space
to be able to see someone, right?
Then.
The e-sports industry farm.
What are they talking about?
Why are you browsing information
on the so-called e-sports industry farm?
How am I supposed to know
what people said there?
I was also wondering
why would they say things like that?
Let me ask you.
Is this the Yang Jian Yang,
who broke up with you last year
and used to live next door?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yang is Jian Yang.
That's right, the one who lives next door.
My relationship with him
didn't end up impeding my college life.
Why are you bringing that up?
We simply came across each other yesterday
during the game.
Before that, we have never seen each other.
Then who is Cheng?
He is flirting with you.
Cheng is our captain.
He is the most innocent.
Don't make things up.
What flirting?
Do I look like I have got the charm?
No.
I will tell you what.
You are a young lady.
Playing e-sport with a bunch of boys.
You gotta be extra careful, do you know that?
Don't fool around,
and leave the netizens to gossip around.
That would leave you a bad impression.
Mum, I got it.
I gotta go.
Yao.
Cheng.
What?
Why are you back so early?
Shorty.
What's going on between you
and this Jian Yang from the CK team?
What is it?
Our encounter in
the qualifying game last night
was posted by someone
on the e-sports industry farm.
With snapshots of all our conversations.
Don't tell me you didn't see it.
I saw it.
Why are you looking at the farm as well?
There are more than a thousand replies.
The mysterious relationship
between the three of us
is good enough for a TV series.
Its content,
A flattering heroine,
A desperate secondary lead actor.
And a cruel lead actor.
Come on, let's talk.
(Did some fan see Yang talking with
another girl on the day of the Spring Final)
(Is she this Smiling?
Maybe they already knew each other)
Of course, I knew her.
I have known that girl many years ago.
Yang.
Stop being unhappy.
How about some yogurt?
Piss off.
Oh, shoot.
Even Yang began to curse.
It's over.
Something's going to happen.
What do we do?
Go, go.
Me?
Yeah, go.
Me.
Yang.
Let's talk about this Smiling.
Who is she?
Do you really want to know?
She's my ex.
She is playing professional games
only because of me.
Come on, come on, here, here, here.
All middle, all middle.
Come to the middle.
No, no, no.
Go, go, go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Hit, hit, hit.
Go, go, hit it.
You'll die if you don't hit it.
No, I can't, I'm leaving.
Leaving, leaving, leaving.
Go, go.
I am sorry, that was my girlfriend.
I am sorry, so sorry.
Jian Yang.
Seeing as you are having so much fun.
How about you teaching me how to play?
And I can join you.
Sounds good, come on.
Take a seat.
Which one do I pick?
Can I choose the good-looking one?
Stop scrolling, pick this.
White hair with long strands
of hair on the temples.
That's him.
This one looks so ugly.
A long as you are good-looking.
Are there any characters that
don't have to run around,
but are able to perform explosive moves,
good-looking,
and have a strong presence,
with no need to partner
with others when laning
in order not to get scolded
because of lame skills at the same time?
Yeah, midsolo.
Choose Tamamo-no-Mae.
You gotta control a lane
or you won't gain experience.
Don't use skills.
Give the minions the last hit.
How?
What's Acing the minions?
You land the basic killing blow
on an enemy minion
whose health is low enough.
I can't do the Acing.
Did you lie to me?
Help, help!
I am dead again.
How come I am dead again?
If you don't come to
the middle lane, Jian Yang.
You are losing your girlfriend.
Coming in hot.
I will kill whoever touches you.
(Victory)
Sweet.
What about after that?
After that.
I really did lose my girlfriend.
Jian Yang.
Happy Birthday!
Thanks.
Open it and have a look.
How is it, do you like it?
Yeah.
As long as it's from you.
Let's go, let me help you put it on.
Just to see if they look good.
Come on, put it on.
Are you going out?
School is about to begin.
Have you finished your paper?
Stop procrastinating
and ask me to write it for you.
What's wrong?
I am not going back to school.
What?
A manager from a professional team
has spotted me.
He asked me to have a tryout in Shenzhen.
If everything goes well.
I will be staying there to play the game.
My parents have agreed.
You know I am not good at studying.
I don't know what to do after graduation.
I like this job.
I think I might go further in this field.
♪It's not moving♪
♪The clock is not moving♪
♪Where does the wind come from♪
He joined a professional team after that.
With his teammates and fans.
And had a bright future.
I was wondering at that time.
Do I still hold a position inside his heart?
At first, I thought that I did.
And I tried to communicate with him
on a daily basis.
I listened to him talking about
winning another victory.
How much his fans love him.
Seeing the picture he sent to me
of the competition scene.
It's like I was with him.
Witnessing the honor.
But I never understood.
Even though we were close.
We could no longer go back.
♪And then hold on with the shell♪
Yao, did you see my game today?
How did it go?
Did you see my action on the third round?
That's an absolutely unbeatable move.
I saw, everyone was complimenting me.
Yeah.
They were all asking where this Yang is from.
He's so strong.
You are about to become a famous star.
♪Don't expose the most intentional
by-stander on this street♪
Come on, go, go, go, I got the ult, I got it.
Teamfight, teamfight, let's do it.
Let's do it, have a teamfight.
Come on, kill him.
♪The clouds, are not moving♪
♪The clock, is not moving♪
♪Where does the wind come from♪
(Jian Yang)
What are you doing?
♪My heart, is moving along♪
♪My heart, is lost♪
I am about to sleep.
I am so tired.
(Onmyoji Arena Pro League)
♪We gotta calm down♪
♪None of us like to be intruded by others♪
♪With a door locked inside our hearts♪
♪And then hold on with the shell♪
♪No one but you in the world
knows I am lying♪
Sorry,
the number you dialed is...
♪Running all the way to you♪
♪Struggling to go through the motions♪
Jian Yang.
Let's talk after your training match.
(New message)
(Jian Yang, let's talk after the training match)
♪We♪
And then?
Then he became someone really famous.
And then he refused to pick up the phone,
and never replied to my messages on WeChat.
What about after that?
After that we broke up.
Pretty understandable.
Think about it.
A long-distance relationship,
and both of them were busy,
with almost no freedom.
Every little thing
could be magnified.
It's understandable they broke up.
The captain's got a life.
Come on,
who wouldn't have a life in our business.
Yang.
You were literally creating
an enemy spy from the beginning.
Look.
You first trained her to be
the No.1 Tamamo-no-Mae on the Chinese server.
And then broke up with her.
Raised the level of hatred to a new height.
And then let her join the enemy's team.
That is going to
make her your biggest weak point.
What kind of play of suffering is this?
Yang's got a show going on.
No, Yang.
What did this team do
to make you do this to us?
We have got the message that
you are some kind of masochist.
Cut it out.
My story is not finished.
What if they two
got together again?
Then he just turned the enemy's spy
into our own spy, didn't he?
That's good.
Yeah, Yang.
I mean, don't count your chickens
before they're hatched.
Cheng didn't say a thing
in last night's game.
He is the type of person who is really hard
on himself and always keeps silent.
The gossip says
Cheng is Xu Xian.
What, what does that mean?
What Xu Xian?
Why do you mention Cheng?
What Cheng?
Not me.
Why mention him?
What did I? Mention Cheng?
It was on the internet.
Why did you kick me?
Who is Cheng?
So annoying.
Bro, let's go, let's go.
Go. A break-up should be decent.
Nobody should say sorry.
Yang, I apologize, sorry for that.
Come on, come on, let's play some games.
Come on, come on.
Yao,
let's get together again.
What's wrong?
Nothing, never mind.
Cheng.
I've told you everything.
The reason why
I didn't tell everyone anything
is because we broke up more than a year ago.
It has long been over.
I didn't expect this would cause
so much trouble.
Let alone affect you.
I didn't criticize you.
Why are you looking at me like that?
It's just I think.
I have just joined the team not so long ago.
And I haven't made any achievements.
While causing so much trouble
right from the get-go.
Besides, I was playing duo with K yesterday.
I was hoping to
mend the relationship between he and I.
But what I did yesterday
seemed to have upset him.
No.
But I heard from Chubby.
You have never had
any unfavorable news like this.
And this is your first time getting up
on the wall because of this.
I feel really sorry.
As a girl to be a professional player,
where you will be surrounded by boys,
it will be inevitable
to attract some attention.
I thought you already expected it.
I did.
But not this bad.
Wait until the surge of interest has gone.
What is left
will be your achievements and strengths.
The closest one is probably
the National League.
But the premise
is that you are qualified to be part of it.
I swear, Cheng.
I can definitely make it.
Rest assured, Cheng.
I will keep a close watch of Biscuit,
and make sure you have lots of kittens.
What's the matter, Cheng?
Why are your eyes reddening?
Nothing, I am allergic to cat's hair.
(ZGDX's midsolo girl seems
in love with captain, CK Yang gets involved)
Is the gossip about my "husband" true?
I am so sad.
I am mentally unstable now.
I will cancel the subscription.
Turn into a troll from a fan.
You've got questions from your fans again?
Don't you have a phone?
Actually, you don't have to care
too much about what they say.
Lots of their words don't make sense.
It's not like they don't love you
once you are in a relationship.
In the fans' world,
It is pretty normal for them
to switch between a fan and a troll.
I couldn't believe it when someone told me
that they saw you with Cheng
shopping, hand in hand.
It's so annoying.
This is it?
That night,
I lost both my "husband"
and my "wife".
This strange news really did finally appear.
I am kind of worried about you.
As the only female professional player.
Don't fall at the very beginning.
Tong Yao!
What?
Look.
Here it says me and you, hand in hand.
They literally didn't spend a penny on lying.
I have never touched your hands at all.
Now that I touched your hands,
do you still feel it's unfair?
Your cat is about to be suffocated.
Tong Yao.
We used to have a long-distance relationship,
plus the inappropriate timing.
Which makes you feel that our relationship
was a waste of your time,
that's why you found something unimportant
to have a fight with me over
and then broke up with me after that.
Now that you are
a professional player yourself.
You are also fully aware of
the daily routine of a pro.
I didn't mean to leave you alone.
I didn't want to break up with you at all.
The KTV incident is in the past.
And I shouldn't have lied to you.
It was my fault.
But I did apologize to you.
Yao.
Can we have a good conversation?
What are you doing?
Are you creating a shadow ID
and arguing with others on Tieba?
Do I look like such a bored person to you?
Yeah.
That's how I see you.
Childish?
In my view.
It is necessary to clarify this on Weibo.
About what?
Me, you and Jian Yang.
There is no White Snake Legend between us.
No need for that.
Yes, there is.
I can't just stain your reputation.
Go check the special group on Douban.
(I am your father)
Nonsense, nothing like that.
Stop guessing.
Is that you?
Why?
The worst job
should be done by the man.
Cheng.
Why, why this look?
Take it back.
Although I have no idea
who will be lucky enough to be your Mrs. Lu.
But right now,
I am starting to envy her.
Because you will definitely
take good care of her.
No one can touch her
and nothing will harm her.
What Mrs. Lu?
Are you retarded?
We have an open training match appointment
with FNC tomorrow.
It will be recorded and shown to the fans.
Make it a good match, don't lose face.
Biscuit.
Jian Yang,
What's past is past.
No more mentioning.
You and Lu Sicheng.
(Ai Jia)
Hey Bro.
Hi Ai Jia.
I have something important to ask you.
Are you going to ask things
about Tong Yao and Lu Sicheng?
Don't worry,
nothing is happening between them.
It's all gossip on the internet.
Leave it.
I will keep playing the game then, bye.
♪Whose reasoning and expectations♪
♪Don't seem to be my inner monologue♪
♪To be myself or to run away♪
♪Should I just sway with the wind?♪
♪You're the one
who came through the sea of stars♪
♪Those corners open unexpectedly♪
♪It seems someone will really understand♪
♪my helplessness♪
♪The loneliness that
comes with the gradual leave♪
♪I'm beginning to believe♪
♪the existence of a tacit understanding♪
♪That fate can be changed♪
♪Because persistence♪
♪has never been pale♪
♪The successes and failures
we have gone through♪
♪The crowd of people cheering tomorrow♪
♪Your look fuels my passion♪
♪Welcome the sunshine♪
♪Let's welcome the sunshine♪
♪Do you still remember♪
♪that I watched the shooting stars
pass by with you♪
♪How many times I seem to have heard♪
♪the wish I made that night♪
♪We all made a promise♪
♪Youth is about no regrets♪
♪If I have a dream in my heart♪
♪I'll follow the light♪
♪The moment we ignite with passion♪
♪Will light up the night♪
♪How foolish the stubbornness
that no one understands♪
♪How strong the desire to return to glory♪
♪Remember that moment at the top♪
♪Let's welcome the sunshine together♪