=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 22=
Whatever the truth is,
the priority now is to get the Spear.
Mount Lookout is in the spotlight now.
The Demons may be attracted there.
Donghua,
pass my edict immediately.
Every immortal lord can fight
for the Spear.
Whoever makes the Spear choose him
will own it.
But Your Majesty,
when immortals and demons come,
I’m afraid there’ll be a disturbance.
Don’t worry.
I’ll also be there.
If any disturbance occurs,
I’ll personally handle it.
Yes.
Why did the Taicang Spear reappear?
The Fire Kylin?
Is Bai Jue really alive?
Anyway,
you were far too impetuous.
That was Demon King Sen Jian!
Luckily, you survived.
I was trying to save you.
You could have used many other ways.
If you risk yourself
like that once more,
I won’t take care of you ever again.
Do you hear me?
Yes.
May I talk now?
It’s the life-saving pellet
my father gave me.
Eat it.
Feed me.
How cruel!
If I were choked to death,
you would regret.
North Sea Lord,
during the fight,
you went too far several times.
If you talk nonsense again,
during the long life,
I won’t mind making you mute
for more tens of thousands of years.
Houchi,
since we met on Mount Lookout,
I’ve felt we knew each other before.
I know you don’t believe this
and you don’t like it
when I follow you without permission.
But we went through
a life-and-death fight.
What’s your point?
I mean
it’s my first time to like someone.
I adore you.
North Sea Lord,
I have no other feelings for you.
I’m too busy with important things
to get stuck in love.
I know.
You’re looking for Boxuan.
But now that I confessed to you,
I won’t take it back.
If you still feel upset about it,
I’ll stick to you and won’t leave.
Who’s upset about it?
Then why are you staring at me?
Are you blackmailing me?
Yeah.
Like you said,
I’m the plaster.
I should stick to you.
What if I won’t change my mind?
Then I’ll learn from Xiaoli
to pretend to be sick
and let you take care of me.
I’m not Sen Yu.
I won’t be easily softhearted.
Take the pellet regularly.
Houchi.
Why is Prince Jingjian still here?
Fengran, don’t you hate the ones
from the Heavenly Palace?
I was so careless
that I fell into his trap.
Goddess Houchi,
enjoy yourselves.
Pretend I weren’t here.
Greetings, Goddess Houchi.
Greetings, too.
Please be seated over there.
Thank you for helping us last time
and for letting Qingmu stay here
for recovery.
I’m quite grateful.
You’re welcome, Goddess.
I didn’t help much.
Now that you’re Fengran’s friend,
call me Houchi.
All right, then.
How’s Lord Qingmu doing?
He’s tough.
We don’t need to worry.
Lord Qingmu has deep feelings for you.
He’s a good man rare to be seen.
Your Grace,
you should cherish such love.
Don’t overthink.
We’re just friends.
Through the last fight,
I changed my view towards him.
I think he’s a straightforward man
and he’s nice to you.
In the Heavenly Realm,
most men say they love you,
but run away in case of danger.
In a life-and-death fight,
how many men could protect us
with their lives?
I’m not as lucky as you
to meet such a loyal man.
Chang Qin,
I heard that the fox confessed
she was pretending to be sick
and Sen Yu exiled her to garrison
the Demon Region.
You’re even so well-informed
about what happens
in the Xuanjing Palace?
I’ve got many friends.
She mostly get gossips.
Houchi.
Qin,
if you hesitate, you lose.
Maybe it’s not the one you can’t forget,
but the old days when you were with him.
You’re a girl yearning for freedom.
Never should you be stuck
in the Xuanjing Palace.
After you’re done with your business,
come to the Qingchi Palace.
Let’s drink and get hammered.
You’ll be warmly welcomed
to the Qingchi Palace.
Take care.
Besides that,
I also heard something important,
about Boxuan.
Tell me about it.
Who just mocked me for gossiping?
Tell me!
Tell me first
what happened
to you and Qingmu lately?
Why don’t you tell me
what happened to you and Jingjian?
I...
Master,
if Wu Huan hadn’t tricked Goddess Yuemi,
she wouldn’t have died a tragic death
in the Abyssal Ridge Swamp.
These years, Wu Huan did
countless dirty things
when she tried to annex the Demons.
Muguang and she are birds of a feather.
Why must we negotiate peace with them?
Since I woke up,
I’ve been failing to return to True God
because of the thin spiritual aura
in the Demon Realm.
But Muguang and Wu Huan
have cultivated themselves
in the Heavenly Palace
for sixty thousand years.
They’re much more powerful than before.
Don’t say that, Master.
If you didn’t sacrifice
your Purple Moon Power
for all demons’ cultivation,
regardless of your own,
we would have been annexed.
How would we still live in peace?
I hear Bai Jue’s Taicang Spear
has appeared on Mount Lookout?
Yes.
Muguang sent his son
for peace negotiations,
simply because he wants
the Purple Moon Whip
so that he can reopen the God Realm
with Four Weapons.
But that year,
you activated the Destruction Formation
and was known as a guilty man.
Even if the God Realm is reopened,
it does no good to you.
I know you’re loyal to me.
But if they get the Taicang Spear,
the Immortals will stand
a better chance.
How about exchanging
the peace negotiations
for the chance to get the Spear?
That’s the best plan.
You’re right, Master.
I was far too short-sighted.
I’ll go get it done immediately.
So, such a big thing happened
on Mount Lookout.
You said that
there was God power of Fire in Boxuan.
The Fire Kylin is
an ancient Divine Beast.
It has the power of fire, too.
Boxuan was missing on Mount Lookout,
and now the Fire Kylin appeared on that.
Are they related?
When I check on Mount Lookout,
I’ll know if the Fire Kylin is Boxuan.
Go with Jingjian to the Heavenly Palace
to untie the Magic Rope.
As for Qingmu,
let him stay here for recuperation.
No!
If you’re going to look for Boxuan,
I must go with you.
You just had a big fight
with the Demon King.
You shouldn’t go on a long trip.
Mount Lookout is in the teeth
of the storm,
where immortals and demons gather.
You might be in danger if you go alone.
You’re badly wounded.
Stay for recuperation
and take care of yourself.
I just ate the pellet you gave me
and I’m feeling much better.
Pellets from the Qingchi Palace
are really extraordinary.
Don’t give me that.
Go back and lie in bed.
Lady Fengran.
Don’t call me.
I’m on her side
and I can’t help you.
Jingjian, say something for me.
He’s calling you.
I won’t listen.
Why are you all staring at me?
I hear the Fire Kylin
hurt Lord Xianshan,
the disciple of Lord Donghua.
It’s a fierce beast.
I’ll worry if you go alone.
How about
letting Qingmu go with you?
Just because it’s a dangerous trip,
I don’t want to take him.
You don’t know him.
He loves defending the weak.
If he gets into any conflict,
he’ll be wounded again
and his further cultivation
will be harmed.
I didn’t know you cared about him.
I don’t.
Jingjian!
It’s a misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding.
The Magic Rope just pulled me
so that I touched the door accidentally.
Shall I cut off your hand, then?
You won’t have the same trouble again.
No, no, don’t bother.
I’ll leave you alone.
It’s your fault!
You insisted on eavesdropping
and got me scolded, too.
Remember.
You owe me ten jars
of North Sea iced liquor.
Rest assured.
You’ll have them.
It’s a useful rope.
Do you have another one?
Give it to me
so that I can be tied to Houchi.
We haven’t met
for only a couple of days,
and why do you sound so...?
You have no idea.
Houchi and I had a predestined fate.
Where did you learn it?
From the story book in the Human Realm?
You don’t trust me?
Absolutely not.
Aren’t you not good at
getting close to any lady?
Do you remember the sword grave
on Mount Lookout?
You couldn’t see it,
but I could.
She could get in there, too.
Also,
this is her bracelet.
It’s the same as mine.
They were made by the same man.
So,
this is why
you fell in love with her?
She’s sometimes clumsy,
sometimes stubborn
and sometimes clever.
She’s indeed lovely.
I...
Anyway, when staying with Houchi,
I did many fantastic things.
I never expected to see you in love
before I died.
I’ve got my life worth.
When your sister said she liked me
and tried to see me with excuses,
I didn’t understand
and I felt annoyed.
But now,
I indeed experience
how she was feeling.
My poor sister.
She ignores many other immortals,
but only likes you...
In love,
no one can be forced.
How does Houchi feel for you?
Does she adore you, too?
I won’t give up, anyway.
Got it.
Let me help you.
Excuse me,
may I have a word?
My father has gone to Mount Lookout now.
Lady Fengran and I will go to him
to untie the Magic Rope.
Why don’t we four go together
so that we can take care of each other?
Yeah.
You make sense.
I think Qingmu is too stubborn
to let you go alone.
Why don’t you
just satisfy him?
All right, then.
Let’s go together.
I’ve received
my father’s instruction feather,
and he’s in the Daze Mansion.
Let’s get up the mountain.
Fengran,
go with Prince Jingjian to see
the Heavenly Emperor
and ask him to untie the Magic Rope.
I’ll wait for you behind the mountain.
Houchi,
my father often mentioned
his old friendship with Lord Gu Jun.
And we’ve been expecting a chance
to mend fences with the Qingchi Palace.
Jingjian,
go with Fengran to see your father.
I’ll stay and accompany Houchi.
All right.
See you later behind the mountain.
Before the Spear picks its owner,
the Heavenly Emperor must be here.
Jingzhao will also come, I guess.
How long can you still avoid them?
Who told you I was avoiding them?
I’m not scared of Jingzhao.
You’re not?
Let’s go, then.
No.
I’m not going with you.
I don’t want to be hated by all ladies.
All right.
This time,
I’ll announce to everyone.
What?
No one can get me,
but Goddess Houchi.
How dare you!
I risked my life for you.
For the sake of that,
shouldn’t you defend me from the ladies?
Nonsense.
I’m not speaking to you.
All right. Don’t get angry.
I know.
You don’t want to see anyone
from the Heavenly Palace.
I’ve got an idea.
What is it?
Jingzhao will not recognize you.
What do you think?
Then I can carry you
in my sleeve.
Qingmu,
how dare you turn me into a frog!
You...
What about now?
Qingmu, don’t push it!
All right. No more joke.
Are you satisfied now?
Good.
(Daze Mansion)
Heavenly Father.
Heavenly Father,
Lady Fengran and I were tied
to the Magic Rope by accident.
Could you please untie us?
Thank you, Your Majesty.
It’s been years
since I last visited the Qingchi Palace.
Is Gu Jun back from his journey?
He isn’t back ever.
Now that you left the Qingchi Palace,
what about Houchi?
Is everything all right with her?
Yes, it is.
Thank you for the concern, Your Majesty.
Jingjian,
you did a good job
in the Demon Realm.
When you were on your way back,
the Demon King sent a letter to us
and agreed on the peace negotiations.
I’ve proclaimed to everyone that
demons are allowed to come
to Mount Lookout
and fight for the Taicang Spear.
I didn’t do much.
I’m also surprised that
they agreed on the peace negotiations.
Sen Jian is the Demon King.
The old hatred can’t be as important
as all the beings in the Three Realms.
You’re right, Heavenly Father.
It’s a blessing for the Three Realms
when immortals and demons make up.
Why?
Why can’t we get in?
Yeah.
That’s right.
Everybody, calm down.
His Majesty proclaimed that
you could come to look for the Spear.
But for your safety concern,
please stay here for some rest.
When the Spear appears,
we’ll invite you in.
The Feather Umbrella?
You’re Princess Jingzhao?
I’m glad you know me.
You want the Taicang Spear, don’t you?
I don’t think you need to get in.
Let’s have a fight here.
If you lose,
you don’t need to get in.
Your Grace,
we shouldn’t fight demons...
Say no more!
Leave immediately!
Or I’ll get your demon cores!
Wait here for me.
I’ll go have a look.
Qingmu!
You also came for the Taicang Spear?
I won’t compromise to you today.
Let’s fight for it.
But if I get it,
I’ll hold a banquet for everyone.
Do come to the Heavenly Palace
and congratulate me.
Your Grace,
why did you badly wound these demons?
They made rude remarks.
The Demon King punishes the demons.
But you’re the princess
of the Heavenly Palace.
How can you punish them
on behalf of the Demon King?
I...
Thank you for helping us.
You’re welcome.
Not all immortals are
as unreasonable as her.
Qingmu,
what do you mean?
Now that the Demons agreed on
the peace negotiations,
the Immortals should behave generously.
If the princess takes the lead
to make trouble,
I’m afraid even the Heavenly Emperor
will be mocked.
You’re right, Lord Qingmu.
I am?
Then why did you just watch,
instead of stopping her?
As the saying goes in the Human Realm,
whoever breaks the law
should be punished.
Even children can tell right from wrong.
But immortals like you
turned a blind eye to that.
That was funny.
Qingmu,
even when I was finicky,
you hadn’t been so strict on me.
Today, the demons were aggressive.
I badly wounded them,
in a fit of anger.
Father.
Father, who is this old lady?
Why is she so bad-tempered?
What... What did you call him?
Father.
Old lady,
why are you getting so close
to my father?
Don’t you know
he has a wife?
Since when has he got a wife?
Why doesn’t anyone know?
Little girl, don’t talk nonsense.
All right.
Don’t make fun of her.
This is Princess Jingzhao.
Qingmu, is she really your...?
I stayed in the North Sea
and have never come out before.
This time, Father took me here
to see the Spear.
I didn’t know it could be so fun.
You’re Princess Jingzhao?
Greetings, Old Master Jingzhao.
Who do you mean “old”?
You naughty girl!
How dare you!
Am I wrong?
I hear you’re more than
twenty thousand years old.
But my father is
only a few thousand years old.
In this way,
if you got married early,
your son would be as old as my father.
You’re certainly an old master to me.
You...!
She’s just kid.
Am I wrong?
You’re a grown-up.
You must be polite
so that others will respect you.
I saw what you just did.
I didn’t do anything.
My father is upright.
And how handsome he is!
Don’t worry.
I won’t act wildly
like this old lady did.
That’s good, then.
You little girl,
you’re his daughter,
but you have no spiritual power at all.
I’m sure
your mother is a mortal
who wants to become an immortal
by giving birth to you.
What a plan!
You make sense, Your Grace.
Your parents are Gods
and you’re a noble princess.
But why are you still not a Goddess
when you’re twenty thousand years old?
I hear Houchi from the Qingchi Palace
became a Goddess
even before she was born.
You...!
Naughty girl.
How dare you keep humiliating me!
See how I’ll teach you a lesson!
She’s mine.
I’ll instruct her.
Don’t bother.
For the sake of your father,
as long as you salute
and apologize to me,
I’ll forgive you.
All right.
You just want me to salute to you?
Do you want me to kneel
or make a deep bow?
Your Grace,
I can salute to you.
But I fear you can’t
receive it.
Your mother can be a very humble woman.
Why can’t I receive
your salute?
Hope you won’t regret.
Who are you?
How can you bring the thunder?
I told you
you couldn’t receive my salute.
You...!
You’re Houchi?
Your Grace, it’s good for you.
It’s my first time to know
someone forcing a Goddess
to salute to her.
I guess you forgot
how you were punished by thunder
on Mount Lookout last time.
What’s your relationship with Qingmu?
Why are you with him?
Your Grace,
it’s my privacy.
Qingmu.
Even if he’s cold to me,
he’s never been so rude.
You must have done something to him.
If you talk nonsense again,
I won’t mind issuing another edict
to the Heavenly Palace.
You think you can?
I’ll show everybody
what you are on earth
as the Goddess!
Your Grace,
Houchi is a Goddess.
You can’t fight her.
If you insist,
don’t blame me for being rude.
You’ll protect her?
Well, I won’t let her go!
Stop!
Heavenly Father.
Are you all right?
From this day on,
pick good immortals
and cultivate good ones
for the God Realm.
I’m Muguang,
a Gold Dragon from Mount Tianci.
I’m God of Stars.
Chief God of Chaos, congratulations.
I’m the Chief God of Chaos.
It’s my duty
to protect the world.
Your Majesty.
Houchi,
I didn’t know you had grown up.
Your Majesty,
now that you have come,
I’ll leave everything
to you.
We usually don’t interfere with fights
between immortals and demons.
I was just angry about that.
Excuse me.
Let’s go.
About the peace negotiations
between immortals and demons,
the Demon King and I
have reached an agreement.
From this day on,
whoever harms the peace
will be
severely punished!
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Who was that man
behind Houchi?
For your information,
he’s my good friend, Qingmu.
You personally made him
North Sea Star Lord.
It’s such fine liquor.
Where did you get it?
Donghua sent his disciple
to bring it to me.
He’s a smart man.
Indeed,
we should mark today.
My father is upright.
And how handsome he is!
Stop it.
Jingzhao looked like
she was going to eat me.
Fruit?
When I was travelling
in the Human Realm,
I learnt some small tricks.
Are you trying to make me happy?
You’re a Goddess, instead of a kid.
Fruit can’t make you happy.
Every time I was unhappy
when I was a kid,
Boxuan made me happy with food.
If you want to talk about the past,
I’m all ears.
If you don’t,
you can just sit like this.
Why did you
leave with me today?
If you stayed, you would talk to
the Heavenly Emperor,
the strongest and most powerful man.
So what?
When I wanted to leave, I left.
I can tell that
Jingzhao really cares about you.
It’s power and wealth
others can’t even beg for.
You really don’t want any?
I simply need enough food
and accommodation.
What do I need the wealth for?
I accepted the title,
simply because Jingjian was my friend
and I couldn’t reject him.
Don’t brag.
I’m serious.
After I had the title,
I should’ve gone to the Heavenly Palace
to express my gratitude.
But I was travelling in the Human Realm
and didn’t go there.
You stood the Heavenly Emperor up?
In the Heavenly Palace,
there’re too many rules.
I’ll feel uneasy
and uncomfortable.
Why are we talking about me?
What happened between you and Jingzhao?
You’re not unreasonable.
She has nothing to do with the past.
You’re even kind to Jingjian.
Why are you so hostile to her?
It wasn’t my first time
to meet her on Mount Lookout.
You’re Houchi?
Do you know who I am?
I’m talking to you!
Don’t you hear me?
Look how weak you are.
How dare you talk back!
Simply because you have little
spiritual power,
Mother abandoned you
and the Qingchi Palace.
You’re a shame to the Qingchi Palace
and to Mother!
What happened later?
Luckily, Boxuan came in time
and got me out of the water.
Otherwise, I would have been
the first Goddess
that was drowned.
From then on, I’m scared of water.
I haven’t learnt to swim yet.
I don’t mean this.
I mean...
You mean my spiritual power?
Jingzhao is right.
I have little spiritual power.
It took me forty thousand years
to come out of the shell.
No matter how hard I try,
I can’t gather the spiritual power.
Father is traveling around
to find treasures for me
and he seldom comes back.
Fengran wasn’t there yet.
The Qingchi Palace was cold and lonely.
No one accompanied me, but Boxuan.
Later, Boxuan left, too.
I never left the Qingchi Palace.
I don’t care if I’m humiliated.
But I don’t want my father to be mocked.
So,
that’s how you grew up.
I kind of envy you sometimes
that you lost your memories.
Your parents
are among the best immortals.
You should have enough spiritual power.
Is your body sealed by something?
If it were,
my father would have noticed that.
All right. Don’t try to persuade me.
No matter what you say,
I won’t be nice to Jingzhao.
Now that she bullied you,
she should bear the consequences.
I didn’t know it before.
But from now on,
I won’t interfere with you two.
I thought you would advise me
not to hate her
because she was a little girl
at that time.
Why must I say that?
You’re the only one I...
Drop it.
I won’t give you more burden.
Look.
Make a wish.
It’s simply the light of cloud riding.
Why shall I make a wish?
Only when you believe in something,
it can come true.
Haven’t you heard of it?
Be quick.
I wish Houchi will be a real Goddess
and be invincible.
Nonsense.
Come on. Make a wish.
I wish Lord Qingmu could have
his wish come true.
I made two wishes.
What’s the second one?
Not telling you.
But I’m sure it will come true.
Don’t get me wrong.
It’s...?
The Taicang Spear is coming out.
The flame...
It must be the Kylin.
Qingmu,
if the Kylin is Boxuan,
he’ll protect the Taicang Spear.
Those who fight for the Spear
will not let him go.
I have little spiritual power
and I can’t defend him.
No matter what happens,
you must protect him.
Don’t worry.
I’ll let no one hurt him.
It’s really Hongri.
Donghua,
when I saw that Houchi looked
so much like Master Shanggu,
I was too excited
to control myself.
When I calm down now,
I have confusions.
Please help me out.
You’re being too polite, Your Majesty.
I understand your confusions.
When I first saw Goddess Houchi,
I also felt familiar
because of her appearance.
But speaking of temperament,
the air of Chaos or her origin,
she may not be Master Shanggu.
I agree with you.
But beside her,
there’s Lord Qingmu
who looks the same as Master Bai Jue.
I don’t think it’s that simple.
You said that
Master Bai Jue might have come
to the lower realm.
If Master Bai Jue is still here,
he shouldn’t look like Lord Qingmu.
If we think
Qingmu is Master Bai Jue’s offspring,
he doesn’t have parents
to be tracked down.
No matter what the truth is,
I think we have hope
to reopen the God Realm.
Your Majesty, why not find a chance
to fight Lord Qingmu
and see how much he has inherited
from Master Bai Jue?
Sounds like a good idea.
As for Goddess Houchi...
Lord Gu Jun is travelling around.
Maybe the Queen of Heaven
can tell you something.
I don’t think so.
When she left Houchi,
Houchi hadn’t come out of the shell yet.
I’m afraid we can’t figure it out
until Gu Jun comes back.
Heavenly Father.
The Taicang Spear has come out.
Even demons are fighting for it.
But why haven’t you gone there yet?
The Spear belongs to immortals.
We can’t let any demon have it.
I stressed it many times that
there was no difference
between immortals and demons.
Why does True God Bai Jue’s weapon
have to belong to immortals?
Heavenly Father!
The Demon King and I agreed that
we wouldn’t interfere with the Spear.
You can go with Jingjian.
The Spear has spirit.
No matter who has it,
as long as we can
disregard previous enmities
and reopen the God Realm together,
it’ll be a good thing
for the Three Realms.
Yes.
Jingjian, protect your sister.
Yes, Heavenly Father.
Yeah.
As in the legend,
who gets an ancient weapon
will become a God.
Jingjian,
help me.
I must become a Goddess this time.
Jingzhao,
the Spear is guarded by the Kylin.
Let’s see and don’t be impulsive.
Lord Xianshan,
has the Kylin turned up?
Not yet.
You think you can fight
for Taicang Spear?
I’d like to see
who dares to fight with me for it.
Hongri?!
He’s not Hongri.
But how come?
It’s Hongri’s spiritual aura.
It’s simply a piece of his soul.
How dare you ordinary beings
break into the cultivation place
of True God
and offend him.
Leave immediately!
What do you think?
He isn’t Boxuan.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪