watch on kisskh.me
(Asian music)
please watch on kisskh.me to supported us
FEI: It all took place
on the day
of the magical eclipse.
Wu Shifu was desperate.
The secret he guarded
was in danger.
Shame on us, Master! Our Kung Fu
is not up to your teaching!
You still have so much to learn!
FEI: What had become
of the ancestral values?
Courage, honesty, loyalty?
A mysterious stranger
was doing all he could
to force the master
to sell his school.
Someone clearly wanted
to take over the land
upon which it was built.
The greed of the world
was destroying everything.
His school was his life, and hs
students were like his childre.
Without a family of his own,
he would have no one
to pass on his legacy
and all the responsibilities
that came with it.
To whom would he entrust
his heavy secret?
What if no one was there
to protect the sacred cave
during the next magical eclips?
Now alone, he had lost all hop.
And that was when we met.
(Crying)
He gave me my name.
In Mandarin,
it means "to fly in the sky".
My name is Fei.
My adoptive father, Wu Shi Fu,
would go on to teach me
the values of Kung Fu
and make me the new guardian.
But they were still trying
to chase us away.
And when they took away
my adoptive father,
they destroyed the school.
In the end,
they even got the bracelet.
(Gasps)
Now I was the only one left
to protect the secret
of the cave
during the next magic eclipse.
So, school was finally out
and it was gonna be amazing!
We'd go swimming,
hang out at the cinema,
visit the museum,
take long walks...
We even organized a huge
potluck picnic for all of us,
and, this time,
Adrien would join us!
His father
had given him permission.
That's right, holidays
were off to a great start!
Even for Cat Noir and me!
We did have a few missions,
but no akumatized villain
in sight.
It seemed like Hawk Moth
had taken holidays, too!
We relaxed
'cause we still didn't know
what holidays
for Hawk Moth meant.
Basically, we thought
everything was going well,
until everything
started to go wrong.
Sorry, but I can't get away
from the bakery today.
If the package
doesn't get sent off today,
Uncle Wang won't get it
in time for his birthday!
All right. I'll go.
Thanks, sweetie!
(Phone rings)
MARINETTE: I'm experiencing
a little setback.
Why does that not surprise me
in the slightest?
Save me a seat
next to you‐know‐who, please!
I'll be there as fast as I can!
But don't you know?
I thought you knew!
What?
What am I supposed to know?
Adrien's gone to Shanghai!
Huh? There must be a mistake!
I know everything!
His five first names
and every name day,
his yearly schedule
and even his shoe size!
If there were anything
to know about him, I'd know it!
Well, he didn't know either.
He told Nino the opening
of his father's shop in Shanghai
had been moved up
at the last minute.
Shanghai?
RELAXING VOICE:
You are a dolphin,
leaping from wave to wave
in an ocean of tranquility.
This store is essential
for the future
of the Agreste family.
Opening it much sooner
than expected
is very good news.
There will be other fun times
with your friends.
You're right. Besides,
I'm glad I get to spend
time with you, Father.
I'm looking forward to it, too.
But before that,
I still have to sort out
organizational details.
(Sighs)
Did you check everything out?
All the conditions necessary
for the magical eclipse
will be met tomorrow as planne.
Please, Master, think!
It is for good reason
the Prodigious was abandoned
in favor of the Miraculous.
It was secured in that cave
because it is too dangerous!
Precisely, Nooroo.
Ladybug and Cat Noir's
Miraculous
have held me in check
for too long.
I won't pass up an opportunity
to destroy them
with this higher power.
What I started 15 years ago,
I will finish tomorrow, at last.
‐ Mom!
‐ The package!
‐ It'll never make it in time!
‐ Yes, it will.
Because I'm gonna hand it
to Uncle Wang myself.
‐ Uh...
‐ You see,
because it's high time
I visit my uncle in person!
Because my uncle...
is my roots! And I've tried
to connect with Adri ‐‐
I mean, my roots for so long.
And he keeps...
I mean, they keep eluding me.
And without him, uh, I mean,
them... without my roots,
‐ I mean, I feel incomplete.
‐ Marinette,
are you saying that...
you want to go to Shanghai?
Your mother and I
have been waiting
for this moment for so long.
We always thought
you'd want to connect
with your Chinese family!
We've been putting
money aside
since you were born,
enough for a family trip.
We were just waiting
for you to ask.
For you to be ready!
Still, this is a bit sudden!
We can't close the bakery now.
If you want to give Uncle Wang
his gift in person...
You'll have to go alone.
You're the best parents
in the whole world!
WANG:
What a joy to see you again!
I'm so happy
you finally made the trip!
Yes, it's good, and this way
you'll get your present on time!
Your visit is my present,
Marinette.
Your mother said you wanted
to connect with your roots,
and that's the happiest
you can make me.
The restaurant
had many guests planned,
but I cancelled everything.
I took a vacation
for the first time since...
Since your mother
moved to France.
You didn't have
to do that for me!
Of course I did.
Family is sacred.
Your English has improved
since you last came to Paris.
I have worked hard so it'd be
easier to communicate with you.
And now I can tell you
all about your ancestors
and show you every family photo.
Next time,
I'll take you to visit Shanghai
and teach you all the Chengs'
traditional songs.
The Chengs
have traditional songs?
The Bund District
is so impressive, Father!
Have you ever spent time
in Shanghai outside of work?
Of course I have.
You must have places to show me!
I'd love to see them together!
I suppose. But before we do,
I have some details to work out
for tomorrow's opening night.
I guess I'll just stay
at the hotel and wait for you.
No. Take advantage of this
beautiful day to walk around.
I'll join you
in the early afternoon.
Your great‐great‐great‐
grandfather designed dresses
for the Beijing opera
performers.
Marinette! Marinette!
It's Marinette!
Yes, Bastille. I'm very proud to
finally introduce my grandniece
Marinette to you!
Nice to meet you, uh, Bastille.
Bastille has always been
in the family. Look!
He was already there
with Grandpa Yan
and Granny Mei Cheng,
and with Xia‐Bing, your mother.
‐ Xia‐Bing?
‐ Yes.
She only took the name Sabine
when she moved to France.
Wow! I've never seen
that photo of Mom.
Magic ingredient!
Yes, Bastille.
I haven't forgotten.
Do you remember
my style of cooking?
Huh? Uh... Oh, right! Ha, ha!
You improvise around something
that fate brings you!
And today fate has
brought you, Marinette!
But I don't have
any ingredients on me!
‐ (Phone buzzes)
‐ Oh! (Giggles)
Oh! I know!
I could go for a walk
and see if fate brings me Adr ‐‐
I mean, a magic ingredient!
Aren't you afraid
of getting lost?
‐ You don't even speak Mandarin!
‐ I won't get lost.
I have my phone.
It has a GPS, and a translator.
Very well, but don't go too far.
Everything you need is nearby.
I'm sure our meal tonight
will be very special indeed.
Croa!
You want to put Adrien
in a soup?
Of course not, Tikki! We'll look
for a magic ingredient
and go say "hi" to Adrien.
‐ You mean "ni‐hao"?
‐ You speak Mandarin?
Of course!
Kwamis speak all languages.
That makes sense. You never know
who your next holder will be!
‐ But how will you find Adrien?
‐ See? It's easy.
We're here, he's there.
We just need to follow this map!
This is gonna be super easy!
Hey, aren't you Adrien Agreste,
the famous model?
‐ Grr!
‐ Please, let them.
I don't mind.
Ah! Hmm.
Hey!
I'm here, Nathalie.
Now all I need
is to find
the perfect person
to akumatize.
Oh, wow. It didn't look
so far away on the map!
I'd like to see
people as people,
think of them as stories.
Their smallest pleasures,
their greatest joys,
their disappointments,
their successes.
That's how my adoptive father
would've wanted me to see them.
Ah! Ah!
(Crying)
Huh?
To be the guardian
he wanted me to be,
I must forget who I really am.
I must get the key back
at all costs.
And for that, I need money.
There is someone who could
tell me what happened
to my adoptive father,
but I have to pay him.
Hmm?
(Phone rings)
Father? You're done? Oh...
Yes, of course. I understand.
Later? Yeah, sure. As you wish.
See you later, then.
PLAGG:
Your father will never change!
You can depend
on the consistency
in a soft cheese,
but in a human being? Ugh!
What I wouldn't give
for something to eat!
Ah! I've got what you need,
Plagg!
Remember Wang Shifu?
Marinette's uncle?
His Thousand Delights restaurant
is in this town!
Ah!
There's a place
I'd like to go. Do you mind?
Sorry!
Adrien! Adrien!
Adrien!
Adrien...
Sorry!
Oh, no!
That poor girl needs help!
Shoot!
Tikki, spots on!
Tikki?
Tikki!
Aaah!
(Anxious heartbeat)
Tikki!
Huh?
Marinette is in Shanghai?
What an incredible coincidence!
‐ Or fate!
‐ Ah! Love is beautiful!
‐ Love! Love!
‐ Ha, ha!
No, Marinette's just a friend!
Oh! Maybe we could surprise her.
Do you mind
if we wait here with you?
Oh, my!
That would be delightful!
You can help me
prepare our meal.
‐ (Uncle Wang laughs)
‐ Croa!
MARINETTE: I had lost
my Miraculous, my kwagatama,
and Tikki. Without my smartphoe
to guide me or to translate,
I had no way
to get back to Uncle Wang
or get myself understood
to get help!
Uh... uh...
Bastille, get some chili peppers
from the pantry, please!
Chili pepper!
Chili pepper! Coming in hot!
I'm looking for these earrings.
Did you see anyone
wearing them?
‐ Is Marinette often late?
‐ Marinette? Yeah. All the time!
It would actually be unusual
for her to be on time!
I'll call her anyway.
(Phone rings)
It's Marinette, leave a messag.
Beep!
Marinette, this is Uncle Wang.
I hope you didn't get lost!
‐ I've got Adr ‐‐
‐ Shh!
Uh, a... surprise! See you soon!
Oh! These are nice!
Thank you, ma'am.
It's not what I'm looking for,
but it's very kind of you.
Thank you.
I'd come here every day, to sel
whatever I'd gotten my hands o.
Little by little,
I'd pay the one
who'd carry out my revenge.
Cash!
Fei, what treasures
do you have for me today?
‐ Hmm.
‐ You're going to tell me
‐ there's nothing of value?
‐ I want to help you, really!
But everything has a price.
And the price of these things
‐ is not very high.
‐ I'm tired of stealing!
I want you
to tell me his name!
Until you bring me enough things
to pay that price,
I can't give it to you.
This purse is not bad.
This phone's just junk.
‐ The earrings...
‐ But they're antiques!
I know more about that than you.
They're commonplace.
Ugh! How awful. But at least
that can go in the claw crane.
‐ Two hundred yuans for it all.
‐ What? Are you kidding me?
You know, Fei, I like you a lot.
At 200 yuans,
I'm actually doing you a favor,
in memory of the noble Wu Shifu
and all he stood for.
So, if you respect his values,
why not introduce me to the man
who can tell me
who burnt down the school?
Because, just like the school,
those values no longer exist.
What matters today
is driven by the market!
Cash is king, baby! It's sad,
but adapting is the key
to success! Two hundred yuans.
At that price, I'd rather
take them to that poor girl!
Wait!
Hmm. That's a great idea!
If you find her, your "poor"
girl can buy them back!
This pitiful stuffed animal
must be very valuable... to her!
Sentimental value.
And feelings are priceless!
If I bring you
the owner of these things
and she buys them all back,
will you finally tell me
what I want to know?
A deal's a deal!
Hey!
I had lost all hope
of finding my things.
Now, I was just trying to find
my way back to the restaurant
to ask for his help.
But I was completely lost.
Sorry!
You're the girl
they were chasing!
They're running after me, now!
I guess you don't speak English?
Yes, I speak English. Follow me!
‐ We lost them!
‐ (Groans)
‐ Something wrong?
‐ I'm so glad
I found somebody
who understands me!
People here are so nice,
but I can't explain
my situation to them!
I'm sure I can help.
Tell me what happened to you.
Someone stole all my things.
My purse, my phone, my earrings.
‐ You found them?
‐ What? These? No.
A nice old lady
gave those to me.
What about the real ones?
Do they have
sentimental value?
Oh, yes. Someone important
gave them to me.
Someone who trusted me.
I also had a jewel
stolen from me...
one that someone special
had entrusted me with.
Like you,
I want it back, at any cost.
‐ So, you get it.
‐ Yes. I'll help you!
Really? Thank you.
I need to go back to my uncle's.
He has a restaurant in Shanghai,
but I don't know the address.
It's them again! Follow me!
Wham! Bam! Pow!
‐ (Laughs)
‐ Marinette, it is me again.
I and... "surprise"
are very worried!
Please, call me back!
I should not have let her
go out alone.
‐ I'm sure everything's fine.
‐ I'll still call the police.
And I'll go see
if I can find her.
‐ Are you sure?
‐ She can't be very far.
And I do speak Mandarin.
Stay here. I won't be very long!
It'll be easier
to find Marinette as Cat Noir.
And how will you explain
Cat Noir's presence in Shanghai?
I'll figure something out.
Plagg, claws out!
I think we're OK now.
Why were you alone in Shanghai?
I'd gone out
to meet with a friend
and then I realized that someone
had stolen my things.
‐ Hmm?
Come on!
Put these on, in case
we bump into those kids again!
Why d'you have
all these costumes?
I... I just got back
from a costume party!
Let's take a bike.
I thought about your earrings.
I know a street
filled with pawnshops.
Maybe your thief tricked them
into buying your things,
‐ pretending they were theirs.
‐ Oh. OK.
Oh! Do you think
we could find my uncle's number
so I can call him?
He must be worried.
Uh, I ran out of credit.
I can't call anyone. Sorry!
Don't worry, you can reassure
him in person very soon.
‐ What's your name, by the way?
‐ Fei.
I'm Marinette.
I'm so lucky I ran into you!
Mi‐Hao.
Don't worry. I'm Cat Noir,
Paris's superhero!
Paris? What are you doing here?
I'm looking for a French girl
who went missing in Shanghai.
French superheroes
deal with lost tourists?
Uh... yes, among other things.
Part of our public service!
Sorry. I haven't seen her.
Good luck finding your citizen.
Oh, I knew I should've studied
Mandarin a long time ago.
What about you?
How come you speak English, Fei?
My father loved that language.
He wanted me to know it.
Besides, his school had lost
all its local customers,
but he thought he could teach
Kung‐Fu to tourists.
But his school went up in smoke,
and, with it,
everything he believed in.
Not everything.
You're still here.
I have become the complete
opposite of what he believed in!
I don't get it. He wanted you
to be a mean and selfish coward?
Why would you say that?
Fei, you've been
helping me for hours now
even though
you don't even know me,
and you were super brave,
protecting me from those
who were chasing me!
You're such an amazing person!
So, if your father
wanted the opposite for you...
I'm not as amazing
as you think.
We're here.
It's Marinette, leave a messag.
Beep!
You've reached the voicemail
of Adrien Agreste...
‐ Gonna be OK! Gonna be OK!
‐ I hope so, Bastille.
I hope so.
Look this way.
I'll go that way.
(Gasps)
There! They're here!
My Miracu... uh, my earrings!
Wow! What luck!
Hello.
I really need to get these back.
They're very,
very important to me.
I'm so happy to have found them!
Could you translate?
That won't be necessary.
I speak English.
So...
these earrings
are very precious to you?
Yes! Infinitely precious!
100,000 yuans to get them back.
100,000 yuans? Is that a lot?
That's the law
of supply and demand!
If it's precious to her,
it's precious to me!
That's disgusting! Using
people's misfortune to get rich!
You're the one
who robbed the girl.
You're the one who
brought her to me. So, tell me,
which one of us
uses people's misfortune more?
‐ Marinette!
‐ I'll get you out of here.
‐ Stop it, Fei, I'll pay.
‐ But that's a huge sum!
I'll call my uncle
and explain everything.
Could I please use your phone?
May I have the number to
the Thousand Delights, please?
I know it.
Your uncle is a great chef.
Yes, and I'm so ashamed
I have to ask him.
‐ Here's the number.
‐ Thank you, sir,
that's very nice of you.
‐ We'll find another way.
‐ But, Fei...
If you don't buy them now,
I can't guarantee
I'll still have them later.
If a customer wants to buy them,
I'll sell them!
‐ Fei, I can't lose them again.
‐ Believe me,
no one will buy them
at that price.
CASH: Fei? What are you doing?
You don't want to know
who went after your father?
Have you forgotten who you are?
Actually, I just remembered
who I really am!
‐ I'm taking you to your uncle.
‐ I can't leave without ‐‐
Hop on the bike, quick.
You stole my earrings?
Didn't you want them back?
Yes! But not like that!
Stealing is wrong!
That seller paid a lot
of money to buy my earrings!
This way,
he'll have lost all his money!
Marinette, I promise
I'll explain everything,
but you've gotta get
on the bike, now!
Hmm?
Where's the red plush toy?
She duped me.
That little brat duped me!
Argh! Get them!
What if that poor man's taken on
a debt to buy these earrings?
Marinette, stop arguing and run!
These guys... see? Mad at us!
Believe me, you have no idea
how furious they are!
Tikki!
‐ Tikki!
‐ No, no, no! Stick with me!
‐ These guys are dangerous!
‐ What do you mean "these guys"?
The other ones
seemed pretty dangerous too!
Fei, please, let me go get help!
The only person
who can help us here is me
and the Kung Fu
my father taught me!
What's happening?
We, the Street Vigilantes,
fight evil,
even when, uh,
it strikes out at, uh,
more evil.
Go home! You'll get hurt!
We don't take orders
from a thief!
‐ A thief?
‐ He doesn't know
what he's talking about!
Run!
This city is too big.
I can't do this alone.
Oh!
Milady, a girl we both know,
Marinette Dupain‐Cheng,
is missing in Shanghai.
I'm already there.
If you get this message,
meet me. I need help.
The time has come.
Master, please reconsider!
You'll trigger a magic that is
much too powerful for you!
The Guardian of the Prodigious
is a formidable opponent.
You'll never be able
to defeat him!
Who said I would be
the one challenging him?
‐ What's this place?
‐ This is where I live.
Marinette Dupain‐Cheng?
This is where I have to be...
right now.
Sorry, that's all I have.
Fei, why do we have to be here?
I have to guard
my father's legacy.
But your father...
Disappeared with his school.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
They did everything
to make us leave. Everything.
Intimidation. Burglary.
They took everything from us.
Even the bracelet
he had entrusted me with.
The jewel I told you about
it's as precious to me
as your earrings are to you,
except that it had a power.
Who are "they" exactly?
Precisely. I don't know.
My search for their identities
brought us together today.
There's something
I've got to tell you... I ‐‐
You really thought you could
get away from me, Fei?
‐ You... You know each other?
‐ (Hysterical laugh)
Of course we know each other!
How do you think I ended up
with your earring, kid?
She stole them from you
and then she stole them from me!
I was about to tell you,
Marinette, I... I swear!
You saw how desperate I was
to get my earrings back
and you knew I'd be willing
to pay a huge price for them!
I'm sorry! He told me he knew
someone who could tell me
what happened to my father!
But he demanded a huge sum
‐ in exchange for the truth!
‐ Truth isn't free.
No pain, no gain, baby!
You're gonna call your uncle
right now
and ask him
for the money he owes me!
I won't let you do this!
Run, Marinette!
All this greed. Even back then,
it worked in my favor!
CASH: A deal's a deal!
Nooroo! Dark wings rise!
I want my money!
And you're gonna give it to me
or you'll never get answers!
I just want you to tell me
the truth, once and for all!
The truth? If that girl
doesn't call her uncle,
you'll meet the same fate
as your father!
Don't you dare
talk about my father!
I may have failed him,
but it's over.
I'll find the answers
all by myself!
You have to stay with me.
I can protect you!
You haven't protected me.
You've just lied to me!
You have to trust me!
‐ I can't.
‐ I shouldn't have stolen.
Please forgive me.
You did what you had to do.
And so must I.
King Cash, I am Hawk Moth.
You want to be rich?
Something very valuable
is hidden behind that waterfall.
If you help me
get my hands on it,
I will make you rich
beyond your wildest dream.
A deal's a deal!
The silver blades on your fan
will slice through anything.
The gold ones will turn anything
they touch into a statue.
Time to get rich!
Tikki, Hawk Moth's
here in Shanghai too.
Do you think Fei
is being sincere, Marinette?
I'm not sure yet. But for now...
Tikki, spots on!
Yeah!
Milady, a girl we both know,
Marinette Dupain‐Cheng,
has gone missing in Shanghai.
I'm there.
If you get this message,
meet me. I need your help.
Aw, nice kitty.
(Phone rings)
‐ Miaow, Milady!
‐ I've just arrived in Shanghai.
‐ Have you found her?
‐ Not yet, but with you here,
‐ I'm sure we will together!
‐ She's not the only one here.
‐ I just saw an akuma!
‐ What? I'll be right there!
Hurry up, Cat Noir!
It's time to prove
that money can open any door.
No one is allowed
into the sacred cave!
Who do you think you're
dealing with, little mosquito?
‐ You're wasting your time!
‐ And time is money!
Aaah!
Grab on!
Where's the fortune
you promised me?
Soon, soon. Have patience.
‐ Who are you?
‐ Ladybug!
I'm Fei. You're one
of the good guys, right?
Yes.
Now I can finally see
if this was a good investment.
So you were my mysterious buyer!
I've never made so much money
on a lousy trinket! (Evil laugh)
I've been waiting
for this moment for 15 years.
‐ That's my bracelet!
‐ Is it special?
I don't know. I was supposed to
protect the cave and bracelet.
And I failed.
Human, prepare to face
the judgment of Mei Shi,
the Lion Protector
of the Prodigious.
‐ The Prodigious?
‐ Do you know what this is?
No, but if Hawk Moth wants it,
I must stop him from getting it!
You stay right here!
Hmm.
Put the Prodigious
around your neck, human,
and prepare to face my judgment.
Who told you I had
any intention of facing you?
‐ Huh?
‐ King Cash,
the time has come
to honor our deal.
Turn him into a gold statue.
Oh, no, you won't!
That's not in the rules!
No!
I'm taking over
my father's mission!
Fei, I told you to stay away!
You're the one
I'll be judging then, human.
Hurry, Cat Noir!
THE RENLING:
Greetings to our new Renren!
‐ New what?
‐ Renren!
The person
who wears the Prodigious!
Who are you talking to?
Only the Renren can see us.
Some kind of magic creatures,
but apparently,
only I can see them!
The Prodigious is mine,
King Cash!
We are the Renling,
the spirits of human values.
Each of us can turn you
into a different animal,
if you are worthy
of the virtues it represents.
If you want me, Tang Tang,
the Renling of Patience,
to turn you into a Mantis,
you must show patience.
I don't have
any patience right now!
I am Xiong Xiong,
Renling of Calm!
‐ Calm? Is this a joke?
‐ Calm as a bear.
Big and strong like a bear.
Xiong!
‐ All right!
‐ Thanks... Uh...
Lady Bear, apparently. For now!
Lucky charm!
What are you supposed
to do with that?
I don't know yet.
Tang!
OK, I'm starting
to get the hang of it!
Xiong!
She!
We've gotta destroy his fan
in order to de‐akumatize him!
Got it! Long!
‐ What's wrong?
‐ I should be able
to turn into a dragon
and gain control
of natural elements.
I'd love to electrify his armor
but I can't transform!
The power of the dragon is
the most powerful of them all.
Your intentions must be noble
and just if you aim to use it.
Of course
my intentions are just!
I want revenge on the guy
who destroyed my life!
Revenge is the opposite
of the values of the Dragon.
Your judgment
and intentions are clouded.
Revenge isn't
the same thing as justice!
Then I'll find another way
to defeat him! Hou!
‐ No!
‐ Who would have thought?
The Prodigious
and your Miraculous,
both in one day.
Cataclysm!
No!
Where's my money?
It's just you against us three
Hawk Moth! It's over.
You mean you're over.
Yan Luo Shi, I am Hawk Moth.
Surely, you're not going to let
a girl who mistakes revenge
for justice become
the holder of your Prodigious?
Like Yama,
the King of the Infernal,
I will cause
carnage and destruction
until she returns
the jewel to me.
We've gotta break the ball,
the akuma's inside!
Fear, humans!
Adrien. No, not the Bund!
Yan Luo Shi, stop,
or I'll remove your pow ‐‐
I take orders from no one!
OK...
Is this bad news or good news?
Let's recharge
and meet up to think of a plan.
Aaah!
Ying!
Hou!
Ma!
It's all my fault.
Give me back the Prodigious!
You are not worthy of it!
‐ He's right.
‐ No!
You alone can defeat him.
Only the power of the dragon
can reach the akumatized object
‐ inside of him.
‐ I wish I could use
the power of the dragon,
but I am not worthy.
‐ You can do this.
‐ No.
I can't do anything right.
‐ No, wait!
‐ Ying!
We don't have a choice.
I'll try to use my power on him!
Cat Noir, no!
Cataclysm!
No!
(Sobbing)
Fei...
Marinette?
I'm sorry I couldn't
forgive you earlier.
No, I don't deserve
your forgiveness.
I lied to you, I stole from you,
and everything that's happening
is because of me.
My father would be sad to see
how miserably I have failed.
I know that you were just trying
to do the right thing.
Yes. But I failed
to follow my father's values.
He would never have devoted
all his energy
to seeking revenge.
He'd have kept on
doing good around him.
Then you know
what you have to do.
My Prodigious!
Long!
Aaah!
Mei Shi!
Stop destroying everything!
Tikki, spots on!
Lucky charm!
Perfect!
Calm down, Mei Shi!
I don't want to hurt you.
I'm not here to destroy you
or to get revenge.
I'm here to save you and to
bring you back to your senses!
I'm not Mei Shi any more!
I'm Yan Luo Shi!
I did a little shopping!
Red with black spots? Strange
pattern for a Chinese vase!
This isn't a Chinese vase,
it's the solution
to our problem!
Kinda like a giant pill!
To be swallowed
with a lot of water,
if you get my drift.
Absolutely!
Yan Luo Shi!
You're finally giving me back
what's mine?
Yes. But first,
you should have a big drink
of water
to cool down.
(Vomits)
Voilà!
No more evil‐doing for you,
little akuma!
Time to de‐evilize!
Gotcha!
Bye‐bye, little butterfly!
What happened? You were able to
access the power of the dragon?
I had some help.
BOTH: Pound it!
Huh?
I am the one
who did all of that?
What a terrible
violation of humanity.
Don't worry.
We'll fix everything for you.
Miraculous Ladybug!
Huh?
Kitty!
You focused on the greater good
and let go of your revenge.
You now possess all
the required values of humanity.
The Prodigious is in good hands
with you, Renren.
Wow!
Come on,
let's wipe the slate clean!
How much do you want?
Hold on, hold on!
We can talk this out, right?
You destroyed
my father's school,
made me an orphan
and forced me to steal for you.
You caused me to betray
all the ancestral values
that my father had taught me.
From the beginning,
you have always been
the source of my misfortune!
And for what? Money!
There are no words
to describe what you are.
But today, I will...
let justice take its course.
‐ Well done, Fei!
‐ Here's to a true, wise Renren!
About time! I was wondering when
you'd finally put it back on!
ALL: Mei Shi?
You thought that was
the end of my mission?
It was only the beginning!
Ladybug, Cat Noir,
thank you for your help.
Now we only need
to find Marinette!
Yes, that's right!
We've gotta... find Marinette!
Don't worry! I brought her
to safety during the battle.
Ying!
How about a little trip
to the Shanghai courthouse?
So, we're going home?
Sure. Why not?
I mean, only if you insist.
Say, which direction
would be the shortest way
to go around the world? Across
the Arctic, or the Antarctic?
Oh! What a fascinating question!
It so happens
I've always wondered myself,
but never had the chance
to find out!
You know what?
We should do it right now!
And next time we see each other,
in Paris,
‐ we can check our stop watches!
‐ That's an excellent idea!
‐ I'll go this way!
‐ Then I'll go that way!
‐ See you soon!
‐ Woohoo!
Phew!
You know, on your birthday,
it's a tradition
that you try to slurp a long
noodle without breaking it,
as it represents longevity!
(Laughter)
In China, your 60th birthday is
often the first you celebrate.
What? You've never celebrated
your birthday before?
Never. And I'm very happy to do
it for the first time with you
‐ and your boyfriend Adrien.
‐ BOTH: Uh, we're just friends!
Anyway...
Come on, open your gift.
(Door bell rings)
Sorry,
we didn't mean to scare you.
We just wanted
to give this back.
Ah! My kwam...
My homemade necklace!
Thank you. Thank you!
Let your friends in!
An accordion?
It's a nod to Sabine,
Marinette's mom.
I raised her.
I've always told her
how I dreamed
of playing the accordion.
But I never took the time.
I know how to play if you want!
Congratulations, Marinette!
It seems like you have found
the magic ingredient after all.
I think if someone's
the magic ingredient,
it's definitely
sister Marinette!
‐ Is it OK if I call you sister?
‐ It's more than OK, sister Fei.
How do you say it in Mandarin?
(Laughter)
Oh, no! What did I say?
It's too embarrassing
to translate, Marinette!
If you wanted, back in Paris,
I could teach you some Mandarin.
Badly. I mean, gladly!
Amazesome! Argh! Mmm...
Sometimes even her English
sounds weird, right?
MARINETTE: Coming to China,
I've found so much more
than I'd ever hoped for.
An amazing uncle,
a new friend...
and a new Mandarin teacher.
Ah!