[Girls Planet 999]
[First survivor announcement]
[The first survival announcement]
[The first survivor announcement that
decides their survival and elimination]
of Girls Planet 999 begins now!
[When we decided on our parts,]
[Who will survive]
we only had one chance each.
Don't be sad.
[and who will leave?]
♫ How you dare ♫
[I want to survive for sure.]
Do you want to go home?
[Who will stay in Girls Planet 999 to
continue chasing their dream to debut?]
[I don't want to.]
♫ Oh, yeah ♫
[I want to survive no matter what.]
[I want to stay.]
[It's not over until it's over.]
[I think I have to go home.]
Thank you so much.
Planet TOP9. Who will take first place?
[Who is the first Planet TOP9
voted by Planet Guardians?]
Please show us.
[This was filmed in compliance
with the COVID-19 prevention guidelines.]
[All the cast and staff in the recording
got PCR tests in advance.]
[Let's clean.]
-Ready.
-Go.
There's so much dust.
-So much.
-I know.
Be clean.
My back is about to crook.
I cleaned too hard.
Clean, clear, and confident.
Excuse me.
Perfect.
It's me.
Stop.
♫ The same dream ♫
[How about we play the Strawberry Game?]
[Sure.]
Two strawberries.
[Thank you all for cleaning.]
[We prepared some snacks.]
[Please move to the cafeteria.]
-Now?
-Cafeteria?
But I'm already having snacks.
[We prepared some snacks.]
Okay.
Snacks!
Let's go have snacks!
What snacks are there?
-[Snacks?]
-[Let's go!]
[Is there cake?]
-Snacks.
Snacks!
Give us snacks.
Where are our snacks?
Please give us snacks.
Hello.
-How are you guys?
-Good!
Now that I'm standing here
I'm a bit nervous. I like it.
I came because
I realized there isn't much time left
for us to see each other.
I also bought some snacks
for you guys to have while rehearsing.
Come up one by one
and I'll hand out the presents.
-Great work. Good job.
-Thank you.
You can do it! Great job.
What happened to your wrist? Does it hurt?
-It's fine.
-It is?
Thank you.
-Great job, you guys.
-Thank you.
Me!
Okay. I'm coming.
-Here you go.
-Thank you!
-I'll see you guys at the next shoot.
-Thank you.
Look.
I can't dare to touch it.
There's even a card.
Ta-da!
There are chocolate cookies.
They are so good!
I'm not going to eat it.
It's good.
-It's good.
-It's pretty, right?
-Thank you.
Hey, guys!
-Hello!
I'm going to go now.
No!
Today is a very happy day for me
because I got to meet you guys.
-I'll see you at the next shoot.
-Thank you!
Bye!
Goodbye.
I wrote a letter for you.
-For me?
-Yes.
-For real?
-Yes!
-A present for you?
-What?
Wow.
Thank you.
This is important.
It helps relieve stress.
Yes!
-Wei!
That's Wei.
"Dear Ye Young."
"I prepared this present for you
to help you relieve stress."
"I used the prettiest photo I could find.
What do you think?"
Done!
Yes!
This is my album.
And one for you, Tzu Ling.
Only I have this album.
Hey, this is big so I like it.
-Oh my.
-I'm the present.
That's so cool.
"I'm enough for a present."
"Please accept it."
-Yes!
-That's funny.
-Amazing, right?
-I'll read it.
"Dear Cheuk Ying."
"We share the same dream."
Ye Seo!
"Let's survive"
"and debut together."
Let's do it!
"We may have to part ways soon."
No, we'll never part.
I think I'm going to cry.
Oh, no.
Don't cry.
"I want to be with Da Yeon
when I perform on my debut stage."
"Even if I don't get to debut,"
"I want to see Da Yeon debut,"
"because I know she can do it."
Thank you.
I've never seen Tammy cry.
What if you guys don't make it
because of me?
That won't happen.
Just...
I'm sorry I'm not popular.
You're in 4th place. C group, 4th place.
Be confident.
"When we performed 'Maria' together,"
["it was cute, cool, and awesome."]
"I believe it's fate"
"that we got to become a team."
She's crying.
-Why...
-Why are you crying?
It's okay.
We'll be happy
no matter what the result is.
Right. We're happy.
I'm grateful that you're in my cell.
-We can do it.
-Yes.
Let's do this.
Hikaru.
Why were you the only one doing that?
Wow. Is that us?
We're so charismatic.
-"Mic Drop."
I look fat.
[I look fat.]
-Oh my.
-Look at us.
Oh no.
In 3, 2, 1.
We are Smile Cell.
Lucky Seven!
Oh, it's the TOP9 seat.
Oh, I'm so nervous.
It's me.
-In 3, 2, 1.
-Two, two, U.
-In 3, 2.
We're Teams "Yes or Yes".
-Oh my.
-How cute.
Is that her?
I'm getting so nervous.
I'm scared.
Hello. I'm Planet Master Yeo Jin Goo.
-Hello!
Two months ago, 99 girls
from Korea, China, and Japan
who speak different languages
and who have different cultures
gathered here with
the same dream of becoming a K-pop star.
But unfortunately,
someone will have to leave Girls Planet.
At the first survival announcement,
a cell will either survive or
be eliminated together.
Who will stay and who will go
among the 33 cells
will be decided by the votes of
the Planet Guardians.
From 164 countries all over the world
we had 39,360,000
and 509 votes.
Numerous Planet Guardians
supported and cheered on for your dreams.
Thank you all.
Thank you.
That's a lot.
Those votes will decide
the ranks from 1 to 17.
Only 17 cells will survive
and remain in Girls Planet.
But those who are eliminated
could still have a chance
by the masters' Planet Pass.
Among those who are eliminated,
one per group K, C, and J
will survive with the Planet Pass.
And the five teams
who won the Connect Mission
received a benefit during the global vote.
Let's see
how the benefit affected
the girls' survival and elimination.
Also, the new Planet TOP9
changed by voting
will be revealed.
Who will have the honor of
becoming the first TOP9 member
that is solely selected
by Planet Guardians' votes?
The great story of the girls.
The first survival announcement
of Girls Planet 999.
It begins now.
The first survival announcement
of Girls Planet 999.
Who will have to leave
and who will get to stay?
I will now reveal the first survival cell
of Girls Planet 999.
Right away?
Right away.
Before I announce
the last place, 17th cell...
My goodness. Why?
What?
-"Before"?
-What's going on?
-What is it?
I will announce the 16th cell first.
-Seriously.
-I knew it. It's Mnet.
That's so cruel.
We placed 16th.
We should be around here somewhere.
I'm getting goosebumps.
The cell that placed 16th
received the voting benefit
from the last Connect Mission.
Is that us?
-Is it us?
-Could it be us?
Do you think that's us?
-Who is it?
I have no idea.
I hope we placed 16th.
-What now?
-It's going to be okay.
And this cell includes
a girl who played the main vocalist
in the Connect Mission.
That's not us.
Is it Bo Ra's cell?
-Yes. That's right.
-Bo Ra.
♫ You see if it's love
you will know right away ♫
♫ You will notice ♫
-No.
-It's you.
There's also Hye Rim.
It's Hye Rim.
♫ I don't know what you'll choose,
so I got you two choices ♫
The survival cell will be on the screen.
Who will be the first cell to survive?
The 16th cell survived
through the global voting.
The music...
This music... Everyone's hands are sweaty.
The 16th cell is...
Please show us.
It's coming.
Kim Bo Ra, Zhang Luo Fei,
- and Hayase Hana.
-Congratulations.
What? My goodness.
I never imagined this.
-Why are you crying?
-Congratulations.
-Don't cry.
-Thank you.
-Congratulations.
-Good work.
I love you.
This cell received
the double vote benefit.
The benefit must've helped them
-That's possible.
-place 16th.
My goodness.
The benefit is really important.
Congratulations.
-Congratulations.
I will now announce the next cell.
The cell that placed 15th.
Unless we placed 15th, we're at stake.
We're unlikely to make it.
-My goodness.
-My gosh.
15th place.
This cell chose E.B.S.
for the Connect Mission.
They chose a boy group's song
[and presented a wonderful performance
on the stage.]
♫ Break and face it ♫
E.B.S.
Please.
This cell does not have a member
who was in charge of a killer part
or a leader in the Connect Mission.
What?
-Ye Eun. Isn't that you?
-No.
-I think that's you.
-Maybe them.
-I think it's you.
-It's them.
Who is it?
Who will get to enjoy the joy of survival?
The 15th cell.
Please show us.
Congratulations.
-See?
-Congratulations.
It's An Jeong Min, Wang Ya Le,
and Fujimoto Ayaka.
Please get on to the stage.
I will continue the announcement.
Next is the 14th cell.
We placed 14th last time.
But what if it's not us?
Please let it be us.
The K Group girl in this cell
performed Apink's song
in the Planet Demo Stage.
♫ Mr. Chu
Right on the lips ♫
♫ Plant a sweet kiss ♫
Apink?
Hye Won?
-Ye Eun?
Why does it always apply to me?
Also, this cell received
the winning benefit
in the Connect Mission.
That's Hye Won.
It's either you or Hye Won.
-Right here.
-Here.
I don't know. I can never guess.
The 14th cell that survived
through the global voting.
Please show us.
The 14th cell.
This cell received
the double vote benefit.
Please get on to the stage.
Follow me soon.
-Okay?
-Yes.
Hurry up.
Stop crying and follow them.
Thank you.
Why are you so sad?
Let's listen to the three cells
that survived in Girls Planet.
First of all, I'd like to thank
the Planet Guardians
who cheered and supported us
to show the next performance.
Ji Yoon and the members of Our Season
who I performed with.
I love you so much and thank you.
Dear Planet Guardians. I love you.
Let's listen to the 15th cell.
Thank you very much, Planet Guardians
who voted for us.
Please continue to support us.
I'd like to thank Planet Guardians
for giving me another chance to perform.
And my Apink members.
Get here as fast as you can, okay?
Thank you so much, everyone.
Liang Jiao.
Do you think you can continue
with your sister?
I'm not crying because I survived.
I'm crying because I'm afraid
my sister might not survive.
Go, Liang Jiao.
The survivors of Girls Planet.
Congratulations.
Please move to the seats
according to your rankings.
Next is the 13th cell
that survived in Girls Planet.
My heart aches so much.
This girl's Planet Demo Stage performance
recorded over five million views.
What? Five million?
-"BOOMBAHYAH"?
-Is it "BOOMBAHYAH"?
It's "BOOMBAHYAH".
♫ BOOMBAHYAH ♫
Isn't it "Crazy"?
Did "Crazy" record over five million?
♫ C-R-A-Z-Y, copy me ♫
And this cell showed their cute charms
performing "YES or YES".
-Se In.
-Chae Yun?
Se In or Chae Yun.
-Oh, Se In.
-Se In?
It's Chae Yun.
-It's Chae Yun.
-It could be you.
Ririka.
Why is everyone mentioning us?
-Don't look at us.
I will announce the 13th cell
that survived.
I'm scared.
I'm so afraid.
The 13th cell.
Please show us.
We made it.
-I'm not going to cry.
-It's Lee Chae Yun,
Leung Cheuk Ying, and Kishida Ririka.
-Let's walk fast.
-Walk fast.
Walk fast.
-Thank you.
-I love you guys.
Next is the 12th cell.
This cell
performed "YES or YES"
during the Connect Mission.
And in this cell,
there is one member
who took the killer part.
It's Ji Won or Do Ah.
♫ Choose between the two, yes or yes ♫
♫ Choose between the two ♫
- ♫ Yes or yes ♫
The 12th cell
will advance to the next mission.
The survivors are...
Please.
It must be Do Ah.
It might be us.
-We weren't as good.
-Right.
It's Huh Ji Won, Chia Yi,
and Yamauchi Moana.
This cell received twice their votes
with the benefit they earned.
-Congrats.
-Congratulations.
Next is
the 11th cell that will remain
on Girls Planet.
One of the survivors
in this cell
is the youngest member of a group.
Myah.
Who's the youngest member of C Group?
And this cell earned the benefit
during the Connect Mission.
-It's either Myah,
-Myah.
Chae Hyun, or Ayana.
I'll announce the 11th cell
chosen by the Planet Guardians
all over the world.
If it's Myah, that means
she went up so much.
She received three times the votes
and she even did the killer part.
Please reveal the 11th cell.
It's Guinn Myah, Yang Zi Ge,
and Kamimoto Kotone.
This cell received three times the votes
with the benefit they earned.
-It's crazy.
-Please come up to the stage.
Let's hear from the three surviving cells.
I'm truly grateful to the Planet Guardians
for giving us a chance to perform
in the next round.
I love them so much.
And I love my cell so much.
-Gosh.
-Me too.
I'm really grateful
to be able to stand here right now.
Planet Guardians, thank you so, so much.
And Chia Yi, Ji Won.
I'm really happy
to have been your team.
Thank you as always.
Dear Planet Guardians,
please show a lot of love to the girls.
-Myah.
"Pretty U" guys,
thank you
for being so nice to me.
I love you.
I'm done.
Please move to your seats.
Congratulations on becoming survivors.
I'll look forward to seeing
greater performances in the next mission.
Congratulations.
The first survivor announcement.
Next up is the tenth cell.
Who was in tenth place last time?
Oh, please.
The K Group girl in this cell
performed "POP/STARS" by K/DA
during the Planet Demo Stage.
♫ Ain't nobody bringing us ♫
♫ Down, down, down ♫
♫ They could try but we're gonna
wear the crown ♫
♫ You could go ♫
Don't cry already. Why are you crying?
-I don't think it's me.
-Don't cry.
We were ranked 9th and 10th.
-Ninth and tenth.
-Right.
We were ranked 9th and 10th.
At the crossroads
of survival and elimination,
the tenth cell has survived,
and they are...
I can't stand to watch this.
Please. Let it be us.
If we don't make it now,
we won't be able to survive.
Don't cry.
Please reveal the tenth cell.
-It's you.
-Reina.
It's you!
-Choi Ye Young, Chen Hsin Wei, and Reina.
Congratulations.
Please come up to the stage.
-Ye Young.
-Congratulations.
Next is the meaningful number
for Girls Planet 999.
Guess what.
The ninth cell.
That's right. It's the ninth cell
that survived on Girls Planet.
I'm having low expectations now.
One of them is a member of the team
that won first place
in the Signal song evaluation.
Oh, gosh.
-Hikaru should be...
-Hikaru's place might be higher.
-It might not be us.
-Oh, my.
It might be them.
I'll announce the ninth cell
that will stay in the competition
and continue with another mission.
-Congrats.
-It's Kim Da Yeon, Wu Tammy,
-and Sakurai Miu.
-Congrats.
-Da Yeon.
-Congratulations.
Please come up to the stage.
Let's hear from the survivors
this time as well.
When other girls were called,
I felt like there was no place for us.
So I didn't get any hopes up.
But I'm really grateful
to the Planet Guardians.
I hope they keep supporting us. Thank you.
And Chen Hsin Wei.
He's ugly.
He's an ugly man.
-Did you say an ugly man?
-Yes.
I'm sorry.
Why?
Don't be.
I've never thought I was handsome.
No.
You're a handsome man.
I mean it.
Thank you.
-It's a joke.
-You're really handsome.
I'm joking. Don't worry.
Let's hear from the ninth cell.
I'm so grateful and happy
that we get to perform again
with another chance.
Thank you.
Up to the ninth cell has been revealed.
Before moving onto the next cell,
we've prepared a video as a break
for the Planet Guardians
who must've watched it nervously.
-Are you curious?
-What is it?
-Let's watch together.
-What?
-A fashion show?
A fashion show?
"My head hurts."
-"My stomach hurts."
-"Hurts."
I don't see anyone.
She's so pretty.
Have you been well?
-Yes!
Do you want to know
why you're gathered here today?
-For a fashion show!
If you're an idol,
you must never leave this out.
It's fashion.
By the way, I'm here with someone today.
Please come out.
Who is it?
My gosh.
[I'm a huge fan of his.]
[I couldn't breathe.]
[Fuka told me to stop staring at him.]
Hello, it's nice to meet you.
I'm a model, Jung Hyuk.
I'm a model, Bae Yoon Young.
Jung Hyuk, tell me.
How will Planet Fashion Queen proceed?
Nine people who were a team during
the Connect Mission will be a team.
[Please choose one model, one stylist,]
[and lastly, one who will be
in charge of hair and makeup.]
The models will have 30 minutes
to get changed and hair and makeup done.
Two teams who stand out the most
will be chosen as
the Planet Fashion Queen.
And everyone in the two teams
will get a free pass for the day.
Wow, the free pass is...
Free pass. I wanted it so badly.
♫ Freedom! ♫
How will you pick two winning teams?
The first winning team will be
the Best Dresser Team who has
an outstanding fashion sense and
expresses the current trend the best.
And the second winning team,
will be who expresses an
out-of-the-world fashion sense.
It'll be the Worst Dresser Team.
-Then we...
-We'll look cool.
[Honestly, I thought
it would be better to]
go for the Worst Dresser Team.
[I wanted it so bad.]
Go, girls!
Let's do this.
Stand by.
-Do well.
-Okay.
Let's do this!
-Let's go! Stand by.
-Let's do this!
-Three, two, one.
-Two, one.
-Go!
Hey.
I think I can do better.
Oh my gosh.
What?
Should I go up like this?
Say you have them because it's hot.
Our model is so cool.
You look good.
There's not much time left.
-It's okay.
-I don't know. Just run!
Try this one.
-No, not like that!
-Sorry.
We'll now start
the Planet Queen Fashion Show.
I'm so excited.
So pretty.
She's so good.
[It felt like I was at
a real fashion show.]
[The vibe... It wasn't the Sumomo I knew.]
When you first walked out,
you did so well that I thought
I better take it seriously.
Thank you.
Wow.
She has really great proportions.
Power walking.
I want to give you more points.
You almost sprained your ankle here.
Most people get startled
when that happens,
but you handled it professionally.
You went back to posing,
and your level of confidence was the best.
Joung Min!
Your body shape makes the clothes shine.
I was shocked
[when you took off the jacket.]
[Everything was perfect.]
You should join my agency.
You can pick the one you want.
Why are you trying to steal our talents?
We need stars in the model industry too.
We need them too.
What is this?
-Who is that?
-Wen Zhe.
Wen Zhe.
[She is usually really funny.
It was crazy.]
When I looked at you,
-I want to dress like you.
-Me too.
-Thank you.
You really have the current trend down.
Wow!
Oh my.
Wow.
[It was shocking and horrifying.]
The makeup... It was insane.
Your hair and makeup are shocking.
It's not just...
It's not just your hair and makeup.
Hello.
Gosh.
[Ji Min is normally not like that.]
She cried
with eyelashes on her cheeks.
The Best Dresser Team is...
Team 2 of "YES or YES".
The Worst Dresser Team is...
Congratulations, Team "Pretty U".
♫ Freedom ♫
Hey, why is it so dark?
It's dark.
I'm scared.
Where are we?
-What is this?
-Look!
Wow!
This is amazing!
There's Ririka here.
Raccoon Ririka.
The ears move.
♫ Baby shark ♫
-Judy Kim Ye Eun.
-Guinn Myah.
I think it'll be scary.
I'm scared.
I can't ride it. I'm not tall enough.
I might faint.
It doesn't work?
It's going up. It's going up.
Why am I here?
This is so scary.
This is not a joke.
Thanks for everything, guys.
It's fun!
It was scary.
It's pretty.
Here it goes.
I like the merry-go-round.
Hello.
This is so romantic.
We were able to see
their unexpected charms
that were different from
when they were on stage.
Next,
here is the next cell to survive.
I'll announce it.
I should stay calm.
My heart is beating so fast. I'm dying.
Of the remaining 25 cells,
only nine will survive.
Only nine.
The 17th cell.
And from the 8th to the 1st.
First, the 8th cell.
I'll announce it.
Hold hands? No, yes? Not now?
Not now.
-You sure?
-Yes.
I'm so nervous.
I think it'll be Su Yeon.
I hope it's Su Yeon.
Yes. Me too.
Let's hold hands.
I wonder who's eighth.
Who's eighth?
Not us.
-Not us.
-In the
Connect Mission...
It's us if he says "Yes or Yes".
Killer part?
-The benefit
-Went to her.
did not go to her, but she survived.
-Do A?
I think it's one of us.
"The Eve"?
We didn't get any benefit points.
Bahiyyih?
-It could be one of us.
-Yes.
And the girl in this cell,
during the Connect Mission...
-Killer part.
She led the team.
It's Zi Yin!
We were both leaders.
Ya Ning and you?
-Let's do this.
-Thank you.
-She was a leader too.
-There's one over there.
For us...
Ya Ning? Xu Zi Yin?
So hard.
Which cell will survive?
I don't know.
Please show us the eighth cell!
Oh no...
What do we do?
We did it!
Wow.
-Good job.
-Great work.
You did great.
-"POP/STARS".
-It's 10, 9, 8.
It's 10, 9, 8.
KDA, yes!
This is amazing.
Kim Su Yeon, Fu Ya Ning, Nonaka Shana.
The seventh cell that survived
on Girls Planet.
Let's hold hands now.
Okay.
I think Do A will be 7th
and Chae Hyun will be 6th.
Because of the benefit points.
They need to call us now.
If not, we won't have a spot.
Do Ah.
I think Chae Hyun will be higher up.
I want to go up there quickly.
Don't you agree?
Maybe he'll go, "'Fiesta' Team 1!"
That's us.
I'm so nervous.
I think it'll be either Bahiyyih or Do Ah.
In the Connect Mission, this cell...
"YES or YES"?
-"YES or YES"?
-"Performed 'YES or YES'."
"This cell performed 'YES or YES'."
This cell performed "Fiesta".
Us?
Is it us?
-Gosh.
-"Fiesta".
My heart's beating so fast. "Fiesta".
♫ When flowers bloom in all colors
and petals scatter ♫
♫ The fiesta reaches the climax ♫
♫ Fiesta,
I swallowed the sun in my heart ♫
Ji Min.
It could be her.
Hold on.
The seventh cell to survive
by global votes.
I can't wait to find out about this one.
Please show us.
So cool.
-Congratulations.
-Good job.
Huening Bahiyyih.
-Why are they so low?
-No idea.
Because of the benefit?
Next is the sixth cell that survived.
Please.
Oh, no.
-There aren't many seats left.
-I know.
Let's hold hands.
My stomach hurts.
Gosh.
The K Group member of this cell
may or may not have debuted
as a girl group.
-It's us.
-Let him finish.
And she has.
It's us.
Ye Seo, Do Ah, me...
It's Do Ah.
Ye Seo debuted too.
-Oh, please.
-Don't do this.
If we don't place sixth,
it'll be over for us.
I really want to place sixth.
What do we do?
-I feel like I might die.
-The sixth cell.
Wait.
Oh, gosh.
Please show us.
Come on out!
It's really...
Right, it's us.
-What a relief.
-I know.
-Do Ah.
-Good job.
-Gosh.
-Good.
I'm so glad.
Let's hear from the girls who survived.
I'd like to give sincere thanks
to the Planet Guardians
for voting for us.
A total of 99 girls.
I don't feel so happy
because I'll have to say goodbye
to some of the girls today.
I think
we're already a team
who performed "O.O.O" together.
I hope we will see each other again.
We'll work harder. Thank you.
We'll work harder,
so please keep supporting us.
Thank you, Planet Guardians.
They're so pretty.
I'm grateful to the Planet Masters.
The 99 of us went through so much.
Thank you so much, girls.
We'll work harder
to show better performances.
Thank you.
The 8th, 7th, and 6th cells,
please move to your respective seats.
-Thank you.
-Oh, that.
-Lucky seven.
Good work.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5... 17.
Yes!
-I was so nervous.
-Me too.
We're safe.
Good work.
A lot of cells are still waiting
for the results.
What do I do?
I feel like I'm melting away.
These are the cells in the upper ranks.
I'll announce the 5th, 4th, and 3rd cells.
Oh, the 5th, 4th, and 3rd.
Let's make it in the top five.
First, the fifth cell.
Ye Seo.
-Ye Seo?
-Ye Seo.
-It's us!
-Us.
It's really us!
Let's go higher. Please.
-Gosh.
-During the Connect Mission,
this cell...
"Took the victory."
-Benefit.
-Benefit?
This cell performed a girl group song.
It's not us.
-Ye Seo, Ayana...
-Yu Jin.
Can't you feel my heartbeat?
Gosh, I'm nervous.
The fifth cell.
Please show us.
Ayana.
This time, it's the fourth cell.
Please.
-Ye Seo?
-Young Eun?
-Xiao Ting?
I want to win.
My heart's about to explode.
Me too.
All the other cells got the benefit
except for Su Rui Qi's cell.
-You're right.
-It could be Hikaru's cell.
-Us.
-What?
-Us?
-Us.
No!
No, we have to place higher.
It's really starting now.
I can't breathe.
This cell...
But I'm okay with taking fourth place.
-It might be Ye Seo.
-I agree.
During the Connect Mission...
-They won?
-E.B.S.
Hey.
One of them was the leader...
-It might be her or you.
-of a team.
What?
That's Mashiro and Yu Jin.
I'll work hard.
-It must be us.
-It's us.
Oh, gosh.
Who is it?
-Yu Jin's cell or...
-Mashiro.
I'll announce the fourth cell.
The fourth. This is crazy.
This makes no sense.
Please show us.
-Congratulations.
-Ye Seo.
All three of them are so pretty.
It feels...
-It feels strange.
-I know, right?
Let's move onto the top three cells
who received the biggest support
from the Planet Guardians.
I'll start with the third cell.
I'm so cold.
I'm really nervous.
Xiao Ting.
-Su Rui Qi.
-Me too.
TOP3. It's TOP3 now.
No way.
Yu Jin...
This is so neck and neck.
In this cell,
-Tell us.
-there's a girl who was in charge of...
-The killer part?
-The killer part in the Connect Mission.
-It's not us.
-Not us.
-The killer part.
-The two of us.
♫ How you like that? ♫
♫ You're going to like that ♫
♫ Break and face it ♫
♫ So they can see us ♫
Hikaru, what's with your face?
I think it's either Xiao Ting or Rui Qi.
Probably Rui Qi because of the benefit.
-I think she can win without the benefit.
-Also in this cell...
Also in this cell, there's a girl
who got first place...
-She's number one.
-Gosh.
-That's you.
-It's the two of you guys.
Both of them did.
This is so fun.
During the Signal song.
♫ The sky is open beyond the stars ♫
♫ It's time for your dreams and mine
to connect ♫
My heart's about to explode.
Here, give me your hand.
It's a fight between the two
-first-place winners.
-You're right.
So fun.
I'll announce the third cell who will make
the upper rankings.
The third cell survived
with the global voting.
It might not be us.
Please show us.
The benefit might help them get
a high ranking.
Who is it?
-Yes.
-Right.
It's us!
The benefit can't be ignored.
Let's hear from the survivors.
First, the fifth cell.
I'm thankful to Ayana who made our cell.
Great work, Yiman.
And my "YES or YES" teammates.
I'll be waiting, Hye Rim.
Sumomo and Yu Ling too.
I love you.
-Mashiro.
-Yes?
Please let us know how you feel.
We'll practice harder
and get better
to live up to your votes,
support, and expectations.
I want to thank Ye Seo and Xing Qiao.
I'm grateful
to my "Fiesta" teammates.
And Nagomi,
I'm truly grateful
that we got to do this together.
I love you.
Thank you.
Next, the third cell.
I always felt like I was a kid
lost in the woods.
I'd like to give thanks
to the production team
for giving me the chance to prove myself.
Thanks to them, I made 99 friends.
I got to make touching memories.
Also, Hikaru picked me and Rui Qi.
I'm thankful that we'll be together.
I'll work even harder from now on.
Thank you.
Please go find your seats
according to your rankings.
Congratulations.
What do we do?
Look at the view!
Now, only the cells
in the 1st, 2nd, and 17th places are left.
There are only three left.
Please say 17th place, Lee Ra Yeon.
Who will survive?
Before I continue with the announcement...
-What?
-Before that.
There is a very fun video prepared for us.
What is it?
We'll get to see the hidden sides
of the girls we couldn't see on TV before.
Planet Guardians. Let's watch together.
[-What's that?
-What's that?]
Ta-da.
What's this?
-What's that?
-What's this?
What's that?
Awards?
-Awards?
The Planet Awards?
It's a trophy.
"You are a candidate for the awards"
"the 99 girls will vote for."
-What?
What is this?
Let's check together.
-In 3, 2, 1.
"First to wake"?
-"First to wake"?
Oh, "First to wake".
-Wake up?
-I...
-Did you wake up early?
I voted for you.
That's you.
-I didn't.
-No?
You were always there for breakfast.
Kim Bo Ra.
Bo Ra's always the first one up.
She's always there alone for breakfast.
She's always
completely ready for breakfast,
[from head to toe.]
[She wakes up early, gets ready,
and comes to practice before anyone else.]
Is that you waking up?
-Yurina.
If we have to head out by 8 a.m.,
[she wakes up at 6:30 a.m. to get ready.]
Yurina wakes up about
an hour and a half before us.
[She gets ready and grabs breakfast.]
I wonder who it'll be.
Yurina, you win
the First to Wake Up Award!
-Congratulations.
-It's nice.
It's pretty.
Which award do you think it is?
I know what it is!
You know what it is?
Is this for the prettiest?
I know what it is too!
We're right.
Let's receive it together.
Okay.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Neither of you is letting it go.
Can't we both be the winners?
-Hello.
Xiao Ting is pretty.
Xiao Ting is so pretty!
[She's so pretty.]
[It's the kind of beauty
that makes you smile.]
[She's so pretty.]
[Ji Won has the look I like the most.]
I'm seriously with her all the time,
[and she's constantly pretty.]
[I can't get used to it.
Every time I look at her, I'm amazed.]
[I'd say Ji Won is the prettiest.]
Thank you.
I mean it. You're really pretty.
It's all yours.
Let's share it.
We did it.
Bye.
-"Best Makeup Transformation Award".
-Transformation.
What?
Without any makeup on,
[she looks as innocent as a baby.]
[But with makeup, she looks fierce.]
[She's like a different person.]
♫ An odor to a nice smell ♫
♫ Mic, mic, bungee ♫
♫ Mic, mic, bungee,
bright light ♫
[Amazing.]
She always wears glasses
when she doesn't have makeup on.
[Then she seems kind of quirky.]
[But with makeup,
she's like a different person.]
Yes!
Thank you.
It's still an award.
This could be a weapon
if it's held this way.
-"The most popular".
-Okay.
Most popular? That's us, of course!
Even I think I'm really popular.
I think that about me too.
-Thank you.
-Congratulations.
♫ Congratulations ♫
She's hardly in her dorm.
[She's so cheerful and outgoing.]
[She never seems shy.]
[She always introduces herself first,]
[befriends them,]
[and loves to talk too.]
-We're...
-We're popular.
Myah's the youngest
[and full of energy.]
[She's so cute]
[when she approaches me.]
Since you won the Cutie Fatale Award,
show us your cutie fatale charm!
Show us.
I love you.
That's so cute.
-This way.
-Amazing.
Thank you.
That was fun!
The Planet Awards certainly showed us
the participants' many charms.
Congratulations to all the winners.
You won awards.
Congratulations.
It's time to reveal the top cell that won
the most votes from Planet Guardians.
I will now announce
the top cell.
-First place?
-The top cell first?
What?
It's unbelievable.
I want to place first.
Which cell will take first place?
We'll first meet two contenders
on the screen.
Which one?
It's obvious.
Yu Jin?
Yu Jin.
[Yu Jin was in first place
in the interim evaluation.]
[Yes, that's true.]
I'm not sure.
[Yu Jin was ranked first.]
[Shen Xiao Ting was second.]
First and second. They're both good.
Both cells are ready.
Let's reveal the first contending cell.
Oh, I can't look.
Let's see it!
-What?
-Amazing.
I knew it.
That's amazing.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
-Congratulations, May.
-Thank you.
Top place. That's high.
I knew it'd be them.
[Their energy is different.]
Let's check the 2nd 1st-place candidate.
Xiao Ting.
Yurina.
Come here.
Wait a minute.
Show us the 2nd 1st-place candidate.
Let's go.
As expected.
-Congrats.
I'm so jealous.
It's cool to see
the 1st and 2nd-place cells compete.
Yurina.
Nice.
-Right.
-We're the best.
-They're both Team "How You Like That"?
-The legendary team.
♫ How you like that? ♫
♫ You're going to like that ♫
Impressive. They were in the same team.
They're rivals now.
These top one candidates
got the most votes from
the Planet Guardians all over the world.
One of them will take 1st place
and the other, 2nd place.
They're the best.
-Both of them must be happy.
-I know.
-Cai Bing.
-Yes.
Do you think your cell
can become the top cell?
Are we confident?
-Yes.
-Yes, we can be the top cell.
How cool.
They topped the interim evaluation
after all.
Okay.
Shen Xiao Ting, what do you think?
-Oh, she's so pretty!
-How pretty.
She's so pretty.
It doesn't matter which rank,
they're both great rankings for us.
Any result is good for us.
She's too pretty, it's unfair.
I'd be happy with second place too.
Now, let's check who will take the honor
of placing first
in the first global voting.
Gosh.
It will be revealed on the screen.
Oh, my gosh.
I can't stand watching this.
Even I'm nervous.
We need popcorn for this.
According to the result, the top cell
-received 2,929,629 votes.
-What?
-That's crazy.
-How many digits?
The 2nd cell received 2,649,735 points.
The difference is 279,894 points.
Gosh.
How did they get so many votes?
It's crazy.
That's inviolable.
They're the top cell indeed.
Between the two cells,
who received the biggest number of votes
from the Planet Guardians?
-I can't even guess.
-I have no idea.
♫ Choose between the two, 1st or 2nd ♫
They must be so nervous.
Please show us.
Who is it?
Good job.
Congrats.
Indeed.
I'm so proud of them both.
-Hey!
-Congrats.
Thank you.
They're the top-ranking survivors.
Let's hear from them.
Well...
First off, dear Planet Guardians,
thank you so much
for voting and supporting us.
Congrats!
And my "How You Like That" teammates.
Where is she? Yeon Gyung.
I really appreciate your hard work.
I love you.
Me too.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for letting me seize
this precious opportunity.
Thank you, master.
Yu Jin, thank you so much
for picking me.
I love you.
Me too.
Wen Zhe, happy birthday.
Gosh.
Let's hear from the second cell too.
I'd like to give thanks
to the Planet Guardians for letting us
take such a high place.
Thank you so much.
Ji A.
Make sure you make it
so we can perform together.
I love you.
All 99 girls make me cry.
Why am I crying?
The 2nd and 1st cells.
Congratulations once again.
Please move to your seats now.
They're so cool.
The 1st to 3rd cells are so cool.
Now, only one cell
remains to survive.
I'm most curious about the 17th.
The last 17th cell had the closest call,
but they get to survive and stay.
This must be so nerve-wracking.
So many need to survive.
I'm not giving up,
but I feel like I should practice
accepting reality.
The 17th-place candidates...
There are two candidates?
Let's check the candidates on the screen.
Oh, my goodness.
I should just relax.
The first candidate.
Gosh.
Please show us.
-Ye Eun?
-Jeong Min?
Hye Rim? Isn't she popular?
Xu Ruo Wei.
Oh, Wen Zhe. Please.
-Ji A...
-Ji A.
-Zhou Xin Yu.
-Please.
So many of them.
Please show us.
Who? Please.
My heart is about to drop.
Gosh, Ji A.
Ji A.
Don't cry.
I hope Ji A makes it.
-Ji A was so good.
-Right.
The 1st candidate for the 17th cell
is Ji A, Xin Yu, Moka's cell.
Let's check the second candidate
on the screen.
This is so scary.
Hye Rim got the benefit
through the "YES or YES" performance.
♫ Choose one already, yes or yes ♫
Team 1 of "YES or YES".
Congratulations.
I think it's plausible.
Sun Woo's cell also got the benefit.
♫ Just remember this ♫
But their interim ranking was too low.
I have no idea.
Please show us
the second candidate.
Wen Zhe's face!
The 2nd candidate for the 17th cell
is Se In, Wen Zhe, and Momoko's cell.
Please come up the stage.
This is totally unexpected.
This is crazy.
-It's either one of them.
-Please.
It's neck and neck.
It's so hard.
The last cell to survive and stay.
They are the candidates for the 17th cell.
One of these cells will become
the 17th cell and continue
to pursue their dreams.
Oh, my.
The other will become the 18th cell
and sadly be eliminated.
Oh, it's so cruel.
The two cells must be desperately hoping
for their cell to survive.
Wen Zhe,
do you think your cell will survive?
I...
I want to survive.
The one last cell to be called.
The 17th cell will be revealed
on the screen.
Gosh.
Oh, my gosh.
The surviving 17th cell
and the eliminated 18th cell
were distinguished by 69,234 votes.
What, 69,000?
That's quite a difference.
Yoon Ji A, Zhou Xin Yu, and Shima Moka
threatened the team
[that had the biggest number
of TOP9 candidates]
with their powerful performance
during the Connect Mission.
Let it be Ji A, please.
Ji A...
Kim Se In, Wen Zhe, and Okazaki Momoko
[showed off their skills
as good as the winning team]
[and made an impressive performance]
during the Connect Mission.
Who will it be between the two?
Let it be Wen Zhe.
One of the 2 candidates
will place 17th and survive.
The other will place 18th and drop out.
Who do you think will win?
-I have no idea.
-Right?
The 17th cell.
I can't stand watching it.
Please.
Please show us.
It's so nerve-racking.
I'm sorry.
That's too bad.
Congratulations! The 17th cell is
Yoon Ji A, Zhou Xin Yu, and Shima Moka.
Without "How You Like That" Team 2...
Our leader Seung Eun guided all of us.
And the expressive Tzu Ling did so well.
So we were able to make it this far.
I want us to continue together. I'm sorry.
Planet Guardians, thank you so much.
The 18th cell is eliminated by one rank.
The Planet Guardians that got us to 18th,
thank you so much.
I'm sorry for making sad birthday
for Wen Zhe.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
[It's always sad.]
Due to the votes from Planet Guardians,
51 girls survived
and 48 were eliminated.
I'll now announce the stars of Planet Pass
the 48 are desperately hoping for.
Who received another chance
by the masters' mutual consent?
[Who will survive?]
Out of the three contestants
who'll survive,
the first survivor is
from J Group.
This person has
performed a song by OH MY GIRL.
-OH MY GIRL?
-Fuko?
♫ I am now sure ♫
-Oh, Ruan.
-Ruan was in "Pretty U" Team.
She sang OH MY GIRL's song
during Planet Demo Stage.
♫ My heart skipped a beat ♫
The first survivor who is given
a second chance.
Who will survive
with the Planet Pass?
-Ruan?
-Ruan.
[Fuko. Hayashi Fuko.]
It's J Group's
Ikema Ruan.
Good job.
-I'm sorry.
-Why are you sorry? You did well.
-No. You did well.
Good job.
When I saw Ikema Ruan,
I thought someone like her
should be a celebrity.
She put in a lot of effort from the side
for the benefit of her team.
It was touching.
Continuing on, I'll announce
the next Planet Pass winner.
I will announce the name.
-She's from C Group.
-Xu Ruo Wei?
-Let it be Wen Zhe.
-Wen Zhe.
Let it be Wen Zhe please.
The Planet Pass survivor from C Group.
[-Please.
-Please.]
During Connect Mission...
Did she receive a benefit?
She was not able to receive the benefit.
That's Wen Zhe.
Do you want to go home?
I don't want to go home.
[Team 1.]
I think it's Wen Zhe.
Xu Ruo Wei?
Xu Ruo Wei didn't receive it either.
Lin Chen Han did well too.
[The winner is "Pretty U" Team.]
Please.
I'll announce the next contestant
who'll continue with the Planet Pass.
The second person to get the Planet Pass.
The person who will remain
on Girls Planet.
I wonder who that is.
I'll reveal it now.
My goodness.
I have no idea.
-I'm so nervous.
-Xu Ruo Wei.
From C Group.
The person who will remain
on Girls Planet.
I wonder who that is.
I'll reveal it now.
-My goodness.
-I have no idea.
I'm so nervous.
From C Group.
It's Wen Zhe.
My goodness.
It must be her birthday gift.
Happy birthday.
♫ Happy birthday to you ♫
I can see how genuine she is in her eyes.
She is so sincere.
I can't imagine how much she practiced.
She improved so much very quickly.
That's why I chose her.
Happy birthday.
Now the last Planet Pass survivor
of Girls Planet 999.
I will announce the name.
Who among K Group?
[Seung Eun.]
[Hye Rim.]
There are too many of them.
So many of them should be saved.
I have no idea.
The last recipient of the Planet Pass
performed "Wow Thing"
in Planet Demo Stage.
♫ Just like my beating heart ♫
♫ Boom, boom, boom ♫
♫ The whole world follows me ♫
Must be Hye Rim.
Sun Woo or Da Yeon.
Both Hye Rim and Sun Woo...
There are three people.
Sun Woo, Da Yeon, and Hye Rim.
Three of them.
In the Connect Mission...
They both were main vocalists.
-The main vocalist.
She aced the mission as a main vocalist
[and impressed the masters.]
♫ I don't know what you'll choose,
so I got you two choices ♫
They both were great main vocalists.
It's Hye Rim. Don't say it's me.
Can't they just spare them both?
The last recipient of Planet Pass.
I'll reveal
the third survivor.
So nervous.
Please save them both.
The last survivor.
This is scary.
I'll reveal it now!
From K Group.
It's Kim Hye Rim!
Congratulations.
Hye Rim.
You must look pretty.
Stop crying.
[We chose Hye Rim.]
She showed great leadership.
She's like a legit main vocalist already.
Her "YES or YES" team could win mostly
because of Hye Rim.
The masters have given you another chance.
How are you feeling?
First of all, thanks for giving me
the last chance.
Thank you very much.
I'll hold onto this last chance
and do my best.
What a great birthday present.
My cell...
We all tried so hard.
Sorry I can't be with you.
I'll try to show you my best.
Thank you.
Please go to your seats.
We now have 54 survivors
who will keep on dreaming.
But this isn't over yet.
Apart from the cell voting earlier,
the Planet Guardians voted for the girls
[they're rooting for three per group.]
Nine girls with the most votes
from Planet Guardians
will become Planet TOP9.
Who will it be?
-How happy would they be?
-I know.
I'd be super happy.
I'd be very flattered if I could make it.
Totally.
From the Planet TOP9 chosen
by the masters,
let's see how much change there has been.
Number one chosen by the masters,
Ezaki Hikaru.
Do you think you'll be in TOP9
by global votes too?
I did all I could.
I hope the Planet Guardians noticed it
and selected me.
Out of 54 survivors,
I'll reveal the Planet TOP9
that symbolizes
the debut group of Girls Planet 999!
Drum rolls.
I really have no clue.
I'll announce number nine
of Planet TOP9 first.
Number nine has shown growth
in every performance
and her pretty voice has captured
the masters and many Planet Guardians.
Voice?
Who is it?
In the Connect Mission, she appealed
with the song "YES or YES".
♫ Hey, boy, look ♫
♫ I'm going to make this simple for you ♫
♫ Choose between the two, yes or yes ♫
♫ Choose one already, yes or yes ♫
As a result,
her team
won.
Chae Hyun or Ji Won.
-Chae Hyun for number nine?
-Who is it?
Number nine chosen by the global votes!
-Oh, my.
-Who is it?
I have no clue.
Number nine goes to...
-Chae Hyun?
From K Group.
It's Kim Chae Hyun!
Chae Hyun.
So cool.
Congratulations.
Kim Chae Hyun is
in the first Planet TOP9.
Thanks to all Planet Guardians
around the world
who voted for me.
I'll keep trying my best.
Thank you.
-So cool.
You're so cool.
I'm so happy for her.
That's so cool.
That suits you.
She got the first necklace.
-It shines.
-She's finally sitting there.
Doesn't it look crushy?
So cushy.
Now number eight out of Planet TOP9.
Number eight now.
Number eight ranked
sixth in Japan,
eighth in China,
and ninth in Korea.
From which group, do you think?
I have no clue.
She was in TOP9 chosen by the masters.
It's so hard to guess.
Someone from C or J Group?
-Cai Bing.
-Or maybe Ji Yoon.
-What about Ye Seo?
-Maybe.
-Maybe Ye Seo is higher up.
-Yes.
The benefits from the Connect Mission
were given to her.
Cai Bing.
Ye Seo. It's Ye Seo.
Ye Seo or Cai Bing.
Number eight chosen by the global votes.
Number eight is...
[I'm curious.]
It's Kang Ye Seo!
Number eight of TOP9 is Kang Ye Seo.
Congratulations.
Thank you for voting for me.
And my cell members.
Mashiro and Xing Qiao, you did great.
I'll keep working hard and grow.
Thank you.
Congratulations, Ye Seo.
It's Mommy.
So cool, Ye Seo.
She must be happy.
Now revealing
number seven of Planet TOP9.
Maybe someone from another group?
According to the global votes,
she got many votes from Spain, France,
and England.
Bahiyyih?
-Hikaru?
Cai Bing.
What?
Is she popular in Spain?
All foreigners like her.
In the cell ranking I just announced,
her cell was in top three.
They're all so popular. I have no clue.
For the Connect Mission,
she performed "How You Like That"
by BLACKPINK.
♫ How you like that? ♫
♫ Now look at you, now look at me ♫
Yurina?
Cai Bing?
-Cai Bing?
-Cai Bing.
-Xiao Ting.
I don't know.
Number seven was decided
by the global votes.
From C group...
From C group?
Who is it?
-Don't put your hopes up.
Cai Bing!
Cai Bing.
Congratulations on being number seven.
How do you feel?
I'm delighted and happy.
As you've put me up so high,
I'll try my best to deserve
all the votes you've given me.
Thank you.
Respect.
[She has this aura...]
It's time for J group.
It's time indeed.
It's number six now.
Now number six out of Planet TOP9.
I used to be number six.
According to the individual votes,
she was ranked second in Japan,
third in China,
and eighth in Korea.
So high.
-Yurina or Hikaru?
-Hikaru?
Hikaru or Yurina.
Someone from J Group.
She ranked second in Japan,
so she must be from J Group.
She's also in TOP9 selected
by the masters.
-That's Hikaru.
-It's Hikaru.
Hikaru?
Please.
In the Connect Mission,
she performed
a boy group song, not a girl group.
♫ The dark streets ♫
♫ Countless desperate dreams ♫
♫ So they can see us ♫
I think it's Rui Qi.
I think it may be Hikaru.
Maybe Ji Yoon.
It could be any of them.
The girl who made it to Planet TOP9.
Hikaru or Su Rui Qi.
Su Rui Qi.
Hikaru.
It's 100 percent Hikaru.
Number six of Planet TOP9 is...
Come on, Hikaru!
Su Rui Qi from C Group!
Is it really me?
That's amazing.
-Rui Qi is popular in Japan!
-Yes.
Rui Qi is popular in Japan.
Let's hear from her.
It's like a dream.
I didn't think I'd make it to TOP9.
First, thank you, Planet Guardians.
I'm very satisfied.
Thank you.
It feels like a dream.
Congratulations.
Only five seats remain for TOP9.
Still no sign of J Group.
There will be one soon.
Let's see who will sit
on those five remaining seats.
Someone from J Group, please.
Now number five of TOP9.
This participant
ranked
first in Japan.
First?
Isn't that Hikaru?
That's amazing.
I think it's Yurina.
And she was the leader
in the Connect Mission.
What?
Bo Ra?
Xu Zi Yin?
Fu Ya Ning or Shen Xiao Ting.
Who is it? I have no clue.
I have absolutely no idea.
Number five decided by the global votes.
From J Group.
-Who is it?
Who?
Sakamoto Mashiro!
Congrats, Sakamoto Mashiro.
Thank you.
Please say a few words.
I didn't think I'd make it to TOP9.
I wasn't that prepared.
Yet many people voted for me,
so I'm happy.
I'll perform as well as the rank requires.
This is just the beginning for me.
Please keep your eyes on me. Thank you.
All number twos are doing so well,
but what am I doing?
When will I get to TOP9?
There are only four left, right?
Right.
Xiao Ting and you...
No.
What if I don't make it?
-What should I do?
-Then...
Only four seats remain.
-Bahiyyih...
-I don't know.
The first survival announcement
of Girls Planet 999.
Now, among Planet TOP9,
we only have numbers 4, 3, 2,
and one left.
My gosh.
So nervous.
Who will take the glory of
becoming number one?
We'll meet the four candidates
on the screen.
Is this how it works?
Right away?
Now we get to know.
Xiao Ting.
-Hikaru.
Yu Jin?
Bahiyyih. Huening Bahiyyih.
Right.
It's obvious.
She's so popular.
Bahiyyih.
I'm so nervous.
-I can't stand this.
-You'll make it for sure.
-Shen Xiao Ting.
-I don't know.
It's too high.
First place.
-No.
-You have to place first.
I can't.
These four are ranked first to fourth
of Planet TOP9.
Who will they be?
Will be revealed now!
-Two, three.
-What?
Amazing.
What?
You're there, too!
Yurina.
We made it.
That's awesome.
It's Yurina.
Amazing.
What?
-What about Bahiyyih?
-She's not there.
Bahiyyih is not there.
Bahiyyih is not there?
I thought she would be one of them.
No way!
Choi Yu Jin from K Group.
Shen Xiao Ting from C Group.
Ezaki Hikaru from J Group.
Kawaguchi Yurina from J Group.
These are the four candidates.
I think Yu Jin will rank number one.
Right.
Yu Jin would be in first place.
Third and fourth places
would be from J Group.
First place is Yu Jin.
And the rest are all possible now.
First, I'll announce fourth place of TOP9.
It would be from J Group.
Ranked second in Singapore,
Vietnam, and the Philippines.
Ranked third in the USA and the UK.
And ranked fourth in Korea.
-Globally popular.
-Globally.
Is it Hikaru?
Yurina?
I think it's Yurina.
Hikaru.
So nervous.
-In the Connect Mission,
-The Connect Mission.
she performed
"How You Like That" by BLACKPINK.
It's one of those three.
It's one of you.
I'm okay.
Does that mean I'm higher?
No way.
Got to stay in first place.
Let's go for first place.
It's Yurina.
-Yurina?
-Yurina.
I think it's Yurina.
I can't breathe.
Fourth place of Planet TOP9 goes to...
Who is it?
"It is Kawaguchi Yurina."
She must be so nervous.
Congratulations to Choi Yu Jin of K Group.
Yu Jin?
Choi Yu Jin.
What?
Yu Jin?
Choi Yu Jin.
-What?
-Yu Jin?
-Fourth place?
What? Congratulate her!
Congrats.
Yu Jin.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Not first place?
-I thought she would be in first place.
-Me too.
I can't believe it.
Wait a minute.
Then who is in first place?
Please give us your speech.
Oh, my gosh.
In the cell voting,
I was ranked in the middle.
So I expected that I'd survive,
but this is totally unexpected.
I'm grateful just to be
one of the candidates.
I'll make sure to perform better
and live up to this rank.
Thank you.
I thought she'd place first too.
Me too.
Maybe it's Shen Xiao Ting.
Could Yurina end up placing first?
If Yurina places first,
it'll be shocking.
This is amusing.
Let's continue with the announcement.
Third place of TOP9.
I hope she keeps her first place.
I know.
-Could it be you?
-Yes, first place.
-It might be you.
-Let's not get our hopes up.
As the result of the first global voting,
the US, the UK, France, and Mexico
gave this contestant
second place.
And she placed first in Columbia.
That's crazy.
She's a worldwide star.
She's global.
That's all over the world.
-Awesome.
-It really is all over the world.
Moreover,
she has been evaluated
with BLACKPINK's song
on this show.
It's Yurina.
♫ It serves me right ♫
♫ Now, one, two, three ♫
♫ How you like that? ♫
Yurina?
It'll be amazing if you come first.
It's all of them.
Yes, it's all of us.
Oh, wait. "BOOMBAHYAH."
♫ Even if someone dares to stop me,
I'm gonna go brrr, RAMBO ♫
It's all of them.
-Oh, right.
-It's them all.
It's all three of them.
Come on, it's all of them.
-You're right.
-Let me announce it.
Who is it?
I don't know.
This is so fun.
It's unpredictable.
Third place of Planet TOP9.
It goes to...
Who is it?
From J Group.
Yurina? Hikaru? I'm confused.
-Hikaru?
-Yurina?
Yurina.
It's Yurina.
Yurina?
Hikaru might place first.
I'm curious.
-Ezaki Hikaru!
-My gosh.
Ezaki Hikaru!
Yurina...
Yurina.
This is crazy.
They're ranked 1st and 2nd. That's crazy.
The 1st and 2nd ranks are
in the same cell.
This is unbelievable.
That cell is too strong.
What is this?
Congratulations, Hikaru.
Thank you.
Any remark for the fans?
When my face showed up on the screen,
I felt like I was dreaming.
It's so hard to believe that
I'm in this high, third rank.
Planet Guardians
from all around the world,
thank you so much for letting me
take on this dream-like place.
From now on, I'll do whatever it takes
to make my dream come true.
Please look forward.
Thank you, and I love you.
So cute!
We love you!
-She's cute.
-How cute.
Thank you!
What is happening?
Yurina is unbelievable.
I can't wait to see who's ranked first.
We only have 1st and 2nd places
left to be announced.
It's unbelievable
that they are in the same cell.
It's a twist.
One after another...
Who shall have
the honor of placing first?
How can they be in the same cell?
Who do you think it will be?
Shen Xiao Ting.
Shen Xiao Ting, the TOP9 candidate,
ranked first in C Group
in the global voting.
Kawaguchi Yurina
ranked first in J Group.
Thumbs up!
These two are in the same cell.
Since they are
both the first-place candidates,
let's hear from them.
This is so unreal.
I never thought
I'd make it this high.
I don't think it's important
who ranks first
because we'll be together either way.
Thank you.
I never thought I'd be in TOP9.
It's like a miracle
that I made it
with my cell-mate, Xiao Ting,
so I'll be happy regardless of the result.
Thank you.
Who will be
the first contestant to take
first place of Planet TOP9
with Planet Guardians' votes?
Shen Xiao Ting ranked first
in C Group
in the global voting. Will it be her?
That surprised me.
My gosh.
Or will it be Kawaguchi Yurina
who ranked first in J Group?
The final score
of the first-place contestant
is 4,446,387.
I'm so proud.
This is crazy.
The first-place contestant
chosen by the Planet Guardians.
I'll announce the name.
Who is ranked 1st of Planet TOP9?
The contestant with glory
will be revealed now.
Coming soon shortly after commercials.
The honorable TOP9's 1st place
chosen by the Planet Guardians!
I'll announce the name now.
They must be so nervous.
I'm so curious.
I can't make any predictions.
Xiao Ting?
Yurina?
I really have no idea.
[Yurina and I are]
[the only ones left,]
[so my place is either 1st or 2nd.]
[But I'm hopeful.]
[Maybe I'm in first place.]
[It was totally unexpected,]
[so it feels surreal.]
[I feel like I'm dreaming.]
Planet TOP9's 1st place.
It's J Group's Kawaguchi Yurina!
Congratulations.
-Kawaguchi Yurina! Congratulations.
-My gosh!
Good job.
Kawaguchi Yurina!
-My gosh.
-Congratulations.
-This is crazy.
-Unbelievable.
Awesome.
The rankings are crazy this time.
I feel like I'm dreaming.
Good job.
This is crazy.
Out of 164 countries
that participated in the global voting,
Kawaguchi Yurina placed 1st
in 83 countries.
That is more than half of the countries.
She is really amazing.
-I got goosebumps.
-That's crazy.
First of all, thank you to
Planet Guardians
who voted for me.
I'm honored by this result
because I'm still unskilled in many ways.
I'll work harder from now on
so that the Planet Guardians who voted me
will acknowledge that Kawaguchi Yurina
really does deserve to be in first place
in the TOP9 in the first round of votes.
I'll do my best so please cheer me on.
Thank you.
Shen Xiao Ting was placed second
in the TOP9. Please tell us
how you feel as well.
Planet Guardians,
I'm so thankful that you voted for me
and for liking me.
All the experiences
and the feelings I'm getting
on this show are new to me.
People started recognizing me
and acknowledging me for the first time.
I was able to work my way to the center.
People have high expectations of me now.
I'll keep on driving myself
so that I don't disappoint you.
My goal isn't to be in the TOP9 now,
but to be in the final TOP9.
Thank you.
Please go to the 1st and 2nd place seats.
Good job.
The first
survival announcement is over.
Global Planet Guardians voted and decided
the first Planet TOP9. Congratulations!
However, that was only the first mission.
Until final debut members are decided,
today's Planet TOP9
cannot be at ease either.
The TOP9 can always change according
to the votes
cast by Planet Guardians!
[Let's try to maintain the TOP9 position.]
[I want to remain in my place.]
[I feel like my place isn't secure
as the 9th place in the TOP9.]
The surviving 54 will begin
a new mission
to debut as a K-pop idol group.
The Planet Guardians' global voting
will also begin anew.
[I'll have to go up the ranks because
I may be eliminated at this rate.]
[I want to remain here.]
[I want to go up a lot.]
For the girl you support
to continue dreaming of
being a K-pop idol,
please send in your precious votes.
Whose dream
will you protect?
[Here are the results of the first
global voting at Girls Planet 999.]
[These are the rankings of each survivor
and the Planet TOP9.]
[Planet Guardians around the world.]
[The second global voting begins now.]
[To protect their dreams
as Planet Guardians,]
[you can vote once a day]
[on the official app.]
[The second voting is for
individuals votes,]
[and not cell votes.]
[Ten of the lowest ranking members]
[from each group, which makes
30 in total, will be eliminated.]
[First, access the voting screen]
[and select three girls
from Groups K, C, J,]
[selecting nine girls
you support in total.]
[Press the final submission button]
[to complete your vote.]
[The results reflect 50 percent
from Korean votes]
[and 50 percent from global votes
outside of Korea.]
[The number of votes]
[will become points.]
[Planet Guardians!]
[Whose dreams will you protect?]
Oh, I want to be
in the TOP9.
-You can!
-No.
You worked hard,
so you'll make it.
I know it.
It was fun.
You can do it.
I know it.
[We all worked hard,]
[so I felt really bad.]
I'll do my best to make you proud.
I love you.
-We were always here together.
-I know.
Every single day.
-We were the best cell ever.
-Yes.
-Totally.
-The best.
We were!
Totally.
I'm okay.
-Good job!
We were awesome.
Don't go.
You're the only one left.
You can do it. Make us proud.
[Even though I was eliminated...]
[I was so happy to meet great people.]
[I got to know myself
better on this show.]
[Girls Planet]
[helped me grow.]
[Girl's Planet's second mission]
will be revealed now.
It is a combination mission.
In this mission, current cells
will be disbanded.
[We're in trouble.]
[I don't want to get eliminated.]
[I was determined to get the benefit.]
You should do better.
You're in first place,
so you need to do better.
Why did you choose to do it?
I think you'll blow up the stage.
Slowly.
Take slow breaths.
You'll otherwise hyperventilate.
Breathe slowly. That's it.