=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 28=
Impossible!
This is impossible!
Houchi.
How is Houchi?
Don’t worry.
The Pilgrimage Hall has selected her
as the master
and transferred
all its spiritual power to her.
She needs at least days
or at most years
to absorb the spiritual power.
Take her to have a rest now.
The Pilgrimage Hall has selected her
as the master?
It’s impossible!
In front of so many people,
Houchi absorbed the spiritual power
of the Pilgrimage Hall.
Why is it impossible?
The Pilgrimage Hall
is a treasure for the Immortals.
We can’t let others own it.
Gu Jun is a disciple of Master Shanggu.
Hadn’t the Pilgrimage Hall fallen
to the Heavenly Palace,
it should have been hers long ago.
Wu Huan,
tens of thousands of years ago,
we were sorry to Gu Jun,
and Houchi.
Let’s give her the Pilgrimage Hall
to compensate for it.
Where is Qingmu now?
Heavenly Father,
Qingmu is at the Zisong Hall.
Please visit him there.
Your Highness,
if His Majesty knows
you did nothing
to save the North Sea Lord...
It’s dawn now.
No matter how capable Qingmu was,
he’s dead, with nothing left.
It can’t be changed.
What can His Majesty do about it?
Yes.
Heavenly Father, please.
What...?
So weird!
His spiritual power was messy
and twisted not long ago.
How come he’s recovered suddenly?
Jingzhao...! Nonsense!
Heavenly Mother,
I love Qingmu so much.
I can’t watch him die.
Heavenly Mother,
please ask Heavenly Father
not to blame me anymore.
Jingzhao, do you know
you’ll lose your cultivation
without the dragon core,
and you’ll be the same as a mortal?
I don’t care what you did before,
but it’s a serious thing,
how could you make a decision
by yourself?
Do you know
you may die
if anything goes wrong?
Jingzhao, you’re so stupid.
The dragon core is your essence.
It contains all your cultivation
and it’s the basis for you
to become a Goddess.
It can detoxify various poisons,
but how could you be so generous
to give it to others?
Jingyang,
help Jingzhao get up.
She’s weak now.
Jingzhao.
Don’t bother.
Jingzhao,
there are so many good men in the world,
why do you only want him?
I like him for so many years.
I can’t extricate myself from him.
But you could have waited for
Heavenly Father to save him.
Why did you choose this way?
You’re not loving him.
You’re forcing him.
He would rather die
than marry me.
I’m as light as a feather in his mind.
How could I force him?
Jingzhao,
it’s just a man,
and a blind man.
No matter how much you love him,
you can’t give up yourself
for him.
I could only use this way
to let him remember me forever.
How could I miss it?
Even he’ll marry Houchi,
with my dragon core on him,
he’ll never forget me.
He can never avoid me.
Jingzhao,
what you do is not love.
Listen to me,
let him go,
and let yourself go.
Let him go?
If I can’t get him,
others
can’t, either.
Jingyang,
put Jingzhao in the Fairy-locking Tower!
Without my order,
never release her!
Your Majesty,
she’s so weak now,
how could she go there?
It’s what she deserves!
Heavenly Father,
Jingzhao did take a wrong move,
but with her health condition now,
she may lose her life if we do so.
Life?
Your mother and I
spent so much time and effort on her.
What she becomes now
is what she deserves!
Heavenly Father,
I only like Qingmu.
If you don’t agree,
then,
kill me.
Jingzhao!
Get out.
I don’t want to see you.
Get out!
Heavenly Father!
- Jingzhao.
- Heavenly Father.
Heavenly Father!
Jingzhao was obedient since childhood.
How could she become like this?
She’s grown up
and has her own ideas.
As parents,
we have to make a plan for her.
What’s most important now
is her health.
Without the dragon core,
Jingzhao can’t cultivate herself
anymore.
A mortal can’t bear the spiritual power.
I surely know this.
But what can we do now?
Huan,
you could have saved Qingmu,
but why didn’t you do it?
If you had saved Qingmu,
Jingzhao wouldn’t have become like this.
Qingmu
refused our marriage proposal
in front of all immortals.
I wanted to give him a lesson.
How could I really watch him die?
But I didn’t expect that
Jingzhao loved him so much
that she even gave him her dragon core.
If the True God is still alive,
maybe he can save Jingzhao,
but sadly...
Your Majesty,
no matter how hard it is,
we must find a way.
We can’t
let Qingmu leave here
before we find the way
to save Jingzhao.
That’s all we can do now.
Qingmu.
Houchi.
How do you feel?
You’re awake.
I thought I’d never see you again.
Don’t cry.
I’m fine now.
I’m still alive.
Look,
I’m in perfectly good condition.
As Goddess Houchi
from the Qingchi Palace,
you’re well-known
even in the Heavenly Palace.
If anyone else sees you
cry and laugh,
what should you do?
Does the wound in your chest still hurt?
No.
It’s cured.
I’m all good after seeing you.
You don’t have
any dragon breath left in your body.
And
your spiritual power
seems stronger.
Yeah.
It’s a blessing in disguise.
Luckily, the Heavenly Emperor
saved me in time.
Not only the Heavenly Emperor,
Jingjian and Fengran
also helped a lot.
I must ask Chang Que to pick
some best spiritual materials
and send them here
to thank them.
Good idea.
But I have to stay more days here
to attend the birthday banquet.
Birthday banquet?
I was saved from the dragon breath
thanks to the Heavenly Palace.
I have promised Jingjian
I’ll leave after the birthday banquet.
You refused the marriage proposal
and then broke into
the Fuyao Hall at night.
And after what happened
in the Pilgrimage Hall,
the Heavenly Emperor still saved you.
It’s reasonable
for both of us
to attend the birthday banquet.
You can’t attend it.
Why?
The Heavenly Emperor
invited me before on Mount Lookout.
Why can’t I?
I don’t want you to do anything
you don’t like.
But...
All right.
There is no “but”.
You have absorbed the spiritual power
of the Pilgrimage Hall.
You need a good rest now.
When you stabilize the spiritual power,
go back to the Qingchi Palace
to wait for me.
I’ll boil the medicine for you.
Heavenly Mother,
Qingmu is my close friend.
Fengran...
Fengran is the girl I like.
Today,
I don’t dare to let you in.
Your Highness.
Greetings, Lady Fengran.
I want to talk to you.
Please sit.
- Yester...
You first, please.
Yester...
Yesterday...
I know what you said
was to save me.
Don’t worry.
I won’t harass you
with unreasonable demands.
You’re young and capable.
As a prince in the Heavenly Palace,
you have to consider your reputation.
After Houchi and I
go back to the Qingchi Palace,
I won’t disturb you a bit anymore.
But...
Don’t worry.
Others may discuss it for days,
but they will forget it one day.
You can marry others then.
I was just worried about
imaginary troubles.
Anyway,
from now on,
I won’t blame you for Jingyang.
This is glossy Ganoderma
from Endless Mountain.
I will send it and the others
to Princess Jingzhao now.
It’s all my fault.
Jingzhao is spoiled
and got bold and reckless.
Now,
she’ll suffer a lot.
His Majesty has ordered
Qingmu not to leave here.
He’ll be dealt with.
You’re worried about the princess,
but don’t hurt your health.
It’ll be good if it’s so simple.
It’s easy to make another dragon core
for Jingzhao.
Cultivating herself from a mortal
will take her tens of thousands of years
to become an immortal.
If it ends with nothing serious,
it’ll be too merciful for them.
Fengnyu,
do you think Houchi
is similar to Gu Jun?
Your Highness.
Goddess Houchi is stubborn
and indifferent.
It’s exactly the same as God Gu Jun.
But Gu Jun is so charming
that he can impress anyone who sees him.
In terms of appearance,
Goddess Houchi is a little ordinary.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Shanggu?
No.
She just looks like Shanggu,
but her temper and bearing
are quite different.
This is such a coincidence.
Maybe Goddess Houchi
resembles her birth mother.
She has weak spiritual power.
Her birth mother must be a mortal.
I don’t know who her birth mother is.
This is the daughter
of the Queen and me.
Her name is Houchi.
How come the Queen...
Even the Gods
can’t escape love affairs.
The Heavenly Emperor felt sorry for him
and couldn’t do anything to him.
So, I became the egg’s mother
in front of all the Gods,
giving her a good identity.
Gu Jun is a flood dragon.
If Houchi is really his daughter,
I have a way to get back
Jingzhao’s dragon core.
Are you planning to...
Fengnyu,
do you remember
the Huajing Pond,
a restricted area in the Qingchi Palace?
Except for Gu Jun,
no one else is allowed to get in.
Yes, I do.
One day, I went to the garden with you
and almost entered the Huajing Pond.
God Gu Jun was very angry.
Maybe there is
the secret about Houchi’s birth mother.
Or why Gu Jun doesn’t allow
anyone else to enter?
It seems
it’s not me
who betrayed our relationship first.
Fengnyu,
Gu Jun isn’t there now.
Go check it for me.
Yes.
Why are you looking at me like this?
Because you’re beautiful.
But we’ve known each other
for a long time.
Why didn’t you praise me before?
I didn’t praise you like this before?
It was my fault.
From now on,
I’ll praise you three times a day,
for twenty thousand years.
Are we even now?
Well, from now on,
I’ll beat you three times a day.
Then, we’ll be even.
Seriously?
In the past,
you had weaker power than me.
Now you have the same power as me.
Of course, it’s quite different.
Let me see, is it serious?
Look.
You tease me with such a simple trick.
That’s because you have me in your mind,
or I can’t make it.
Don’t talk.
Let me hug you like this for a while.
♪Time disturb my feelings♪
I thought you’d die this time.
I’m fine now.
Until then, I realized
how much I love you.
It’s a pity
that we can’t be born together,
but I hope we can die together.
It’s exactly the same
as the love story of the mortals.
Houchi,
if I become a mortal one day,
what will you do?
I’d like to give up all my cultivation
and become a couple with you as mortals.
Even if we can only live 100 years?
100 years are good enough.
Without you,
to live 1,000 years or 10,000 years,
or even become an immortal
means nothing.
If you’re not with me,
foreverness is meaningless.
♪For a little talk♪
♪If it’s such a good time
and such a beautiful scenery♪
♪Hope♪
♪Go with me♪
I promise you,
I will accompany you forever.
From now on,
we’ll never separate.
Tell me,
when will you return
the dragon core to Jingzhao?
If you refuse to answer it,
I’ll kill you to take it back now.
Jingyang.
You can’t solve the problem by this.
Why are you always helping an outsider?
The future of Jingzhao
has been ruined by this guy.
Your Highness,
the birthday of the Queen of Heaven
is coming.
At that time,
I’ll give the Heavenly Palace
an answer.
Remember what you said.
If I can’t return the dragon core,
I’ll compensate for it
with all my cultivation.
You needn’t do anything.
If you don’t do it,
I will kill you!
I only remembered power of the God
could detoxify you.
But I forgot
the dragon core also could
detoxify various poisons.
Jingzhao went to your room
and told me Mother
went to the Pilgrimage Hall.
I was afraid Houchi and Fengran
would be embarrassed,
and went there too in a rush.
Unexpectedly,
I hurt her
and you.
Jingjian,
it’s not your fault.
I asked you here
because I want to meet Lord Donghua.
He may have other solutions.
Houchi,
you looked at the chessboard
for a long time.
What were you thinking?
I can hide nothing from you.
Fengran,
look,
the Fuyao Hall of the Queen of Heaven
has a similar layout
with the Pilgrimage Hall.
Does the Queen of Heaven have
relationship with the Pilgrimage Hall?
You don’t know
that the Queen of Heaven
was from the Pilgrimage Hall.
So she manages the Heavenly Palace
as the God Realm.
If so,
the Queen of Heaven knew
True God Shanggu.
True God Shanggu?
Why are you mentioning
the master of all Gods?
When I was absorbing the power
of the Pilgrimage Hall,
I saw True God Shanggu.
She looks exactly the same as me.
How could it be?
Where did she appear?
I don’t know.
I’ve never been there.
It’s not the Immortal Realm
or the Demon Realm,
neither the Human Realm.
The God Realm?
Maybe.
But it has been closed for 60,000 years.
Maybe it’s just a dream.
I don’t know why,
but I have a messy mind recently.
Maybe because you have
redundant spiritual power.
You’ll be fine in a few days.
Demon Lord Ziyue said
that I had a seal in my body.
If the seal is broken,
I may not be me anymore.
What? I don’t understand.
You’re who you are.
How absurd Jingyuan is!
In my childhood,
whenever I asked my father
about the Queen of Heaven,
he would say nothing
and looked very sad.
I couldn’t bear it.
So, I stopped asking him.
Now it seems
what happened
is not that simple.
Houchi,
don’t think too much, all right?
Forget it. Go pack our things.
We’ll leave here tonight.
Tonight?
What about Qingmu?
Qingmu will stay to attend the
birthday banquet of the Queen of Heaven.
He insisted on this.
I think he’s hiding something from me.
Forget it.
We’ll be happy
once we leave this place.
Don’t you have any reluctance?
Why should I?
Because of Jingjian.
Houchi,
you’ve gone bad with Qingmu.
If I don’t teach you a lesson,
you don’t remember
I’m the Lady of the Qingchi Palace,
do you?
Stop it. Stop it.
Come here.
I stop. I stop.
Houchi.
Why are you here?
Jingjian hasn’t come back.
If you want to find him,
go somewhere else.
No.
I’m coming to find you.
I want to have a talk with you alone.
Houchi.
No worries.
This is the Heavenly Palace.
I’ll be fine.
Sorry that I’m delayed
for something.
Please forgive me.
It doesn’t matter.
This is a beautiful park.
I was watching the scenery here.
It’s good.
I invited you here
because I have a difficult question
to ask you.
The Gold Dragons
were in the heyday in ancient times,
but have declined now.
A lot of things
are not known by others.
You’re a senior of ancient times.
Do you know the dragon core?
You’re in the Heavenly Palace already.
But you don’t ask His Majesty.
Is this
related to Princess Jingzhao?
Yes.
It’s related to her.
I was poisoned by the dragon breath
days ago.
To save me,
Princess Jingzhao
gave me her dragon core.
It’s a big favor.
But I don’t deserve it.
So, I can’t accept it.
Please tell me
how to take the dragon core out.
The dragon core will disperse
once entering someone else’s body.
Except the True God,
no one
can take it out.
However,
I have a method.
But it’s too dangerous.
Dare you have a try?
Please tell me.
It’s known that
immortals who practice enough
can become Gods.
After enduring 49 thunder strikes
on his body,
he can extract a core
and form a small circle in his body,
turning five elements
into spiritual power continuously.
The Green Dragon Platform
in the Heavenly Palace
is the place for the immortals
to become Gods.
But it hasn’t been opened
for 60,000 years.
If you practice enough,
you can make a core
and replace the dragon core
to solve the problem
of Princess Jingzhao.
Although Qingmu has outstanding
spiritual power,
he’s far from becoming a God.
In the past 60,000 years,
no immortal became a God successfully.
If he goes to the Green Dragon Platform,
I’m afraid he’ll die with nothing left.
It’s not a good idea.
Is there any other solution?
Do you know
why I come to you today?
Tell me if you want to.
Leave here if you don’t want to.
I’m not interested in guessing you.
As a Goddess,
can’t you find
my difference from before?
I can’t.
Houchi,
I’ve lost all my spiritual power
and my spiritual root.
I’m even not as good as you were before.
Are you satisfied?
You should go to the Queen of Heaven
or the Heavenly Emperor.
Why do you come to me?
What if I tell you
I lost all my spiritual power
because of Qingmu?
Thank you, Lord Donghua.
Sorry for disturbing you. Farewell.
Wait.
Where did this yellow dog come from?
I discovered it on Mount Lookout.
It’s smart.
But
I took it with me for a long time,
it still doesn’t like me.
If you like it,
you can take it.
With its qualification,
it’ll become your Spirit Beast
within 100 years.
Spirit Beast?
It’s too precious!
How could I take it?
You’re young and capable.
You obtained your Taicang Spear
from my Mount Lookout.
There is destiny
between you and me.
Please don’t refuse it.
Okay.
But
Lord Donghua,
if I die on the Green Dragon Platform,
can I leave this yellow dog
to my beloved Houchi?
You are virtuous and stood by heaven.
You will be fine finally.
Prince Jingjian!
Your Highness,
something may happen at the Zisong Hall.
The status of Goddess,
Qingmu,
and everything I failed to get,
you get them easily.
Now I make it out that
there are many ways to beat you.
It’s not bad to be a thorn
in your heart.
What did you do to Qingmu?
I detoxified his dragon breath.
I saved his life.
I gave my dragon core to him.
We will accompany each other
and will never separate this life.
Jingzhao!
Why did you do this?
If you don’t tangle with Qingmu,
you have nothing else to do?
It should be my question.
You couldn’t even break your shell.
You were abandoned by Mother.
Why do you always compete with me?
Houchi!
This time, he will marry me,
not you.
You’re joking, Your Highness.
About the marriage,
I’ve made it clear.
This life,
I’ll only marry her.
I’ll never regret it.
Qingmu...!
Jingzhao!
Why don’t you have a rest
at the Xiuyang Hall?
You shouldn’t have come out.
Come on, go back with me.
No.
Be good.
No!
Houchi.
When did it happen?
The day before yesterday.
Why didn’t you tell me?
I...
Your Highness,
at the bottom of the Huajing Pond
was a room.
Obviously, someone lived there.
Why is there nothing special?
There are a lot of books,
recording what happened
in the God Realm of ancient times.
Apart from them,
nothing special.
Maybe the portrait in the room
has something to do
with the room’s owner.
Why does Gu Jun hide his identity?
He’s related to the God Realm.
Who is he?
Houchi. Qingmu.
Shanggu. Bai Jue.
They look so much alike.
Is it really a coincidence?
Never mention
what happened today.
Go back now.
Yes.
I don’t believe it’s a coincidence.
Even the Pilgrimage Hall
belongs to Houchi now.
I’d rather kill the wrong,
instead of letting go.
Three-head,
you achieved your cultivation so fast
because of Master’s Purple Moon Power.
But you didn’t report to Master
what happened in the Abyssal Ridge Swamp
and only followed Sen Jian’s order.
Did you forget who your master is?
I dare not.
It’s the Demon King’s order.
Demon King has strong spiritual power.
I’m not his match.
You said
what you shouldn’t have said.
Master, forgive me!
I’m guilty.
Please punish me, Master.
You know I value Houchi the most,
but you hid her conditions from me.
Sen Jian,
do you have a different mind from me?
Master,
what I did
is all for your safety.
Now your identity
has been exposed to Wu Huan.
If you come into contact
with the Heavenly Palace
because of Houchi,
I’m afraid... you may invite trouble.
How dare you!
60,000 years have passed.
You’ve forgotten my temper, haven’t you?
Although I lost some God power,
I still have a lot of measures
to control the Demons.
Master,
I’m absolutely
loyal to you.
Back then, I could ruin all the beings
in the Three Realms for her,
not to mention the Heavenly Palace now.
Sen Jian,
if you dare to act
beyond your power again,
I’ll give all the honors
to someone else.
Did the hitting
hurt your God veins?
I’m fine. I’m fine.
I have to say,
you should remember it.
No matter what happens to Goddess Houchi
from the Qingchi Palace,
you must report it to Master.
That Three-head
only told me that
he hurt Qingmu
in the Abyssal Ridge Swamp,
without mentioning Houchi.
It’s my fault.
Qingmu is also counted.
Any news about these two
must be dealt with carefully.
Do you still blame Master?
How dare I?
I just think that
he cares so much about Houchi,
I’m afraid he may be misled by love.
You have no idea.
Goddess Houchi may have
all kinds of connections
with Master Shanggu.
I can’t tell you more details.
Just keep it in mind that
without the Demon God,
the Demons will lose protection.
The Demon God is the foundation
of the Demons.
It was my mistake.
Master is kind to the Demons.
He even ignores the recovery
of his own power,
supporting demons for so long.
I don’t care about others,
but if only I am alive,
I won’t I betray Master.
Master knows you well.
He asked me to give it to you.
Take it.
You’ll be fine within a month.
The Purple Moon Pill?
Master cares about you.
Don’t disappoint him.
I understand.
Houchi,
stop being angry.
Although Qingmu did it wrong,
he did it out of kindness.
You’ve experienced so much together.
You can’t be mad at him for Jingzhao.
I am not mad at him.
Why don’t you agree to meet him?
I’ve been thinking
how to solve the matter
about the dragon core.
Have you found a way?
Almost.
In my opinion,
Jingzhao is really contemptible.
Even she saved Qingmu,
she’s too shameless!
Anyway,
she saved Qingmu.
We should thank her.
How about this?
Let’s go back to the Qingchi Palace
and close the protection barrier
for tens of thousands of years.
It will pass then.
We can’t withdraw
in the face of everything.
If we leave here tonight,
how can the Qingchi Palace
gain a foothold in the Three Realms
in the future?
You talk
more and more like a Goddess.
I like it.
Houchi.
You look so anxious.
Are you thinking about
how to please me?
Do you want fish soup?
It’s a new dish I learned recently.
When did I become a glutton
in your eyes?
No, no, no. You’re not gluttonous.
It’s just that
I want to cook some tasty food for you.
Since you studied the menu
for me carefully,
I forgive you.
Houchi.
I heard long ago
that the Milky Way in the Heavenly Realm
is stunningly beautiful.
It’s composed of stars
in the Human Realm.
Would you like to go with me to see it?
Of course.
I’d like to watch it with you
however long it may be.
Let’s go.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪