=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 27=
- Greetings, Goddess Houchi.
- Greetings, Lady Fengran.
We’re fairy maidens
in the Heavenly Palace.
What are you doing here
in broad daylight?
For your information, Lady Fengran,
we’re here to see Goddess Houchi.
Me?
You’re a Goddess,
but you seldom appear in public
in the past sixty thousand years.
Ridiculous!
What do you think Goddess Houchi is?
A rare beast?
Sorry, I didn’t mean to offend you.
Please punish me.
Don’t panic.
Now that you came to see me,
and you have seen me,
you may leave
if there’s no other business.
Yes.
You were rumored to be vulgar.
After they saw you today,
they would know the rumor wasn’t true.
Lord Qingmu and Jingjian are back?
Yes,
Your Grace.
They must have saved Jingyang.
I knew
nothing could stop him.
Your... Your Grace.
Why are you faltering?
What else is it?
The heavenly guard reported that
Lord Qingmu was back
with Goddess Houchi and Lady Fengran.
What did you say?
How dare he!
Heavenly Father has got us engaged.
How could he bring Houchi back
in such an imposing manner?
Where are they?
Prince Jingjian took them
to the Zisong Hall
before he went to see His Majesty
with Lord Qingmu.
Heavenly Father?
Jingyang was saved.
The Three-head Fire Dragon was stopped
from becoming a God.
It’s all ascribed to you.
I’ll greatly reward you.
Heavenly Father,
Lord Qingmu saved the day
during the fight
against the Three-head Fire Dragon.
I don’t dare to claim the credit.
Don’t be too modest, Jingjian.
Lord Qingmu made a contribution
to the Three Realms.
Now I’m giving you the North Sea
as your possession,
and you’ll enjoy the great glory
in the Heavenly Palace.
Your Majesty.
What do you mean, Lord Qingmu?
Your Majesty, do you remember
you granted me a promise
before I left the Heavenly Palace?
Sure, I do.
What?
The possession isn’t enough?
What I want
isn’t any territory.
What do you want, then?
Feel free to tell me.
Please call off the engagement
between Princess Jingzhao and me.
No!
Heavenly Father.
Don’t, Heavenly Father!
Qingmu!
Jingzhao.
Back off!
Heavenly Father,
don’t!
He wants to call off the engagement?
It’s such good luck for him,
but he doesn’t want it?
How arrogant!
Qingmu, do you really mean
what you just said?
Yes.
Why?
Is my daughter not good enough for you?
I don’t mean that.
Princess Jingzhao is noble.
I don’t dare to disrespect her.
But I’m in love with a girl.
I’ll marry no one, but her.
If I marry Princess Jingzhao,
it’ll be unfair to her.
Your Grace, please forgive me.
Your Majesty, thank you,
but I can’t marry her.
Heavenly Father.
Your Majesty.
Lord Qingmu,
I’d like to know
who the girl is.
You want to marry her,
even when you have to
give up the North Sea and Jingzhao.
The girl I adore
is Goddess Houchi of the Qingchi Palace.
I’ll marry no one, but her.
Please grant us, Your Majesty.
It’s really her.
How daring Qingmu is!
Yeah.
Heavenly Father,
please don’t grant him!
If my engagement is called off,
how disgraced I’ll be!
Your Majesty,
you never change your edict.
How could you change it for him?
I promised that
as long as Qingmu brought Jingyang back,
I would grant him a promise.
Immortals witnessed it.
How can I
break my own promise?
Your Majesty,
then the Taicang Spear...
Forget it.
Qingmu,
I’m calling off your engagement today.
From this day on,
on your marriage...
Heavenly Father!
You can make your own decision.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Worried about Qingmu?
Immortals are always tough.
Even if Qingmu has a plan,
I still worry there’ll be an accident.
After staying in the Qingchi Palace
for so many years,
I’ve thought of you as my sister.
I’m not as thoughtful as you are
and I can’t help much now.
But I want you to know that
no matter what danger there is,
or how we may end up,
I’ll stay with you.
Heavenly Father called off
the engagement
between Qingmu and Jingzhao.
Qingmu can make his own decision
on his marriage.
Didn’t you want Qingmu
to call off the engagement?
He made it,
but why do you look unhappy?
What they’re doing
reminds me of my sister.
Qingmu.
Qingmu, what’s the matter?
Qingmu!
- Qingmu, what’s wrong with you?
- Qingmu!
- Qingmu, are you all right?
- Qingmu, what’s the matter?
Jingjian,
what’s the problem with him?
He was all right, wasn’t he?
It is the dragon breath
of the Three-head Fire Dragon.
It is weird and dominant.
When it first entered his body,
it was like some normal spiritual power
and was hard to notice.
But when it was noticed,
it had already intruded into his veins.
What’s wrong?
Nothing. Let’s go.
Is there any cure for him?
The Three-head Fire Dragon
was a Demigod.
Normal power can hardly
detoxify the breath.
Qingmu can’t be saved
unless the power of a God
is put into his body.
Then no one can save him,
but the Emperor or Queen, right?
I’ll go beg His Majesty.
Houchi,
after the meeting at the hall,
Heavenly Mother kept quarreling
with Heavenly Father
for Qingmu’s calling off the engagement.
Heavenly Father was so annoyed
that he locked himself for seclusion
in the Pilgrimage Hall.
The Pilgrimage Hall?
That’s the shrine of the Heavenly Palace
with a barrier outside it.
Only a God can step in.
If anyone breaks in,
he’ll be killed by the barrier power.
Once Heavenly Father is there,
it takes at least several months
before he comes out.
And Qingmu is badly injured.
If he can’t be cured
by this time tomorrow,
I’m afraid he’ll die.
Now, no one can save Qingmu,
but Heavenly Mother.
I’ll go beg her.
Wait.
I’ll go.
Don’t, Houchi.
Qingmu just called off
the engagement with Jingzhao.
She will embarrass you.
You know she’s mad at that.
Even if Jingjian begs her,
she won’t let it go.
For me, Qingmu
gave up the marriage
and the possession of the North Sea.
I can’t just wait and do nothing.
As long as I can save him,
I’m willing to do anything.
And I’ll take any consequence.
I’m Houchi from the Qingchi Palace.
I request to see Her Highness.
It’s you, Goddess Houchi.
I didn’t recognize you
before you came near.
I thought it was a maid.
Please kindly report to Her Highness.
I’m sorry to tell you that,
but Her Highness is having a rest.
Please wait here.
Wait a second.
How long will the rest be?
How am I supposed to know
how long Her Highness wants it to be?
Sometimes one hour.
But when she’s upset,
she doesn’t see anyone
for three or five days.
By the way,
I heard that someone
made trouble in the hall
and annoyed Her Highness.
I’m afraid you have to wait
for a few more days.
Her Highness can refuse to see me.
But what if it’s about the safety
of the Heavenly Palace
and about immortals and demons?
Heavenly Mother,
they humiliated me like that!
You must defend me!
Qingmu called off the engagement,
but he hasn’t married Houchi yet.
You still have a chance.
But I want to ask you something.
What is it, Heavenly Mother?
You’re the princess,
with the bloodline of the Gold Dragon.
You’ll inherit the Heavenly Palace.
Must you marry him, but no one else?
Heavenly Mother,
I want no one,
but him.
Even if he doesn’t like you
and hates the marriage?
He hasn’t realized how good I am yet.
I believe that
I’m not inferior to Houchi at all.
As long as Qingmu marries me,
and we can live a quite long life,
I will make him
fall in love with me.
Good.
You’re indeed my daughter.
I had ups and downs in my life,
but I never gave up.
You shouldn’t give up, either.
But,
Heavenly Father already granted him.
Your Highness,
Goddess Houchi is outside the hall.
She’s here to see me in person.
Looks like
you still have a chance.
How do you feel?
What’s wrong with me?
You were poisoned with the dragon breath
of the Three-head Fire Dragon.
Do you know it’s fatal
and it may kill you?
Don’t worry.
Houchi went to see my mother.
As long as she helps,
you’ll be safe.
Jingjian!
What?
How could you let Houchi...?
I’m Houchi from the Qingchi Palace.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Shanggu?
No.
She just looks like Shanggu,
but her temper and bearing
are quite different.
Your Highness.
Speaking of rank, we’re both Goddesses.
The fist-and-palm salute is enough.
But I’m your senior.
And you gave no salute to your mother.
Is this what your father taught you?
I grew up in the Qingchi Palace.
I only have my father, Gu Jun.
I never heard about my mother.
You’re a noble queen.
I don’t dare to call you Mother.
You’ve got
your father’s temper.
Tell me.
What are you here for?
I’m here
to make a deal with you.
A deal?
It’s been sixty thousand years.
I wondered if you
had forgotten the Qingchi Palace.
But you just mentioned my father.
I guess you remember why we exist.
When the God Realm was closed,
Master Zhiyang asked you,
His Majesty and my father
to manage the lower realm.
There have been battles
between immortals and demons
with continuous conflicts.
We’re always impartial
and are never restrained by either side.
That’s why the Three Realms coexist
and stay in peace.
I’m right. Don’t you think so?
You’re right.
Today, I’m here for something big
for both immortals and demons.
If you grant my request,
I’ll take my men
to pay allegiance to the Heavenly Palace
so that we can
fight against demons together.
On Qilian Mountains
are massive spiritual veins.
If we have them,
we’ll gain more power.
In less than a hundred years,
there’ll be a few more Gods.
By then, demons can’t fight us anymore.
Your offer
really sounds attractive.
But you’re so generous.
I guess you offered it
for something more important.
Let me guess.
For North Sea Lord Qingmu?
I indeed offered it for him.
He was poisoned with the dragon breath
of the Three-head Fire Dragon.
Only the power of a God or a Goddess
can save him.
I’m really curious.
If your father were here
and saw his daughter
he had been caring for
give Qilian Mountains out
to someone else,
simply for a man,
how would he feel?
You’re wrong, Your Highness.
In this world,
not only power is the most attractive.
If my father were here,
he would want me to stick to my feelings
and do what I want to do
for whom I like.
You usually value strength.
For this,
you attempted to force Lord Qingmu
many times
to work for you.
I think
I’m just satisfying you.
If you pledge loyalty to us,
demons will no longer be a threat.
It’s indeed satisfying me.
But Houchi,
at this moment,
I won’t grant your request.
Why?
Because you haven’t offered
what I really want.
You overestimated the Qingchi Palace
and also yourself.
I haven’t taken back Qilian Mountains
simply for old friendship.
If I send an army,
do you think you can stop me
with all that you can do?
You want
Qingmu to marry Jingzhao?
Exactly.
It’s been sixty thousand years.
You’re known as my mother,
but you never visited me.
When you have seen me today,
you still don’t care for me.
I wonder
except for your past with my father,
what else makes you
hate me so much?
I don’t care about you at all.
But what I have seen today
brought me much interest in you.
You look proud,
but have to yield to me.
I feel quite happy to see it.
Qingmu,
you don’t need to worry.
My mother is annoyed
because you called off your engagement.
But she isn’t unreasonable.
Houchi is her daughter, after all.
She won’t embarrass Houchi.
If she could really let go of it,
why did she say those words earlier?
Because...
- But Qingmu,
- Because...
Houchi is begging the Queen of Heaven
to save your life.
What if you break in
and annoy her?
If the Queen of Heaven
really wants to save me,
I’ll admit I misunderstood her
and I’ll take any punishment
by myself.
The Heavenly Emperor allowed Qingmu
to call off his engagement
with Jingzhao.
If you get them engaged again,
don’t you fear you’ll be mocked?
If Qingmu proposes to Jingzhao
and explains to everyone that
he was joking about the calling off,
His Majesty is always kind
and he may grant it.
Qingmu told everyone that
he liked me.
How will you explain that?
All immortals know that
you’re known as a Goddess,
but you have as weak power
as a low immortal.
But North Sea Lord Qingmu
was already the strongest lord
as early as a thousand years ago.
Speaking of strength,
how can you be good enough for him?
In my opinion,
he loves you,
possibly just for a while.
Jingzhao knew him before you.
In the Heavenly Palace,
there have always been rumors
about their relationship.
When I spread some rumors,
others will think
you kept bothering him.
By then,
I don’t know
if you’ll be mocked.
So,
you got a plan long ago?
I’m sorry to have disturbed you.
To tell you the truth,
it’s easy for me to save Qingmu.
But you humiliated Jingzhao
over and over again,
which annoyed me!
If you want me to help,
kneel right here for a couple of hours.
When I get happy,
perhaps,
I’ll help you.
What?
We’re both Goddesses.
But I’m tens of
thousands of years older.
Can’t you kneel to me?
In the existing Heavenly Palace,
I’m the queen
while you’re the subordinate.
I’m the senior while you’re the junior.
I’m the superior
while you’re the inferior.
You are supposed to kneel to me.
Besides, don’t you want to save Qingmu?
Don’t kneel to her!
Goddess Houchi and Your Highness
are both Goddesses.
There’s no such thing
as superior or inferior.
She doesn’t need to kneel.
Qingmu, you haven’t recovered.
Who allowed you to come?
If I didn’t come,
would you really do such a stupid thing?
Lord Qingmu, you came at late night.
Didn’t you make enough trouble
earlier today?
I’m humble,
but I’m also stubborn.
I don’t want Houchi to grovel for me,
do anything she doesn’t want
or flatter anyone
she doesn’t want to see.
Qingmu.
Do you know what crime it is
to break into my Fuyao Hall at night?
I’m sorry,
but I don’t understand.
You’re the queen, but why must you
go against ethics to break us up?
Simply because we love each other,
you want to force us with your power
and threaten her with my life?
Fine. Now that you disobey His Majesty
and force me to marry Jingzhao,
I won’t mind being accused
of disrespecting you.
I’m dying, anyway.
Qingmu,
don’t be stupid.
Let’s go.
I don’t want to stay
for even a single second.
You’re indeed brave.
When did I say
I would disobey His Majesty?
However,
I won’t help you
unless Houchi kneels to me.
She won’t ever kneel to you!
Houchi,
didn’t you say
you had deep love for Qingmu?
His Majesty is in the Pilgrimage Hall.
If you don’t want to kneel,
you can go ask him for help.
The Pilgrimage Hall?
It’s said that
the Pilgrimage Hall is shielded
in the barrier from the Shanggu Realm.
Whoever breaks in will be killed,
unless he’s a God.
Your Highness,
you’re trying to kill her.
Which one of you will live?
It’s all up to you.
Let’s go.
How was it?
Did Her Highness agree to save you?
She almost did,
but...
If you dare to go
to the Pilgrimage Hall,
I’ll be mad at you.
It’s about your life.
I must go there
and ask His Majesty to save you.
No way.
I won’t let you go.
Let me go and get Heavenly Father back.
I have the power from him.
I guess I won’t be hurt.
If anyone should go, that’s me.
I’m stronger than you.
No.
Stay here and look after Qingmu.
I’m going to the Pilgrimage Hall now.
I’m known as a Goddess.
Enough.
Houchi,
since we departed from
the Qingchi Palace,
we haven’t had a good time together.
Death isn’t terrible to me.
As long as you’re by my side,
I’ll die without regret.
I want to go to the North Sea.
Could you go there with me?
It’s where we pledged love.
I’m never tired of looking at it.
Qingmu,
let’s go back.
Houchi,
in fact, I knew you
earlier than you thought.
A thousand years ago,
I woke up in the North Sea
without any memory.
But I kept dreaming of a girl.
What girl?
She has your face
and stands in the thunder.
How can it be me
in your dream?
It is you.
Maybe our love story
had begun before we met each other.
♪Loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
After I knew you,
I finally got to understand annoyance,
happiness,
and all the other emotions.
Fate made us meet at this moment
and it’s already my luck.
I’m satisfied.
But I...
If there’s the next life,
I wish you could meet me
before I meet you.
What if there’s no next life?
Where can I find you, then?
Then live a good life alone.
I don’t expect the next life.
I only want this life.
I don’t want you
to give up the Qingchi Palace for me.
Nor do I want you
to give up your dignity and life.
Even if you keep me alive,
I’ll spend the rest of my life
in regret and guilt.
I just want you to be happy.
♪Tears turn into clouds♪
Qingmu,
let’s get back to the Heavenly Palace.
I must save you.
♪When everything♪
♪Works out♪
Jingzhao,
what did Heavenly Mother say?
She won’t see you.
She said she wouldn’t save Qingmu
unless Houchi agreed to leave him.
Jingzhao,
I know you feel aggrieved.
But Qingmu is dying.
If you really like him,
you should care about his life first,
instead of being self-willed.
Jingjian,
I know his life matters most.
But no matter how hard
I begged Heavenly Mother,
she didn’t agree to compromise.
Does she really want him to die?
Don’t talk nonsense.
Heavenly Mother is always proud,
and she loves you.
Maybe she’s just discontent
because she saw you get humiliated.
All right.
I’ll keep begging her
until she changes her mind.
They’re back.
Where’s Houchi?
Qingmu is dying.
Now that Houchi isn’t here,
she must have gone
to the Pilgrimage Hall.
Considering her weak spiritual power,
she’ll get killed.
No way. I have to go save her!
Stay here and transfer power to him
to keep him alive.
I’m going to the Pilgrimage Hall.
It’s our business.
Considering your embarrassing identity,
if you’re involved,
you’ll be blamed for being
disloyal and unfilial.
Fengran!
(Fuyao Hall)
Heavenly Mother,
you are still in the mood
for watching portraits?
If Qingmu isn’t saved tonight,
he may really die.
Come and look.
This is Yuran of the Feng Clan.
He became a lord when he was
three thousand years old.
His grandfather is Fengyun,
the former head of the Feng Clan.
He’s good-looking
and has strong power.
He’s kind of noble, too.
Heavenly Mother,
what do you mean?
I’ve changed my mind.
Qingmu is far too stubborn.
Even if you marry him,
you can’t change him.
Heavenly Mother.
I’m not eager to marry Qingmu now.
I beg you to save him.
I love no one, but Qingmu.
No one can replace him!
Your Highness,
something big happened.
What happened?
Houchi is trying to break
into the Pilgrimage Hall.
Now she’s confronting
the heavenly soldiers.
Houchi is really risking her life?
How dare they cause trouble
in our territory!
The Pilgrimage Hall is our shrine!
Even if you’re a Goddess
from the Qingchi Palace,
you mustn’t break in!
Houchi, are you all right?
Fengran, stop them for me.
Houchi.
Houchi!
(The Pilgrimage Hall)
Greetings, Your Grace.
The barrier of the Pilgrimage Hall
doesn’t block her at all?
What are you waiting for?
Kill the trespasser!
Jingjian, what do you mean?
Heavenly Mother,
it’s my idea to let them come here.
If you want to punish Lady Fengran,
please punish me, too.
Your idea?
Do you think it’s easy to fool me?
Don’t lie to me
simply to show off your courage!
Heavenly Mother,
Qingmu is my close friend.
Fengran...
Fengran is the girl I like.
Today,
I don’t dare to let you in
and I can’t let you in.
If you insist on
entering the Pilgrimage Hall,
please... punish me first.
I’m Houchi from the Qingchi Palace.
I request to see you, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty!
He’s meditating.
I can’t wake him up
unless I talk with spiritual power.
But I have weak spiritual power.
Forget it.
I can’t care that much.
Your Majesty,
Qingmu is poisoned
with the dragon breath.
No one can save him, but you.
Please lend a helping hand.
Please save Qingmu!
For the sake of my father!
Houchi!
What makes me inferior to her?
Why is it you?
Where’s Houchi?
To marry you,
I ignored my parents’ order.
But what did she do?
You’re so badly injured because of her,
but you still want her?
Qingmu, look at me.
It’s me who’s saving your life!
Don’t hurt her. Don’t hurt her!
You don’t want me to haunt you,
but I insist on saving you.
I’ll not only save you,
but also make you never forget me!
Houchi?
Don’t be anxious.
You have weak spiritual power.
Let me pass some power to you
and you’ll feel better.
What...?
The Pilgrimage Hall is choosing Houchi
as its owner?
Bad Bai Jue,
you keep me cultivate myself here,
but you’re enjoying himself
in the lower realm!
When I take over the instruction feather
of Chief God,
I’ll kick you to the lower realm first,
let you live in the deepest part
of the North Sea
for ten thousand years, no...
for sixty thousand years
and you won’t come out forever.
Houchi!
No.
She may not handle the Power of Chaos.
If it continues,
she’ll be in danger.
(The Pilgrimage Hall)
Your Grace, happy birthday!
What do you think?
Are you satisfied?
(The Pilgrimage Hall)
Impossible!
This is impossible!
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪