(There's never been fake news
from the E-sports Industry Farm.)
(I'm your only diva of true news.)
(There's a lot of news
in the e-sports industry lately.)
(There is finally)
(a rumor out that
the idol of the industry, Chessman,)
(- Rumor has it that he has a girlfriend now.)
- Thank you.
Smiling.
(FNC's jungler Kun)
(unexpectedly appeared in the audience.)
(I'm thinking of the last time
when he kept ganking Smiling,)
(we have every reason to suspect)
(that there are some
hidden secrets between them.)
You're cute, Smiling.
(Of course,)
(the biggest blockbuster)
(is Cheng's amazing hug
at the scene of the match,)
(as well as the solo game of
the two center players of ZGDX.)
Come on, Shorty, let's solo.
(Excuse me.)
(Who will be the ultimate girlfriend
revealed in public?)
=Falling into Your Smile=
=Episode 17=
What?
I just took a nap by accident.
How did I miss
such a big solo game?
Oh my God, Jinyang, I'm going deaf.
What happened then?
You won the solo against Cheng and then what?
Don't tell me you will chicken out.
I knew Lu Sicheng must like you.
He must have lost to you on purpose.
You think so too?
In the eyes of romance novels and fans,
that's true.
He seems to have lost to me on purpose.
But here's the thing.
When I was playing against him,
I could feel
he wasn't going easy on me at all.
He really wanted to beat me.
Maybe I did win
because I'm more familiar with
the middle lane routes and terrain than him.
Pretend.
You go on pretending, I'm hanging up.
No, it's true.
And...
Forget it.
I don't know what's going on either.
I told you
not to put up "flags" so nonchalantly.
Like you won't fall in love
with a professional player.
You'll be biting your own tongue constantly
after saying that kind of thing.
What about Cheng?
What did he say?
You guys didn't ask him a single question
after the solo?
What should I ask?
We're all teammates.
What if
I made an inappropriate action
and got rejected,
how could we play again in the future?
How embarrassing.
You were really thinking too much.
I didn't even think that much
with Ai Jia at the time.
We are teammates.
Compared to things with uncertain results,
I'd prefer to play well in the tournament.
And I don't want someone else to say,
you girls came to play professionally
just to be famous or to find a man.
Okay.
I'm starting to feel sorry for you.
I didn't expect that
our silly girl
would actually grow up some day.
Or else?
But
I have to advise you as someone experienced.
In this kind of situation,
women should not act rashly.
Men won't be able to hold back
if they really do like you.
Really?
But
if he really takes his time in making a move,
then
it probably really is just your fantasy.
Okay.
Bye-bye.
Cheng, you haven't left yet?
Didn't you say
your blind date
asked you to meet her one last time?
It's already late.
Why haven't you gotten ready to go?
What's wrong?
You're not going?
Didn't someone say she didn't want me to go?
Who is she to meddle?
You... You heard all that?
I'm not deaf.
Then why did you pretend…
I care about dignity.
I... I was just saying it off handedly.
I was afraid that you would be distracted.
Think about it.
Our teammates, they all hope to
win the championship trophy this year,
as well as the championship skin,
"revenge of Hierophant" or something.
Biscuit.
There you are.
Let's go.
Let's go eat some canned food.
What's up?
What are you two talking about?
What Hierophant revenge?
No, nothing.
I'm going back inside.
You're not going out?
I'm not going out.
You stood her up again?
I said we'd make it
at the entrance of the base
so that I don't have to drive out.
There is no dating in e-sports.
Our goal this year
is to win the national championship.
Good that you know.
Let's go, Biscuit.
Let's go eat canned food.
Cheng.
You lost the solo on purpose, didn't you?
Why would I lose it on purpose?
Yang told me.
Then why did you lose?
Do you want me to explain
the reason for my defeat to you?
Do you want me to write
an 800-word review for you?
The whole world can see that
you lost on purpose.
No.
I miscalculated the distance of the lines.
She caught the opportunity.
You wouldn't make that kind of mistake.
At least I haven't seen it before.
I'm not an immortal
who doesn't make mistakes.
Besides,
why would I lose to her on purpose?
I don't know about you.
Anyway,
I did see the tenderness.
You're blind.
Our team's midsolo
can't recognize that kind of tricky set up.
Besides,
now that she's beaten me,
she's thinking about how to take my place
and take over the team.
To be gentle with her
- is to be cruel to me.
- What? What's he saying?
He's saying yes and meaning no.
I don't understand you men.
Why do you all like to play
this kind of double-faced trick?
What's the difference
between your behavior
and the boy in kindergarten who likes to pull
the pigtail of the little girl
he has a crush on?
I'm going.
Let's go.
What?
Someone's coming to see you later, too?
No.
I'm here to check the weather.
Aren't we going out
for a late night snack later?
No, we'll just have it brought in.
Miss Su.
I already told you last time.
We're not a match.
Lu Sicheng.
Are you not happy
that I went to see you
at the site of the match,
you think that I'm too high-profile?
I really didn't mean it.
I answered what they asked me.
I didn't expect you to be so famous.
And I didn't expect
they would analyze what I said so deeply.
Now those fans of yours
are already in an uproar.
I'm really sorry.
They even found my Weibo account.
Some people are really nasty,
saying things like
I'm shameless.
I pretend to be your girlfriend.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
It's not your fault.
It's your fans.
Although I don't know much about
the e-sports industry,
if it means that we can be together,
I am willing to
learn about and understand it.
It has nothing to do with this.
I don't know if Lu Yue told you
something that made you misunderstand.
Some nonsense such as
the rules of this industry.
You can ignore it.
The truth is that if I want someone,
I will protect her.
So it has nothing to do with this.
Then you're afraid that
your fans will be upset?
I'm not an idol
in the entertainment industry.
I'm an e-sports player, not a monk.
Then what is it?
We're not a good match.
In what way?
Family background,
appearance, IQ or height?
Give me a hug.
Even they can be together.
Isn't it good?
Bye-bye.
That little girl
is young enough to be his daughter.
What kind of person do you like?
Someone who can play games better than me.
Isn't that all just a hype gimmick?
No, it's not.
But is there really such a person?
I heard you're a good gamer.
No one is better than you.
It's not necessarily
in terms of the Onmyoji Arena.
If she can play Tetris better than me,
that will work.
It's just that if it is in Onmyoji Arena,
then I'll go straight to marrying her.
Bye.
Why is Cheng not back yet?
The shop is very popular.
The crayfish will be all gone if we're late.
Yeah, what's going on?
It's been 20 minutes.
That's right, I'm starving to death.
Screw this, I'm going to go check it out.
For what?
Your performance this month is in danger.
Ranking, ranking, ranking.
What?
- I can't do it.
- Don't.
It's your fault
for telling me to go to the gym.
We'll rank while we wait.
Why don't I go check it out?
Okay, go.
What are you looking at? Get logged in.
You two get on with the ranking, I'll watch.
- No way.
- I can't do it.
What? You're scared of ghosts again?
Chubby said he's hungry.
He asked me to rush you to buy crayfish.
Well...
Where's your blind date?
She's gone?
She's gone.
Let's go. Let's drive to get some crayfish.
We have to drive there?
The shop is in the south of the city.
If you had told us earlier,
I wouldn't have run out.
I didn't ask you to chase me out.
You...
Sir.
You want so many crayfish at once.
Are you entertaining friends at home
with your girlfriend?
She is not my girlfriend.
She's my teammate.
Teammate?
I see the way she looks at you.
That's either the way a girl
would look at a boyfriend
or the way she would look at a husband.
The girl likes you, am I right?
If you don't like her, just say so.
Don't break her heart.
Let's go.
What did you say to the waitress?
You were smiling so sweetly.
What's wrong with your eyes?
She gave you a discount?
No, she didn't.
Then why were you smiling so happily?
She said you look at me
as though you were looking at your boyfriend.
No way.
How can a waitress be that bored?
Take a break.
What's wrong with you?
Your hand hurts?
Is your hand injured?
I've been playing professionally
for a long time.
And I'm a shooter.
It's normal to have a little hand injury.
It's just a strain injury.
As long as I don't usually lift heavy things,
I…
What are you doing?
Why did you not say earlier that
you have a hand injury?
Why is that such a big deal?
I have a strain injury, not a disability.
Give it to me.
No.
I once carried gas tanks
for my mother at home.
I'm not that delicate.
You just wait for me here.
Hey.
Lu Sicheng, open the door.
What a novelty.
What?
It's the first time for me
to be taken care of by a little girl.
But I'm not a little girl.
In a word,
thank you.
Let's go.
Seatbelt.
Cheng.
Did you lose that solo game on purpose?
What do you think?
I don't think so.
It's not like you're a little girl
who needs to be coaxed like that.
You make it seem as if
you know the trick well.
You wouldn't get it anyway.
I can see it.
I'm a girl.
You're not.
You are.
Cheng.
What is it?
I…
You have to arrange
your training time wisely,
so as not to aggravate your hand injury.
We have a physiotherapist
coming to our base every month.
Cheng.
I think...
Do you want to listen to a song?
No rush.
♪With a door locked inside our hearts♪
♪And then hold on with the shell♪
♪No one but you in the world
knows I am lying♪
(What you want)
(will all come to you.)
♪Running all the way to you
after calling your nickname♪
♪Struggling to go through the motions♪
♪Don't expose the most intentional
bystander on this street♪
See?
At least 5 kg are mine alone.
And this row of
RIO
is our midsolo's favorite.
She once said
RIO Light and shrimp go perfectly together.
That's right.
(Turn the camera around a bit)
(so that I can look at others.)
(I don't want to look at you, you fatty.)
What fatty? Speak nicely.
This is how you expect me
to turn the camera for you?
You are a fatty.
Let me show you.
This
crayfish is at the price of 156 yuan a pound.
Before it's cooked,
they even spit out colorful bubbles.
(Food poisoning, right?)
(It looks like hormones.)
You…
Okay, okay.
I won't talk to you.
Live streaming slows down
my vigor of eating crayfish.
Don't forget
to give me gifts.
Why don't you eat?
He thinks it's too much trouble
and leaves a taste on the fingers.
The smell won't dissipate for two whole days.
It's too unpleasant.
Look at his psychological burden.
Unless you peel the crayfish
and put it in a bowl for him.
You thought you were eating Boston lobster,
expecting someone else to serve you?
You watched me peel it.
I didn't put rat poison in it.
Forget it if you don't eat.
Have another sip of RIO.
Hurry up.
What do you think? I told you so.
Why is Cheng so obedient?
Want some more?
You like to peel crayfish for people?
I was about to say,
"I'm not going to serve you
even if you want more".
You paid for it.
So at least I should let you taste it.
That's being polite.
Rude.
You two solo during the day
while feeding each other shrimp
and flirting at night.
You two have gone conjugal!
(Chubby, I dare you
to turn the camera around!)
(Let us see what's happening over there.)
Turn what?
No, I can't turn it with a handful of oil.
(- Who's feeding the shrimp to whom?)
- You can slap me.
(Who's conjugal with whom?)
You guys, just look at me.
Who wants to see
you eating shrimp on live streaming?
- Who wants to see you, chubby?
- Go away.
No way.
Shut up.
I just got a call from the club.
They want us to participate in an event.
There's a competition this weekend.
What's the event?
Cheng.
You've repeatedly rejected Su Luo lately.
Mrs. Lu is so angry that
she's taking it out on the club.
I've put off all the other events I could.
But I've already signed the contract
for this Saturday's out-of-town event
for the Next Gen Anime Expo.
So…
We have a full schedule
of competitions afterwards.
How can we be going out of town on Saturday?
We go and come back on the same day?
What the club means is that
we'll go directly
to the airport after the match,
and then we can fly back
after the event on Saturday.
Can we not go?
Then you'll have to find Mrs. Lu.
Tell the club
that this is the last time.
(Onmyoji Arena)
(Luyun Mountain Stream)
(With a song of confession,
the clouds fade away)
(Ping'an)
We left two hours early.
I didn't even eat breakfast. I'm starving.
I'm really sorry.
It was because I was afraid of traffic jams.
So the trip was arranged in advance.
Breakfast benefits.
Rui.
You've finally become humane.
You knew I haven't eaten breakfast.
- I'm so hungry, brother.
- What are you talking about?
I'm telling you a truth that
the early bird gets the worm
through my actions.
If I have a good panini like this every day,
I guarantee that I can quit staying in bed.
If one breakfast
can keep you guys from staying in bed,
I would really will
be willing to be your breakfast housekeeper.
Come, come, look over here.
One, two, three.
What are you doing?
Taking a picture
to send to the official blogger
so that she can hook up
KFC's breakfast sponsorship.
Rui is the best at stingy skills.
- What are you talking about?
- Rui.
What exactly is the event today?
I don't know. The club arranged it.
Cheng! Cheng! Cheng!
Sorry, sorry.
- Cheng.
- We're putting on makeup, sorry.
- Sign for me.
- Sorry, you can't go in.
Please sign for us, Cheng.
No, they're having their makeup done.
- Cheng.
- Sign for us.
One autograph, just one autograph.
Keep your voices down.
Okay, okay, okay.
Hurry up, everyone!
Cheng!
- Cheng.
Cheng got up so early today.
I didn't think he'd be so patient.
Cheng is a veteran.
Does he want to be trolled
by his ignorant fans saying that
he's too indifferent?
- Cheng, mine.
- Thank you.
I want a signature too.
Sign here.
And mine.
This is mine.
Tong Yao, please help me sign one.
Thank you.
(Lu Sicheng)
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you, Cheng.
- Thank you.
- Mine.
Thank you.
Thank you!
Cheng, it's done.
There's not much time left,
so try to hurry up.
Thank you.
Please sign it.
- Cheng.
- Cheng, sign for me.
Smiling, please help me to sign it.
Here.
- Thank you.
Please sign it here.
Thank you.
And this one too.
So handsome!
You are even more handsome
in person than in photos.
(Lu Sicheng)
Thank you.
Sign this for me, Smiling.
And this one.
Thank you.
Thank you, Cheng.
- Thank you, Cheng.
- Thank you, Smiling.
- Give me an autograph too.
- I want one too.
Can you sign for me too?
Smiling, please give me an autograph.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Smiling.
You've been here three times already.
That was for myself just now.
- This is for my friend.
- Thank you.
It won't take you long anyway.
Just sign it.
Cheng.
Sign for me, Cheng.
Rui.
What's wrong?
She's been here three times already.
Is she done?
Okay, I'll take care of it.
Sorry.
We don't have time for the makeup.
Why don't you stop signing for now?
It's just an autograph.
So what?
Why are you so pretentious?
Good job.
These people just want to
show off to their friends, like
"I can go backstage to see someone,
do you want his autograph?"
And then they run over
to ask for an autograph.
In fact, maybe
they don't even know what you do.
They just know
you're celebrities who play games.
Your hair is done. I'll leave now.
Do you want to eat?
I'm on a diet.
I'll eat then.
(The girl from the e-sports team is pretty arrogant.
Acting like she is a big figure.)
(This girl is a professional?
She must be a staff member, right?)
(I think I know who you are talking about.)
(Making a fuss.)
(To be honest,
I've always had an issue with her.)
(I've always had a bias towards her.)
Everyone, take a look.
This is the flow of our event,
including some
interactive parts
in need of your cooperation.
Thank you.
Please prepare for the game too.
(Event execution flow chart)
Let the team members hug the show girls
and run from left stage to right stage.
The first show girl
to hit the gong with a hammer
will be the winner.
I see it.
It's completely pointless,
making a spectacle of ourselves.
Rui.
Have you seen this flow sheet?
Why is there such a game?
Don't worry, let me see.
This…
Don't look at it.
We're dressed like this.
It's not suitable for being picked up, right?
Yes, that's right.
This skirt is too short.
We all live by our hands.
And we all have hand injuries.
This is not good, right?
This game
is not good for us.
It'll cause bad influence.
Why don't we change it?
We have all the game props ready,
and the timing is just right.
Now you suddenly say you want to change it.
That's not appropriate, don't you think?
No, look...
It's barely any time at all.
Just put up with it.
We have a game tomorrow.
What if someone gets hurt?
Who's going to play for us? You?
Miss,
you've been staring at me like that
since the beginning,
you've been looking for a fight, haven't you?
Didn't I just tell you that
the props are ready, the timing is set.
I can't change it.
No.
Listen to me.
It is true that our members
have injuries on their hands.
If…
We are all paid to work.
Don't make it seem like
you are more noble than us.
If you are really so unwilling,
then don't come.
Don't take money from the organizer
and at the same time pick a fight here.
Are you game players
all so high maintenance?
My boyfriend is also an e-sports player.
I don't see him being
so fragile like you guys.
You're all men.
It's like you're dying
just by carrying a girl
weighing several dozen pounds
and walking across a stage.
Do you want me to post a microblog saying
your team members are the most precious?
What are you doing?
What are you talking about?
Who are you threatening?
Okay, okay, okay.
Who threatened you?
Don't get upset.
We don't have to…
Don't touch me.
- Cat.
- Are you okay?
Why did you hit him?
Miss.
How could you hit me?
Are you going to blackmail me?
Lu Sicheng, let go!
Calm down, Miss.
Let go!
How can there be
a professional player like you?
What are you doing?
You want to hit a woman?
Did I hit you?
Like you're the only woman?
With which eye do you see that I'm a man?
Who are you?
Tong Yao.
This room is full of people.
Let go of me.
Don't stop me.
Are you done?
It's okay. It's okay.
We'll head out first. We'll head out first.
- Don't be upset.
- It's not worth it to be upset with her.
Except for Tong Yao,
everyone else
should go to the event immediately.
Take it easy.
Now,
your favorite ZGDX
is starting the competition.
Are you two ready?
Yes, we're ready.
Okay.
Ready?
Go!
Go, handsome!
Come on!
Go, go, go!
Good! Cat wins!
Let's have Chessman, Cheng, and K on stage.
Cheng! Cheng! Cheng!
(E-sports Industry Farm:
E-sports player Smiling acted like a diva)
(E-sports Industry Farm: Refused to cooperate
with the event and injured someone)
(Kitten ow)
It's okay.
My friends have come to pick me up.
There are many people at the scene.
My wounds have been taken care of.
Thank you all for your concern.
(A normal girl)
(can't possibly play professionally.)
(Either she is a transgender person…)
(Make it clear.)
(Or she is a psychopath.)
(Why did he hit you?)
(What did you say?)
I...
I just wanted to emphasize that
the organizers paid
them to perform.
(The ZGDX midsolo)
(picked a fight at the drop of a hat?)
(Is she crazy?)
(Outrageous.)
(Female fights are particularly exciting.)
(No matter what the reason is,
she always crosses the line.)
(Thank God you're okay.)
(Jiaqi is so gentle.)
(I could tell Tong Yao was of bad quality)
(just from her looks.)
With your concern and support,
I'll be fine soon.
Thank you all.
(My God.)
(E-sports player Smiling acted like a diva)
(This is currently the most popular)
(Refused to cooperate with the event and injured someone)
(e-sports Mulan,)
(E-sports player Smiling pushed someone)
(with a very bad temper.)
(Ning Jiaqi was injured)
(She just hit someone at the drop of a hat.)
(Spoiled by you brainless netizens)
(It's hard to hear some bad comments about her.)
(Is hitting people something to be proud of?)
(You told me it was a brawl.)
(- Before you start slandering her…)
- Hey, Mr. Zhang?
(- Let me laugh for a while first.)
- It's me again, me again.
Could you help me
block the keywords?
Yes, yes, about the fight.
- I'm really sorry.
- No problem, no problem.
I'll issue an official letter for you.
Thank you, thank you.
Mr. Zhang,
it's not like what the Internet says.
This is all our responsibility.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
We will definitely solve the problem
as soon as possible.
Please don't worry.
Mr. Li.
You're both here?
We are waiting for you.
Director Wang will be here soon.
You can talk to her yourselves.
Lu?
Director Wang herself came?
I thought…
Thought what?
Thought this was not severe enough?
No, no.
Director Wang.
You're Tong Yao, right?
This is our first encounter.
I'll introduce myself.
My name is Wang Lan.
I am the executive director
assigned to ZGDX by the Lu's Group.
I have another identity they all know.
I am also the mother of
Lu Sicheng and Lu Yue.
Mrs. Lu?
Director Wang,
you go ahead, I'll go out first.
Director Wang, allow me to explain.
Really, you can't blame Tong Yao for this.
That woman was obviously there
to pick a fight.
And our competitions
have been very intense lately.
Cheng's hand injury also recurred.
If his hand injury worsens
due to running around
lifting those girls,
and thus affect his performance
in the game, it'll be bad.
Tong Yao was concerned about Cheng.
- So she's…
- Someone said…
ZGDX's midsolo acted like a diva.
No, that's not the case.
Some people also say
ZGDX's midsolo was very arrogant
just like a shrew.
Director Wang,
I am also responsible for this.
She and Tong Yao actually…
Of course, you are responsible.
Two months' salary and bonus
will be deducted.
Don't bargain with me.
It's really terrible to have such a mother.
As for Tong Yao,
how about this?
Why are you here?
Cheng, Director Wang is inside.
You can't go in right now.
(Cheng.)
- Cheng.
- You're finally here.
You're not at
the ribbon cutting ceremony with Dad?
What are you doing here?
Why are you so rude?
You can't even call me mom, can you?
It's such a big deal.
Of course, I had to come
and take care of it personally.
It's a simple matter.
I've already figured out how to handle it.
It's true that Tong Yao started it.
So no matter what,
the club has to take a stand first,
issue a statement of apology
and bump it to the top to show our sincerity.
But no one can be free to
speculate the truth of the matter.
So,
Rui,
go find some platforms and media
that are in good relationship with us
to clarify the situation.
Yes, yes, I think Cheng is right.
Besides the media,
I will find some other buddy teams,
such as CK and YQCB,
to help us clarify it
when they are live streaming.
And then?
And then…
Then what else?
You can't just only apologize
in an apology statement, no?
The club must give an explanation
for beating people.
Otherwise, it will seem insincere.
Then Director Wang,
you, how are you going to
make the punishment?
Ban Tong Yao from the competition.
Ban me from the competition?
Well.
You don't want to take this
to Tournament Control, do you?
Ban her from one match.
That's fine.
But...
Rui, take Tong Yao out first.
I have to talk to my mother about something.
Okay, Director Wang, we will go out first.
Go.
Sit.
♪You say the world
is always not gentle enough♪
♪Fortunately, you're free,
the most special player♪
♪Invite me to be your number one teammate♪
♪So I had my first encounter with my dreams♪
♪You said you'd always be behind me♪
♪Rumors ran to me and hurt you♪
♪How long will it take
from now to the future♪
♪You're love that never needs a reason♪
♪I want to be close to you,
a little closer to you♪
♪You can be expressionless
and pretend to be calm♪
♪The rhythm of your heart is the best proof♪
♪You never say anything,
your eyes send a message♪
♪You and I are the only ones
in the world who understand each other♪
♪The moment you think of me♪
♪I happen to be thinking of you too♪
♪I want to be closer to you,
a little closer to you♪
♪You can be expressionless,
pretending to be calm♪
♪The rhythm of your heart is the best proof♪
♪You never say anything,
your eyes send a message♪
♪You and I are the only ones in the world
who understand each other♪
♪The moment you think of me♪
♪I happen to be thinking of you too♪
♪You never say anything,
your eyes send a message♪
♪You and I are the only ones in the world
who understand each other♪
♪I like in every season♪
♪I'm at the top of your list♪