(E-sports players spend
most of their time in silence)
(tapping away at their keyboards.)
(So they often forget)
(that they're public figures, too.)
=Falling into Your Smile=
=Episode 18=
Hello?
(Yao, you had a fight with someone?)
(Are you okay?)
(Here, let me talk.)
Yao.
(When you're away from home,)
(you must protect yourself.)
(Don't get into trouble with others.)
Mom, Dad.
I'm fine.
I know. Don't worry about me.
I'll be careful next time.
I have something going on, talk next time.
How is it?
Do you feel good?
I'll go post an apology right now
on the official Weibo account
and then stick it on top.
Then I'll go back to my dark room
and reflect on myself.
Well, not all things
can be resolved with
being angry in society.
The punishment that the club gave you
actually isn't too bad.
That's not bad?
Banning me from a game at this stage?
The punishment can be big or small.
A ban or a fine
is not important.
Just one game.
Now this is hot and trending.
If it is really gets to the level of
the image of e-sports
and it's made known to the tournament host,
do you think a ban for one game
will be enough?
Cheng.
(Next Gen Anime Expo Event
Execution Flow Sheet)
What is it now?
Aren't we all spoiled little princesses
of our parents?
She deserved to be slapped for being rude.
You'd be punished anyway.
Why didn't you give her another slap?
Don't fan the flames.
She can't mess with this.
Haven't you read the public opinions online?
I saw.
That's why I said
it's a loss not to give her another slap.
If women can't
sanction women,
then aren't these people
going to be out of control?
Why do we have to speak of
personal quality with people like them?
I really can't stand these girl fans,
always making unreasonable demands.
They think they can do whatever they want
just because they spend money?
Actually.
What?
Your female fans are not aggressive enough?
No, no, no.
Mulan,
what's with your breathless
and upset attitude
as if you were banned for life?
Our captain is so angry.
Why is he angry?
Last time, he was trying to convince me
to behave well.
Don't lead the public opinion myself.
We just had the talk.
And now I'm banned from the game.
That's quite bad.
If I were your captain,
I guess I'd also be furious as well.
But why didn't you explain?
You're just going to
take all this in silence?
It's not that I don't want to explain.
It'll just seem like I'm quibbling
no matter what I say.
It doesn't help.
And it's Mrs. Lu.
Mrs. Lu.
Lu Sicheng's mother.
What can I say?
What do I dare to say?
Look! Look!
It's already been posted.
(Penalty for Tong Yao's violation
Banned for one game.)
(Two months' salary and
all bonuses deducted.)
Tong Yao.
You've got quite some
ups and downs in your career.
Shut up!
What did your club PR say?
Just let your post hang like this?
What can I say?
If I apologize, I have to do it
with a good attitude.
It's only normal for my post to hang there.
Look at this.
Here is another video.
The so-called truth.
What's going on?
(Don't tell me)
(our Tong Yao got her salary deducted)
(because she refused)
(the Princess hugging interactive part)
(and pissed off
some show girls who wanted to)
(get into the players' arms.)
- Tong Yao.
(- What are you playing at?)
- Your chance has come!
Who sent the video of Comic-Con?
What video?
Not me. I didn't go that day.
I was holding you back.
Where do I get the time to
take care of such details?
It's probably a staff member,
good at leading the public opinion,
in charge of everything.
In an instant, the public opinion
is lying in the charge of him.
Awesome.
Welcome to my world.
Whoever sent it,
you're my hero.
And about what happened the other day,
I'm sorry for all the trouble
I've brought to you guys.
I apologize.
Don't say that.
Don't. I'll live a few years less for that.
Who is the hero?
- Who is it?
- Come forward.
Maybe our midsolo
would be so excited and marry him.
Ha, I knew it! For someone so far-sighted
and who can win from a thousand miles away,
that must be our…
Do you guys have way too much time?
Train. We have a match tomorrow.
Are you still angry?
Who?
- Everyone.
- Mind your own business.
Our neighbor wants to play a training match.
You guys get ready.
If you play well today, I'll buy you dinner.
Let Lu Yue play
in tomorrow's match with Obsidian.
Lu Yue should play
in the training match later too.
Let him warm up his hands.
Come on.
Give me Ootengu.
I want Ootengu.
Besides Ootengu and Higanbana,
can't you pick someone else?
Such as Marisha Ray, Aoandou,
or Enenra.
He only know how to play
these two shikigamis.
The one banned from the game
and the one who's retired,
can you guys be quiet?
No one uses the shikigamis you mentioned
during the tournament.
What's the point of practicing them?
Others don't use them. You can.
Sometimes the pattern is more important
than the version.
See?
Your opponent has chosen Enenra.
Think about it.
When you play Enenra,
which one they pick
will annoy you the most?
Cheng, give him Oitsukigami.
Even if you are a substitute,
you were at least a pro
who played full games
for two seasons last year.
You have to let Tong Yao
tell you what to choose?
How come?
Did you hear that, Cheng?
Oitsukigami.
Follow me, Enenra.
Follow me to chase Oitsukigami.
Salute.
Go, go, go.
He's still ignoring you?
K, Cat, go to the top lane.
- Yes.
- Yes, sir!
Don't just go to the top lane.
Come and take care of your midsolo, too.
Cat, I'll help you
cross the top lane early.
He is worried about you.
I sat next to him at dinner today.
I saw
him delete the video
of the program in his phone.
He asked me not to tell anyone.
What do you mean?
Quick, help me!
No matter what you think,
Lu Sicheng is first and foremost
the captain of this team.
He has the obligation to protect
each and every one of you,
and protect the team from trouble.
Last year when this kid was in trouble,
he also did a lot
to keep it down.
He was punished with a temporary ban.
If this kind of thing goes too far,
a lifetime ban is possible.
So,
there are some things he can't help you,
nor can he teach you.
Don't rely on him too much.
Understand?
Tong Yao.
You need to know
understanding yourself
- is the only way to really understand.
- Lu Yue.
I've been attacked!
A bunch of troubled kids
are always creating trouble for the captain.
It's okay.
Don't think too much. It'll all pass.
Hold on, hold on.
Don't get yourself killed, man.
Can you not be so grumpy?
Where is our midsolo?
Are you really settled to be a loser?
Shut up, I'm about to take off
once fully equipped.
I'm starving to death.
Can we still finish the game?
Come to the middle lane to push the line.
Leading the line alone,
are you waiting to be caught?
I'm coming!
Pick up a team fight.
Go, go, go!
- Ultimate skill prepared.
- Go, go, go.
Chubby, save your ultimate skill for me.
Lu Yue.
Where are you? Go.
Midsolo. Go.
One more! One more!
Just one more! Just one more!
Go, go, go!
(Victory)
- Yes!
- Nice! Yes!
How's that, Tong Yao?
It's not a bad game, right?
Ignoring your Master level
in the early stage of the match,
you destroy the turret
quite quickly with Oitsukigami.
This feels like
watching my own pup grow up.
What?
The first time we beat him in an instant.
The second time we won with ease.
The third time we felt a little resistance.
The fourth time we felt difficult.
Now we're about 50-50.
You guys, wake up.
Next time when we meet our neighboring team,
it's possible that we won't win.
Can you say something nice?
Something nice?
Sure.
From now on, during work time,
whoever is caught playing Connect the Dots,
browsing through Weibo and reading comics
will get his or her salary deducted.
Do you hear that?
Going to the gym is okay, right?
What about mahjong? It's also a competition.
Mahjong is also not allowed.
That's national culture.
Can you be more professional?
I usually watch videos of games
and occasionally play backgammon
on a break.
That's madness.
Can we please stop talking?
I'm starving.
Me, too.
Well, let's go. I'll buy you dinner.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go, let's eat.
- I'm starving.
- Let's go.
Tong Yao, what are you doing?
I'm not going.
You guys go ahead. I'm not hungry.
I'll go live streaming later.
I'm running out on my salary
with all the deduction.
I'm not in the mood to spend money.
Hundreds of thousands for one push,
isn't it expensive?
Why not buy a few purses with that money,
or buy a few dresses to have fun.
Okay, go ahead.
I'll bring you something nice
when I come back.
Behave yourself in your live streaming.
Don't talk nonsense again.
I know, I know.
Bye-bye.
Hello.
I just ordered the congee. Is it ready?
Very soon, sir.
Thank you.
Is it on mute?
Why are the fans getting all hyped
while Tong Yao is not talking?
I guess she's really learned her lesson.
She's practicing hard.
That's true.
She wouldn't be so quiet before.
Your congee is ready, sir.
Thank you.
I'm going back now.
Let's go back together
when we're done eating.
The congee will get fishy if it gets cold.
You guys eat.
Cat.
Do you understand what Cheng did just now?
What's there to wonder?
Cheng just didn't have enough to eat.
(Why did you hit others?)
(Why did you get into a fight?)
(How dare a professional player
who got into a fight)
(still come to live streaming?)
(I don't know why you girl fans)
(like to cheer for that.)
(Smiling indeed hit someone.)
(So what if she was defending her teammates?)
(These players earn up to
a million yuan a year.)
(How miserable can they
be to play an interactive game?)
(Pretentious and petty.)
This user "A passerby".
Wait a minute, don't block him yet.
Let him speak.
Players earn
hundreds of thousands of yuan a year.
Did they eat your food or spend your money?
Playing professionally is
not a monkey selling art.
We can't call it off
if we're not feeling well?
(That's non-sense.)
(A group of Internet addicts.)
(You can easily earn so much
money and still be petulant)
(playing a few games.)
Earn so much money easily?
Then you should come, too.
Come on, come on. Don't wait.
Now the clubs are all
still recruiting for youth training.
Who's stopping you?
(What's wrong with doing an activity?)
(Everyone else can do it.)
Say you have a heart condition,
and your P.E. teacher asks you
to run for 1,500 meters.
Will you go?
Others can run, but you can't?
(I saw Chubby and them
all did it in the end.)
(They were also holding those show girls,)
(smiling happily.)
What? Should they cry instead?
(If you really don't want to do it,)
(then what's the use of ZGDX staff?)
(Have a team member to bear all this.)
(You were being used and you
continued to defend them.)
(Are you happy to be punished
for what you did today?)
Yes.
I'm very happy.
Honestly,
I don't regret
insisting on not doing this game at all.
It wasn't suitable.
What's wrong?
We only learned about it
after we got there.
It was a temporary notice.
I don't blame
Rui for not being able to refuse it.
Honestly,
the only thing I regret is
this has caused a lot of trouble
for my teammates as well as the club.
They took a lot of the heat with me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I shouldn't have rushed over there.
There were so many people there.
I should have just…
So fast.
(You're so cool.)
I made a mistake, really.
I should have gently
communicated with the organizer
about the situation.
That's right.
Because some of the team members
had just finished physical therapy.
They really couldn't do strenuous exercise.
It's definitely possible
to communicate with everyone
and discuss the solution.
Yes, we are all civilized people.
Chat-room manager,
please give this "A passerby"
a small red flower.
I think he was right to scold me.
I also think I was too impulsive.
Yes, yes, yes.
Like a shrew.
A real shrew.
I really shouldn't have done it.
I shouldn't have done it.
No small red flower?
Forget it.
Thank you, Cheng.
(Your eyes are about to fall out,)
(and stick on him, anchor.)
(You turn your face around
faster than you turn a page.)
Stop it.
Captain Lu Sicheng
hasn't spoken to me all day.
It's as if I've fallen into a cold hell.
I haven't found a way to save myself yet.
I'm now still in the depths of hell.
Coax him?
Do you think he's still 3 years old?
How?
Coax him.
Yes, yes, yes.
He plays well with Hakurou.
He makes me shiver
from a thousand miles away.
This man said he was going to
report me to Cheng's room.
Where is the chat-room manager?
Block him.
This kind of people who
sows harmony between teammates
should be banned to set an example.
(Stop it, you fool.)
(Five minutes ago, the system prompted that)
(Lu Sicheng has entered
your live streaming room)
(while you were still blabbering.)
(You want to be killed?)
Everything I said was a joke.
I'm going to make a self-reflection now.
Next week at the regular meeting on Monday,
I'll deliver my 10,000-word
self-reflection speech with sincerity.
Okay, I'm going to
go write my self-reflection.
Off the air. Bye.
(Live streaming ends)
Idiot.
I'm so annoyed.
Will Lu Yue plot to usurp my throne
by this opportunity
and I'll be downgraded
to shiver by the water dispenser
for the rest of my life,
where no one will care for me in the team?
The only time my teammates will think of me
is when they order takeout.
Who's free to order takeout?
Your teammates
talk so much that
they even want to talk to the air.
Why would they leave you alone
to guard the water dispenser?
I think you're just hungry.
The captain brought you some congee, right?
Go to sleep when you're full.
The ban will be over after one game.
You may still be the starting player.
The captain won't be able to
ignore you for life.
Really?
Didn't your club already issued
the announcement?
How can it be fake?
That's not what I'm asking.
Think about it.
If he really decides
not to talk to someone for his life,
why would he worry if she is hungry
and still brings her congee?
He'd just want to push
her head into the sewer,
let her eat shit till her death, okay?
What you care about is
whether the captain cares about you or not.
Now the whole team is involved.
Do all girls in love
go insane
like you?
I...
Tong Yao?
Tong Yao.
I thought you'd be poor.
I didn't expect you to be so miserable.
What?
You've been kicked out by the captain
and are living on the streets?
We just watched you fail your live streaming.
You're screwed.
No, I'm not.
Where did you guys go after
the late-night supper?
Why did you come back so late?
No.
We didn't go anywhere.
We went straight back after dinner.
That's right.
Then how come Cheng...
Cheng said
he was afraid the congee
would get cold and fishy.
But now it seems
he was probably afraid you'd starve to death.
What did you say?
Say it again.
You two haven't spoken to each other yet?
No.
You two.
One of you is too proud.
The other is too arrogant.
Do you intend to fight for life?
That's nice.
It's hard.
Very hard.
(Group A, Game 3 ZGDX vs. Obsidian)
♪You only want to see more♪
♪We love the sharpness that comes with us♪
(Obsidian e-Sports Club)
(For all of you on site
and in front of the screen,)
(good afternoon.)
We're now at the group match of 2020
Onmyoji Arena Pro League
between Obsidian and ZGDX.
- I'm Dudou.
- I'm Qiu.
(Let's start with)
(the lineup of both sides.)
(It's worth mentioning that)
(today, ZGDX's starting midsolo)
(is Lv.)
(It's been a long time)
(since we see Lv in the arena.)
Don't worry.
The club has already arranged it.
They won't discuss your ban.
Thank you, Rui.
(I always thought Lv is)
(a very capable player.)
(But the opponent midsolo
is also quite a good player.)
(Although Obsidian's record is mediocre,)
(this particularly player
is among the top 5 midsolos)
(in the professional league.)
I ran into this midsolo on the other side
when I was playing ranking games.
He can use every shikigami.
When it comes to Lu Yue who is only good at
a few shikigamis, it's a real problem.
(Smiling, Go)
Cheng! Cheng! Cheng!
There's no way they don't know
I got banned today.
Every member of ZGDX has fans.
Most of them are die-hard fans.
Their presence here
means they haven't given up on you.
I let them down.
No way.
Mr. Wang?
Yes.
We're at the scene.
Is Lu Yue nervous?
No.
- Really?
- Play well, Lu Yue.
- No problem.
- Play well, it's on you.
Let's see if we can beat them this time.
Come on, come on.
Test, test.
Okay, okay, everybody can hear, right?
I can hear you. I can hear you.
Okay.
Higanbana and Ootengu.
Obsidian has been banned
These are the shikigamis that Lv is good at.
(It seems that Obsidian)
(has also made a targeted deployment)
(after learning Tong Yao)
(was banned from one game yesterday.)
How cunning!
Yes, take a look at ZGDX.
They've banned Aoandou and Tamamo-no-Mae.
(It seems like there's going to be
a tough fight between the two midsolos.)
(To be honest,)
(I personally look forward to
this game very much.)
(Yes, this is also a big game)
(for ZGDX.)
(If they win,)
(they will be in the top of the group)
(with a grand slam for now.)
(To be honest, I was very confident about)
(their grand slam.)
(But)
(after the incident yesterday,)
(it's quite awkward now.)
(Yes, in the first few weeks,)
(ZGDX was in a near-perfect state.)
(Even Chessman)
(who rarely praised people)
(have complimented their midsolo,)
(saying he was very confident)
(about this season's competition.)
(Now looking back to it,)
(it's quite ironic.)
(Stop it.)
(Onmyoji Arena)
(We all know that player Lv from ZGDX)
(has always been known for
his stable operation.)
(But his shikigami pool)
(has always been criticized)
(because it's too shallow.)
(Yes, and today)
(Higanbana and Ootengu have been banned.)
(I'm curious)
(what kind of shikigamis he'll use today)
(to deal with this game.)
Lu Yue.
You can take Enenra.
No problem.
Chubby.
Give Lu Yue Enenra.
Is it my brother or me?
Enenra.
Lu Yue actually took out Enenra.
In this version,
Enenra is a very strong shikigami.
Especially because he can release skills
within a super long range,
consuming the opponent on the line,
and it is also very difficult to deal with
in the late-stage team fight.
Well this way,
I do think that Enenra is
(very suitable for Lv to use.)
(I wonder what kind of performance)
(they'll bring to us.)
(Well, now that both sides)
have finished choosing their shikigamis.
Let's take a look at
the finalized list of shikigamis.
(ZGDX's topsolo, Cat)
(has Karasu Tengu.)
(And K is using Yasha.)
(The midsolo Lv has Enenra.)
(For the shooter position,
Chessman has Hakurou.)
(Chubby has Ichimoku Ren as assist.)
(Look at the Obsidian side,)
(the topsolo is Hououka,
the jungler is Itsumade.)
(The midsolo is Marisha Ray.)
(The laners on the bottom lane
are Miketsu and Hotarugusa.)
(Let's play it with a steady pace.)
The team is ready to start the game.
K, help the Cat in the early stage.
Okay.
Cheng, I'm with shift.
I'm always at your disposal.
Okay
Lu Yue, don't press the line.
Okay.
(Lv is playing very steadily.)
(That's right. Don't be
too aggressive in the early stages.)
(There's a situation in the middle lane.
There is a fight.)
(Ready to go back to his turret.)
(But obviously it's too late.)
(Enenra goes forward with an instant step.)
(Directly unleashes the skill combination
to kill off Marisha Ray.)
First Blood is amazing!
(Lv actually got First Blood.)
Good for you, Lv.
Not bad.
This is a good move.
It's pretty cool.
Lv plays Enenra
just a little bit better than I do.
A little bit?
I think he's a lot better than you.
That's right.
If I was better than him,
I would be playing professional, right?
Nice.
Not bad.
Lu Yue, join the team fight.
Get the monster after the fight.
Chubby, stay close.
Coming.
Minion, take it.
(There is a small team fight
down the bottom lane.)
(Nice!)
(Defeat)
(ZGDX killed two people,)
(winning the team fight.)
I'm going to take my line.
Come back after it.
(ZGDX is now hitting the monster.)
Shooter, watch out, don't get caught.
Try to move backwards.
(We can go up. We can go up.)
(Killed off monster)
(But there are not enough people.)
I took the monster.
Lu Yue.
Right away.
(Why is Lv still hitting the line
and not going to the team fight?)
Wait, I'm coming!
Come on, what are you doing?
(Let's go to the team fight.)
(What's with the obsession
on hitting the line?)
Lu Yue, hurry up,
I'm running out of blood too fast.
I can't take it anymore, hurry up.
Control, control, control!
Controlled, controlled.
Up, up. Good.
(Defeat)
Retreat.
Lu Yue, are your headphones working?
Can you listen to us?
(The gold advantage they just built up)
(is caught up)
(by Obsidian in this team fight.)
(Lv didn't coordinate well)
(- this time.)
- Cat, hold on. Wait for the next fight.
(Adjust and continue.)
(Cat, you're always with K.)
- Be ready anytime.
- Going the same route as before.
Good.
- Can't beat it, can't beat it.
- Help me, help me!
- Let's go, now.
- Hurry up.
(Defeat)
Last team fight, chase them.
Okay, here we go.
Go! Go!
Push it.
(Reinforcements join the battlefield)
Just push the line.
In one breath.
A chance of the last team fight.
Yes! Yes!
Lu Yue, we would've won earlier
if you played this way.
It's true.
Seeing your substitute
getting the cheers on the stage
while you can just sit here
and watch in silence,
how does it feel?
I once said in the post-game interview video,
I'm happy to have a teammate like Smiling.
Because she joined us,
ZGDX
will be stronger than ever this summer.
But now they're questioning my vision.
They are questioning
whether I made a mistake,
whether I was wrong about
the positioning of you and Lu Yue.
Why?
Keep your head up.
But I don't care if people question my vision
and my judgment.
The point is you.
It's you I care about.
(Timer)
Seven minutes left.
Before the next game starts,
I want a reason so strong that
no matter what anyone says,
I won't give up on you.
With you looking at me like this,
I can't say anything.
If you go on any longer,
I can't even remember my ID number.
6 minutes and 40 seconds left.
Can I ask a question?
In what capacity and from what position
are you asking me this?
Your captain, your teammate.
Any passerby on the street will do.
Six minutes and thirty seconds left.
What I want is an answer
that will convince everyone,
not just some double talk
to fool me.
Please be as honest
as you were yesterday
when you were talking on live.
Six minutes and twenty seconds left.
Stop the count down.
Give me some time
or give me a hint.
This came too suddenly.
I'm not prepared at all.
I can't say anything.
Start with your behavior that day.
I hit someone.
AGI's topsolo
cursed people in the ranking game
before joining the professional team,
and abused his teammates
in the early days in the professional team,
he said their skills made him sick.
That's how he was criticized
as a keyboard warrior.
Since then, everyone said he was unqualified.
He has been ridiculed for two years.
Now he won't swear for a second
even he goes live streaming
for ten hours a day,
and he will never type away his anger.
What's the use?
Still can't clear his name.
CEL's captain
was blindly arrogant, abandoned his teammates
and disappeared from training.
He even went out to play games with girls
when preparing for
the national finals tournament.
In the end, he was defeated
in the national finals.
He crossed the turret,
didn't make his ultimate skill and was killed.
He has been ridiculed to this day.
People say he deserved it
for being proud and arrogant.
Even though everyone knows that a year later,
his temper has changed greatly.
He is more discreet and restrained,
serious and calm.
What's the point?
He can't get back on.
Do you remember what I reminded you of?
Watch what I say and do.
Anything that happens
to a professional player
can be put in spotlight easily
or even kill one's career.
So don't make any trouble yourself.
Where did you put it?
The back of my head.
In yesterday's training match,
Lu Yue was killed in
3 minutes and 50 seconds.
After that,
his gold and other aspects
couldn't get up again.
Along it, at 5 minutes and 37 seconds,
7 minutes and 49 seconds,
12 minutes and 11 seconds,
K tried to raid the middle lane three times,
but they all ended in failure
because Lu Yue was used to
being a coward under his own turret.
It ended in failure.
In today's game,
just now,
at 12 minutes and 20 seconds,
when K robbed the monster,
we had four people
while the opponent had five.
But the opposing shooter
was inferior in both equipment and gold
since I contained him in the early stage.
Coming.
So it was possible for us to win.
Even if we were pinned by Obsidian,
we had a good chance to win.
At the key moment,
Lu Yue couldn't keep up the pace.
He went to the middle to collect the line.
As a result, we were one man short.
- Three against five.
- Can you listen to us?
Lu Yue, are your headphones even working?
Withdraw.
This was against Obsidian.
If it was against CK or YQCB,
we would have lost.
Feelings.
Bad coordination.
Why is that?
Because when you are in the training match,
you're used to pressing
the opponent into the turret.
K practiced a habitual
anti-ambush jungle trick because you.
Tong Yao, back up a little.
Kosodenote will come to gank you.
K, rush to support.
Coming.
(Killingspree)
She is an aggressive player.
Impulsive.
But her judgment rate is still quite high.
When she crosses the river,
I will help her ambush.
Because K changed to fit your style,
he was not able to adapt immediately
when Lu Yue came on the field.
If it were you in that fight just now,
you would have gone straight up.
So they did the same
without hesitation.
Why?
Habitual coordination.
Where did it come from?
(Defeat)
Come on, Tong Yao is on.
Come on, come on. Follow up.
(Double Kill)
Nice.
From the usual training matches
and ranking double-queues,
the team and teammates
have changed to accommodate you.
So how can you be so irresponsible?
Do you still think
you're the only one affected by the ban?
You did something wrong
and accepted the punishment.
And that's the end of the story?
You sat below the stage
and watched your teammates play.
Have you ever thought about the fact that
your teammates are
also getting punished with you?
They have to forget about
all the training with you
and start adapting again.
If you're not repented
the first time you get banned
and you make the same mistake
and get yourself banned again,
will the team still hire you?
Should you still be allowed to
participate in future training matches?
Should you still be invited to ranking?
Should the team change their style again
because of you?
There are many people
who are good at this game.
There are countless people
waiting to replace you.
Should we continue to use you
or should we use Lu Yue?
Or do we recruit a new midsolo?
Lu Yue was banned for being impulsive.
He hurt Ming.
He was the reason that we can't
participate in the national finals.
He came back in disgrace this time.
His teammates chose to forgive him.
You can ask him
if he has forgiven himself by now.
Thoughts.
Onmyoji Arena is a team game.
There is no individual heroism
in e-sports.
Three minutes left.
As I said,
I don't care what everyone else thinks.
All I care about is how you see yourself.
Continue or quit.
Professional gaming
isn't where you can do as you please.
Professional careers are short.
The golden pinnacle is fleeting.
You can't afford to waste yourself,
and certainly can't afford to delay others.
And I am the captain of the team.
Miss.
I don't care what you think.
But I'm sure
that as a top professional team,
ZGDX wants you here to play the games.
There may be people in this industry
who treat you differently
because you're a girl,
they might look down on you,
discriminate against you, admire you,
love you or take pity on you.
But I won't.
In my opinion,
you have an identity that
has nothing to do with gender
as soon as you put on the team uniform.
That's my teammate.
Cheng.
Cheng, open the door.
Time's up.
It seems like you still
don't have anything to say to me.
I don't know how to say nice things.
And I don't know how to apologize
without a proper reason.
All I know is
I want to win every game with you guys,
and not to miss a single one of them.
I don't want to let you guys down again.
I don't want to be
a stumbling block for anyone.
I want to be your teammate,
and wait for the day when
I can stand on the top of the world
where you and I are both striving to reach.
I know you've been wronged.
You may think that
you were defending your teammates.
Why do you have to be treated like this?
We all thank you for your defense.
So we finally played that game
in order to help you
change some people's opinions,
and tried to collect more evidence.
I do as well.
I also thank you for defending me.
But I'm not asking you
to get rid of your edges.
Miss.
I just want you to know,
before you protect others,
you must first learn to protect yourself.
When will I be able to protect myself?
When you are so strong
that no one can defeat you.
Captain.
Cheng.
What are you doing?
It's almost time to play.
I'm going to the game.
Cheng.
Are you one of those people?
What?
Strong enough to be fearless.
I'm not.
I have my fears,
hesitations,
and times when I don't know what to do.
Cheng.
One last question.
Go ahead.
You've been ignoring me
for the past few days.
Is it just because you're angry,
or because of something else?
Because I was afraid.
My captain, it's about to start.
I was afraid I'd go soft-hearted.
♪You say the world
is always not gentle enough♪
♪Fortunately, you're free,
the most special player♪
♪Invite me to be your number one teammate♪
♪So I had my first encounter with my dreams♪
♪You said you'd always be behind me♪
♪Rumors ran to me and hurt you♪
♪How long will it take
from now to the future♪
♪You're love that never needs a reason♪
♪I want to be close to you,
a little closer to you♪
♪You can be expressionless
and pretend to be calm♪
♪The rhythm of your heart is the best proof♪
♪You never say anything,
your eyes send a message♪
♪You and I are the only ones
in the world who understand each other♪
♪The moment you think of me♪
♪I happen to be thinking of you too♪
♪I want to be closer to you,
a little closer to you♪
♪You can be expressionless,
pretending to be calm♪
♪The rhythm of your heart is the best proof♪
♪You never say anything,
your eyes send a message♪
♪You and I are the only ones in the world
who understand each other♪
♪The moment you think of me♪
♪I happen to be thinking of you too♪
♪You never say anything,
your eyes send a message♪
♪You and I are the only ones in the world
who understand each other♪
♪I like in every season♪
♪I'm at the top of your list♪