=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 46=
Bai Jue, you call yourself True God?
Lord of the World?
I’ll tell Yuanqi
his biological father
is North Sea Lord, Qingmu.
You don’t
deserve him.
I won’t see you
or think about you
ever again.
Tell me everything.
That day,
I did go to the Dome
with the Ancestral Sword to see Bai Jue.
In my defense, I was only there
to reopen the God Realm.
There was no conspiracy whatsoever.
Have you got any proof?
As unreliable as I seem,
I wouldn’t sink so low to work with him.
That’s more like it.
What else?
What do you mean?
What else are you keeping from me?
Nothing.
Really?
Yes!
Yuanqi,
what do I always say to you?
Being honesty is the fundamental law.
Where’s Gu Jun?
He...
He’s supporting the God Realm.
Tianqi,
why are you still lying?
Do you also think
an immortal’s life is nothing?
No, Shanggu...
I...
I start to think
Yuemi and Zhiyang
aren’t in the God Realm as you said.
That’s another lie, isn’t it?
Aunt, don’t cry.
You’re making me cry, too.
Uncle Tianqi knows he’s wrong.
Yuanqi,
tell me
who named you.
At first, I was called “Qi”,
meaning abandon.
Mother left me.
Father abandoned me,
hence that name.
Yuanqi,
listen,
all parents in the world
love their children.
I’m sure yours loved you dearly.
You’re more important than everything,
including their own lives.
If he asks you about his parents,
just tell him
his father is North Sea Lord, Qingmu.
He was a hero
who always fought for
the weak against the strong.
He was dedicated
to his love and justice.
Your mother
led a wonderful life.
She had close friends...
She has a caring Father and a loving husband.
She was carefree throughout her life.
She had a caring Father
and a loving husband.
She was carefree throughout her life.
Shanggu,
does that remind you of something?
Are you afraid it does?
Uncle Tianqi told me
my Father is Qingmu and Bai Jue.
They’re the same person.
Bai Jue brought you up yesterday.
What... what did he say?
He said
it’s not that he didn’t want you
or love you.
But he can’t forgive himself
because of guilt.
He told me
he isn’t good enough for you.
I’ve never looked down on him.
You’re his flesh and blood, Yuanqi.
One day,
he’ll get over the past
and let it go.
Then he’ll come to you.
Will he?
When have I ever lied to you?
Uncle Tianqi.
Yuanqi,
this whole thing is too complicated.
I was going to tell you
once you’re old enough to understand.
Yuanqi,
when your mother Houchi
gave birth to you,
my Spiritual Strength was inside her.
Yuanqi,
from now on,
I’ll be your mother, alright?
Mother.
Mother!
Congratulations, Your Highness!
You’ve gained devil power!
After the Tribulation,
you’ll become the Overlord.
This day has finally come.
We’ve been living in constant fear
year after year.
Now, all that will come to an end.
60,000 years ago,
in the God-Demon battle,
Xuanyi was outnumbered
and crushed by Gods.
This time,
I’ll take the three True Gods
down one by one.
All Three Realms will be in my pocket.
The world
will be under my feet!
What?
The Nether World is unstable.
Your Majesty, have you wondered
why that devil became powerful enough
to be the new Devil God
after hiding for 100 years?
Lord,
what are you implying?
According to those
ancient books and records I read,
one whose power reaches God’s level
can conceal the Devilish Energy.
I killed Yuemi.
What did you say?
I’ve lied to you for 60,000 years.
So all these years,
you’ve never changed.
Murder,
jealousy,
fear,
greed,
all those sins
have demonized you long ago.
That battle 100 years ago
killed and injured
tons of Demons.
Thanks to your company
these years,
we can recuperate.
I wouldn’t take credit for it.
All that owes to Master Bai Jue.
Your Majesty, you’ve been through a lot.
Your Majesty...
Qin,
I did tons of stupid things
that hurt and disappointed you so much.
Since Father left,
all I have is you.
Without you,
I wouldn’t have come this far.
Qin,
once we return to Xuanjing Palace,
I’ll ask the Fox Clan to marry you.
You’ll be my empress.
Hold on.
Don’t turn me down so soon.
I’ve meant to do that for so long.
Please give me a chance.
I’ll show you
the old Sen Yu is gone.
The man you see today
will only belong to you
forever and ever.
What do you think?
Could you
give me some time?
Sure.
I’ll wait.
Report!
Prince Jingjian from
the Heavenly Palace is outside.
I knew that old fart
would ask him to be the messenger.
Greetings, Prince Jingjian, Fengran.
Prince Jingjian,
don’t give me your Father’s crap,
or our newly restored peace
would be gone.
You should’ve seen him in the Dome.
He was such a hypocrite!
Let’s not point fingers first.
You should keep the promise
you made to Master Bai Jue
and withdraw your troops immediately.
The longer the confrontation,
the bigger the risk.
That’s a flagrant violation
of our peace agreement.
Sen Yu is still upset about
what happened in the Dome.
Please don’t mind him.
I know him well.
Immortals way crossed the line!
I couldn’t just suck it up.
I sincerely apologize to you
on behalf of them and my father.
Save it.
I hate that kind of routine.
I know
we’re sort of to blame
by disturbing the Human Realm.
Still, you...
Well...
Well... this tastes good.
Have a bite.
Sen Yu knows it’s your favorite.
He picked them himself
in the third heaven
and he was going to bring them to you.
That’s too kind of you, Sen Yu.
It’s nothing.
You saved my life.
Jingjian,
may I speak to you in private?
Please.
Come here.
Have a seat.
Jingjian,
I’d like to
ask you something.
Go ahead.
Rumor has it
that Fengran and your mother
are mortal enemies.
Is that true?
It is.
Then how come you two
are still so sweet
and close as a whole all these years?
My mother is unforgivable,
but Fengran is lenient enough
to ignore her.
It does sound like
you choose your wife over your mother.
You don’t know what happened
and I can’t tell you that.
How about this?
Let me ask you a few questions.
Fire away.
Can anyone decide their births
or parents?
Of course not.
Can anyone hide their feelings
to not be hurt by love?
No.
If you were me,
could you find a way
to bury the hatchet
between my love and my mother?
No.
Since there’s nothing you can do,
why not let it go?
I used to
think too much.
Fengran is much better
than me in that regard.
She abhors evil.
She knows what to love and hate.
She taught me not to
run away from difficulties.
I’m more than content
to have her in my life!
I was eager to kill Wu Huan,
but I chose not to
for Jingjian’s sake.
Chief Goddess Shanggu is back.
She never tolerates anything evil.
I’m sure she’ll bring justice
to my parents
and restore peace in all Three Realms.
I’m happy for you.
About what?
That you’ve finally
found the love of your life.
How are you and Sen Yu?
He proposed to me just now.
I didn’t say yes.
You made the right choice.
Let him wait for another
eight or nine hundred years.
Fengran,
something bad is happening. Let’s go.
I’ve checked.
They all died of energy loss.
They look the same as those
killed by Devilish Energy
in the Parasol Forest.
Did that killer kill them too?
Did anyone see how they died?
No.
This place is only one kilometer
from your camp.
That’s right.
So?
How come our soldiers died here?
Jingjian,
Demons are aboveboard.
We’d admit to our murder.
I understand
your father doesn’t trust us,
but you too?
Then they could only
be killed by immortals.
You think she did it?
Soldiers died
right before the withdrawal.
The killer must’ve done that
to incite another war
in the Demon Region.
I’ll go back to report to Father.
Jingjian,
don’t you think
there’s another possibility?
Please enlighten me, Father.
The one who killed the three soldiers
isn’t an Immortal
or a Demon,
but a Devil.
Earlier today,
reports came in from
the three lower realms
that Devilish Energy
had wreaked havoc everywhere.
I’m afraid a new Devil God
has appeared in the Nether World.
Devil God?
Is he behind the massacre
of the Feng Clan 100 years ago?
I believe so
even without any proof.
Who is it?
What are you talking about?
You didn’t even notice I came in.
What brings you here?
I’ve prepared food at Fuyao Hall.
Jingzhao and Jingyang are already there.
It’s a family dinner.
It’s been a while
since we sat together
and talked to each other.
I made this soup for you.
Jingyang,
when you were little,
you always took food from your siblings.
A big bowl of fish soup wasn’t enough.
I was naughty.
I always thought others’ food
tasted better.
Come to think of it,
I haven’t cooked for 60,000 years.
Does the fish soup still taste the same?
Father,
the Demon Region needs me.
Please excuse me.
Good day.
Jingjian,
we’re having a family dinner.
It won’t take long.
Must you leave now?
I can’t remember the last time
we had dinner together.
Whatever business you have,
finish the soup first.
I’m not hungry.
Jingjian!
Are you turning your back on us
for that woman?
Just enjoy the food
without me.
Jingjian!
I’m sick of his attitude!
Forget about him.
Let him go.
Are you done with your soup?
Three more soldiers were killed
in the Demon Region.
The cause of death is unknown.
I have a reason to believe that
someone killed them
for ulterior motives.
Jingyang,
why do you think
anyone would kill them?
I guess
maybe...
maybe Demons killed them to...
Demons again.
What’s your problem with them?
Or are you covering for someone?
Jingzhao,
the Nether World
has shown strange signs.
Nowhere can see them
more clearly than the Dome.
Why didn’t you tell me?
Father,
I didn’t notice anything.
Being with Master for the past 100 years
has taught you nothing
but only made you overbearing.
Wu Huan,
taking only three lives is so not you.
You have to do more
to play Immortals and Demons off
against each other.
What are you talking about?
When did I kill them?
Other than those three soldiers,
Fengran’s parents,
Bi Xi, who guarded
the Ghost Suppressing Tower,
Elder Danfeng
and my master Yuemi
all died in your hands.
I cannot cover for you again,
or I’d fail as the Heavenly Emperor
and a father.
You’re right.
I killed them all.
It’s really you.
I can’t find
any Devilish Energy on you,
but we can go to Master Shanggu.
Let her check
if you’ve really become a devil.
Even if she comes,
I’m not afraid of her,
let alone you.
It was you
who dumped me
into the Nether World.
I was so desperate to survive
that Devilish Energy
got the better of me.
It’s all your fault!
Mother!
Jingyang,
you’re always on my side.
Move!
I can do anything for you,
but now, you...
I’m doing this for our family.
Your Father is tired.
Let him rest.
Jingyang!
You’re a Goddess.
True Gods entrusted you
with the safety of the Three Realms!
So what if they’re True Gods?
Devil God was one of them.
When creating the universe,
Qingtian said
all six worlds are a whole.
Gods and Devils are equal.
But there are good and bad ones.
Without Devils,
the four True Gods
wouldn’t have perished.
The God Realm wouldn’t have collapsed.
Devils are our mortal enemies!
You’re stupid!
Muguang,
aren’t the Three Realms thriving
under our leadership?
We’ve established
total supremacy for 60,000 years.
Once the God Realm reopens
and Shanggu returns to power,
we’ll go back to the pathetic old days
and grovel to others.
But without the God Realm
and True Gods,
we’ll dominate the Three Realms forever!
Why did you
become like this?
I shall be the head
of this household.
Father! Father!
One day, you’ll understand
that I made the right choice.
In the Three Realms,
only the winner gets to make rules.
Being a devil or not
isn’t important.
I’m powerful enough
to battle any True God.
Jingzhao,
nothing can hold you back.
Once Bai Jue is gone,
victory can be expected.
It’s cold outside.
Why weren’t you resting inside?
I couldn’t sleep.
We were so close to
withdrawing the troops,
but Immortals accused Demons
of killing their soldiers.
The tension is on again.
They’ve been against each other
for thousands of years.
The long-running feud
isn’t that easy to be resolved.
Prince Jingjian.
We were going to retreat,
but Immortals were hostile
and wouldn’t do the same.
What do you suggest?
I’ve reported the deaths
of the three soldiers to Father.
Please give me some more time.
It’s difficult to remove overnight
all the grievances
accumulated over the years.
I understand.
But let me be clear.
If the war is on,
we’ll battle it out with you.
Calm down.
We must find the cause of their deaths
for the crisis to subside.
Sen Yu, trust me.
I’ll do my utmost
to stop another war.
After all,
the last thing we want to see
is more deaths.
Fine.
If you won’t strike,
neither will I.
Look.
The drum has been beaten so many times
that it’s cracking.
It contains spiritual power.
Self-healing can take
thousands of years.
I wish it was intact.
Don’t worry.
Just wait for it.
It’ll be as good as new.
Yuemi,
I’ve told Shanggu you’re
in the God Realm so many times,
that I almost
start to believe that myself.
Back then, I ignored your feelings.
So many years have passed.
I’m still alone.
That’s probably karma.
Now, Shanggu regards Yuanqi as her son
as I expected.
Bai Jue becomes a complete villain.
Things play out
as we imagined.
The problem is
Shanggu will regain
her memory sooner or later.
I wonder how she will feel
about Bai Jue’s plan
over the past 60,000 years.
I won’t judge them.
Let’s drink.
It’s too late to regret.
Why would you rather
be with her in the first place?
Yuemi,
is it really you?
Look at the night sky.
It’s starry.
Tianqi, I’m back.
♪How much luck do I need♪
You’re really back!
Yuemi!
It’s my fault.
You died because of me.
Tianqi,
don’t blame yourself.
It was heaven
that played a cruel joke on us.
But don’t worry.
From now on,
I won’t leave you ever again.
You...
You aren’t Yuemi!
I should’ve killed you long ago.
He just died like this?
Tianqi is the God of Water.
His death
will change the sky.
My devil power is invincible.
The Three Realms
shall prepare for a new ruler!
Master.
Tianqi still hasn’t come back?
Yes.
I’m getting worried.
Don’t be.
If you find the wind
and the rain too strong,
I’ll activate the barrier
to block them.
It’s still early in autumn.
How come it’s freezing?
Greetings, Master.
What can I do for you?
Devil God has appeared,
damaging the Three Realms
with the Devilish Power.
You must’ve heard that
in the Heavenly Palace.
Father is also concerned about it.
He said he’d come to consult you.
I found
that Devil God is as powerful as Xuanyi.
Immortals must work together
to get rid of that devil.
None of us
can beat the Devil God alone.
Tomorrow,
I’ll invest the power of the Dome
in the battle.
Just leave now.
You can no longer stay here.
Master,
I understand I’m insignificant.
But over the years,
I’ve been serving you
with my heart and soul.
I need to ask you something
before leaving.
Have you ever had any feelings for me?
Jingzhao,
you’re still young.
It’s not wrong to be vain,
but greed can bury you.
You’d better let go of your obsession
and find a new way
to cultivate yourself.
Honestly,
if there’s any regret in my life,
that is, we didn’t have
the cross-cupped wine
on our wedding day.
I might not be able to
see you again.
We’ve been together for 100 years
as if we’re a couple.
All I’m asking for
is to drink with you before departure.
That’ll be our farewell drink.
Please.
What’s in the drink?
How dare you poison me!
Your drink was poisoned
by the seed of Decide Flower
and my Mother’s devil power.
You’ll be gone
in a few minutes.
How come the snow is so heavy?
What is happening?
The frozen earth
indicates that fire is dying out.
That’s Bai Jue’s power.
Is he in danger?
Heavenly Emperor’s edict is as follows:
True God Bai Jue died of
unbalanced energy.
Princess Jingzhao
will take over the Dome hence.
Master,
are you happy
with that announcement?
Who do you think you are?
I’m no longer a humble maid.
Just so you know,
Tianqi already died before you.
After you,
Shanggu will be my next target.
From this moment on,
I’ll be the supreme lord
of all Three Realms!
Master.
Look!
That’s from the Dome.
How come the Devilish Energy
is so strong?
Chang Que,
stay and watch
the Qingchi Palace and Yuanqi.
Close the gate.
No one shall get in or out.
Yes.
I’m announcing to the world
that we’re mourning for
(Changyuan Hall)
True God Bai Jue for three years.
Yes, Your Highness.
Are you blind?
That woman is a devil!
Rebels,
gossipers
and blasphemer
shall all be executed!
Look!
How did Devils get
the Demon Gathering Streamer?
We aren’t able to stop her.
If we don’t get the Streamer back,
they won’t stop moving
until death.
That’ll cause catastrophic damage
to both Demons and Immortals.
Hang in there!
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪