=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 45=
Please punish me.
Houchi?
Who is that?
After I woke up,
the Three Realms have all changed.
My memory still remains
at the Nether World.
The Nether World?
We haven’t met for long.
As my servant,
you didn’t even greet me.
I’m sorry.
You just awakened.
Do you
feel well?
I am energetic,
full of the Power of Chaos.
Never mind.
Since it’s all in the past,
I’d say something else.
Over these 60 thousand years,
have you been the Leader
of the Feng Clan?
Master, you don’t know.
When the God Realm was in chaos,
the Feng Clan was in a panic.
Elder Feng Yun appointed me
to be the Leader.
I could not refuse
but accepted.
It’s known by the Three Realms.
If you don’t believe it,
you may ask other immortals.
Since you’re the Leader
of the Feng Clan,
why did you kill Wuxi and Feng Yan?
I am wronged, Master.
It’s Elder Danfeng who killed Feng Yan.
Who is Elder Danfeng?
What’s the feud
between Feng Yan and her?
Elder Danfeng has killed herself.
I didn’t know the truth.
You mean,
there is no evidence for these things?
I didn’t mean that.
After 60 thousand years,
you’ve changed a lot.
No.
I just underestimated you
from the very beginning.
Wu Huan.
I don’t wanna see you again.
When the God Realm is reopened,
you shall not enter it.
Yes, Master.
(Daze Mansion)
Do you eat this?
I wanna eat this.
This? Okay.
Here.
It’s good.
Is it?
Did Master Shanggu really awaken?
If it’s true,
wasn’t the wedding
of True God Bai Jue...?
Things have changed.
The Heavenly Palace
would have a disaster.
I am Donghua.
My respect, Master.
Aunt, did you help me get revenge?
I wouldn’t let you suffer.
You may all rise.
It’s Lord Donghua’s birthday today.
I came in a hurry.
Yuanqi dirtied your Spiritual Spring.
We are so sorry.
Your presence
has been a great honor for me.
I refined this elixir
when I was bored.
It was made as candy for Yuanqi.
Now I give it to you
as a gift.
It’s refined by True God.
It can ascend an immortal to a god.
It’s a great gift.
Thank you, Your Grace.
You are welcome.
Fengran told me
you’re of great potential.
I guess you’ll soon ascend to a god.
After your ascension,
you may visit the Pilgrimage Hall
when you’re free.
Thanks for your blessings.
Do you mean
you’ll soon go back to the God Realm?
But it was closed
60 thousand years ago.
I have a plan for it.
Let’s go.
My respect, Master.
Jingzhao.
Are you the daughter
of Muguang and Wu Huan,
the woman Bai Jue just married?
Yes.
I slept for tens of thousands of years.
I know little about the things
in the Immortal Realm.
I wonder how old you are.
I am 20 thousand years old.
20 thousand years old?
You’re no longer young.
Let me ask you.
Have you ever taken charge of
the Three Realms
and benefited the people
as your father did?
No.
Have you ever set up a sect,
cultivated disciples as Donghua did
and made contributions
to the Three Realms?
You neither earned honor
nor made contributions.
Do you have the right to see me?
Just because you are
the Princess of Heavenly Palace?
Don’t you want to know
this kid’s identity?
- His mother is...
- Jingzhao.
Mother.
Yuanqi.
Who hit you just now?
Mother.
Wu Huan.
You are the Heavenly Empress.
I’ll show you some respect.
You shall disciple your daughter
and never repeat
the same mistake.
Mother.
Did she really slap Wu Huan?
What was her look?
Did her face
turn purple with rage?
You don’t allow us
to go to Mount Lookout, do you?
Why are you asking?
Do you want a weapon or not?
It depends on what it is.
You...
That Wu Huan
was slapped by my aunt.
Her face swelled like a pig.
How could Bai Jue
marry that woman Jingzhao?
Yuanqi is a good kid.
Poor boy.
Shanggu.
Be honest.
Do you mind that
Bai Jue married another woman?
He’s so cruel to his own son.
Isn’t it ridiculous
if I still care about
the old affections?
By the way,
is Yuanqi’s birth mother named Houchi?
How did you know it?
Can’t I know it?
Do I have anything to do with Houchi?
You shouldn’t go to Mount Lookout.
She has passed away.
You don’t have to know.
Just 60 thousand years.
Why is everyone so strange?
Strange?
I’m the same as ever.
I have no secret to you.
Tianqi.
The thing about reopening
the God Realm...
Since you’ve awakened
and all things are set,
it’s time to reopen the God Realm.
I’ll cultivate hard
and recover my power.
Then we may have a try
at the Bronze Bridge.
Sure.
That boy.
I have to repair it for him.
Yuanqi.
Aunt.
What is it, Aunt?
Keep an eye on your uncle.
If he has any move,
tell me immediately.
Uncle Tianqi?
Is it okay?
When it’s done...
The delicious wonton in Southsea.
Deal.
Hadn’t Muguang gotten in my way,
I could’ve killed Houchi.
There would be no shame like this!
Wu Huan.
Master Shanggu awakened.
That’s a huge matter.
I was going to the Xuantian Hall
to tell you about it.
At the Mount Lookout,
Chief Goddess told me
she’d cultivate in seclusion
in Qingchi Palace.
The day to reopen the God Realm
will soon come.
In that case,
I might not disturb her.
Well, I have something to ask you.
Go ahead, Your Majesty.
Where is Fengnyu?
Fengnyu?
She told me she’d cultivate
in the mortal world.
I agreed.
She might’ve gone back
to the Parasol Forest.
Don’t you surely know it?
I dare not deceive you.
The Immortal Realm
isn’t peaceful lately.
Many immortals were murdered.
According to investigation,
their death has something
to do with Fengnyu.
Fengnyu is kind by nature.
How could she kill them?
Your Majesty.
Be sure to look into it.
I hope she didn’t.
I’m going to the Dome.
If there’s any news about Fengnyu,
let me know immediately.
Shanggu is already strong.
The fight against True God
must not be delayed.
Now,
we must estrange them
to turn the tide.
Go to the Demon Region.
I need more evil force.
Yes.
I’m not missing you.
I’m just used to wearing it.
My wrist feels light if it’s taken off.
Aunt.
Why haven’t you gone to bed?
Shouldn’t it be my question?
I’ve done my job well.
I saw Uncle Tianqi sneaking
out of Qingchi Palace.
He seldom hangs out all these years.
He has no friends.
It’s fishy.
You can still catch up with him.
When I’m back,
I’ll take you to Southsea
for wonton.
It’s great to have a mother.
Aren’t they unacquainted?
Why did Tianqi give Ancestral Sword
to Bai Jue?
Find a chance to open the God Realm.
Shanggu is already suspecting.
If this continues,
she’d recall her past with you.
I’ll watch over Jingzhao.
She won’t say anything more.
If Shanggu comes again,
just give her the cold shoulder.
If it doesn’t work,
play some tricks.
Tricks?
What are they talking about?
I can’t hear clearly.
What are you doing?
If I remember correctly,
I’ve told you
not to come to the Dome.
Where is my Ancestral Sword?
Why can’t I sense it?
Is it your excuse to get in my room?
I saw
Tianqi and you plotting something.
If it doesn’t work,
play some tricks.
Our relationship long ended
60 thousand years ago.
You keep harassing me.
I feel troubled.
I’ve died once
in the battle with Xuanyi.
Thus,
I meant it
when I told you
that I wanted a new life.
If you can’t forget me,
I’m glad to have some pleasure.
Bai Jue.
You are so disgusting now.
Disgusting?
Those girls all like it.
Don’t take yourself so seriously.
Tianqi and you must hide something
from me.
I’ll figure it out.
Master.
Muguang and Sen Yu are here.
Yuanqi.
Where’s your mother?
I can’t find her so early.
Where did she go?
Uncle Tianqi has come back.
Why hasn’t my mother been back?
Didn’t she tell you?
I just got up.
I don’t know where she went.
Never mind.
Given your mother’s power,
she’s unrivalled in the Three Realms.
She must be bored
and hang out alone.
That’s nonsense.
She won’t go alone.
She’ll take me along
if she hangs out.
Yuanqi.
What’s the matter?
Tell me the truth.
Are you hiding something from me?
No.
No?
Why do I feel
you’ve gotten ungrateful
since your mother awakened?
If I help you,
I’d be truly ungrateful.
You and your mother
cheated me once.
Are you doing it again?
Don’t be oversensitive.
Be honest.
Where has your mother gone?
Uncle Tianqi.
I wanna eat
the delicious wonton in Southsea.
Tell me first.
I get dizzy when I’m hungry.
I can’t recall anything.
Mother said
the wonton in Southsea is the best.
I wanna eat it now.
You...!
You’re so tricky.
Wait here.
(Changyuan Hall)
You said I indulged my subordinates.
Any evidence?
Show me.
Is it groundless?
Alright.
We’ve talked for a while.
It’s already noon.
Why don’t we eat something
as we talk?
How is it?
Are you dizzy now?
I think of it.
My mother went out last night.
But I don’t know
where she went.
Last night?
What time was it?
Why didn’t I notice it?
You just sneaked out of Qingchi Palace.
Of course you didn’t.
How did you know I sneaked out?
I happened to see it. A coincidence.
Coincidence?
You should’ve gone to bed.
I went out to pee.
Did she tail me
last night?
Tell me honestly.
She thought you’re fishy,
so she let me keep an eye on you.
I saw that you went out.
So she followed you.
You...!
Are you so obedient to her?
I can’t be ungrateful, can I?
You can’t betray her?
I shouldn’t be so nice to you.
Give it back.
Uncle Tianqi.
These are my dried fruits
and snacks I saved.
Take them.
Uncle Tianqi.
Don’t be angry with me. Okay?
Ouch! Ouch!
Only this time.
Don’t do it again.
You have my word.
These are your favorite.
Have them yourself.
Did you do anything wrong
that you don’t want her to know?
(Endure the Hardship)
Why can’t I sense the Ancestral Sword?
Who are you?
Chief Goddess.
Sorry, I didn’t know it’s you.
Please punish me.
Do you know me?
It’s windy here.
Don’t catch a cold.
In terms of your vibe, appearance,
and power,
you’re not half as good as Hongri.
I’m humble,
from the Abyssal Ridge Swamp.
I’m not on a par with God Hongri.
You look ingratiating.
You are indeed the type Bai Jue likes.
I’m flattered.
You may rise.
Thank you.
My master is having dinner
with Muguang and Sen Yu.
He doesn’t wanna see me.
I don’t wanna see him either.
Master.
You are noble.
And you are close to my master.
You can come and go as you please.
Right?
That’s pleasant to hear.
I’m flattered, Master.
When the God Realm is reopened,
please do take care of me.
Back then
when you were badly injured
and got unconscious,
I was the person
who escorted you back to Qingchi Palace.
Was I badly injured?
Who injured me?
Well...
Tell me!
I did it only on orders.
I knew nothing.
Nothing.
What’s the sound?
It could be the dancers
at my master’s banquet.
He does have the mood.
I’m going to report.
Hold on.
What’s the order, Master?
I’m hungry,
but I don’t wanna contact
with these people.
If you don’t mind,
you may go with my look.
Eat and then just leave.
Good idea.
What’s your name?
Three-head Fire Dragon.
You are clever.
Lead the way.
This way, please.
Greetings, Mother.
Mother.
What’s the hurry to summon me here?
Master Bai Jue
grounds me for one year,
for I brought up Houchi
to Master Shanggu.
I came secretly.
What?
Just because
we offended Shanggu yesterday
at Donghua’s birthday party?
Yes.
Is Father angry with you?
It seems
you no longer have a position
in the Dome.
You cannot gain respect
in the name of Bai Jue.
Not that serious.
Even for the sake
of my father,
- he would...
- I know your father well.
Other than the men,
we must rely on ourselves.
Mother, what do you mean?
I’ll let you be the Master of the Dome.
Mother.
Are you killing a god?
Are you crazy?
Jingzhao.
You no longer have affections
to Bai Jue.
Why don’t you gamble on it?
Let me go.
No.
- Let go! Let go!
- Jingzhao.
I wouldn’t risk our lives
if it’s not guaranteed.
What’s wrong with Master?
He drinks today,
and even watches the dance.
It’s too odd.
Could it be a trap plotted by Master
and Muguang?
A trap.
It must be a trap.
They want me to withdraw troops
by pleasing me.
I’m starving.
Disgusting.
Ignore him.
The braised pork is fat but not greasy.
Good.
Hey. You say it.
Master.
I have something to say.
Cultivation
is all about improving power.
The demons only mean to
improve their cultivation.
Yes.
We went too far.
For the good wine,
I’ll bear with it.
If the immortals can retreat first
and lend your land to us
for cultivation,
we will be good.
Dream on.
Demons and immortals
are of the same origin.
Now
you occupy the land of power,
while we have to cultivate
at the barren land.
It’s unfair.
Good land belongs to the capable.
It’s been a rule
since the ancient time.
If you don’t agree,
try to take it!
You...!
Demon King. Heavenly Emperor.
You must be drunk.
A war comes with casualties.
You may both compromise.
The demons should compromise first.
What are you talking about?
You are a demon!
Take your time.
I’m going to pee.
Wait.
You took 1,000 Sacred Beads
and promised to help me.
Do you deny it?
Like master, like servant.
Demon King.
What are you whispering with him?
Why don’t you tell me?
Okay, I’ll cut to the chase.
Master.
He complained to me
how hard the cultivation was
in the Abyssal Ridge Swamp.
Now he said otherwise.
I think
he must’ve been coerced by someone.
Sen Yu.
Don’t forget you’re a junior.
Nor should you forget
where you are.
Isn’t it the Dome?
A corrupted place.
A den of iniquity.
True Gods indulge themselves.
Divine Beasts bribe.
Immortals and demons are
at each other’s throats.
Is it something new
during my 60-thousand-year sleep?
Master.
You may all leave.
- Yes.
Bai Jue used to be my master.
You like drinking with girls.
As your disciple,
I should serve you.
Come on, Master Bai Jue.
A toast to you.
What?
You drank with dancers.
Wouldn’t you drink with me?
The wine...
The wine is for heartless men.
It will kill them.
Are you a heartless man as well?
It’s fine.
I can make a cure for you.
It won’t take long,
just 60 thousand years.
Is it fun
to make me a fool?
Do you have no heart?
Was the wound on your chest
made by Yuanqi’s mother?
What do you mean?
If I were her,
I’d stab you too.
You have no heart to Jingzhao,
or to Yuanqi’s mother.
You’re even so cruel
to your own son.
I laughed at myself.
Back in the Nether World,
I foolishly
wished to be the right person for you.
Drink no more.
I wished to see you when I woke up,
to tell you what I experienced
in the Nether World
60 thousand years ago.
But what about you?
Two marriages.
A son who hates your guts.
You’re unfaithful.
Given what you did,
how should I face you?
What should I face my affections to you?
♪Blocked between my eyebrows♪
My love to you
is built up bit by bit.
Now it’s all deducted by you.
Isn’t it what you expected?
As you wish.
♪What’s in my hand is
what I can’t get over♪
♪How are we destined to meet♪
♪Tide rushes and the moon rises♪
♪The trip takes a thousand years♪
♪Wake up the clouds♪
♪But can’t wake up the helpless love♪
♪It’s dreamlike♪
♪And it’s also aimless♪
♪For one single glance at you♪
♪I don’t regret cultivating myself♪
♪Even if I have to love alone♪
♪I’ll never stop loving you♪
Slowly, Master. Mind the steps.
Don’t follow me. I’m not drunk.
I won’t tell anyone
what happened today.
You are smart.
I don’t worry about that.
Did you take 1,000 Sacred Beads
from him?
2,000.
1,000 from Muguang.
1,000 from Sen Yu.
No wonder you asked me to go.
Bai Jue and you are a perfect match.
I’m flattered.
My respect, Master.
Have you forgotten what I said
at the Mount Lookout?
I’m humble.
I shouldn’t show up in front of you.
But I
have something
that you should know.
Your Grace.
What are you doing?
Do you forget Master Bai Jue’s order?
Master is intelligent.
Even if I don’t say it,
I guess you’ve suspected it.
Am I right?
Master.
Princess Jingzhao
is meeting with Master Shanggu.
Master.
You have the Three Realms,
yet I only have Master Bai Jue.
I beg you to leave him,
and leave the Dome.
If you agree,
I’ll tell you everything.
Are you threatening me
with my curiosity?
I dare not.
I just wanna tell you
Qingmu and Houchi’s stories,
and exchange Bai Jue’s past
for a favor from you.
Please fulfill my wish.
Why do I need you
to tell me our affairs?
I shouldn’t have come today.
I’ve never seen you in such a hurry.
What?
Is here something
that I can’t see
or are you afraid that
Jingzhao has told me something?
I’ll tell you
what you want to know.
Okay.
Tell me then.
What’s the relationship
between Houchi and me?
Who is Qingmu?
The God Realm was sealed.
You didn’t involve in it.
I was badly hurt and got in sleep.
My body conceived Qingmu in North Sea.
Are you Qingmu?
Am I Houchi?
Qingmu has vanished.
I don’t accept average vessels.
Houchi was in Qingchi Palace,
and met Qingmu.
They fell in love
and married in the mortal world.
Is Yuanqi our child?
Not ours.
He’s theirs.
You made yourself innocent.
Qingmu and Houchi
were ordinary immortals.
Now we’ve awakened.
And they no longer exist.
Certainly,
nor do their affections.
Was your wound
made by Yuanqi’s mother?
Well done.
You’re right.
With the stab,
I’m even with that ordinary couple.
Don’t you feel sorry for them?
Yes or no,
it has ended.
It doesn’t matter.
Why did you keep it from me?
I didn’t mean to.
It doesn’t matter anymore.
I don’t wanna bring it up.
Doesn’t it matter?
You don’t wanna bring it up?
Did Tianqi tell you this?
Over the 60 thousand years,
Gu Jun sees Houchi as his daughter.
He cared about her a lot,
and even died for her.
Tianqi told me
Gu Jun was in the God Realm.
Why did he lie to me?
What do you think?
He thought it didn’t matter.
There’s no need to bring it up.
You’ve awakened.
You should cultivate hard
and restore the past.
The past relationship
doesn’t matter anymore.
Now
I no longer need any reason.
You’ve changed.
You were
cold,
but you were kindhearted.
Your theories about
justice and righteousness
didn’t feel like empty talk.
Now
you are heartless
and ruthless.
Do you really care about the beings?
I’m always responsible
for all the beings.
It never changes.
You ignore the past.
But Yuanqi is still a kid.
He’s left in the Qingchi Palace,
and knows he’s abandoned
by his father.
How should he face it in the future?
Haven’t I made it clear?
I despise the love
between Qingmu and Houchi.
Their love
was a mistake to me.
And Yuanqi is the consequence.
Seeing him,
I’d think of
those unbearable memories.
You’re the True God,
the Master of all beings.
I’m going to tell Yuanqi
his birth father is
North Sea Lord Qingmu.
You
are not.
You and I
shall not meet
ever again.
♪Large memories are for you♪
♪Become veins and engraved in the palm♪
♪Countless twists and turns
Drifting away for many times♪
♪I can’t help missing you
But I can only hug your back♪
My birthday is of high grade.
You are the True God Bai Jue.
Isn’t this gift too casual?
♪Protect a heart♪
♪If love finally♪
♪Becomes ashes♪
♪I will be the shadow in your eyes♪
Leave.
I don’t wanna
see you again.
Now,
we are even.
There will be
no bond between us.
♪Exchange a one-second encounter
for a lifetime♪
Shanggu,
I took away your memories
after you went to the Nether World.
Then,
you wouldn’t know
what the Tribulation of Chaos was.
♪I am willing to indulge in the past♪
♪When tears dizzy the smile♪
♪How much luck do I need♪
♪To get myself♪
No hurry to awaken,
♪Be always stuck♪
better when
the Tribulation of Chaos ends.
After all
I’ll keep you company every day.
Shanggu.
Yuanqi is like me in appearance
and like you in temper.
You will like him,
and be kind to him.
Fengran.
Didn’t you go to the mortal world
with Jingjian for operas?
I knew you wouldn’t
leave me alone.
Of course not.
I wouldn’t leave
your mother alone either.
Tell me.
Where do you want to have fun?
I’ll go with you.
I want to go to the mortal world.
Your mother likes to hang out there.
What does she enjoy?
Food.
Chinese dominoes.
Kites.
I wanna play them too.
Don’t have fun too much.
Have you studied these days?
Yes, I read
the Classic of Mountains and Seas.
The ancient books are obscure.
You should work hard.
Understand?
Fengran.
Why is your tongue so strange today?
Can’t I ask you?
Of course you can.
Fengran.
I’m hungry.
We should hurry,
or Uncle Tianqi would find it out.
Okay.
Let’s go.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪