♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
=The Eternal Love S3=
=Episode 10=
Do you feel sleepy?
Not at all.
Then come with me.
Let's go.
Take this.
Face my sword!
You can't keep pulling your punch.
You need to strike.
Otherwise, I can't improve.
I can't become the greatest.
Again!
They are practicing swordplay here.
(Princess's Residence)
What?
Are you preparing a little excitement...
before our bedtime?
You've been training day and night lately.
As a token of my admiration,
I prepared this new sword for Your Highness.
Let's go.
Where to?
To practice swordplay in the yard of course.
I will gladly accept...
this beautiful sword.
However,
I'm not in a mood for practice today.
Then what do you want to do?
This stance
can strengthen your core muscles,
increasing your stability.
I'll start.
Sorry.
I can't do it anymore.
Thirty-seven.
Thirty-eight.
Thirty-nine.
(Didn't know this trick would be this handy.)
No, I'm exhausted.
(Why is he so shy?)
(I thought you're great at flirting.)
Hold.
The test is tomorrow.
I will never embarrass you.
No, I feel so sleepy.
Get up. Stop pretending.
That's all for today.
Accept whatever will come to pass.
She's really asleep.
But the look on you when you're asleep...
is quite adorable.
(Mo Residence)
The army of 20,000 strong is assembled
in the suburb.
The Wei Clan is willing
to provide us with the provision and weapons
as a token of goodwill.
Wei Qian Mo finally has lost patience.
Everything is in place.
As long as we have the imperial token,
we can finish off the enemies.
Very well.
You may leave now.
Yes.
You are four hours late.
Finishing off the enemies?
How bold of her.
You heard the conversation.
What do you think?
Father, don't you think it's odd
that Her Majesty granted the second princess
the imperial token?
The second princess is gaining
a lot of attention now.
The imperial token must be a test
of her ambition.
Does it matter?
Her Majesty might never suspect you.
But now,
the second princess and I are in the same boat.
It's normal Her Majesty would be wary of me.
It's all the more reason to take swift action.
The longer this goes on, the more obstacles we face.
But recklessness will cost us everything.
If you still have loyalty for me,
then prove it with your action.
My devotion for the country...
has never wavered.
Oh no, I'm so nervous.
Tan, calm down.
Lately
you've been practicing day and night.
You've become more robust.
You can surely overcome the test with ease.
You sure I'm more robust now?
My arms are beefy?
Oh, no.
I don't want to be a muscular barbie.
But even so,
why am I still not confident
that I can defeat General Lu?
General Lu is indeed...
a little...
But fear not.
All the best. You can do it.
I'll return with good news.
Tan.
I should get going.
All the best.
You're...
This is your final test.
So it's normal to be nervous.
I can accompany Your Highness
to the palace.
You said I couldn't leave you,
but I bet you can't bear to leave me either.
Feel free to take the test alone
and hope for the best.
Want to leave? No way.
We'll begin the test of swordplay.
Your Highness resorted to some petty trick,
but you tried your best.
You have potential.
Her Majesty is away today.
I was ordered to supervise the test
and observe the fruition of
Your Highness's training.
But I didn't expect that in mere ten days
Your Highness's stamina and skills
have improved significantly.
Her Majesty will be glad to know this.
Much obliged, Official Xiao and General Lu.
(Where is he?)
(He finally took the initiative to come with me,)
(could it be...)
Why are you here?
I know what you're up to.
You must never touch the imperial token.
This has nothing to do with you.
I must take you with me!
Your Highness must be lost.
Eighth Young Master is here too.
What secret would require both of you
to come to the royal bedroom?
You worthless fool!
Your ruined my plan!
What plan could it be
that would require both of you to break into
Her Majesty's bedroom?
It's nothing serious.
Don't take this wrongly.
I was actually...
stealing something.
I...
I drank the tonic soup Her Majesty gifted me.
So I feel I've become stronger
and more refreshed. I even had a better appetite.
The martial art training became
a piece of cake for me.
So I thought...
it must be the tonic's effect.
So Your Highness is here
to steal the prescription.
Yes.
I admit.
I have ambitions.
I wish to devote my life to serving Dongyue.
But if my body is too frail to fight,
I'm afraid I can't realize my ambition.
But because the tonic was meant
for Her Majesty,
I knew I didn't have the right to request it.
I have been blinded by greed.
I asked my prince consort to steal it.
(She used herself as a scapegoat.)
Coveting Her Majesty's belonging
is no petty crime.
I must report to Her Majesty.
Both of you will wait outside the royal
study for punishment.
You are so obsequious!
Is this even worth reporting?
She stole my prescription?
It's time to teach her a lesson
to make her behave.
From what I saw,
they were defending each other.
Perhaps the second princess knows about
the Mo family's conspiracy.
She pawned the imperial token to fool me.
And now she lied about stealing a prescription.
Her actions indeed are very suspicious.
(Imperial Token)
Keep this safe.
The Mo family can't cause us any trouble for now.
We must wait and see.
Yes.
Your Majesty. I am willing to take the punishment
on Her Highness's behalf!
Cheng Cheng.
I'm fine.
Your Majesty. I am willing to take the punishment
on Her Highness's behalf!
A message from Her Majesty.
The prince consort lacks manners.
The second princess must be punished with
ten lashes and reflect on her mistake.
This is my fault.
♪Like the wind, I♪
♪I'm banished to the end of time♪
♪I can't hold onto the dream♪
♪So I can only let it crumble♪
♪Your arrogance is manifesting♪
You didn't have to do that.
Consider this...
a silver lining.
I will repay your kindness...
for taking the rap for me.
How?
You could keep me company at night.
It seems like you don't
feel your injury at all!
Don't forget,
today,
it's my eldest brother's turn.
That's easy.
I hereby announce
to cancel all the shifts.
It's not like I'm a beast
that could eat you alive.
From now on,
don't put your life in danger again.
I know the world can be unfair at times.
There are difficulties in life.
But if you want to fight for men's rights,
the imperial token is not
the only solution to realize your goal.
You and I have a different status.
I have no choice.
You are my prince consort.
Your problem is our problem as well.
Your goal is our goal.
Our?
You were punished because of me.
Would you blame me?
I would spoil you nevertheless.
(Silly.)
(That's because you're my beloved Cheng Cheng.)
As for my suggestion earlier,
would you consider it?
What suggestion?
To keep me company at night.
Even the injury
can't stop your ill intention.
Your charm doesn't cease to mesmerize me.
(Is he giving up already?)
(I should play hard to get tonight)
(and make you come to me willingly.)
That hurts.
Where? Did I touch the wound?
Rest well.
If you can't fall asleep,
you can come to my room later.
(Qu Tan Er was very honorable today.)
(Has my gratitude for her)
(caused me to fall for her charm?)
Is he lost or something?
What is taking Mo Lian Cheng so long?
Jing Xin.
Yes, Your Highness.
It's getting late. You may go now.
It's not midnight yet.
Not to mention you're still carrying injuries.
I can't neglect my duties.
Just do as I said and go.
It's an order.
Yes.
With a bodyguard standing outside,
of course Cheng Cheng wouldn't come in.
Everything is set.
(She took the blame for me and got punished for it.)
(She suffered the injury.)
(But why is the pain in my heart.)
(Should I take this step forward?)
Why isn't that Mo Lian Cheng here yet?
Did I miscalculate?
Did it not work?
Cheng Cheng!
♪Another late autumn, another night♪
♪The swallow has returned, when will you♪
♪Should the yellowing red letters
be taken down or not♪
♪Hope makes it more heartbreaking♪
You may not remember me,
but you still care about me, right?
♪Red brocade in the bronze mirror♪
♪The lonely Jiangnan♪
♪is still noisy♪
♪And the light sigh from the deep boudoir♪
I shouldn't be bothered.
If he forgets, I'll help him remember.
His memories are just kept somewhere.
They are not gone forever.
Cheng Cheng...
♪She longs eagerly day and night♪
♪Each stitch sends love from afar♪
♪Only, how could she♪
♪let you know of her misery♪
♪All is well in her letters♪
Your Highness has been frowning.
Please have some soup.
Yan Chen is madly in love with her.
Everyone was impressed by her performance
on the test.
Who does she think she is?
Please calm down.
Qu Tan Er is not enjoying the spotlight.
What do you mean?
There was a message from Official Su.
After the test just now,
Qu Tan Er and Mo Lian Cheng
sneaked into Her Majesty's room
to steal a prescription.
She was caught at the scene and got punished
with lashes in front of everyone.
She was stealing a prescription?
Does her greed know no bounds?
But Yan Chen is still obsessed with her.
How foolish of him.
The nostalgia got the better of Young Master Mo.
He will see her true nature eventually.
During her training, Qu Tan Er
has been very competitive.
She won't give up on Yan Chen so easily.
Your Highness.
Young Master Mo will understand
your affection one day.
When Cheng Cheng first regained
part of his memories,
I think I pushed him.
He got upset.
Stay away from me. I'm in a bad mood.
But what caused it the second time?
Stop! Let her go!
(Misunderstanding)
Don't stare at us like that!
I know what you're thinking!
(Misunderstanding, Angry)
(At the great hall,)
(I told you my heart would belong to someone.)
Why didn't you get the meaning?
(Misunderstanding, Angry, Jealousy)
(Upset, Misunderstanding, Angry, Jealousy)
Could it be...
Cheng Cheng regains his memories
when he gets angry.
But it seems like
he gets angry quite often.
This should be easy.
There is nothing I can't achieve
when I put my back into it.
I feel pity for the prince consort.
Mo Lian Cheng.
Why didn't you greet me this morning?
I'm not feeling very well today.
I apologize.
Don't forget next time!
Mo Lian Cheng!
Look at the way you walk.
It's not elegant at all.
You should learn from your brother.
I apologize.
I'll do my best to correct it.
How can he be so calm?
Young Master Mo.
Your snack is here.
What? What are you doing?
Sorry, Prince Consort.
As ordered by Her Highness,
you can't have the snack.
I still have some in my room.
Why am I the one who gets more upset every time?
Tan, do you think the plan is working?
I don't think it is.
Then there is only one method left.
I'll get a homewrecker.
Then he will panic for sure.
Jing Xin, bring Mo Yan Chen to me.
He's here.
Yan Chen.
Your Highness.
Make yourself at home. Sit.
Very well.
Jing Xin.
You're not needed here. You may leave now.
Yes.
Why has Your Highness only
invited me to dinner?
Xiyue gave this pork jerky as tribute.
I invited you to try them out.
It's only natural to share
the finer things with you.
Come on.
I'm overjoyed.
I shall make a toast to you first.
Very well. Cheers.
Here.
Try this.
It's all right. I can do it myself.
I can pick it up.
(I'm sorry, Yan Chen.)
(Would he be mad and come to me?)
Young Master.
What is it now?
The main prince consort and Her Highness
are enjoying dinner.
They are having a good time.
They treat each other like a special guest.
They are spoon-feeding each other.
I see.
Very well.
Tan Er.
Would you like me to play a song for you?
Sure.
Your Highness, it's an urgent matter.
An urgent matter?
An urgent matter...
But...
Since it's urgent, I should give you privacy.
I take my leave now.
We'll dine again another time.
Jing Xin, how was it?
I saw Yu Hao
walking back and forth outside the room.
Does Cheng Cheng know?
How did he react?
I was waiting for quite some time.
But I never heard
any sounds inside.
Nothing?
Why doesn't he care about me?
Why isn't he jealous or upset?
Do I mean nothing to him?
Tan.
Perhaps the prince consort
is restraining his urges.
Restraining his urges?
Fine.
If he won't come,
I'll go to him instead.
Let's go!
Yu Hao, go out with Jing Xin.
Your Highness is trying to break the rules again.
Do you not remember?
The Three Orders and Three Rules. I know.
But I still remember you as my Cheng Cheng.
I'll always be with you.
You merely lost your memories.
But I know what you're planning.
Please let me be with you, okay?
That won't be necessary.
If you become part of this,
I'm afraid...
I don't want Your Highness to become a drag on me.
You're just stubborn.
You're giving me the cold shoulder,
but you still keep my booklet.
Please don't make any assumptions.
It was Yu Hao.
He forgot to get rid of this.
Even I've said this,
you still won't change your mind?
I'm tired.
I need to rest.
♪I hear the gentle waves of the ocean♪
♪The blurry memories have become clear to me♪
Your Highness.
Your Highness, mind the stairs.
Curse that Mo Lian Cheng. Nothing works on him.
He's so unbearable when he lost his memories.
I miss Cheng Cheng.
Your Highness, don't be upset.
Perhaps the prince consort
has his reason to do so.
Yes. He just can't remember our past.
It's not that he doesn't love me.
♪Like the wind, I♪
♪I'm banished to the end of time♪
♪I can't hold onto the dream♪
(I'm in this time of turmoil I don't belong.)
(I have no choice.)
(I can't put Father and my family in danger.)
(I can't put Tan Er in harm's way)
(because of my plan.)
(Whether I lost my memories)
(or I become the lover in your memory,)
(nothing matters.)
(You should have)
(a peaceful life with my brother.)
(Forget me, Tan Er.)
(Even in this loneliness,)
(I shall have an ease of mind.)
Ever since the moment I arrived in Dongyue,
fate has been playing tricks on us.
I may not remember him the second time,
he could still find me and protect me.
And our son, Yu Er, too.
Yes. He lost his memories.
I can't blame a patient.
Your Highness.
I don't understand what you're saying.
Jing Xin.
Will you believe me?
Will you believe what I say?
I believe you.
I've been by your side since you were little.
You've been nice to me.
Whatever you do or say,
I will always believe you.
Whatever happens,
I will never leave your side.
How many times have I told you?
Call me Tan.
I'm glad to have you with me.
Otherwise, I would have given up already.
Tan.
Don't be upset.
When you feel sad,
I feel sad as well.
You have my word.
Whatever lifetime we live in,
I'll never leave your side.
I'll protect you.
Yes.
I'm a princess!
I can't be defeated so easily.
Besides,
I have you with me.
Go for it.
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪A flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter what
hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have to
travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter what
hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have to
travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪