♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
=The Eternal Love S3=
=Episode 09=
You can ask the servants to do this in the future.
Come forth.
Send the prince consort back to the residence.
You.
General Lu came to train you personally.
Second Princess, please follow
what the master says.
Take the training seriously.
Cheng Cheng, save me.
Hold it tightly.
Her Highness is not good with physicality.
Official Xiao, please start the training easy and
gradually increase the difficulty.
Cheng Cheng, Cheng Cheng, don't leave.
What are you waiting for?
Keep training.
Speed up.
Why did the empress ask me to come?
Her Majesty knows Your Highness has been
training hard recently,
and wants to grant you this tonic.
Bring it over.
What is this black thing?
There is no bitter smell of herbs,
but the delicious fragrance of meat broth.
Is this some kind of game?
I feel too guilty to receive Her Majesty's favour.
If Your Highness is receiving such a favour,
you should not let Her Majesty down.
Her Majesty also asked me to tell you
that Your Highness should train your body well
and master both civil and military skills.
If you don't pass the military training,
there will be huge punishment.
I understand.
Your Highness should head back now.
Tan Er, you've worked hard.
The herbs in the tea will help you get pregnant.
I see why
you suddenly started to care about me.
You want me to get pregnant.
Tan Er, I'm doing this for you.
If you have any illness that
you don't want others to know,
you can tell me.
Nonsense.
Did someone spread that rumour
or did you think of it randomly?
My son can walk already.
Can't believe I'm being questioned on this.
Tan Er, I'm not thinking too much.
Look, you've been married for a while.
You even married two consorts.
But your tummy
isn't making any progress.
How can I not get worried?
In the narrower sense, it matters to our Qu Family.
In a broader sense,
I worried about the future of Dongyue.
Of course I'd be anxious, right?
Could it be that the Mo Family's two sons...
Stop thinking too much.
I'm not pregnant because I don't want to be.
Nothing is wrong with the three of us.
How can you not want a baby?
You can have as many babies as you want.
I can take care of them for you.
It's not as easy as you're making it.
Having a baby is not just my own business.
So that's why
you should respect each other, love each other,
and work together.
I know
you and the main prince consort
have a strong relationship.
I'm not worried about that.
However, you should also take care
of the secondary prince consort.
You shouldn't ignore either of them.
Ignore him?
I'm being proactive...
Okay.
I'll listen to you.
I'll take good care of the secondary prince consort.
Okay, daughter.
It's all up to you.
They both belong to you.
I wouldn't have had to wait until now
if Mo Lian Cheng
had just agreed.
Look.
All these herbs are good for your sex life.
Remember,
you have to take them with both prince consorts.
Also,
you shouldn't have a preference when you choose
who to serve you at night.
Only treating them equally
can make the family harmonious.
I am the princess of Dongyue.
I get whoever I want.
Tan Er, don't blame my nagging.
If you can provide offspring for the Qu Family,
you'd accomplish something great for the Empress.
Only when you have a bright future
can I enjoy my old age.
Taking turns serving you?
Sounds good.
Lian Cheng and I will take good care of
Your Highness.
This strategy will not only
build a stronger relationship between us,
but can also serve as an example for the nobility,
so that the elders and the empress can rest assured.
I came up with this idea
after thinking things through.
Does she want to break the agreement
and use the power of all sides to force me?
Your Highness is taking the big picture
into consideration.
I'll do my best to cooperate.
Very good.
Lian Cheng, what about you?
I've never forgotten about the intentions of
our marriage.
If this can help strengthen our relationship,
I'll do my best to support it.
If it breaks our agreement
and promises,
I will not tolerate it.
How dare he threaten me?
How dare he be so confident as a concubine?
Eighth Brother, you're overthinking it.
Her Highness keeps a good balance between us.
We serve her well.
How come there will be unfortunate incidents?
Here.
Tan Er, have some shrimp.
Eldest Brother, have some shrimp.
Are we done eating?
Your Highness.
If we are done,
we should rest.
Eldest Brother, you should do it.
This can't be right.
Elders should come first.
His Highness is more important.
Eldest Brother.
You shouldn't decline out of modesty.
We are brothers, there's no need to be so indecisive.
Take it.
Since I have leverage on her,
I reckon she won't force me to do anything.
I'll see what happens and react accordingly.
I'll take it.
Well.
Am I yielding to her?
Eighth Brother.
Eldest Brother.
It's natural to feel nervous before your first time.
I'm here to have a few drinks with you.
Maybe Eldest Brother just wants to relieve
his sorrow through alcohol.
I'm unsure why Tan Er hasn't asked us
to consummate our marriages,
but we shouldn't think too much.
Although the final step of our wedding
has been late,
it has finally come.
Eldest Brother, you and Tan Er grew up together.
You two have a solid relationship.
Why don't you just
ask the question you want to ask?
Tan Er must have her own considerations.
I shouldn't burden her further.
If a man always yields,
concedes, and tolerates everything
in a marriage,
then how is that different from a prison?
How can there be happiness?
Everyone is selfish.
If you want relationships to last and the family
to be harmonious,
you should think of others.
If you only think about your own gains and losses,
that'd be the reason for letting happiness
pass you by.
Here. Cheers.
What Eldest Brother said makes sense.
Maybe I am blindsided by my will to resist
and have become the most selfish person?
Cheers.
Tan.
You've been getting ready
ever since you came back.
You're just consummating your marriage,
there's no need to over-prepare.
It's going to be a great time.
Of course I need to prepare myself.
Men dress up for those who love them.
Women don't need to do the same.
Pleasing who you love
is not burdensome, it makes me happy.
You always say things I don't understand.
Then you should think about it yourself.
I'm going to find Cheng Cheng and
spend a great night with him.
Bye.
It smells so nice.
Cheng Cheng, Cheng Cheng.
Cheng Cheng.
Your Highness.
You drank?
What did you drink?
Did you leave some for me?
No.
There isn't any for you.
Then, do you have a place in your heart for me?
♪A haggard look is left♪
♪Why do you remain aloof and indifferent♪
♪Did loving me become too burdensome♪
♪The sky turns grey as it is about to rain♪
♪Covering inevitable pain♪
♪The heart has finally been emptied♪
♪Falling into a black hole of stubbornness♪
♪Forcefully making up far-fetched lies♪
♪Even though there are too many sarcastic moves♪
Cheng Cheng. I really miss you.
♪Happiness slips through fingers♪
I want you to call me Tan Er once more.
I want to talk to you in your arms.
I want to hear
your heartbeats and breaths at all times.
I miss our Yu Er.
I miss...
I want you to remember who I am.
♪Falling into a black hole of stubbornness♪
♪Forcefully making up far-fetched lies♪
♪Even though there are too many sarcastic moves♪
♪Going from lovers to strangers
makes me confused♪
♪Happiness slips through fingers♪
♪Dream is the one-time, uninhibited indulgence♪
♪Do you understand my confusion at all♪
♪All because of your silence♪
Sleep well.
♪Do you understand my heartache at all♪
♪All because of your recklessly squander♪
♪I'm starting to not understand
whether there is love♪
She acts amatively every day.
But in critical moments,
she behaves with respect.
Am I really
the Cheng Cheng you miss so much?
Senior Liu.
Liu Bai Shui.
Your Highness.
Why didn't you give me a heads-up that
you were coming?
We know each other well. No need for formalities.
We've only met twice.
Are we that close?
Jing Xin.
Her Highness
was afraid that you don't have
good food to eat in the forest and
asked me to bring some snacks and
two chickens.
It must be a great deal of effort for you
to bring so many things to me.
You should just bring some sliver
when you come the next time.
This is not a big deal.
Her Highness knows
that
I'm very strong.
Why did you hit me?
Senior.
How's your progress?
What progress?
The pills to heal amnesia.
The pills
are complete.
Really?
What you just said makes me feel kind of bad.
Why don't you trust me?
That's great! That's great!
Thanks so much, Senior.
Bring it out for me.
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, okay.
She truly thinks I'm an expert herbalist.
Fortunately, I have some stock.
I knew you would come today,
so I got everything ready and waited for you.
Look.
Senior.
This medicine smells a little too strong.
I'm afraid that even this is not strong enough.
If you take a regular dosage
but nothing happens,
you can take more accordingly.
Accordingly?
How much should I add?
You shouldn't exceed three pills in a day.
I mean, no one will die after taking less than three.
Thank you, Senior. Let's go.
Your Highness.
Please wait.
What?
Do you have anything else to say?
No, I mean...
The slivers...
Don't mention it, don't even mention it.
Senior, it'll hurt our relationship
if you keep mentioning money.
Just keep the rest.
No.
Don't mention it.
You can keep the rest.
No, Your Highness, Your Highness.
Don't mention it.
Your Highness, slow down.
How many times have I said it?
Why don't you understand?
I wanted to say that you didn't
leave enough silvers.
Tan, in order to heal the consort,
you even forgot
that women should stay away from the kitchen.
Mo Lian Cheng likes to overthink.
If we ask him to take the medicine,
he will ask a lot of questions
and refuse to take it.
This will do.
He won't notice even if
he has a pair of eagle eyes.
Tan, you're smart indeed.
But you could've asked
chefs from the kitchen
to do this kind of thing.
Why do you need to do it yourself?
Food made with love
tastes different.
Food made with love?
What does that taste like?
Jing Xin.
These are only for Mo Lian Cheng,
be sure to cook these separately.
Don't worry.
Leave it to me.
Okay.
Taste of love.
I can't smell anything.
Today, I asked the kitchen to prepare
some Jiangnan glutinous rice balls
for you prince consorts to taste.
The round shape of the rice balls
must mean reunion and harmony.
That's right. Have a taste.
Where are the rice balls for Eighth Brother?
I asked them to cook
the rice balls in separate pots.
Yan Chen, you are the main prince consort.
You should taste them first.
I'll wait for Eighth Brother's and
let's taste them together.
That also works.
Now, can you have some?
What?
Lian Cheng, so you don't like
the food I prepared for you?
The rice balls just came off of the stove,
I don't like food that's too hot.
You should eat first.
Here.
I like hot food.
Eighth Brother, you can have mine.
Eighth Brother, let's taste them together.
Thank you, Eldest Brother.
Yan Chen.
It's fine.
The stuffing tastes like
hair-removal medicine.
Maybe hair removal is also popular among
Jiangnan men?
Hair-removal medicine?
This is the normal black sesame stuffing.
What is wrong with the kitchen?
I must go to ask them.
My mistake embarrassed you.
However,
you are a married man.
You should take hair-removal medicine regularly.
How can you make your wife do it for you?
Eat.
It's filled with Tan Er's good will.
Your Eighth Brother is too hairy.
Her Highness has been unsatisfied
for quite a while.
Really?
To me,
the second princess has been saving
the secondary prince consort's face.
She has never mentioned it in front of him.
What am I doing?
Oh my god. He's removing his hair.
How could I make him do this?
You're still up?
I'm going to bed soon.
I came to explain.
I actually got the medicine from
an expert herbalist.
I thought the medicine can bring back your memory.
Who knew it...
You don't need to explain.
Don't get me wrong.
I like hairy men who
are full of testosterone.
I don't care about what you like.
I just
don't want others to talk behind my back.
The gossipy servants.
I'll be sure to punish them
for your sake.
Your Highness, please don't cause
any more trouble.
I'll stay the night
to shut the mouths of the gossipy crowd.
How could I allow her to stay?
To restore my reputation, I can bear this.
If Mo Lian Cheng allowed me to stay,
maybe he's agreeing to serve me?
If she wants to consummate our marriage,
things will become more complicated
if I keep refusing her.
Anyway.
He's mad at me right now.
If I do something to him,
he'll throw me out of his room.
Is it possible that she doesn't want to touch me
because I'm hairy?
♪Fate is in control of parting and reunion♪
♪What really is fate♪
Is she asleep?
She's so cute when she's asleep.
♪The most beautiful moment
is when I fell for you♪
♪Infatuation leads me to jump into a vortex♪
♪From breaking down the barriers
to falling helplessly in love♪
What am I doing?
♪Happiness experienced, mistakes made♪
♪Taking notes on who has come♪
♪Tears shed, mistakes repented♪
♪Such that life has not been in vain♪
(Princess's Residence)
The hair-removal medicine
does work.
Really?
You know what, last night, Her Highness...
You don't know?
I don't.
Tell me, what happened?
You see...
What?
Do you want to know?
What are you guys talking about?
Oh my god. You scared me.
Sit down, sit down.
Keep going, keep going.
Tell me, tell me.
Don't tell anyone else.
Okay, okay.
Her Highness stayed at
the Snow Court last night.
I see how important
the hair-removal medicine is for men.
Do you know where
the second princess stayed last night?
Everyone in the residence knows.
Otherwise, the hair-removal medicine
would've been a waste.
Everyone knows?
Of course, you can ask them.
You can't discuss Her Highness behind her back.
Your behaviour has become poorer.
Eldest Brother, my mistake.
My mistake. Never again.
Are you missing the days
during which you taught me how to play zither?
You are so mean.
Why are you acting all cool
after you've fallen in love with me?
Nonsense.
I'm telling the truth.
You kissed me when I stayed over last night,
right?
You were dreaming.
I wasn't dreaming.
You said no matter where, no matter when,
and no matter who we became,
you'll always find me, love me,
and marry me a thousand times.
Lifetime after lifetime, we will never be apart.
You.
You will belong to me eventually.
Lian Cheng.
Eldest Brother.
Here. I have a bowl of tonic for you.
It has all sorts of great ingredients.
Try it.
Thank you, Eldest Brother.
But, I'm not sick.
It'd be a waste for me to have it.
You must be tired from last night.
You should have some.
Last night.
Nothing happened last night.
But I won't turn down
Eldest Brother's good will.
Here.
On the wedding day, he was happy about it,
but he's a little disappointed today.
Eldest Brother.
It's okay, I'll get it.
Be careful.
I'm so tired.
General Lu is crueler than my personal trainer.
She intends to embarrass me.
Tan.
What?
Today, it's the prince consort's turn to serve you.
Why did you come back to your own room?
I forgot about it.
The prince consort has been waiting for you
in his room for two hours.
But I'm not in the mood right now.
You were the one who decided to take turns with
the prince consorts.
If you don't obey the rule you made by yourself,
it will hurt your reputation.
Waiting like this must be hard on him.
Wait.
You're going like this?
Don't you want to take a shower and dress up?
No need. I'm going.
No perfume powder today?
So you've left
your first time to me.
Are you sleepy?
No.
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪A flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part,
no matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part,
no matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind
in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪