Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
The Eternal Love S3
Episode 14
I'm so terribly sorry.
Sorry.
Where are you going?
I met your gaze.
You're the right man.
You have great reflexes.
You have the capacity of the Five Elements
and the heroic poise that people admire.
I can tell you're a man who can
make waves in human history!
You must have fooled quite a lot of people.
Aside from the weird princess girl,
business has been very slow.
Did she find out I was scamming her,
so she sent her goon to take me out?
This is all a misunderstanding.
The second princess got it wrong.
It's possible
that I got the wrong medicine.
But whatever the case is,
the money had already been spent.
There are no refund policies.
Capturing me won't do you any good.
What was the medicine for?
Who was it for?
I am a hermit anyway.
I enjoy the seclusion
and despise any connection with the officials.
So I became a recluse.
But Her Highness's heartfelt story moved me.
So the medicine...
Of course,
the prescription is top-secret.
As for whom she gave it to,
I have no idea.
Just as the villagers said,
this man really is a fraud.
But Qu Tan Er came asking for his help.
Could there be a reason behind it?
All and all,
I refuse to participate in any mortal affairs.
Of course,
there are duties I cannot neglect.
It's a pleasure to meet a master like you.
Your help will be much appreciated in the future.
Certainly.
It's getting more challenging to run a business.
Perhaps I should hide and wait it out.
Why should I hide?
Anyone loves money.
You have a point.
The fortune-teller the second princess went to
was nothing but a fraud.
The expensive herbs she bought
were meant for Mo Lian Cheng.
You're right.
It couldn't be him.
Perhaps the increased dosage
has made me paranoid.
I wish nothing but a long life for Your Majesty.
You can just leave the trivial matters to me.
Only you can share my burdens.
Prince.
Guess who am I?
Why are you calling me "Prince"?
You still haven't regained your memories.
I have an idea.
Sit over there.
Teach me how to play the zither like you used to.
I can just hold you in my arms.
That's not the same.
Hug me and teach me...
Tan! Bad news!
What is it? Come in.
You sent me to get back at Liu Bai Shui.
But as soon as I arrived,
I saw Xiao Zhen and his men arrive at his doorstep.
He even took money from Xiao Zhen.
That cursed traitor.
Liu Bai Shui?
He got you the hair-removal pill.
I hired him to make you
some medicine to help you regain your memory.
I didn't know he would swap it out.
Who is this man?
I used to know someone
who looked exactly like him.
We both crossed paths with him.
We crossed paths with him?
Forget about him.
Ever since he gave me that fake medicine,
I was certain he was not Liu Qian Shui.
I sent Jing Xin to get back at him.
Liu Qian Shui?
In the parallel world,
he was a sage from the Xuanling Continent.
He was looking for a host for
the Soul-guarding Bead.
So he found me.
He also gave me the Soul-parting Flute.
The Xuanling Continent?
What bead?
The Soul-parting Flute?
Kid, you must have many questions.
I forgot. You don't remember anything.
Jing Xin.
Where is that traitor?
I tied him up.
How dare you lie to me!
If you tell another lie,
I'll order Jing Xin to cut you once.
My guard
is cruel and her blade is blunt.
It might take thousands of cuts
before your finally ends!
My goodness.
What do you want from me?
Why would you want to chop me up?
Your Highness, I explained everything.
I didn't tell anyone about
your amnesia medicine.
Then explain yourself.
Your name is Liu Bai Shui.
Why did you lie to me and say you are Liu Qian Shui?
I didn't lie to you.
I told you right away my name was Liu Bai Shui.
You even asked me why it's nine hundred less.
It was you who mistook me for someone else.
Are you sure you're not
Liu Qian Shui who just dyed your hair black?
I really am not.
Do you have an elder brother named Liu Qian Shui?
No.
What about your father?
Your father's father?
Let me put it this way.
My name is Liu Bai Shui. My father is Liu Hei Shui.
We have Hei Shui and Bai Shui,
but there is no Liu Qian Shui.
As for my identity...
I've been...
I've been single.
For so many years,
I've upheld my innocence
and remained reserved.
Jing Xin, inform the authority.
I want this fraud arrested!
No!
Yes!
Wait, Your Highness.
If we hand him over to the authority,
Her Majesty will take over the case.
During the interrogation,
he will be tortured.
Yes!
The prince consort knows what to say.
You're
clearly a righteous person, a handsome man
with a kind heart and good...
Perhaps...
We should take him out instead.
I like that plan!
Sure!
Your Highness!
Have mercy on me!
Please spare me.
Maybe...
Maybe Your Highness could give me
a chance to redeem myself.
Okay?
You took my rival's money.
You can redeem nothing.
Don't be so sure.
I have a trick up my sleeves.
For example,
I'm a knowledgeable person.
I know fortune-telling and how to
ward off evil spirits.
Stop bluffing!
No! Even if those were bluffs,
I am a master in astrology.
Astrology, you know?
Fine. There is nothing you can't do.
I didn't lie about astrology.
That is true.
I think
I can be of great use to you.
I may not be useful to you now,
but at least I can provide some advice.
Whatever the case is,
please let me stay.
I will be of use to you someday.
Your Highness, show some mercy, okay?
A kind heart
will keep you out of harm's way.
Jing Xin.
I'm grateful to Your Highness.
Much obliged, strong warrior.
Enough of your flattery.
Tell me, what is your plan?
So the prince consort has amnesia.
That is good.
Wait.
I mean you're good-looking.
Good-looking.
Are you done yet?
His handsome look has nothing to do with you.
That is true enough.
But since we're talking about amnesia,
I'm thinking...
Perhaps...
he should try to recall
some incidents that happened in the past.
I thought of that long ago.
We've tried to
recall plenty of the past memories.
But it's not working at all!
It's not working.
If it's not working,
maybe it's because
it was difficult to replicate
the exact event that took place.
But you should at least get the rough image.
Did you do that?
We missed the mark a little on that.
See? This may be the cause.
Apart from that,
did you fail to recall any other memories?
Yes!
There was bloodshed...
and some...
There were some memories concerning our privacy.
My goodness!
Memories concerning your privacy!
That's why you wanted to get it working.
Since they are about to get working,
as outsiders,
we should give them some privacy.
I'm no outsider!
Of course, you are!
Can't you read the mood
with your big eyes?
I'm not an outsider!
Of course, you are!
Your Highness.
What could...
be more embarrassing...
than what you've done so far?
Some matters are not meant to be talked about.
Why?
Do you have an urge for a more
exciting experience?
Your Highness, I did as you ordered
and dug a pit.
Who are we burying?
No! No, Your Highness!
I don't want to die just yet!
Why are you a coward this time?
Jing Xin.
Take Yu Hao on a stroll.
Make some distance if you can.
I have something serious to talk
to the prince consort.
Yes.
Come on.
Prince Consort, if you need anything,
just yell and let me know!
Don't worry.
He's gone far.
But...
Don't say a word.
Jump into it with me.
Perhaps that might make you
remember everything.
Into the pit?
We must pretend that we slip and fall into it.
I'll land on you.
You'll act as a cushion.
You're taking advantage of me.
Why should I be your cushion?
It's not that I want it that way,
but that was how it happened.
If I wanted to take advantage of you,
I wouldn't come to the woods
just to make you fall into a pit.
Hurry up.
Everything will become clear to you.
Nonsense.
It's not nonsense. This is serious!
Stop pulling me
I need to kick you into it.
This doesn't seem right.
What's wrong?
As you mentioned before,
I was an invincible warrior.
You lied to me!
I'll explain what happened.
You were trying to save me.
I panicked and dragged you down with me.
But the pit was too deep.
I couldn't get out even I've tried everything.
If I was an invincible warrior,
why would I even need your help?
I later found out
you were trying to spend some time alone with me.
If we were in love,
why would we be here
if we wanted to spend some time together?
You're lying to me again.
No!
You weren't really yourself back then.
You said so yourself.
It wasn't the real me.
Even if I jumped into this pit,
would I remember anything at all?
This is confusing.
Tell me.
How did we get out of the pit?
You flew out while carrying me in your arms.
I could fly?
If I could fly,
why would I get dragged into the pit by you?
Mo Lian Cheng.
I think you're confusing me on purpose!
I think you remember it wrong!
There is nothing logical about this incident.
I'm not doing it.
I might as well shoot myself in the foot.
Cheng Cheng, let's give it a try.
Just once.
It might actually help with your memory.
What if we get hurt?
Don't worry. I'm not afraid.
But I am.
I don't know martial arts now.
If we fell,
I couldn't protect you.
I'm not the mighty warrior I used to be.
You must be disappointed.
Not at all.
You are worried I might get hurt.
I will never think of you as
a disappointment over this.
I'm more disappointed in myself.
I don't even have a way to restore
your memories.
Honestly...
I don't mind not having the memories.
I...
I don't mind at all.
Tan Er?
What are you so obsessed with?
Is it me or your memories of the past?
Cheng Cheng, you should be in bed now.
Don't you like falling asleep
snuggling your darling?
I'm here to check on you.
I'll get going now.
What is it? Is something bothering you?
Is it because of your amnesia?
Don't worry. I'll figure something out.
Let's work on it together, okay?
Right!
It's June 17.
It's the day we got married.
So it's our anniversary.
How do you want to celebrate it?
I'll grant you any request.
Anniversary?
What about when you married me?
In that case,
we have three different anniversaries.
The first is on June 17.
The second is on October 26.
And now I married you again.
I will remember these dates.
These are important moments that we share.
You've had enough pampering. Now praise me.
But I don't remember the other two dates.
I don't want to celebrate those.
I only remember the day we got married.
Fine.
I won't force you if you don't want to.
We even have an adorable son.
His name is Xiao Yu Er.
He is such a lovely kid.
I'll draw you a picture of him.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Actually...
Yu Er is cute.
He's not as ugly as this picture.
I miss him a lot.
I thought the picture would be
reminiscent of him.
But I overestimated my drawing skill.
I'm clumsy at drawing.
You could describe his look for me.
I'll give it a try.
Really?
I know you're better at this.
Yu Er's tiny face...
is chubby and pink.
He has big and upturned eyes,
much like yours.
If he has big eyes, he takes after you.
The resemblance is remarkable.
You're amazing.
He does look adorable.
He's such a lovely child,
yet I remember nothing of him.
If he's not in my memory,
how can I claim to be his father?
Have I ever carried out the duty of a father?
We have a beautiful son,
but his father
could only see him once every few days.
You were always busy with work.
I might as well raise him as a single parent.
I don't really want to know
about the things I've never done.
Why are you upset again?
You're reluctant to do anything I ask.
I know you're in a bad mood.
So I put up with your attitude.
Isn't that enough?
It is.
I'm tired. I'm going back.
Why are you so gleeful?
Young Master.
I heard a quarrel
in the princess's room.
A quarrel?
Her Highness and Lian Cheng?
Who else could it be?
You should stay out of this.
Having a quarrel in the residence is never good.
Yes.
Her Highness is upset.
Whatever the cause is,
it's my duty to appease her as
the main prince consort.
Since others can't comply with her requests,
I must carry out my duty.
I think it's raining.
It's raining.
Her Highness must feel restless.
I should check on her now.
I'll get the umbrella.
I will make you remember
the danger we had gone through together,
the love we had,
and the thrilling experiences.
I can't let you forget them.
♪Did loving me become too burdensome♪
♪The sky turns gray as it is about to rain♪
♪Covering inevitable pain♪
♪The heart has finally been emptied♪
♪Falling into a black hole of stubbornness♪
♪Forcefully making up far-fetched lies♪
♪Even though there are too many
sarcastic moves♪
♪Going from lovers to strangers
makes me confused♪
♪Happiness slips through fingers♪
Even this tree...
♪A dream is a one-time, uninhibited indulgence♪
was trimmed exactly based on the image
of your memory.
♪Do you understand my confusion at all♪
♪All because of your silence♪
But you didn't do it for me.
♪Why can't you see it?♪
And I...
♪Give me a warm embrace♪
fall like the cherry blossoms.
I now bear the resemblance from your past,
yet I had never known you.
♪I'm starting to not understand
whether there is love♪
♪I'm beginning to feel pain for knowing love♪
Tan Er.
Tan Er?
Why are you here? Still up?
It's raining outside.
I remember the thunder always scares you
since you were a child.
I was worried, so I came to see you.
I'm fine.
You should go back and rest.
Tan Er.
Is something upsetting you?
If you don't want to say it,
I will never ask.
It's been this way since we were kids.
But you always tell me eventually.
Thank you for listening to my thoughts.
Why are you still thanking me?
I told you a long time ago.
I am willing to do whatever it is
that you need of me.
Gratitude is not needed.
Do you not remember?
It's all right if you can't remember.
As long as you are who you are,
I'll always love you.
"As long as you are who you are,
I'll always love you."
I'm not the mighty warrior I used to be.
You must be disappointed.
I don't really want to know
about the things I've never done.
It's my fault for not realizing it sooner.
Tan Er?
Thank you for reminding me.
Cheng Cheng?
I'm tired. I don't want to recall my memories.
You don't need to.
If you don't want it,
I won't mind either.
♪The night was spent in yearning,
the flowers bloom in the morning♪
What did you say?
I said,
I am sorry. It's my fault.
♪The reflection of beauty makes
the yearning unyielding♪
I love you.
That's all that matters.
Even...
♪It's quiet rain on the lonely hill,
I intoxicate myself♪
without my memories?
Those don't matter now.
You're the man I love.
Whatever may come to pass,
I want to be with you forever.
♪The dusk is ever so mesmerizing,
so does your silhouette♪
Even if I'm not the man you knew?
If I must relive this lifetime
ten thousand times,
in my heart,
I can always rely on you.
You'll always be the man who protects me.
♪Love comes with fear, but my disguise
must never fail♪
I know I'm not the man from your memory.
But I love you nonetheless.
♪I've discarded my wariness♪
I wouldn't dare to recall the memories
simply because...
♪All I want is to give you words of my affection♪
the man you knew was perfect.
I'm afraid if I didn't live up to your expectations,
you would feel
that I wasn't worthy of your love.
It's always worth it.
Every surprising and hair-raising moment
that we share
has fortified my love for you.
You don't need the memories.
Because we will create new memories
that belong to both of us.
♪Let's keep the memories of this lifetime♪
♪Your most wonderful moments
will forever remain in my heart♪
Let this kiss
be the first of our new memories.
Okay?
One isn't enough.
From tomorrow on,
I want my dear Cheng Cheng
to have more wonderful memories.
♪I couldn't step on the fallen blossoms♪
♪Our reunion and parting
will sink into the earth♪
♪Let's keep the memories of this lifetime♪
♪Your most wonderful moments
will forever remain in my heart♪
The weather today is nice.
Indeed.
This is part of our new memories.
Let's have a look there.
Sure.
The scenery is gorgeous.
It's great scenery with excellent feng shui.
It's worth purchasing as an investment.
By the way,
we haven't run a business together.
You never bothered
to invest in real estate with me.
You should invest in the love market.
We can turn this place into
a tourism destination.
We can make a fortune together
and use this chance to create
our own new memories.
Do you know how much this land costs?
How expensive could it be?
I'm the princess of Dongyue.
Can I not afford to buy a piece of land?
That much?
It's a lot.
But as princess, you can surely
afford to purchase it.
This memory is too pricey.
It's a lot to pay for.
Are you backing out now?
Never!
As long as we can create new memories together,
this is only a small price to pay!
All right, you don't need to buy it.
My instinct is telling me
if I don't spend the money,
you will think of me as a stingy person.
I don't want you to have leverage over me.
You really don't need to buy it.
That's because
I already have our precious memory.
Really?
Since you're great with words,
I won't mind if you say them more often.
For example,
between me and your money, you chose me,
while gnashing your teeth.
If we were in the past,
I wouldn't get to see you make this decision.
Choices are for the kids.
I want both love and money.
Why can't you see it?
She doesn't care about you at all!
Otherwise,
she wouldn't turn a blind eye to your pain
or let you suffer in silence.
Young Master, that's enough.
You are practicing so diligently
only to get her attention.
But what about her?
The two of them
have been out there alone for an entire day.
Tan Er likes my swordplay.
Leave me be.
Please stop.
You already excel at this.
It's not good enough!
She likes my swordplay to be bolder.
She likes the moves to be unrestrained.
If I become better,
she will start to like me!
She doesn't care about you at all!
So Eighth Brother indeed did it on purpose.
What? Are you disappointed?
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Tan Er, you're finally here.
I'm here...
to tell you that...
Come closer, I can't hear you.
Say nothing. Please.
But...
Tan Er.
Who am I?
You're Mo Yan Chen.
I'm your prince consort, your husband.
You should show me affection.
Sorry, but I can't.
Why?
I never said it.
But it doesn't mean I don't want your love.
Tan Er.
You told me when you were a kid that you only
wanted Brother Yan Chen
to be your prince consort.
Ever since then,
I wanted to be with you till the end of time.
But why are you ignoring me now?
Tan Er.
What did I do wrong to deserve this?
Why do you refuse even to touch me?
Yan Chen.
We should get a divorce.
Yan Chen...
You didn't say anything.
I didn't hear anything.
But that is what's best for the three of us.
I'm not disowning you.
I promise you a good life
after leaving me.
My love has become an obsession!
Without you, I'm helpless.
Sorry.
But at this rate,
I'm afraid I'll hurt you even deeper.
Sorry?
♪The frail and painful changes♪
Why?
Even you are in love with Mo Lian Cheng,
but why can't I have a place in your heart?
♪Without any turns, closure was given♪
Sorry.
♪Turn your obsession into a forceful disguise♪
I will go now.
♪This wound burnt deeply, now we have
forgotten one another♪
♪How come my eyes turned red all of a sudden♪
♪This wound has made my heart strong♪
♪But it can never breakthrough the sadness♪
♪It is just confusion in the mortal world♪
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪A flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part,
no matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply
that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind
in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter
what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply
that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have to
travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind
in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪