Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
The Eternal Love S3
Episode 16
What's wrong? Are you mad at me?
Do you enjoy ordering me around?
Sorry.
I won't ask you
to serve me tea or water again.
I can forgive you.
But Su Yue La won't.
It's a pleasant moment. Why must you
bring up her name?
Your Highness.
Curse that witch.
Why is she here?
I told you.
She won't be restless at night.
There are rules.
Princess and Prince Consort
may sleep together once every seven days.
You must restrain your urges until then.
In that case,
I'll be waiting outside
until Your Highness decides to
go to your room with me.
Your Highness, please be quick.
Tell her I'm not around.
Go on.
It's futile.
She will barge in here to arrest you.
I'm not going.
Just go. Hurry up.
No!
Go on.
Just go.
What happened?
Jing Xin.
She won't let me sleep with Cheng Cheng.
She even asked me to leave the room.
I'll handle it for you.
I'll distract her.
Your Highness.
Please.
Rest well, Your Highness.
I'll wait here and keep watch.
No evildoer will sneak past me!
We have a majestic full moon tonight.
Every time there is a full moon,
I always spend the night alone.
But I have you to keep me company tonight.
I somehow feel...
a little touched.
Everyone would miss some
old friends on quiet nights.
Whether it's old acquaintances or new friends,
I always wish there could be
a soulmate by my side
who could listen to my thoughts at this moment.
A soulmate?
Who wouldn't want a soulmate?
But it's all part of fate's plan.
It's destiny.
It seems like...
you have your fair share of woes too, Official Su.
Mr. Mo, you're Prince Consort's birth father.
You're also a role model of
manly virtues in Dongyue.
You've been a widower for over ten years
and never involved in indecency.
Your virtuous character is truly impressive.
I'm flattered, Official Su.
Her Highness couldn't sleep by herself
and Prince Consort is responsible for that.
He must be supervised closely.
I've invited you here,
so you can show him the right path
and tell him not to break the
moral codes for men again
by seducing Her Highness with his charm!
I insisted on staying in his room.
He wasn't seducing me.
Your Highness and Mo Yan Chen
were childhood friends.
His love for you stays true and unyielding.
If Mo Lian Cheng hadn't employed seduction,
Your Highness wouldn't have disowned him.
You...
Her Majesty has orders for Your Highness.
This way, Your Highness.
Father.
I was merely putting up with
Su Yue La's inspection.
That's all there is to it.
I have nothing more to teach you.
Come to the study with me.
The study?
Since she wants me to teach you
moral codes for men,
you can copy some moral codes and fool her.
Father. Su Yue La is acting suspiciously.
Please be cautious.
I'm aware of what's happening.
I don't need your lecture.
Mo Yuan Long and Mo Lian Cheng are still acting as
loving father and son in the presence of outsiders.
But they barely interact
with each other in private.
They each copied a set of moral codes for men.
My guess is it's just for show
to fool us.
They have grown estranged because of
Mo Yan Chen's repudiation.
They haven't reconciled for the moment.
Whether you're right or not, we can't
draw conclusions rashly.
Keep observing.
Employ some tactics if necessary.
I will aid you.
Yes. I shall take my leave now.
Troubles might stir at the armory
and the provision warehouse.
Come to Black Cloak Alley at 3 AM.
This is my father's handwriting.
But I've withdrawn myself from the rebellion.
I supervised my son as he copied
moral codes for men.
He should learn his mistakes after
copying the text with diligence.
Could it be...
that Su Yue La mimicked my father's handwriting
to see if I'm still working with the rebels?
Then my father must have received a letter
that imitated my handwriting.
Officials, it's time.
When the two rebels arrive,
take them both down.
Yes!
Black Cloak Alley
My Lord.
Why are you here?
Eighth Young Master sent me here to wait for you.
This meeting is Su Yue La's scheme.
There is an ambush ahead.
We should both leave now.
Have mercy on me!
This...
My father is very ill!
I was going to ask for a doctor at the clinic!
Have mercy on me!
Please spare my life!
Scram.
Officials, this is my mistake.
We might have been exposed.
In that case, fall back.
Let's go.
So Her Majesty didn't send Su Yue La here
to teach us the rites or reimpose laws of virtues.
She is here to investigate
whether my men and I have secretly joined
hands with your father's rebellion.
This is huge plotting.
Su Yue La is cunning.
She is also conspiring with Qu Mei Er.
She will be a great threat if she stays.
That is why
we must get leverage on her
to prevent further risks.
She may be sneaky,
but I'll show her the real deal.
Judging by your eyes,
you can show her a great deal.
Her youth is behind her and she is still single.
Perhaps
the loneliness is tormenting her heart.
What dirty scheme are you up to now?
Are you...
You'll see.
Are you sure this person
used to be in love with Su Yue La?
He was her first love.
It's the first love!
I ordered Jing Xin to ask around.
Su Yue La hasn't married other men
because she couldn't move on
from the man in this picture.
But we got the description from others,
then the painter drew this based on ours.
Are you sure this is what he really looks like?
Official Wang has checked this picture.
She is from Su Yue La's hometown.
She confirmed that
the man looks exactly like this picture.
But this man
somehow looks familiar.
It reminds me of someone.
I think I've met this man before as well.
I feel like...
I got it. Come on.
My skill as a makeup artist is unquestionable.
Now he does look like
the man in this picture.
With some beard,
he can win her heart for sure.
You have a point.
I was told that Young Master
will draw me a portrait.
But what is it for?
We should tell him the truth.
You want me to seduce Su Yue La?
How can I do that to her?
Calm down.
I'll double your salary for the next month.
I don't give up my money for honor...
No, I don't trade my honor for money!
This is a great chance to display your charm!
This isn't embarrassing at all.
I wouldn't mind if it was others.
But it's Su Yue La...
I just can't do it.
Young Master, please don't make me do it.
Yu Hao.
You already know the ambush in Black Cloak Alley.
Su Yue La will cause us more trouble in the future.
Her Highness's and my safety...
are in your hands.
You should put some effort into this.
Leave.
She misses the man from her memories,
his gentle manner is never forgotten.
He lives in the cabin in the woods, but his
presence has my heart bewildered.
The plum blossoms are in the wind.
Who is the handsome young man on the field?
♪We part way at dusk, leaving the pieces behind♪
♪Our fate is written on the paper♪
♪The ink dried♪
Are you...
♪The crown cried♪
♪Tales of everlasting love spread wide♪
♪The sand is carried by the gust♪
♪Our youth was blown away, leaving us with grief♪
♪The memory couldn't be wiped,
and you keep half of it♪
Official Su.
♪The petals scatter and show me your image♪
♪One decision makes every difference♪
I am Yu Hao.
I am Secondary Prince Consort's right-hand man.
You know poetry.
I'm flattered.
My elder sister taught me some
poems when I was a kid.
He is just like him.
Is this really a coincidence?
I've been here for days.
Why haven't I met you before?
Official Su, you have your hands full.
Of course, you wouldn't notice a mere servant.
But should you ever need anything,
I'm at your command.
Yu Hao?
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Official Su.
♪I look at her but think of her♪
♪Less capricious, more elegant♪
♪Forget it, don't hurt her♪
It's late at night. Shouldn't you get some rest?
I'll rest after I've collected the tangerine peels.
Orange peels?
Yes.
♪If I could meet her someday♪
An old friend of mine liked orange peels too.
Especially the scent.
Scents can be so fascinating.
We can't see nor touch it.
But when there is a scent,
the memories come pouring in.
I'm sure that old friend
was very dear to you.
It's all in the past now.
Right.
You've served Secondary Prince Consort for years.
Have you ever thought about getting married?
I did.
But unless I could meet
a gentle and upright person much like yourself,
I'd rather stay unmarried.
It's getting late.
You should get some rest.
Yu Hao! Your...
Your sachet...
Did he leave this here on purpose?
He had fallen in love with me.
Princess's Residence
Official Su, is this...
Come on, sit down.
Official Su.
Isn't this what you want?
I don't think it's appropriate.
You took the initiative to show affection...
Then I shall do it as you wish!
Official Su, please behave yourself.
It would be bad
if others saw this!
Let them watch!
They shall witness how I pamper you.
No, Official Su.
Stop yelling.
No one will be here to save you.
Scream all you want, but no one will save you!
How dare you!
How dare you defile a man in my house!
Your Highness! I deserve justice!
This pervert
stole my sachet,
and now she wanted...
She even wanted to tarnish my reputation!
Your Highness, that's not true.
This is a misunderstanding.
Have mercy on me!
This is all a misunderstanding!
A misunderstanding?
Then you can explain yourself
at the administrative office!
Please, no.
Your Highness, please don't do this.
I'm sorry. Please punish me, Your Highness!
If you're sorry,
you should apologize to Yu Hao.
Yes, you're right.
This is my fault.
I couldn't hold my urges.
Please forgive me!
Please...
In your opinion,
how should we punish Official Su?
After all, Official Su...
is a respected officer.
If word gets out...
Prince Consort, please show mercy!
Please have mercy, Prince Consort!
If Official Su
doesn't cause any trouble here,
we could overlook this incident.
What does Your Highness think?
Well...
Official Su...
I get it. I get it!
I definitely won't cause you any trouble.
I will behave at all times.
Your Highness, Prince Consort, forgive me.
Forgive me!
Well...
We'll proceed with my husband's proposition.
I'm grateful to both Your Highness and
Prince Consort for your mercy!
How could I live with this?
I should just end my life...
Your Highness!
You must help me!
That cursed Qu Tan Er...
is blackmailing me with what I did
to that servant.
Her Majesty is losing patience because
I couldn't deliver results.
I'm having a wolf by the ears.
I'm grateful Your Highness would
listen to my worries.
Otherwise, I couldn't handle this harsh life.
Official Su, stand up.
I know your frustration.
But if there's no major movement,
please stay cautious.
If you come to my manor too often,
people might start suspecting.
But I serve Her Majesty.
If Your Highness wants to know
what Her Majesty is doing,
I'll still have to come here to inform you.
Your Highness.
Eldest Young Master refused to
accept the ginseng soup you sent again.
I must see to other matters.
I should go now, Official Su.
Your Highness? Your Highness? Your Highness!
Your Majesty, it's time for your medicine.
How is the investigation I sent you on?
As Your Majesty expected,
Su Yue La and Eldest Princess
have been meeting more frequently.
She is conspiring with Qu Mei Er.
I had already turned a blind eye to it.
The inspection on the operation progress
was a bold move from her.
Your Majesty values loyalty the most.
Su Yue La has defected.
She betrayed Your Majesty.
Her sin cannot be forgiven.
Send my word to Second Princess's
Residence tomorrow.
Su Yue La will be assigned to Yu Prefecture
to work as its new governor.
She must set out immediately.
I shall get rid of the root of the trouble
while she is stationed at that remote land.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
The operation is still a priority.
Yes.
Princess's Residence
As decreed by Her Majesty,
Supervisor of Internal Affairs Su Yue La
is wise and righteous.
She has been appointed the
Governor of Yu Prefecture.
Effective immediately.
The end.
Yu Prefecture?
That is a remote and barren land!
After Official Wu was sent to Yu Prefecture,
her corpse was found in the wild.
I can't go there. I can't be there!
I want to serve Her Majesty! I must stay!
Kneel and be grateful for the offer.
No.
Your Highness. Your Highness!
Your Highness, save me!
Put up a few good words for me to Her Majesty.
I can be your servant!
I will forever be loyal to you!
I will devote my life to serve Your Highness!
Official Su, this is a promotion.
Technically speaking, you should
have my congratulations.
Your Highness. Your Highness!
Your Highness! Save me!
I can't go to that place!
Your Highness, save me! Your Highness!
I can't disobey Her Majesty's order.
Official Su, you should accept your fate.
Be on your way.
Qu Tan Er.
If you did not set me up,
I wouldn't have gone so far!
I'll kill you!
Cheng Cheng, you got hurt.
Qu Tan Er, I curse you!
I'll kill you!
Let go of me!
Qu Tan Er! I'll kill you!
Let me go!
Cheng Cheng, how are you?
Are you all right?
Bear with it a little. I'll get the medicine.
Tan Er.
Are you my Cheng Cheng?
Yes. I am your Cheng Cheng.
I'm glad you're fine.
I'm so glad...
you've been waiting for me.
Do you know how hard it has been for me?
Do you know how badly I want to
go back to raise our son with you?
Do you know how much I had missed you?
♪You turn around as the firework fades♪
♪Fate played a trick on me
so I pick up my flute again♪
I know.
I know everything now.
♪The string broke and the song ended,
they went their separate ways♪
I also know...
you're a stubborn cockroach.
You're a cockroach.
Now, listen to me.
When Su Yue La attacked you,
I regained my memories.
But...
All right, don't worry.
I know everything now.
Whenever I feel worried for you
or when I feel jealous,
our memories together or
any familiar conversations
will come back to me.
I'll regain my memories.
I am aware of these factors too.
I used them to restore your memories.
But it doesn't work every single time.
Just now
Su Yue La tried to stab you.
The worry and fear I felt
were like a leash,
it binds my heart.
My heartbeat elevated.
It was like it's going to come out of me.
You mean
your fear caused palpitation.
When I regained my memories back then,
I had the same feeling.
I get it now.
You managed to regain your memories
because the situation you were in
shared great resemblance
to our past experiences.
At the same time, your heartbeat
elevated in a short time.
When it reaches a certain level,
your memories will come back to you.
A certain level?
We don't have an electrocardiogram
or CT scans in this world.
We don't even have MRI here.
I'm not sure what that particular rate is.
But one thing is certain.
When your emotion reaches its peak,
the gateway to your memories will be opened.
Who would have thought
Physician Qu's theory actually
has academic values?
However,
there are matters at hand
that require time to plan.
Also,
I haven't regained my power either.
As long as you're my dear Cheng Cheng.
As for your power...
Only one thing matters.
Princess's Residence
Tan Er.
Returning a gift is the only excuse I can have
to see you again.
Give it to me.
Young Master, what about we send
someone else to inform them?
No need.
Whenever it is,
I always belong to Second Princess's Residence.
Su Yue La was eventually useful
before she got lost.
Now...
we finally know how to trigger your memories.
Since it's a double delight,
shouldn't we celebrate it?
How should we celebrate it?
You know the rules.
If we kiss now,
you'll become the other guy again.
Even without my memories of the past,
I will always be myself.
I'm still the one who will never get tired
of kissing you thousands of times.
This house...
has no place for me.
Everything I've sacrificed...
was just a joke.
Get out!
How many times have I told you?
I told you to get out.
It's me, Yan Chen.
Why are you here?
Yan Chen, no matter what you want to do,
I'll always be there for you.
Even if I have to anger the world
and get cursed by thousands of people,
I will still be by your side.
Why?
Do I not deserve...
the slightest attention...
or affection from them?
You've done nothing wrong.
It's their fault.
You should blame the customs
for making you obey.
The customs?
It's like a knife...
that is stabbing in my heart.
I could only let my blood...
slowly drain away from my body.
No, Yan Chen.
No?
No one is willing to give me any hope!
You will have the best life out of all men.
You'll have the most freedom.
You'll live more like yourself.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪A flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter what
hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have to
travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter what
hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have to
travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪