Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
The Eternal Love S3
Episode 15
How about it?
If I say
that I don't want him to leave,
even if that means putting on an act forever,
and spending the whole lifetime in a lie
to let him live in a dream,
would you be mad?
Did you say to him that you want a divorce?
I know how much he loves Qu Tan Er
and I know that if he thinks that
Qu Tan Er has abandoned him,
he would be in unendurable pain.
I can't bear to see that.
I know that
his kindness towards you
and towards me
was genuine.
If there is a way to keep up the lie forever,
so that he wouldn't be in pain,
I would gladly do it.
But no matter what choice we make,
we would be hurting him to no end.
Perhaps since the moment the real Qu Tan Er
drowned and lost her life,
Eldest Brother was bound to get hurt.
But he doesn't know
that you're not the real Qu Tan Er.
Don't blame yourself too much.
But it was my arrival
that disrupted the peace.
Let's give him some time
and let him think about it calmly.
We also need to think about it.
To think it through.
Go to rest now.
Okay.
Cheng Cheng.
These days, Yan Chen
pretends as if nothing has happened.
I don't know what to do.
Yan Chen.
During breakfast,
I saw that you were sweating a little.
So I thought that perhaps
your clothes were too thick
and asked a servant to fetch some thinner
clothing out of storage.
Yan Chen...
Alright.
I still need to verify the ledger of the residence.
You keep getting no salary as a punishment,
so I must be more careful with our money.
- Yan Chen.
- Eldest...
I'll put the clothes away.
He has chosen to lie to himself
and pretend that nothing ever happened.
Tan Er!
I was just about to bring you these desserts.
These are your favorite walnut and date delights.
I made them myself.
Yan Chen,
this is the divorce paper.
If you think there's something wrong with it,
please tell me.
I'm sorry.
You're really trying to take care of me
with your every word.
As long as I am willing to leave,
you can give me anything.
What would be wrong there?
Yan Chen...
A divorce isn't appropriate.
Repudiation...
if you give me a repudiation paper,
I will leave.
But if I repudiate you,
your life would be even harder,
only a divorce can...
If you are going to abandon me,
then stop pretending to care about me!
The less of this ridiculous compensation
you give me,
the less sorrow and misery I feel.
As it currently stands,
I have no other choice.
I'm sorry. Please calm down.
No other choice?
I don't want to leave.
I was repudiated by you.
I will wait for you
to come to see me with the repudiation paper.
What else do you want to say?
Go ahead.
I can't explain it well,
but Qu Tan Er really did love you.
However, the current Second Princess isn't...
Even now,
you are still trying to meddle with my emotions.
I know
you won't believe in any of my explanations,
but the Qu Tan Er before loved you very much.
Of course I know that.
Of course I know
Tan Er's love for me was real.
If it weren't for you,
her feelings for me would always be real!
It was just an incident at the harem selection,
yet the next day she climbed over the fence
just to meet you.
The day before, you were the laughing stock of
the entire country for being unscrupulous.
The day after, you got her
to write a song about how morally sound you are.
Don't tell me that
you had no one else to choose but her!
If you indeed had no feelings for her,
why would you choose someone
I treasured like this?
At that time,
I indeed had no feelings for her.
My mistake for realizing it so late.
I was using my own happiness to protect you
throughout all that has happened.
I cannot argue with that.
Perhaps since that moment,
all I can see is her.
I'm sorry.
I will leave this place
as you wish.
Eldest...
♪Got used to looking for your shadow in a crowd♪
♪Thinking back to those days of happiness♪
♪But actually, I know that the me now
and the me before♪
♪Have strayed a great distance apart♪
♪Two hearts in a lonely world♪
Mo Yan Chen.
Wait a second, Mo Yan Chen!
Let me send you back, okay?
Please stay, Your Highness.
Farewell.
Mo Yan Chen!
If Second Princess insists on sending me back,
then I will cut off my hair
right here.
You...
♪Some things fade as you watch them♪
♪There's so much unhappiness
that no one can understand♪
♪The same amount of helpless reluctance
is also there♪
♪Some people are forgotten
as you think about them♪
♪Sometimes you wake up
just as your dreams are coming true♪
♪Making me realize
that I was too naive in the past♪
Mo Residence
What happened?
I have no idea either.
Leave!
Go, go, go, go.
His Lordship has told me to tell you that
the Mo Family's motto is to be faithful and bold,
and those who treat their wives
poorly are not allowed in the residence.
I'm very sorry to say this,
but morals and the family's motto are above all.
Eldest Young Master,
please abide by the traditions.
Either cut off your hair and train as a monk
or leave your name on the memorial arch
to preserve your chastity
in order to right the cardinal guides
and constant virtues.
Young Master!
Eldest Brother, what are you doing?
Get up and come in with me.
It's Father's idea?
I will talk to him.
Feng Yang.
This is fine.
I can finally cut off my feelings.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Eldest Brother!
Yun Ying!
Take good care of Eldest Brother.
Tell him, I know it's not his fault.
Yes.
Mo Residence
Why can't they take him in?
Isn't Feng Yang the head of the family?
Hasn't she always respected Yan Chen very much?
I heard that Feng Yang tried her best to stop
Yan Chen from cutting his hair to become a monk.
But Eldest Brother was afraid that his staying
would affect the Mo Family's reputation.
I originally thought that...
letting him go was the best option,
but who would have thought it'd come to this.
Cheng Cheng.
I wish that he could live a peaceful life.
Who is it?
Father.
Wait a moment.
Hurry and leave from the back door.
Continue to recruit soldiers
and purchase supplies.
But don't act rashly.
Follow my instructions.
Understood.
Come in.
If you have come here for your eldest brother,
then don't bother speaking.
Father, even if you had let Eldest Brother stay,
how much of an impact would it have on you?
Did you have to be so cruel?
I wanted to ask you.
Why did you have to go that far?
Yan Chen being repudiated
will let Her Majesty think
that there's more to your marriage
than what was mentioned before.
Now that Her Majesty
grows suspicious of Second Princess,
the Mo family will look even more suspicious.
Of course I need to ease that suspicion of hers.
Is Eldest Brother's situation
so unimportant to you?
Was it me who caused him to be in such a situation?
Cheng Er,
aren't you the cause of his misfortunes?
Since it has come to this,
and Second Princess is fully devoted to you,
you must make haste
and fulfill your responsibilities.
Father, please accept Eldest Brother
into the residence.
Cheng Er.
You knew very well that Yan Chen
and Second Princess are childhood friends,
yet you still robbed Yan Chen of his beloved.
Was it not you
who wanted to use Second Princess
to take the throne?
Was it not you who
came to me and spoke of your plan?
Have you forgotten about all that?
Indeed, it was me.
But I now have someone I wish to protect
and I have found a reason to not hurt the innocent.
Someone you wish to protect?
Very well.
Cheng Er.
Your mother carried this sword into battle
for many years.
I clean it carefully everyday
as I can't bear to see any dust on it.
Eagles don't catch flies.
Those with weak hearts can accomplish nothing.
Father, if so,
then I can no longer work alongside you.
I shall take my leave.
Forgive me for not being a filial son.
Cheng Er!
Your Majesty.
Has the repudiation of Mo Yan Chen cleared
the cloudiness in Your Majesty's mind?
I once thought that they were using each other
to each of their own benefits.
It is only now that I realize
if their relationship wasn't genuine,
why did she have to repudiate Mo Yan Chen?
Now that Qu Tan Er has abandoned
this childhood friend of hers,
then she will no longer bother
to put up an act in front of me.
Your health is of the utmost importance,
Your Majesty.
No matter what they do,
they cannot escape from
Your Majesty's arrangement,
so there's no need to worry.
Even if we met, you wouldn't recognize me now...
Forget it.
I worried too much before.
Qu Mei Er would not let this go.
She won't let Qu Tan Er
treat this as a private matter.
Let's see how this will go down.
Many thanks to Official Chen and Official Su
for your help.
Once we succeed,
I will not forget your loyalty to me.
Long live Your Highness.
Your Highness, chances like this are rare.
Tomorrow, we will ask to impeach
Second Princess in front of Her Majesty.
But...
But what?
Forgive my bluntness,
but the current situation is dire.
Your Highness, you must not
be held down by your personal feelings this time,
you must draw the line with Mo Yan Chen.
This is for the best.
Right.
If Your Highness were to be involved with
Mo Yan Chen right now,
then in Her Majesty's eyes, it would be immoral.
I fully understand your concern.
However, my Prince Consort will only be
Mo Yan Chen, whenever it is.
I hope you keep this in mind.
Yes, Your Highness.
Speak up. What is with these memorials?
Your Majesty.
Second Princess's Prince Consort,
Mo Lian Cheng,
has ignored all tradition and acted disrespectfully
toward those of higher status.
Second Princess, being the head of the household,
not only has she not stopped him,
she hasn't fulfilled her duties either
and got carried away in her private life.
Furthermore, she repudiated her Main Prince Consort,
Mo Yan Chen, for no reason.
This is against cardinal guides
and constant virtues.
Is that really so?
Not a single word of lie, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, according to Dongyue traditions,
after Mo Yan Chen was repudiated for no reason,
he suffered and was forced to
move into the memorial arch of chastity.
Second Princess being a princess,
is the foundation of our nation,
a descendant of the royal family.
But based on what she has done,
I recommend that she should be abolished.
Agreed.
I also agree.
I agree as well.
I, Qu Tan Er, am here to plead to Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, please clear Mo Yan Chen's name.
I would accept any punishment.
Call her in.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Speak.
Now that Mo Yan Chen
was repudiated by me for no reason
and exiled to the memorial arch
of chastity to suffer.
Was it all my fault?
Second Princess repudiated him for no reason,
it is against order and morals.
Of course it is the fault of Second Princess.
That is correct, Official Chen.
If it is supposedly all my fault,
yet the victim is also suffering,
isn't that illogical?
Your Majesty,
I am at fault.
Therefore, the laws should be rewritten
to clear Mo Yan Chen's name.
Then, I will accept any punishment.
Qu Tan Er, if Her Majesty were to clear
Mo Yan Chen's name as you mentioned,
are you willing to take any punishment?
Of course.
So Eldest Princess,
do you think that Mo Yan Chen is innocent?
Of course Mo Yan Chen is innocent.
Everyone here knows it's true.
If so, then it is my plead to Your Majesty
to have a declaration made, so that innocent men
that were repudiated like Mo Yan Chen
can live a peaceful life.
Afterwards, I will accept
any punishment from Your Majesty
with no objection.
Since a conclusion has been made,
I will allow it.
Prepare to receive your punishments,
Second Princess.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Princess's Residence
Second Princess is grounded right now,
but she told me to bring these
to Eldest Young Master no matter what.
Oh.
Fourteenth Young Master,
how about I carry these for you?
As a woman, it is my responsibility.
Then I take half, and you take half.
Let's go.
Fourteenth Young Master,
when I taught you swordsmanship last time,
you said that I was cute.
If you don't like it,
then I'll never say it again!
But please don't be mad at me.
No, no, I'm not mad at you.
I'm a woman.
How can you say that I'm cute?
It's good to be cute.
Second Princess once told me,
to be cute, you must speak in reduplication.
Reduplication?
For example,
"eat food food", "take a nap nap", "so scared scared".
That sounds right.
Reduplication?
Then Fourteenth Young Master,
"hurry hurry" back to the "residence-dence".
Those "present-sents" are a bit heavy.
Be "careful careful".
When you come to visit the next time,
how about I teach you
"swordsmanship-ship" again?
Sounds good. I'll get going then.
Don't forget your promise of teaching me
"swordsmanship-ship".
But don't get "mad mad" at me
for being "clumsy clumsy".
Or else I'll be "depressed-pressed".
Then I'm leaving, Jing Xin Xin.
Fourteenth Young Master is way cuter than me.
Fourteenth "Young Master Master".
No, Fourteenth "Young Young Master".
Fourteenth Young...
Why is this reduplication thing so hard?
Jing Xin Xin.
Your Majesty,
are you perhaps suspecting
that Second Princess' actions today
had something to do with Mo Yuan Long?
Since when did she care about laws?
She was definitely prepared for today.
It's just a matter of whether
Qu Tan Er and Mo Lian Cheng
are pawns of Mo Yuan Long
or his allies.
Eighth Young Master of the Mo family...
How about I go and investigate what they're up to?
Mo Lian Cheng has acted immorally.
Second Princess's Residence's conduct
needs to be rectified.
Get Su Yue La into the residence for rectification.
Understood.
I hope that Official Su
won't let Your Majesty down
and find the evidence
of Second Princess being beguiled
by Mo Yuan Long.
Second Princess.
Second Princess, Qu Tan Er, humbly accept the decree.
By the grace of heaven's will,
Her Majesty hereby proclaims...
Troubles have constantly arisen
in Second Princess's Residence.
Secondary Prince Consort, Mo Lian Cheng,
disrespected those of higher status.
Cardinal guides and constant virtues
were violated.
Second Princess, Qu Tan Er,
focused solely on her romantic relationships
and neglected her studies.
Thus, Her Majesty has mandated
Secretary of State, Su Yue La,
to supervise the rectification in the residence
so that all returns to normal.
That is all.
Second Princess, please accept the decree.
I humbly accept the decree.
Official Su.
You came in such grandeur.
Those who knew might think
you're here to pass on the decree,
those who didn't would think you're here
to confiscate the residence.
Official Su.
Second Princess has got a quick mouth.
Please forgive her, Official Su.
Official Su, may I ask
if all this rectification business
has a set time?
Such as, at what hour
do you enter the residence
and at what hour do you leave for the palace?
What Her Majesty intended is that
from now on, I no longer need to return to the palace.
Until I believe that
the cardinal guides
and constant virtues have been
reestablished in Second Princess's Residence.
You're staying?
She's planning to walk all over me, huh?
Jing Xin.
Settle Official Su down in a nice guest room
and prepare rooms
for the servants from the palace.
Yes.
It hasn't been long since the position of
Main Prince Consort has become vacant,
and you, Secondary Prince Consort,
have already taken charge of the household.
Official Su, it doesn't seem like you are here
to reestablish the guides and virtues,
but rather, it appears you're here for a fight.
I'm only here because of Her Majesty's orders.
Second Princess, I warn you not to
deduce Her Majesty's thoughts.
I think that Su Yue La
is just using the decree to make a show of force.
It's clear that
she's here to take her revenge
about her little brother losing out in
the harem selection.
Su Yue La is not hard to deal with,
but I'm afraid Her Majesty is behind this.
However, we have indeed been
a little high-key these days.
We've been out promoting
financial freedom for men
and promoting the freedom to divorce.
I think Her Majesty is warning us
to not try to usurp her power.
She's telling us to lay low.
If she wants to punish you,
she has other ways of doing it.
She definitely has something
she wants to investigate,
or else she didn't have to send an official
to stay over at the residence.
Well, in my opinion,
Her Majesty just wants to take you into her harem.
She sent Su Yue La here
to see whether
our bond is unbreakable
or as fragile as glass.
Kisses, hugs, and lift you high.
Why don't you tell me
if our bond is unbreakable or not?
Look at you, being a quick-learner.
We would need Su Yue La to help us
decipher the true intent of Her Majesty.
For now, we will deal with challenges
as they come up.
When the time is right,
she will let the cat out of the bag.
Then... where's my kiss?
You!
How can you do such a shameful act
under broad daylight?
And you call yourself a royal? How shameful!
It's Secondary Prince Consort's fault
for being so charming
that I couldn't resist him.
Very well.
It seems that Secondary Prince Consort
knows a lot about seduction techniques,
but nothing about the moral codes for men.
Our first lesson in etiquette
would be learning
Three Obediences and Four Virtues.
Men should comply by Three Obediences
in their lifetime.
None is their independence.
The unmarried shalt obey their mother.
The married shalt obey their wife.
The widowed shalt obey…
Secondary Prince Consort,
do you know what Four Virtues are?
Four Virtues are
ethics, speech,
visage, and skill.
A virtuous man should act
with dignity and politeness.
A virtuous household should be
tranquil and dignified,
modest and unsullied.
Sand Vulture
*A slang which means "moron"
How strange!
Why are there still mosquitoes
at this time of year?
Shoo shoo.
You have my thanks, Your Highness.
It's nothing. No need to thank me.
Then I'll continue...?
Go ahead.
A virtuous husband should act
with dignity and politeness.
A virtuous household should be
tranquil and dignified,
modest and unsullied.
Now let's talk about
the speech of a virtuous husband,
that is to not belittle, to not speak
with magniloquence, and to not double-tongue.
idiot
*literally "Sand Vulture", means idiot
With his wife...
Sand Vulture?
What's this?
This is the Prince Consort
complimenting Official Su.
You might not know this,
but it is said that
the "Sand Vulture" is a legendary beast.
People say that it has feathers
that shine like the golden sun.
It has a mighty body
that allows it to fly tirelessly
for thousands of miles.
In Prince Consort's heart,
Official Su, you are that big Sand Vulture!
Princess's order is the most important.
Wait a minute!
How can you touch the inkstone
with your bare hands
when grinding the inkstone?
You should wrap it with a piece of paper
as dirtying your hand with ink is unsightly.
Then let me check
if Prince Consort's hand
is dirtied with ink.
Those slender fingers of his are so fair.
Very well.
Then let me see if
any ink has gotten on
Prince Consort's cute little face.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪A flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part,
no matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part,
no matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind
in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪