♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
=The Eternal Love S3=
=Epispde 08=
The medicine is not working at all?
Why didn't I think of him?
Since we're already here,
he might be here too.
Jing Xin, go out of town with me tomorrow.
I need to find someone.
To find someone?
If it's a physician you need,
you don't need to go in person.
I can get it done for you.
No.
The person I need...
is not someone
you can easily hire.
Who is it?
You'll find out tomorrow.
Am I at the wrong place
or does this place get renovated?
This place is far from the city.
When did you come here before?
Let's go.
Black hair.
Is this really Liu Qian Shui?
[*Literally means "streaming thousand water"]
(Hermit Liu)
Senior.
Excuse me...
Liu Qian Shui!
Please spare me, hero!
Could you give me a few more days?
Are you here for fortune-telling
or exorcism?
Insolence!
She's the second princess of Dongyue!
Are you not going to greet her!
She's the second princess?
Then I'm the second prince!
Please, no!
I wasn't expecting Her Highness's arrival.
I apologize for my manner.
All right, Jing Xin.
There is no need for violence.
Wait for me outside.
Fine.
What the...
You're like a coward.
You came here too?
I've always been here.
You've grown younger.
Is this sorcery or did you dye your hair?
I wasn't old anyway.
True.
You're no ordinary man.
You're a sage from Xuanling Continent.
It's been so long.
Some adjustments seem normal.
(So people are already spreading rumors
about my incredible power.)
As your leader,
the chief of the Qu Clan of Xuanling Continent
has a new mission for you.
Chief?
I made some analysis.
It was caused by an anomaly
of the Soul-guarding Bead.
Am I still the host of Soul-guarding Beads?
(What is a Soul-guarding Pork?)
[*"Pork" sounds like "Bead" in Chinese]
(I've never tried that before.)
(How can she be a host of some pig?)
(Maybe she is just crazy.)
(I can put this fool to great use.)
Stop pretending.
There is no outsider around.
Soul-guarding Bead.
The Xuanling Continent?
See? You do know the countersign.
Comrade Liu Qian Shui.
We finally meet again.
(Liu Qian Shui?)
But I'm Liu Bai Shui. Now with nine hundred more?
[Literally means "streaming hundred water"]
(Forget it. I won't be disadvantaged anyway.)
The way you put it
cleared all the doubt for me.
Fine, enough with the fancy words.
Comrade Liu.
It's time to ditch your disguise.
I really need your help this time.
You need my help?
You could have started with that.
I, Liu Bai Shui, may not be a prodigy,
but I am
fairly knowledgeable in the field
of fortune-telling.
- I have the wisdom of Heaven and Earth...
- All right.
Yin Yang and...
I know you dyed your hair.
But where did you get your accent?
Liu Bai Shui?
You're nine hundred short.
Forget it.
You can have whatever name you like.
However, about the thing,
I need to tell you from the beginning.
(Hermit Liu can answer all your doubts.)
Do you understand
what I just told you?
(A parallel universe?)
(She is so hopeless.)
(It would be a pity not to make
a fortune out of her.)
Judging by what Your Highness said,
the secondary prince consort
certainly has amnesia.
But this could be problematic.
You can't do nothing either?
Then do you have the Soul-guarding Bead
and the Soul-parting Flute?
I could give it a try myself.
I don't have them with me.
Can't you be more useful?
You don't have an idea or a magic item.
Or course, I have an idea.
There is a cure for it.
But the ingredients are very expensive
and it's hard to find.
It might require a hefty sum of money.
So you need money.
That's easy.
Look.
I must first travel to Beixuan
to acquire a herb.
That journey alone
could be very costly.
A hundred taels should be enough, right?
Yes.
That's enough for the first ingredient.
As for the second ingredient,
I must go to Nanlu to procure it.
That trip could cost me
quite a fortune.
Fine. Here you are.
All right.
As for the third ingredient,
which is also the most crucial of all,
I must travel
to Xiyue instead.
Trust me.
I will require
several Ferghana horses on my journey
to find the third herb before the next spring.
The next spring?
That won't do.
How much do you need?
Just get to the point.
Sure.
I'll give you a straight answer.
Look.
The truth is...
After we've combined the several main herbs
of this prescription,
the rest of the ingredients
are easy to find.
The other
ingredients are things, such as
millennial ginseng,
knotweed,
and old Ganoderma fungi
that grows on cliffs.
Right!
The most important ingredient of all
might require me to go to...
Xuan...
Wait.
The Xuanling Continent.
After I get there, we'll have all the ingredients
to make the medicine.
Fine.
You can keep all the money.
Feel free to let me know if you need more.
I think it's enough for now.
Judging by Your Highness's heartfelt story,
it seems like.
Your Highness's love for the secondary
prince consort is true.
I'm sure you will find happiness together.
So don't worry.
You paid me well.
I will do whatever within my capability
to realize your goal.
I don't need your flattery.
But I need to know.
How long is it going to take
to collect all the herbs?
I think it's around...
July and August,
ten days to run and hide...
It should take a month or so.
That's too long!
I need it done as soon as possible.
Do you have another way?
More haste, less speed.
I will need more time to brew the medicine.
Trust me.
These herbs have unique features and they
conflict with each other.
The slightest error in the brewing
will cause devastating consequences.
So you must be patient.
Fine.
But get it done as soon as you can.
Sure.
One more thing.
Use the
finest herbs for this medicine you'll be making.
Money is not an issue here.
I assure you.
I will spend
every penny you paid me.
Very well. That settles it for now.
I'm counting on you.
Don't mention it.
I should get going.
Jing Xin, let's go.
Your Highness,
have a nice day!
So she is the future crown princess of Dongyue.
The country is doomed.
Forget it.
Even with all this money,
her sickness is hopeless.
(Princess's Residence)
What is going on?
Your Highness, it's Official Su.
Let's check it out.
I've been expecting you, Your Highness.
Second Princess Qu Tan Er, heed this decree.
As written in this imperial order,
Her Majesty has great expectations
for Second Princess Qu Tan Er.
Thus, the princess's capability shall be tested,
so she can be take up the right position
to serve Her Majesty and the country
as soon as possible.
The end.
I accept the imperial order.
Your Highness has three days.
Her Majesty
has given Your Highness time
for proper preparation.
I hope Your Highness lives up to the expectation.
I should take my leave now.
Jing Xin.
You're a knowledgeable person
and have mastered many art forms.
This is a great
opportunity for you to prove your worth.
Eldest Brother, you're right.
I wish you all the best, Your Highness.
Am I really that amazing to you?
I hope you're right about me.
I need some time to process this.
A fine cup of tea.
Official Su has contributed much to the country.
It's a token of goodwill.
I hope you like it.
I will gladly accept Your Highness's kindness.
You were at the second princess's residence
to send the imperial order.
Was everyone at the scene?
Mo Yan Chen is doing well.
Your Highness has nothing to worry about.
How can he be well?
He gave his heart to Qu Tan Er.
Yet she never answered his love.
As soon as Your Highness rises to power,
Prince Yan Chen will certainly...
Mi Xue.
I want to be more than just his aide.
Your Highness is loyal,
not to mention ambitious.
But there is one thing I don't understand.
I hope Your Highness doesn't find it offensive.
Official Su, you're one of us.
Do tell.
You went out of your way to make this test happen.
If Qu Tan Er actually passed the test,
wouldn't your effort end up helping the enemy?
I had taken that into account.
Whether Qu Tan Er passes the test or not,
it won't end well for her.
I don't understand.
If she passed the test,
Her Majesty would be warier of her.
But if she failed,
it would be evident to Her Majesty
that she is not worthy of being the crown princess.
Your Highness is very tactful indeed.
Impressive.
In that case,
I must send the message to Her Majesty.
I've taken enough of your time.
Mi Xue, see Official Su off.
This way, please.
This is bad.
Why are they going to test me all of a sudden?
What should I do?
I should malinger.
Yes, I should malinger.
Tan.
Tan? What's wrong?
Jing Xin!
Jing Xin, tell Her Majesty now.
I'm ill. I'm in great pain.
I'm afraid I can't visit the palace for now.
Are you faking it?
Was it so obvious?
If you informed Her Majesty,
she would send an imperial physician here.
Would you be able to fool the physician
Her Majesty sent?
This is treachery against the empress.
Are you sure about this?
No way!
No.
I should go into hiding for a couple of days.
Jing Xin, I leave everyone here in your care.
Keep them safe for me.
I must start
packing my belongings now.
Tan! Wait.
Jing Xin, give us some privacy.
I need to have a word with the second princess.
Do you really think you can run away?
What else can I do now?
Everyone here knows that
Qu Tan Er is a knowledgeable person.
I can usually get away by acting smart.
But in a real test...
There is no way I could fool anyone!
I must leave now.
So you know your own flaw.
Am I doing this for myself?
If they saw through my identity,
you would be in deep trouble again.
But since you choose to come here now,
are you going to elope with me?
If you want to elope, you should
elope with someone else.
But if you want to fool everyone,
come with me to the study.
The study?
Can't we elope to somewhere else?
This is Qu Tan Er's handwriting.
How do you know?
I read her letters.
Plenty of them.
She wrote them to a worthless friend.
So I know her handwriting very well.
These are
indeed letters and poems written
by Qu Tan Er.
What I need from you
is to copy her handwriting
as much as you can before the test.
In case Her Majesty wants to conduct any written tests.
But there are so many words.
How can I possibly do it in three days?
I bet I couldn't copy even a word.
One word is all you need.
The word "Yong" is all you need to mimic.
[*"Yong" means "forever"]
That's all?
Whatever Her Majesty wants,
I must only write the word "Yong"?
Are you serious about this?
The word
contains all the common strokes
we need for calligraphy.
When we learn how to write,
we start by practicing with this word.
If you master this word,
you can basically write any word.
If there is any suspicion,
you can always say it's your hasty handwriting.
This is still very tedious,
but it's much simpler than I thought.
Fine. I can do it.
Go for it.
As long as I have you with me,
I can master it in no time.
This is the power of love.
You should start practicing now.
Every four hours,
I'll have Jing Xin
send your handwriting to my study.
I'll send them back after marking.
Why?
If you stay with me,
you can supervise me at all times.
I must keep this a secret from my eldest brother.
If he found out
you're not the real Qu Tan Er,
your life would be in danger.
So you must practice in seclusion.
Other than Jing Xin,
no one is allowed to visit you.
At least show me how to write one word.
(Yong)
Amazing.
It's the same as her handwriting.
I'll give it a try.
(Yong)
Here.
♪I will come and go with the wind
as the blossoms fall♪
♪From a full moon to a new moon,
who longs for loneliness♪
Press downward, but don't overdo it.
A stroke across like a short leash.
A vertical stroke with an elegant curve.
Slow down. I didn't catch that.
♪I will never stop waiting for your return♪
♪We'll wander the land together,
like clouds touched by the winds♪
♪In your journey, I'll never be lonely♪
That's all for the lesson.
You should practice on your own.
I don't want to be executed over this.
♪Zhuangzi said love was the butterfly's secret♪
♪Laozi said love was a mysterious force♪
♪Please, who has the right answer?♪
♪The fool said love was but a riddle♪
♪Kongzi said distance ruins love♪
♪Mengzi said all the stars must align♪
♪But these are bluffs from the saints♪
(Yong)
♪We can say, love, love, love, love♪
(The word has the right form.)
(I can't accompany you tomorrow.)
(I wish you all the best.)
(I love Cheng Cheng, forever and always)
(It's been a long day. Rest well.)
I thought this was a test.
Why am I at the training ground?
Your Highness.
The test is a martial art test,
not a written test.
That means my practice for the past few days
was a waste of time.
I don't know martial arts.
How can I take the test?
I don't have an answer for that.
Your Highness.
Message from Her Majesty.
As a princess of our country,
it's your duty to devote your life
to the benefit of Dongyue.
The test today
is to determine whether Your Highness
has a strong physique
and whether you can shoulder
great responsibilities.
(It's just a physical test.)
(As a former real estate agent
who ran around the city,)
(my stamina must be above average.)
I understand.
I will do my best.
These are bows with draw weights
of one dan, three dan, and nine dan.
[*One dan equals 120 catties]
You may start with the lowest draw weight.
We'll see how much draw weight is your limit.
This is a test of your arm strength.
This should be a walk in the park.
Cheng Cheng taught me this.
I can draw a bow all right.
Hitting the bullseye
won't even be a problem.
(No.)
(Tan Er was frail.)
(Her Majesty knows that.)
(These tasks are easy for me.)
(But if I do it too well,)
(it draws nothing but suspicion.)
Official.
Even the lowest draw weight is too much for me.
I can't even pull the string.
Next.
Your Highness.
Please.
I can't handle it.
That hurts a lot.
That's all for today.
The joy of a newlywed hasn't worn off,
so I lack the necessary practice.
I'm sorry for being such a letdown.
Message from Her Majesty.
Your Highness must come to the palace
to practice every day.
Your next attempt will be in ten days.
Why can't Her Majesty give up on me?
I have to go to the palace every day?
I didn't catch that.
I mean I'll not disappoint Her Majesty again.
(Princess's Residence)
Tan.
How did the test go
with your handwriting?
Forget about it.
Jing Xin, you may leave now.
How did it go?
There was no written test.
But there was a physical test.
I messed up.
I saw how you went over the wall.
Your strength is on par with the other women,
perhaps it's even better.
You did this on purpose.
You saw me went over the wall
so you think I'm strong.
Do you want to find out
what I'm really capable of?
That won't be necessary.
Please enlighten me.
Why did you act like a weakling?
Since you know me so well,
why not have a guess?
That was because you knew
you were much muscular than the real Qu Tan Er.
To avoid suspicion,
you would rather fail the test
by pretending to be frail.
Muscular?
I'm muscular?
If that's how you see me,
I'll stop liking you!
Aren't you afraid of losing my favor?
But the way you improvised
was impressive.
I had underestimated you.
There are more you haven't seen!
We have the time.
You will discover my strength over time.
No.
What?
What was the purpose of this test?
They said I needed a strong body
to take on great responsibilities.
That's about it.
What responsibilities...
would require you to have a strong physique?
The test could have been...
about national affairs or military tactics.
Those are more reasonable.
But they went out of their way
only to find out whether you're strong enough.
Isn't that strange to you?
What do you think the purpose is?
I have no clue now.
But this is worrying.
You care a lot about me.
You took it wrongly.
I'm not the other guy.
You clearly care a lot about me.
Your cold shoulder is just a bluff.
My dear Cheng Cheng never let me down.
I can't wait to prove you wrong.
A physical test?
Qu Tan Er has always been frail.
Her Majesty knows that.
But a physical test...
Was it meant to embarrass her?
Is Her Majesty upset?
Was the princess punished?
You can consider it a punishment.
But it's weird.
It's weird? How so?
Her Majesty ordered the second princess to
practice every day at the palace.
Practice?
Her Majesty ordered only her to go to
the palace and practice.
It's as if
she is being trained to become
the next crown princess.
Your Highness, don't worry.
That might not be Her Majesty's plan.
Perhaps this was a warning for her.
Even if that wasn't the intention,
when the officers share this speculation,
those who are still wavering
would side with Qu Tan Er.
Then it's time to take action, Your Highness.
Your Majesty, please don't be upset.
The second princess lacks training.
She wasn't born with any defect.
That is true,
but she is too weak.
Her frail body
is not fit to serve me.
Now is the opportunity
to have her in the palace.
We'll slowly nourish her without her noticing,
so she can take over your duties.
I don't want to
place my hope on others either.
The altar requires great power.
Destiny waits for no one.
We have many farmlands.
An adequate increment in taxation
will resolve the funding problems.
I will see to it myself. Your Majesty
shouldn't be worried.
I have faith in you.
But my health has been deteriorating.
I hope Tan Er doesn't fall short.
When I need her to succeed the throne,
she must prove her worth to the imperial officers.
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪A flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part♪
♪No matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if ♪
♪I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part♪
♪No matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪