♪Following the way she walked through♪
♪He searches for every piece of memory that he had
with her♪
♪An unexpected encounter in the crowds♪
♪Was the start of their destined journey♪
♪No one can tell the end of the story♪
♪Since every heart is overloaded♪
♪The dream about blooming flowers is illusionary♪
♪Painful yet addictive♪
♪Love is too wild to be reined♪
♪Too deep to be forgot♪
♪The pain will forever stay with the scar on the
chest♪
♪He wants to linger in his dream♪
=Tears In Heaven=
=Episode 29=
Yuzheng.
Why didn't you tell me in advance
that you will come?
We have received
the money, footballs, projectors,
and generators
that you sent to school.
We don't have to worry about
blackouts in school anymore.
These little kids miss you a lot.
They often asked me in my ears,
when is Uncle Lei coming,
when is Auntie Xiaosu coming?
They just kept asking again and again.
Why didn't I see Shanwa?
Where is he?
HIs mother took him to the city.
His father is almost recovered.
His family is now together.
Shanwa is so happy about that.
Oh,
look. This is their family photo.
If I had known you were coming,
I would've asked Shanwa to come to you.
Why didn't I see Xiaosu?
Didn't she come with you?
Tell you what,
when Lei Yuzheng was put in prison,
I thought
he was a coddled and pampered child.
I even made a bet with others.
We bet he won't make it.
But,
he's really got something to be admired.
You know what?
When we got in there,
there were always some people
who wanted to pick a fight with us.
Because of his family's reputation,
he had to suffer more.
He got beaten.
For one time. Just one.
After that,
nobody dared to provoke him.
I've respected few people in my life.
He is one of them.
To tell you the truth,
he would never let me see him.
I have no idea about these.
But I knew it every time you came.
Lei Yuzheng has been through a lot.
He is tough underneath.
But people like him
needs a hand in the desperate situation.
Don't you think so?
I have to leave now.
We can meet after he's back.
Thank you for telling me this today.
You're welcome.
God helps those who help themselves.
The setback is in his mind.
He has to live over it by himself.
I'm leaving.
Yuzheng,
how many days are you going to stay
this time?
Why?
I just came here and
you already wanna drive me away?
No.
I wish you lived here all the time.
Fine.
Then, I'll live here.
Really? Are you kidding me?
You're so busy.
How can you live here all the time?
I'm not busy.
I'm serious.
I have made up my mind.
Fine.
On the island,
you can look at
the mountains and the sea,
and you may feel better then.
Kids,
do you miss Uncle Lei?
Yes!
Is Uncle Lei nice?
Then, ask him to play games with you,
Ok?
Ok!
I'm coming!
Run! Run!
Run! Run! Run!
Did you ask me about
the dismissal of Mr. Xia?
Dad,
uncle Xia resigned himself.
Why I'm the one to blame?
Besides,
what's the big deal?
Why do you get angry like this?
You fired him today.
Who will be the next?
Let me ask you.
How many long-time employees
in the group have been left?
What do you want?
Dad.
I have difficulties in this position.
I can't ask for your permission
for every decision I make.
I took the liberty of firing uncle Xia.
I apologize for that.
But no matter what I've done
went extreme or not,
the performance of the company
during this period of time was improved.
You can see it.
Xiangyuan,
I can let go of this.
But remember,
you have to ask for my advice
before you can take any actions
in the future.
Sure.
I keep it in my mind.
Nothing else, right?
Then, I'm leaving.
Mr. Liu,
why do you come to me?
To be honest,
when Mr. Ning introduced you to me
at the beginning,
I had doubt about your capability.
But today, I have to say that
it's worth it to have you
for this project.
I'm flattered.
Our friendship grows from conflicts.
Look.
I used to be a little harsh on you.
Please don't mind.
No, I don't.
You started this project over
for two times in the middle.
And you paid the bill yourself.
This
is the allowance to you.
That's all right, Mr. Liu.
That's what I should do.
Let's just keep the contract.
I can't accept it.
Fine.
Since you insist so much,
you have my recognition.
I have a big contract
worth of two million yuan
on the way.
Mr. Liu, I'm sorry,
but I wanna take a break,
and I don't take any order
for the time being.
Why? You quit?
It's not like that.
Just for now.
Why?
Your business is just picking up.
You are so young.
Why do you have to close down
when there's money to make?
Money is important to me.
But it's not the most important.
I have a friend who needs me now.
I have to be with him.
Miss Du,
can I ask you a private question?
Is this for love?
I got it.
Miss Du has affections and loyalty.
I admire you very much.
How about this?
Whenever you wanna work together,
come to.
Ok. Thank you.
Hello.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
The studio is closed for now.
I'm not available now.
Thank you. Bye.
What are you talking about?
The studio has been closed?
Du Xiaosu,
what are you doing?
I'm going to find Lei Yuzheng.
Lei Yuzheng?
I know Lei Yuzheng
is very important to you.
You can give up everything for him.
But,
he's not like us, Xiaosu.
He's out of the prison.
He still has a big fortune to spend.
But you...If you close down the studio,
you'll be down and out.
Have you ever thought about it?
I'm talking to you!
Have you figured all of this out?
Siqi,
if it's not for Lei Yuzheng,
I won't have my studio.
If I can't find him,
I'm not in mood for design now.
Don't worry.
Yuzheng,
I just went to town
and got some dishes that go with liquor.
Fine. Come on in.
(Borrowing Regulation)
Here.
Cheers.
Yuzheng,
you and Xiaosu are good people.
I really have no idea
what to do to thank you.
All right. Never mind.
For the kids,
you stay on this island on your own.
There are not many
young people like you now.
Yes.
Even my girlfriend
doesn't understand me.
She always said that
life here is too difficult.
She insisted that I should go
to work with her in the city.
What about the kids
if I leave?
Are you
on break now?
Probably,
she's been married now.
Let bygones be bygones.
Come on. Here's to you.
Yuzheng,
we are men.
I can see that
you and Xiaosu
had a fight, didn't you?
If you really can forget about her,
why do you have to live in this house?
Am I right?
But Yuzheng,
Xiaosu is really a good girl.
There are not many girls
as persistent as she is.
Don't wait
until to lose to know
how to cherish like me.
(Photo-Dating. Private Proposal)
CEO of the public company.
Well...
How come I, Zou Siqi,
cannot find a man to have dinner
with me.
You look so different from the photo.
You beautified it, right?
Dark yellow skin, rough pores.
You should take care of your skin.
I'm telling you,
if we women pay little attention to
the external beauty,
men
won't give us
the chance to show our internal beauty.
You only have two minutes.
I...
Stop talking.
Listen to me.
I'll give you 300 thousand yuan
as your plastic surgery fund.
Enhance your breasts.
Firm your butt.
Plump your lips.
And lose your fat.
After you do all of that,
you can barely be my mistress.
Stop talking! Stop stalking!
How about this?
I give you 50 thousand yuan every month.
And by the end of the year,
you can get a dividend.
Such requests
are acceptable.
Totally acceptable!
You're making me lose my confidence.
Mr. Gold Necklace, look over there.
There is a beauty.
Where? Where? Where?
Take one back home.
Perfect match for you.
As a woman,
aside from
being capable of giving birth,
the most important is that
she has to make contributions
to the family.
At least,
her salary should be half of mine.
Look. I've been
on blind dates for many times.
Why do I come across
the women like moth?
They can't even meet such requests!
All of them don't deserve me.
May I ask
how much is your monthly salary?
4,000 yuan.
Then I don't think
they are good for you.
Another drink, please.
On the way.
Not alone.
I'm leaving after this.
Not alone. Not lonely.
Don't wanna talk to you.
Last time we met,
you were dressing like this.
Don't you know to get dressed
to pick up girls?
I came here to drink.
Nobody cares what I'm dressed with.
Is it real?
It sounds like
there must be a lot of chicks
buying you drinks.
Aren't you the same?
Of course.
Do you think you and Shangguan are
the only luck of me?
Look.
What do you think?
My new boyfriend.
Enjoy yourself.
I'm leaving.
Have a seat. Shall we talk?
How are you doing recently?
What?
Nothing new.
You saw everything?
We've broken up for so long.
Are you still waiting for me?
If you don't want a relationship,
you can just have an affair.
You know I'm not that kind of person.
He Qunfei.
I think you're the man.
Lei Yuzheng has a friend like you.
I'll give him a thumb up.
But I'd like to ask you a question.
Is it worth it?
When Lian Po made amends,
he just bore the rods
and walked through the alley.
How long are you going to bear the rods?
Are you going to be single for him
for your life?
I'm out of my own will.
I've been living a good life.
No one would come here
if everything goes well.
What does it taste like?
This is bitter,
not even as good as medicine.
Siqi. I know
I failed you.
Since you've let it go,
stop saying sorry.
I know
you're just taking it out on me.
I am taking it out on you.
The guy in the bar
is not your boyfriend.
I just don't understand.
How come a good girl like me
has no admirers.
I've also tried blind dates.
But in the end, I realized
I want nothing to do with them at all.
I can't allow anyone else in my heart.
Siqi. I...
Qunfei.
Can we
see each other again?
Sure.
As long as you want,
you can meet me anytime.
It's just...
Stop.
I got it.
Just fit your deeds to your words.
You have my word.
You can treat me to dinner later.
I'm leaving.
Think about it.
We've been working together
for more than a decade.
Over the past years,
I've made a lot for everyone.
Yes. Yes.
That alone makes
you have to accompany me some tea
when you take a break.
Tea is fine.
It's just
we don't feel sure.
We have no idea what you're up to.
Since you've asked,
I'll just make it clear.
In my whole life,
I've hired men I trust,
and trusted the men I hired.
What Lin Xiangyuan has done
sometimes makes me have to change.
I'm planning to
put him on hold for a while.
As far what to do with him,
we'll talk about it later.
About removing Lin Xiangyuan
from the office,
if anyone doesn't wanna
get involved in it,
just let me know.
Hello everyone.
Hello.
(Emergency Exit)
(China opens to the world)
You really live here?
I just heard from Teacher Sun that
the houses on the island were shaken
by the typhoon,
and it was you who fixed them all.
If I hadn't seen it with my own eyes,
I wouldn't believe it.
I just come to see you,
and get you something to eat and use.
(School Magazine)
Did you watch the video of Shanwa?
How funny he is now.
He has learned the seaweed dance.
Seaweed. Seaweed.
And he's got fat and tall.
It must be his mother.
Lei Yuzheng.
Lei Yuzheng, where are you going?
Du Xiaosu,
what are you doing here?
Me?
I came to see you.
Don't you have your own business to do?
You're just like the dogskin plaster
every day.
Of course I do.
From now on I only have one thing to do.
Keep an eye on you.
For what?
No matter where I am or what I'll do,
it has nothing to do with you.
Lei Yuzheng.
You suddenly disappeared.
You have no idea how much
everyone has been worrying about you.
I'm really afraid that
something might happen to you.
Don't you understand
what I'm talking about?
I wanna be alone.
Please stay away from me.
Lei Yuzheng. Stop
pushing away the people
who care about you.
Will you?
We wanna help you.
Du Xiaosu.
In this world,
probably there are many people
who needs your help.
I'm not one of them.
Lei Yuzheng. Stop!
Lei Yuzheng!
Don't let it get to you.
I'm begging you. Don't jump.
Du Xiaosu, what are you talking about?
You scared the hell out of me!
You were coming up all of a sudden.
Why do I jump?
Then why are you standing so high?
Don't you wanna jump to end it all?
If you wanna jump,
I'll jump with you.
You jump. I jump.
Du Xiaosu.
Is there anyone in this world
who is more annoying than you?
When I was in Shanghai,
you had been following me to my home.
I come to this island,
and you follow me all the way here.
If I really can't figure it out,
it is because of you.
Come on. Let go of me.
No!
You wanna keep holding me like this?
What if you get too excited,
and our feet just slide?
We might fall.
Don't scare me.
Unless you say
you are not going to jump into the sea.
You swear.
I swear. I won't jump.
Can you let go of me?
You
didn't
mean to jump into the sea, did you?
I'm not like you.
Go ahead. What do you want from me?
Liu Siyang came to me.
He told me a lot about you
when you were in prison.
Lei Yuzheng.
No matter how you drive me away
in the future,
I won't leave you.
If you wanna stay on the island
as a fisherman,
I'll be a fisherman with you.
If you
don't wanna leave this island
all your life,
then I'll also stay here for my life.
Yuzheng, Xiaosu,
tonight let's...
Anyone?
There...
There is no way out.
We're done.
The tide is in.
How can we go back?
No signal.
Where is your phone?
My phone?
I...
I just came out in a hurry.
I didn't take it.
Yuzheng, Xiaosu.
Mr. Li. Hurry up!
Yuzheng.
Xiaosu.
Xiaosu, are you ok?
Why is your head burning so much?
I'm fine.
Xiaosu.
Don't…Hang in there!
Don't fall asleep.
During this period of time,
I always came here alone,
watching the boundless sea
and the lonely rocks.
They have no one to depend on,
particularly like
what I've been through.
I was sitting here
and wondering that
probably a lot of things
are meant to be.
In that kind of family,
I got fortune and status.
So, the God surely won't make me happy.
I was doomed to lose my mother.
It is doomed that nobody would love me.
And I can't learn how to love.
Everything now...
(The tomb of Wan Hua)
Everything has turned out to be
meaningless.
Lei Yuzheng, don't think like that.
Not that I don't want to
end it all,
and then I would be much more relieved.
But I figured it out very soon.
For people living in this world,
the most painful thing is not
getting old and dying alone.
Instead, it is that,
no matter how much you've paid,
you can't change the reality.
My mother already left me.
Since I was a child,
I have been determined
to become an excellent person
in order to prove to her.
It was such a mistake that
she abandoned me twenty years ago.
But later I realized
my mother had been dead.
Over the past twenty years,
no matter I have loved her or hated her,
I can't change it.
My mother can never come back.
Lei Yuzheng,
I'm cold.
I'm so cold.
Xiaosu.
You hang in there!
Lei Yuzheng.
Can you promise me one thing?
If we...
Xiaosu. Don't worry.
We can't make it.
I'll take you back.
Never leave me alone.
You hang in there!
Promise me.
I promise you.
Yuzheng.
Yuzheng. Xiaosu.
Are you there?
Yuzheng.
Over there.
Teacher Sun.
Xiaosu. Someone is coming for us!
Xiaosu!
Wake up! Xiaosu! Xiaosu!
Teacher Sun. We're here!
Teacher Sun.
Did I rave in my fever?
I take it seriously.
Why do you flush so much?
Your fever is already gone, isn't it?
The fever is already gone.
Why are you being so nice to me?
Of course I have to be nice to you.
The better you treat me,
I feel less secured in my heart
and more scared.
I'm afraid you have to be scared
for a while.
I will always be nice to you.
Dad, it's weekend today.
Lin Xiangyuan said
he would come to see you.
Dad.
The tea is cold.
I'll make you some hot tea.
(Yutian Briefing)
My tea has been cold for a long time.
Tell me. Why do you come to me today,
Mr. Lin?
Dad. Please forgive me.
I'm an ass.
I was not mature.
You've been so nice to me.
I failed you.
I...
Keep cool.
I know.
I was a poor boy.
If it's not you,
I cannot be who I am today.
I would be nobody.
I was too arrogant and swaggering.
And I made you angry.
I shouldn't have fired your old crew.
I shouldn't have embarrassed you.
Dad.
The person I feel most sorry to
is Fanlv.
I was not a good husband
or a good son-in-law.
That'll do.
I swear that,
from today on,
I will
do the real work in Yutian
and take good care of Fanlv
back at home.
I won't make you worry about us.
Here we are.
Thank you.
Xiaosu.
Wait.
I know what you want to say.
I'll pretend that nothing
has happened on the island.
No.
I just wanna say thank you.
For what?
For getting you a cold?
I've been really happy these days.
Thank you.
Well.
Excuse me.
Bro.
You're really my God.
Get up! Get up!
Bro.
Thank you.
It's him
who cured my heart attack.
He...
He‘s not a doctor.
(We together to keep our health)
Such a great doctor
will come to a hospital like this?
Tell you what?
Over these years,
I had heart attack every night.
I had been to many hospitals
but it didn't work out.
Last week,
I was hospitalized here.
Just next to Mr. Liu.
Guess what?
One word by Mr. Liu
just cured me.
What did he say?
He told me
not to buy the shares of Baogang
but the shares of Tianhua New Energy.
You're fooling us.
This stock
raised limit in less than one week.
Over the past few years,
the stock of poor performance
has doubled the price.
Is it true?
Yes, it's true.
What are you doing?
Having a meeting?
It's hospital.
Go back and take a rest.
Go back.
Thank you, Mr. Liu.
I'll see you another day.
See you. See you.
Fine. Take a good rest.
Good for you.
You're unbelievable! Dude！
You're a real-world Shawshank.
You don't take care of yourself
in the hospital,
but help others make money from stock?
I was just playing around.
Nothing to do anyway.
So boring.
In the detention house,
this is not allowed.
I finally come out
but has to be supervised by the nurses.
You have the heart attack
because of smoking this.
You're not afraid of death?
Will you just let me die?
No.
How about this?
You. Just smell.
Take it after you get well.
I quit. Don't worry.
Do you wanna go back to Yutian or not?
The opportunity that belongs to you
is just like this last cigar.
No.
Come on.
Come with me.
Is it too soon to make the move?
What are you talking about?
Get changed quickly!
Come home with me.
You wanna stay in the hospital
suffering from these young nurses
or you wanna come home with me?
Smoke your Cuba cigar.
Cut the crap.
Wait for me. I pack my bag.
Run!
-Thank you.
-Bye.
Good for you.
You know this place very well.
I've been here.
Don't you ask who received me?
I know.
You said you didn't care about anything.
I know you can't let go of her.
Otherwise, why did you come back
immediately after she went for you.
I told you before that
Du Xiaosu was more determined than you.
You will fall for her.
See?
You're right.
(Lei Yuzheng: What are you doing?
Du Xiaosu: What's the matter?)
Lei Yuzheng,
I'm talking to you!
With your beauty and your career,
you've been pretty busy all day.
Don't keep me at loose.
I'm not here on vacation.
I know what you wanna say.
(Let's have dinner together tonight!)
You just have a good rest.
When you get well,
let's take the long shot.
(Lei Yuzheng:
Let's have dinner together tonight)
I've been really happy these days.
Thank you.
For what?
For getting you a cold?
Look at your face, fair and tender.
What kind of a good place
is this island?
You make me wanna go there.
Nothing special.
The view was very good.
The view or the person?
Who?
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle in pain and delight♪
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle in pain and delight♪
♪Your love weeps for a withered soul♪
♪That teardrop of sadness brings extreme beauty♪
♪Indulged in the black whirlpool of your eyes♪
♪Dreams have never been this quiet♪