♪Following the way she walked through♪
♪He searches for every piece of
memory that he had with her♪
♪An unexpected encounter in the crowds♪
♪Was the start of their destined journey♪
♪No one can tell the end of the story♪
♪Since every heart is overloaded♪
♪The dream about blooming
flowers is illusionary♪
♪Painful yet addictive♪
♪Love is too wild to be reined♪
♪Too deep to be forgot♪
♪The pain will forever
stay with the scar on the chest♪
♪He wants to linger in his dream♪
=Tears In Heaven=
=Episode 30=
Du Xiaosu. Your delivery.
Ok. Thank you.
What a beautiful dress!
It's so nice.
It must cost a lot.
Is it from Lei Yuzheng？
Hurry up! Try it on and show me.
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Come on.
Hurry up! Hurry up! Go.
It is true that
the tailor makes the man.
Don't you think I am too conspicuous?
No. Not at all.
But it's just a dinner with him.
Is this really necessary
to wear like this?
Come on. Xiaosu.
Our Xiaosu is the most beautiful girl.
You're so beautiful.
(Nanpu Bridge)
The dress doesn't fit?
Why not wear the one I gave you?
It fits well.
I'm just not used to it.
Do I look poor
as I dress like this today?
You look nice in any outfits.
That's great.
Besides,
the dinner is hosted for you.
Why do I look so good?
Why should I be so conspicuous?
You're with me.
Tonight,
it'll be difficult for you
to keep a low profile.
Why?
There must be a lot of people.
Is there still time for me
to go back and get changed?
It doesn't matter.
Don't worry.
You are glamorous
in any outfits.
Don't give me such expensive gifts
anymore.
I don't think they're necessary.
Fine. I promise you.
As long as you're happy.
Come on. Let's drink a toast.
All right. Cheers.
It's been a while.
We're all friends here.
Relax.
I'll try my best to stop you
from drinking later.
They'll make fun of you.
Never mind.
Don't take it seriously.
Wait for a moment.
Who is this?
Mr. Lei.
Oh Mr. Lei. Mr. Lei.
Your driving skills are getting worse.
You've been so late.
Come on. Please.
You brat. Look at yourself.
Come on. Buddies.
Tonight I play the host
to welcome my buddy.
First,
celebrate the return of my buddy
to Shanghai.
Second,
I wish you a comeback
and a bright future.
Third,
you've already seen it.
I'll just leave it there.
Come on. Cheers!
Cheers!
Xiaosu.
I think
you have known him.
My best cellmate, Liu Siyang.
Oh dude.
We've met.
Mr. Liu is so impressive.
Miss Du.
I've heard so much about you.
Come on.
Du Xiaosu.
Come over here.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Ye.
Yuzheng. You are not generous.
You shall tell me that
you have a girlfriend.
Last time I just felt
there was something between you two.
I really got it right.
I wonder
what can
make Mr. Lei ask me for a favor?
It was because of Miss Du.
Miss Du.
I've already told you so much.
You have to drink a toast.
Miss Du. She can't drink.
She is allergic to alcohol, right?
Yes.
Who's going to ask for trouble?
Right.
I will drink a toast!
Excuse me?
Miss Du. You can't drink?
I've seen it before.
You can hold your liquor.
What's up, Designer Du?
Are you afraid of
being carried back again by my buddy?
That is out of expectation.
Being carried back?
All right. Cheers!
Cheers!
Yuzheng.
It's really you!
Why is she here?
It must be fate for us.
It's been a while.
Where have you been?
I have been abroad.
How long are you going to stay
this time?
I was planning to leave
the day after tomorrow.
But I've changed my mind when I see you.
Xuyou.
You're too partial.
Come on. I accompanied you every time
you came back.
I've never heard that
you would stay one more day for me.
That's it.
You're too partial!
Shangguan is jealous.
Come on. Drink.
Come here. Let me introduce you.
Xiaosu.
This is my girlfriend, Du Xiaosu.
Xu You.
The famous celebrity Xu You.
Nice to meet you. Miss Du.
Nice to meet you.
I want to talk with you.
Miss Du. Shall we?
Wait for a moment. I'll come back soon.
Why bring me here?
Anything important?
No. It's just
there were too many people there.
It was not convenient to talk.
How are you doing recently?
As you see,
I have a girlfriend now.
Let's have a drink.
Come on. Be happy!
Come on. Cheers!
Come on!
Fine.
Why are you so alert?
Don't worry. I won't pester you.
It's been a while.
I am already not the one I used to be.
Yes.
You're different than before.
You're  more beautiful.
Really?
You're not used to
this kind of occasion, right?
Aren't you the same?
It's different for me.
I've been used to wandering alone.
I might just disappear some day.
You're different.
I'm afraid
you have to get used to it gradually.
Come on. Cheers.
Xu You.
I was too young before.
I didn't know
how to deal with relationship.
Now...
It's not getting any better now.
It has been difficult
for all the girls who are with me.
Difficult. That's accurate.
I'm kidding.
My number remains unchanged.
Call me when you're available.
Let's have a nice chat.
Come on.
Are you making a fool of us?
We're waiting for you.
Come on.
Come on. Let me tell you.
We today... I...and...
Where is Xiaosu?
She went to the bathroom.
Here. Fill the glass for Yuzheng.
What's the matter?
You just had one glass.
Who are you sharing it with?
(Entrepreneur)
(Community Meeting Soon)
The women he is dating with
has to be a celebrity,
like Xuyou, right?
Miss Du.
You're different.
I'm afraid
you have to get used to it gradually.
(Lei Yuzheng)
Why did you leave?
I was a little tired.
So I left first.
Why didn't you let me take you home?
No, thanks. I'm almost home.
Don't worry.
Your current girlfriend
will have conflict with
your ex-girlfriend.
They can't meet each other.
Just go back and pamper her.
No big deal.
Everyone comes for you today.
You can't let everyone down.
By the way,
where is Fanlv?
Why isn't she here?
You have seen her recently, right?
Fanlv.
She is not very well recently.
During the time you're not around,
Lin Xiangyuan and she
were not very well.
She lost her baby,
got hurt,
and lost weight as well.
Fanlv has been listening to you
since she was a kid.
Go to see her when you're available.
Ok.
Lin Xiangyuan.
What did you do?
Do you think I don't know that?
I...
I'm begging you.
Don't force me, okay?
I didn't force you
to come this far.
You have made great efforts.
Everything you've got is in vain.
Because I'm the real master of Yutian.
You're just an employee.
How can you win out?
You think those minority
shareholders are on your side.
Does it work?
As long as
I change the strategy,
they will be afraid of
losing their positions.
Since you have taken first step,
you're doomed
to failure.
(Lei Yuzheng: Meet someone with me
at noon tomorrow.)
(I can't go,
as I have to work in studio.)
(He engages in the building materials,
and it's good for you to meet him.)
(I'm really busy, and I don't like
socializing. Please go by yourself.)
Beauty. Alone?
Let's have a drink.
Let go of me.
Come on. Let's have a drink.
Let's have a drink.
Let go of me.
Beauty. Just one drink.
Everybody is here for fun.
Be relaxed.
Yuzheng.
Why are you here?
Fanlv.
You are so drunk.
Where is Lin Xiangyuan？
He? He's busy with the work all day
and doesn't even care about me.
I have known everything about you.
I'll find a way to help you.
But you have to pull yourself together.
You help me?
How will you help me?
You guys
only care about your own
winning and losing.
Do you care about our feelings?
You have no idea
what kind of life I've been living.
Of course I know.
Fanlv.
Shangguan has told me everything.
I wanna have a talk with Lin Xiangyuan.
About what?
You're trying to persuade him
to be nice to me,
right?
Let me tell you.
He's been nice to me.
It's you.
Lei Yuzheng.
Are you really not going back to Yutian?
Are you really going to
give up Yutian to others?
If Lin Xiangyuan
is really capable enough
to lead Yutian forward,
it will be fine.
I really can't believe
you can say that!
Are you still the Lei Yuzheng
I used to know?
I look down on you.
You're a coward!
Mr. Lei.
What a coincidence!
Fanlv is drunk. Take her home.
I didn't get you.
Fanlv is my wife.
It's my business
whether to take her home or not.
Do I need you to remind me?
As the family of Fanlv,
I hope you can take good care of her.
That's my business
whether I treat her well or not.
You're thinking too much.
It's late.
Take her home.
Slow down.
Fanlv.
Have some millet porridge.
Come on. Let me feed you.
Fanlv. Are you still mad at me?
Have some more.
The millet was sent
at the request of my mom.
She knows I'm usually busy with the work
and always drinking.
So some millet porridge
will be good for health.
What?
You don't know me?
No.
Fanlv.
After the graduation
from the university,
I've been working following your dad.
Then in Shanghai
I finally settled down.
I spent all my money
on an apartment.
After I got the key,
the first thing I did was
going back to my hometown by train
and bringing my mom to Shanghai.
I wanted her to know that
her son already settled down
in the big city.
And I took her
to the most famous places
for local food in Shanghai,
and to the best places for shopping.
Guess what?
My mom ended up in hospital
the next day,
with diarrhea and vomiting.
The doctor examined her several times,
but couldn't find out the reason.
I was also very confused.
Later my mom told me,
it was because she didn't
get acclimatized.
Isn't that ridiculous?
In fact, my mother and I
shared the same feelings.
I've been working so hard.
I've been working so hard
to strive for success.
When I finally settled down,
I realized
I didn't get acclimatized.
I know exactly
on the way to success,
I've hurt a lot of people.
Even my beloved wife
is going to leave me.
Lin Xiangyuan.
What is the real you like?
Fanlv.
I did something wrong before.
I hope you can give me an opportunity.
I only wanna be a good son now,
a good husband, and a good son-in-law.
Lin Xiangyuan.
I can believe what you've just said
for the moment.
It's all from your heart.
But I wanna ask you.
Why do you change all of a sudden?
Before tonight,
you were not like this.
Is it because Lei Yuzheng is back?
Fanlv.
Do I need a reason to be nice to you?
I know.
In this world,
the person you're most scared of is
Lei Yuzheng.
I really can't figure out
what reason
can make you change your mind.
Maybe you're really scared
deep in your heart.
What are you being scared of?
I, Lin Xiangyuan,
have never been scared of anyone.
Probably my change now
is a little difficult for you
to accept.
Don't worry.
I'll gradually prove it to you.
Then tell me.
How come you change all of sudden?
I live this easy life
every day
with you, the capitalist.
My ability
is going to be impaired by you.
What are they?
Any soy milk and fried dough sticks?
Get me some.
I saw Lin Xiangyuan.
Last night.
You should've been right.
Therefore,
you have already taken actions.
Or else? Don't you really think
I'll sit back and do nothing?
Good job! Lei Yuzheng.
I've taken you to meet
so many friends recently.
Don't you really think
I was in the jail for so long
that I am desperate for feast.
You want to know the current situation
as soon as possible.
Most of my friends around me
are closely related to
Yutian.
As long as you get in touch with them,
you'll know everything.
Then what have you learned?
He, Lin Xiangyuan, has been scared.
He wants to find out something from me.
Really?
When a man
has ambitions in his career,
though the approaches he adopted were
disgraceful approaches,
I still regard him
as a strong opponent.
Yes.
Tell me more.
What do you know about Lin Xiangyuan?
Lin Xiangyuan has gained
initial control of the company.
As a smart guy,
he should've known that
this kind of power won't last long.
He must think of another way.
Shangguan told me
Fanlv was going to
divorce Lin Xiangyuan.
If they get divorced,
he'll lose everything.
Last night you met him...
In order to warn him
to behave.
Warn him?
You're already the largest shareholder
of Yutian.
Why don't you just
take over the company?
Why bother yourself warning him?
I'd like to.
But have you ever thought about it?
Uncle Jiang is also
the major shareholder of Yutian.
Why didn't he
take action on Lin Xiangyuan?
That's easy.
Lin Xiangyuan is his son-in-law.
I think
it's not as simple as you think.
Before I get to the bottom of it,
I won't go back.
What do you want to do?
One word.
Wait.
Wait?
I learned one thing in the prison.
In a war,
the most powerful weapon
is not the money or the power
but the time.
So I've been waiting.
Waiting for the other side
to mess things up.
Waiting for them
to expose their fatal flaws.
Anyway,
you always have to make the first move.
What are we going to do?
Take you out
to feast.
I like people like you,
flexible and vigorous .
Get in the car.
Ok.
What's wrong between
you and Lei Yuzheng?
I think
there are really big differences
between us.
That is for sure.
Do you think it's that easy
to marry a rich guy?
Playing mahjong for social contact.
Nail down a deal at dinner.
There are a lot to learn in this.
Probably someone is more suitable
for this kind of life than me.
Come on.
If you really love Lei Yuzheng,
you really have to
be tolerant.
You have to get yourself used to
his social circle.
At the very least,
It's just other's
talk about you behind your back.
They might say that
you are a social climber.
So what?
But you just left like that.
How could he not be embarassed?
I didn't leave because of that.
Forget it.
Silly girl like you
can't see the restrictions
at dinner.
If you really don't like it
and feel a lot of pressure,
I can only support you
to back off as soon as possible.
Qunfei.
Have a seat.
Xiaosu.
Have you met Mr. Lei recently?
How is he?
Xiaosu.
Qunfei is stubborn.
You just cannot figure it out.
Don't blame me for speaking frankly.
We and Lei Yuzheng
are not in the same social status.
No more expectation.
It'll be nice to marry someone
with the same social status.
Dad. Have a seat.
Dad. I've prepared something
to eat.
I don't know
whether you like it.
Take a seat.
Xiangyuan.
I understand how you feel.
The reason why we've ended up
in situations like this,
is the contradiction
among us,
the contradiction among me, you and
Lei's family.
It is my fault.
I want to apologize
to Lei Yuzheng in person  one day.
If the conflict is not solved, it is
harmful for the development of Yutian.
I hope you and me can
apologize to Lei Yuzheng
and ask him
to come back to Yutian
as my assistant.
You can still be the president.
Will you?
Yes, dad.
I'll set a date with him.
Mr. Jiang
asked you to invite Lei Yuzheng
to come back in person?
What are you going to do
if he comes back?
Xie Li.
Do you know what my title is
in the group?
Yes, you're Mr. Lin.
No.
I'm the son-in-law of Jiang Jin.
Jiang Fanlv's husband.
I signed a prenuptial agreement.
If I get divorced
for my personal reasons,
not only can I not get any shares,
but I'll also lose everything in Yutian.
What are you going to do then?
What to do?
I have no idea.
It's all a mirage.
It's all
in vain.
Dude.
What are we doing here?
Fishing.
Fishing?
I've been fishing for a whole morning.
Let alone the fish.
There aren't even aquatic plants.
This is the charm of fishing
in the wild.
If you can't be patient,
you won't catch the big fish.
(Lin Xiangyuan)
Ok. See you later.
What's the matter?
Lin Xiangyuan asked me to have dinner.
Banquet at Hongmen?
Yuzheng.
I've been working with your dad
for my whole life.
I've been competing with him
all my life.
Now I'm old.
Yutian should be handed over
to young people like you.
I was wrong about what I've done before.
You're a generous person.
If you can forgive me,
that would be my great privilege.
I can't promise anything else.
Lin Xiangyuan.
What is the real you like?
I'll manage the company well
and I will be answerable to
you and Mr. Lei.
Dad.
After Mr. Lei passed away,
it shocked me.
I've made a clear statement about
the company's shares
and family property.
Therefore,
I made a will with my lawyer.
You and Fanlv can check it out.
(Bequest Distribution Plan)
After my death,
all my shares in Yutian
will be inherited by Fanlv.
But the house property
belongs to you and Fanlv together.
Dad.
You're in good health.
I have nothing else to worry about.
I just hope you two
can be happy.
Dad.
Fanlv and I are planning
to have a grandson for you.
Aren't we, Fanlv?
Dad. Stop talking about these things.
You have to be good.
Xie Li.
Do you know
what is the most important thing
to do after getting married?
Mr. Lin. You can't drink any more.
Having a baby.
Be honest with me.
How have I treated Jiang Fanlv?
Good.
I'll tell you one more thing.
Jiang Fanlv,
because she just lost the baby,
is still using contraception.
(Levonorgestrel Tablets)
Let me tell you.
Jiang Jin made a will.
His property has nothing to do with me,
unless we have a baby.
Everything is unreal!
Unreal!
It's all in vain.
Mr. Lin. Don't be upset.
Listen to me.
I've been with you for so long.
I can tell
you're quite capable.
Where there is life, there is hope.
Are there still opportunities for me?
Yes.
You're a talent.
No matter where you work,
you will have a successful career.
Ok.
I won't go anywhere.
I will stay in Yutian.
Let's have a drink!
Come on, Mr. Lin.
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle
in pain and delight♪
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle
in pain and delight♪
♪Your love weeps for a withered soul♪
♪That teardrop of sadness
brings extreme beauty♪
♪Indulged in the black
whirlpool of your eyes♪
♪Dreams have never been this quiet♪