[antifan_act, hashtag anti-fan, follow]
[Choi Tae-joon]
[Choi Soo-young]
[Hwang Chan-sung]
[Han Ji-an]
[Kim Min-gue]
[So I Married the Anti-Fan]
[Episode 16]
[I'll Stand by You Until the End of Time]
[Mr. Joon]
[The person you have reached
is not available. Transferring...]
I am
doing very well.
As always.
Why have I been crying so much
since that moment?
Come on, Geun-young.
If you were going to cry like that,
why did you say you can wait well?
How did you...
I was worried that you were gone.
This is embarrassing.
We haven't met in so long,
but you found me crying.
I've really been well.
I didn't cry all the time.
Are you all right?
There are so many things
that aren't all right.
Didn't you miss me?
I missed you so much.
Whenever I missed you,
I looked up at the stars
and saw how they're
still shining brightly.
The star that used to shine so brightly,
I'm sorry fell.
If a star falls,
isn't that a shooting star?
You can see regular stars every day,
but it's awfully hard to see
a shooting star,
so people always wait to see one.
I'm sure people will later
look back and say this.
"Who-joon overcame this tough time"
"and became even more special
and brighter than the days before."
You're a big girl now, Geun-young.
You learned how to comfort people.
You should quit working as a reporter
and become a writer.
I really
missed you a lot.
A lot has happened
while we were away from each other.
Do you remember this?
Wait, your father?
I finally found out what "YAMA" means.
YAMA.
You are my all.
Then did you find your father?
Did you meet him?
He's at a place
where I can never see him again.
Then...
It's all right.
Now I know where he is.
Geun-young.
I know this is tough for you.
But I've been...
going through way too much.
But please give me a little more time.
Then I will
make it up to you
by a hundredfold, even a thousand.
I really want to thank you
and I'm sorry.
I love you so much.
You can leave out, "I'm sorry."
[Woojin Hospital]
Jae-joon, you're up.
The weather is nice.
Do you want to go for a walk
before breakfast? The sun is nice.
Let's go out for a moment
instead of lying here all day.
[Reporters, editors,
proofreaders, recruiters wanted]
[Compose new email]
[I attach my resume below.
I look forward to hearing from you.]
[Email sent]
["Who-joon Gets a Free Ride?"]
["He Gets in for Free Then Walked Off"]
["Who-joon Crushes an Elderly Lady"]
["Is Who-joon's Grandma Case True?"]
["A Shocking Photo Taken by a Fan"]
["Who-joon Flips People Off
on a Motorcycle"]
-Hey, Joon.
-You're here.
Why don't you skip the preview today?
It's not a good idea
to be in front of people now.
It's fine. It's not like avoiding this
will make things better.
Don't worry. Let's go.
[Throw out the deceiver, Who-joon!
Boycott Who-joon!]
-Please step back.
-He's coming in.
[Retire, Who-joon!
How do you call yourself a human?]
-Step back.
-No, one second.
-Who-joon, hey!
-What happened back there?
What happened?
Did you really crush that lady?
[Retire, Who-joon!
Who-joon isn't like that.]
What about your free ride incident?
He jumped over the gate
to catch a pickpocket,
not to ride for free.
We never saw an article on that.
Please elaborate.
If you're curious,
go to Gangnam Police Station.
And Joon stopped that lady
from getting crushed by a bodyguard,
not the other way around.
-Let us through. I'm sorry.
-Wait, Who-joon, one word!
-I'm sorry.
-And the photo?
-The article said... Who-joon!
-Retire, Who-joon!
-Who-joon, just one word!
-Can you explain?
[Who-joon isn't like that.]
-What about that photo?
-Anything you want to say?
-Who-joon! Say something!
-Who-joon!
You got worked up back there,
unlike your usual self.
[Moonlight Elegy]
You don't have to say that.
They won't hear us anyway.
Man, that mustache guy.
He didn't even look into this.
But thanks.
There's Joon.
Are you doing all right out there?
Joon, I still had much to learn from you.
Why did you leave the agency?
-Things happened.
-Take Ji-hyuk and go.
Why? We still have lots to talk about.
Who-joon, let's meet up later, okay?
Okay.
You two should talk.
[Moonlight Elegy]
I'm glad Ji-hyuk is with you.
Why? Are you sickened by me
after my little attack?
A big star like you deserves
a farewell ceremony of that scale.
I'm not complaining about anything.
I knew you were a persistent kid,
but I didn't know
you'd struggle this much.
I'm all fine,
so please don't end up like us
with Ji-hyuk.
That rude jerk.
[What happened back there?]
["The public still cold,
how will The Boy Who Cried Wolf end?"]
[Did you really crush that lady?]
[What about your free ride incident?]
[He jumped over the gate
to catch a pickpocket,]
[not to ride for free.]
[We never saw an article on that.
Please elaborate.]
[If you're curious,
go to Gangnam Station.]
He's...
She's a huge fan of yours.
We went to your concerts together,
then I ended up becoming a fan too.
["The public still cold,
how will The Boy Who Cried Wolf end?"]
Yes, I understand. Yes.
As soon as the premiere was postponed,
the lawsuit was filed
over your ad contract.
They're very quick.
Let's pay for the damage.
If we do,
we'll end up paying them
over every single thing possible.
I've been looking for a good lawyer,
so don't worry about it.
And Joon, I'm sure there's a crowd
in front of the hospital too.
Let's stay home tonight.
[I'll remember the day we first met.
The streets, the moment.]
Ms. Lee.
You've made a name for yourself
in this industry.
I guess I'm rather well-known.
But I'm not looking for some fame.
I want to be a reporter
who's known for her articles.
Do you think
your relationship with Who-joon is
an advantage or a disadvantage
as you do this work?
Sorry?
If it becomes a disadvantage,
it's something I'll have to live with.
However,
it can't be an advantage.
I'm not going to use my acquaintance
in favor of my career as a reporter.
I'd also like to ask you
to evaluate me
solely on my articles and experiences.
See? I told you we should've waited.
Ji-hyang, this is
the most important to me.
You can let me off.
-Who-joon!
-Anything to say?
-Why are you here?
-Do you have any words?
-Please say something.
-What about your recent controversies?
-We need a word from you!
-Can you tell us what happened?
-Explain yourself.
-Say something, Who-joon.
[Woojin Hospital]
-You need to speak up!
-Say something!
Just one word!
I'm here.
Have you eaten?
I had such a long day.
You haven't had water, right?
We should have your dressing changed.
I'll talk to the nurse.
Hello.
Have you been well?
I saw that you're in a lawsuit.
You should've called me.
It's all right. I can take care of this.
Your father and I were close.
I couldn't stay out of your business.
[You can come by whenever you want.]
Yes, thank you.
[Cho-Yoon Law Firm]
[CEO Cho Hae-yoon]
We don't know much about lawsuits.
This hasn't happened before.
This is a breach of your contract,
so you'll have to pay the compensation.
I'll reduce the amount as much as I can.
Instead of reducing the amount,
I want to pay for the damage
to everyone who suffered from my scandal.
He's really inflexible, isn't he?
All right. I'll work in that light.
Thank you.
I'm not sure how you'll take this,
but you have a way of doing things
just like your father.
[Shooting Star Entertainment Company]
Mr. Bae, your investors want to retrieve
the investments they made
for the brand launch.
-All of a sudden?
-They invested because of Who-joon,
so this isn't
what they wanted to invest in.
At this rate,
bankruptcy is inevitable, Mr. Bae.
You may go.
Yes, sir.
[I'll remember the day we first met.
The streets, the moment.]
Congrats on getting a job.
You don't have to throw me a party.
Anyway, are you really closed
because of me?
My gosh, you're so gullible.
I'm not the owner.
We're closed today.
Whoa, then did you open the door
only because of me?
Only because you wouldn't show up.
Figures. Your boyfriend is in trouble.
Wait, you knew?
Know what?
I know you.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you first.
Don't be sorry.
He's not just any normal guy.
So if it's getting too hard,
it's not too late to stop.
I mean, he's not
the only guy in this world.
Mi-jung, you're still not over him?
Su-hwan is here too.
Like you said, he's not
the only guy in this world.
Forget your old romance, and...
Be quiet. Let's drink.
The press conference
seemed to hit him very hard.
Is Who-joon all right?
And yes, it turns out he's a year older.
He lied about his age.
I guess so.
But things may get better
once your piece gets out.
Her piece?
Geun-young wrote an awesome article
to defend Who-joon like a saint.
That's why love...
Love for humanity is important.
Of course, love for humanity is important.
She's a faithful friend.
Hey.
I thought you just said love...
Wait, are Geun-young and Who-joon...
Really?
He's now really like a brother.
Su-hwan, I'm sorry for not telling you.
But do you really think
my piece will be helpful?
[Police Station]
[If you fail to make a payment,]
[you'll be detained.]
[Do you understand?]
Jae-joon.
These are your stuff.
And
I need to go somewhere for a while.
I am
trying to get back on track.
When I return,
I'm sure you'd be fully healed.
Let's grab a glass of soju on that day.
It'll be fine. Okay?
-Hello?
[-Hey.]
I settled everything with the accusers.
Thank you. Thank you for your hard work.
So will you really sell your house too?
Yes.
I want to start over with a clean slate.
[Oh, and...]
[Shooting Star Entertainment Company]
[was your former agency Shooting Star?]
[They're about to be sold off.]
[I was wondering if you had
any unfinished businesses with them.]
[Meat Mandu: 5 for 5,000 won]
[King Steamed Buns]
My gosh, 5,000 won?
-Hey, Mr. Bae.
-Did the practice go well?
Yes.
I got some fried chicken.
Take it back to the practice room.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
-Hey.
[-Dad!]
[-What about chicken?
-Dad!]
Hey, I forgot. I'm so sorry.
[-I want chicken.]
-I'm sorry.
[-Did he get us some?
-Come home already.]
-You should take it.
-It's fine.
I'm on my way right now.
Joon.
This is our office now.
The entire first floor?
The entire building.
What?
-Come on, stop lying.
-I'm serious.
Really?
That's amazing.
This isn't mine. It's ours.
We did this together!
This is so big.
Then make me an office down here.
Of course, I will.
[There's an elevator too.]
[Shooting Star Entertainment Company]
♫ In that place with no stars,
all the way in the sky ♫
♫ I always sang this song alone ♫
♫ Thinking someone might
listen to me sing one day ♫
♫ And I sang all night long, listen ♫
♫ Once I wake up,
under the spotlight, right there ♫
♫ That's where I'll stand ♫
I threw away so much stuff
to stand here on this day.
[Shooting Star Entertainment Company]
I can't believe
I have to leave this behind.
-What now?
[-Mr. Bae.]
[All of your debt has been paid in full.]
What?
Geun-young.
I need to go somewhere for a while.
[I wanted to see you before I left,]
but I couldn't have left if I saw you.
[I'll return]
as a confident man
before you and everyone else.
I won't let you wait too long,
and I'll always be in touch.
[Okay?]
I'll be fine.
Have a safe trip.
Okay.
Why did you pay it back?
It wasn't a small amount.
You said
that agency is ours, not yours.
All my life's memories are there.
I needed to protect it.
So brace yourself
and get back on your feet.
I'll pay you back.
I didn't say
you don't have to pay it back.
You have to pay me back.
[Welcome]
[Rest in peace, Choi Seong-wook]
[I think]
[I finally understand.]
[It's about time]
[I revisited where I came from]
[to return confidently]
[before the world]
[and before the ones I love.]
[I didn't ask where he'll be going.]
[But I knew.]
[And Who-joon left just like that.]
Geun-young, the chief is looking for you.
Okay.
[Woojin Hospital]
Jae-joon.
How do you feel?
You're here.
In-hyung.
It seems like
he still can't think of anything
he wants to say.
He's suffering from loss of speech.
I thought I'd leave this world,
leaving him in regret.
But I'm here in regret,
while he lives
as if he's away from this world.
You had a tough time because of Jae-joon.
Are you doing all right now?
I wanted this to happen.
So I don't know why I pity him.
I wanted to be an entertainer.
Someone who's loved by everyone.
Come to think about it now,
I don't know how to receive love
or give it to someone.
I just dreamed of having people love me.
I don't know about the world,
but the people in your life who know you
really loved and adored you,
both Jae-joon and Who-joon.
But I was always anxious.
I think I was comforted
by how Joon pitied me
instead of abandoning me forever.
And although it's belated,
it's a relief to see him in his place.
Do you no longer feel anxious?
Well.
I think it's a relief
that I can stay by his side
and help him.
If I left,
he really would've been alone.
I know what it feels like
to be left alone in this world,
so I couldn't leave him.
Do you know how glad I am
to see you like this, Geun-young?
Me too.
[Her article is shaking people.
What's Who-joon's true nature?]
Just as Who-joon said
during the press conference,
[The anti-fan writes on the pride
and prejudice about Who-joon's duplicity.]
the fact that
he had been lying is irrefutable.
Geun-young, that's more than enough.
Really?
Please write up a good article, Mr. Choi.
Geun-young, I'm sure many people are
dying to interview you right now.
Thank you very much for choosing me.
You're Who-joon's reporter.
We're trying to undo the misunderstanding.
I thought you had less than fond memories
about me, but I guess not.
Well, this means you agree
I'm a nice reporter who works with him.
You'd be much better
if you didn't talk that way.
Sorry? Come again?
Mr. Choi, there is one more person
that could be helpful.
The backstories on the photos
of Who-joon out in the public
must be far from the truth.
Who-joon isn't like that.
I kidnapped him,
but he helped me propose to my girlfriend,
then congratulated us as well.
Beer is the best way to end your day.
Ms. No, what will you do now?
What do you think?
Work on shows that give me an offer.
We were finally reunited after ten years.
Where do you think you're going?
That's the thing about this industry.
Didn't you know?
I got you on the palm of my hand anyway.
Your palm is way too tiny.
Hey.
What is it?
I have this awesome show proposal.
Would you join me?
So that's what he wanted to say.
Yes, sure, whatever.
You're a hard-working type
unlike how you look.
Since when did you work so hard?
Let me see it.
Hey, you have to read this
with an open heart.
Read it over slowly and thoroughly.
-If it's awful, I'm out.
-It's not awful.
Again? "That's Why I Got Married"?
Yes.
["That's Why I Got Married"]
[Table of Contents]
[Mr. Han and Ms. No's
reality marriage show!]
[A not-so-young couple wants to live
together until death does them apart!]
[Starring: Han Jae-won, No Do-yoon]
[Thank you very, very much for reading.
I love you, Ms. No.]
So?
Don't you think it'll go well?
You have a good sixth sense.
Do-yoon.
Will you do this show with me
forever?
My gosh, you're so tacky!
So tacky!
-Hey, you just smiled.
-Come on.
-That means you're in.
-Whatever!
Yes!
[Editor-in-Chief's Office]
[To Choi Hee-gun,
Title: "Manual for Who-joon"]
[To Choi Hee-gun]
["Manual for Who-joon"]
[Email sent.]
[Shin-hyuk]
Yes.
You aren't the only man in this world.
This is so annoying.
We're closed today.
Honey, I looked back on everything.
What did you look back on?
Moving out without a word?
Then texting me afterward?
You have way too many things
to look back on.
Forget it. You need to go.
Let me go.
I wanted to come back to you
as a big success. I really did.
But I couldn't go on without you.
If you tell me to start studying
for the bar exam again,
I will.
Really?
I mean, I could see
how Who-joon could use
a good lawyer like me.
-Stop it. Stop that.
-That hurts. Ouch. Okay.
-Stop it.
-Okay, yes. I get it.
-Okay!
-Cut that off.
[News]
I enjoyed your article.
"Manual for Who-joon."
Yes, right.
I think you worked harder on that
than our articles.
That's not true.
Geun-young,
instead of working as a reporter,
why don't you try becoming a writer?
You should quit working as a reporter
and become a writer.
[3 months later]
[Grand Opening, M. Stina]
It's not much, but eat up.
[Seniors at "Wonder Woman". Be rich!]
-Sure.
-Thanks.
[Your ex-girlfriend Yoon-a.
I shouldn't have left you.]
Su-hwan!
Hey, you're here.
-Your studio looks great.
-It must've cost a lot.
This is why people say
you need to have a skill set.
Anyway, congrats.
You always wanted a studio of your own.
I'm glad you were laid off.
You kept dating one woman and the next,
then ended up becoming
a wedding photographer.
A man who has been in love knows
exactly how people feel
when they're in love.
It means he dated all those women
to help him get to this place.
Watch out. You might end up taking
your girlfriend's wedding photos.
So when will you two get married?
Oh, I'm sorry, Mi-jung.
You don't have to feel sorry.
Hey.
-Wait.
-Have you been well?
Mi-jung couldn't tell you
because you had just been fired,
and she was a little embarrassed.
Sorry.
Then you two are back together?
Are you studying for the bar exam again?
Goodness, what bar exam?
Shin-hyuk is the Who-joon
in the field of streamers now. I'm
going to join him too.
This is a gift for you.
Should I put it over there?
-Yes, okay.
-Okay.
We'll take a tour around.
What's going on?
She acted as if she'd kill him
if he comes back.
She'd be so wasted when she called us out,
but now this. Goodness.
So what about you two?
What are you talking about?
Looking great!
-Congrats!
-You two look wonderful!
Is Ji-hyang not here yet?
-No, I don't think so.
-I see.
And now, we'll have someone
come out and sing
for this beautiful newlywed couple.
We prepared a very special event
just for the bride.
Do you want to find out?
A big hand, please!
Hey, this is Joon's song.
♫ If I just stared at you,
only to turn around in regret ♫
♫ Then what would have happened? ♫
♫ Would I be in a different world ♫
♫ With someone else who isn't you? ♫
♫ I can't even imagine ♫
♫ Having someone else by my side ♫
♫ When it rains, I'll be your umbrella ♫
♫ When the sun burns, I'll be your shade ♫
♫ You and I walk side by side ♫
♫ Things can't get any better than this ♫
♫ The things I couldn't say to you ♫
Now, look at them
as if you're all jealous.
-Okay.
-Kiss, kiss.
Who's going to take the bouquet?
Right.
Geun-young.
Me?
No, I'm not taking it.
-Come on, go.
-Take it!
Did I keep you waiting?
How did you make it here?
Surprise!
-It's Who-joon.
-My gosh!
-No way.
-My gosh.
-This is huge.
-He's here.
My gosh.
I ended up taking the bouquet.
Who-joon!
You're so handsome!
My gosh.
[The next song is a song
that became a huge hit on the internet.]
[The song drew attention]
[as the first song produced
by the world-renowned star, Who-joon.]
[Let's take a listen.]
-Fish cake?
-Thank you, thank you.
Fish cake?
You can have it.
No, it's yours.
I like the soup better.
It's because you don't know
how you're supposed to drink soju.
Then you'll have to teach me.
Hey, really?
[Open this door]
What's going on?
The three of you are here,
but you only ordered two servings.
-Mr. Bae!
-My gosh!
I got some more for you.
Joon.
Jae-joon.
This...
This is...
produced by Joon.
What a relief.
Thank you, Jae-joon.
[Who-joon, look at me.
Let's be together for a long time.]
[Joon]
Please look over this way.
Over here, please.
-Over here.
-Finger hearts, please.
-Thank you!
-Look over here!
-I have no makeup on.
-And you look even better.
-I was lying.
-What?
Where are we going?
Where should we go?
Or should we stay home?
No, my house is a mess.
Then Han River?
Sounds great.
Your hands are cold.
Hello?
You didn't even call on the day
your boyfriend goes on a business trip.
[I'm sorry.
I didn't know it was already time.]
[-Are you at the airport?]
-Hey, Ms. Reporter.
No, Ms. Writer.
You're awfully indifferent about Who-joon
just because you aren't a reporter now.
You got me.
You're coming back tomorrow, right?
You know it's my birthday tomorrow, right?
[The passcode to the penthouse was 0227.]
[How could I forget?]
I don't want to spend
another lonely birthday like last year.
[Everything is different this year.]
[Have a safe trip.]
-Hello?
[-Ms. Lee, I'm so sorry.]
[This month's piece
overlaps with the one from last month.]
[I'm sorry I couldn't check
ahead of time.]
[Could you send us another one today?]
[Well, right now?]
[My flight is delayed.]
[Mr. Joon]
[I can't be there today.
What do I do now?]
It's for the better.
Hello?
I just sent you the final draft.
[I also wanted to discuss
next year's projects with you.]
[-Are you free today?]
-Today?
[I'm sorry. We wanted to get started
on this project right away.]
I see. Okay, I can make it.
Where should we meet?
["Who-joon and In-hyung's Duet
Regains Popularity"]
["Rediscovery of Oh In-hyung,
the Lady of the Duet"]
Hello?
[-Is this Ms. Oh In-hyung?]
-Yes.
[I'm calling with Godin Records.]
[We want to make an album with you.]
Thank you for your offer,
but I don't want to sing yet.
But thank you very much for calling.
Goodbye.
Is that okay?
You always wanted to sing.
I need you
to write my songs.
Yes, I just arrived here. Where are you?
Oh, okay.
Could you take a picture for us?
Sure.
-Thank you.
-Everyone, come on in.
I'll take the photo now.
One, two, three.
[Marry me, please.]
Please take the photo.
One, two, three.
What's going on?
So where's my answer?
[Marry me, please.]
Are you crazy? There's a huge crowd here.
I'm serious right now.
"YAMA" doesn't mean "punk",
but "you are my all."
You know that, right?
[YAMA]
This isn't another prank cam, is it?
Do you want me to show you?
[So I Married the Anti-Fan]
[Cue!]
Let's start here.
What's this?
From the top.
Cut.
Ji-hyang.
One, two, three.
[Marry me, please.]
What's going on?
[We thank everyone for their work
and for all your passion!]
[So I Married the Anti-Fan]