[English subtitles are available]
[Jun?]
[Did he say he'd let you have his slot?]
[He never said anything]
[and didn't come by the office.]
Darn you, Yeo Jun.
Yeo Jun!
I treated you like my senior
because I pitied you,
but you disgust me.
That's better.
It was hard seeing you act so pretentious.
Is that so?
I put on an act knowing you'd like it.
So-bin?
Maybe... I'll catch you some other time.
No, don't go.
Are you here to see me?
Yes, I am!
To pick a fight?
Or maybe you just missed me.
Yeo Jun, do I seem like a pushover to you?
Yes.
Even though I do,
you should still keep your promise.
Don't mess with people.
Especially those desperate--
I never messed with you.
I checked at the office.
You should've just said
you didn't want to give up the position.
As if that's too hard to say.
It is for me.
I don't want you to hate me.
But I only forgot about our agreement.
I got sidetracked on my way to the office.
Don't worry though. I'll keep my word.
-When?
-When I have the time.
And when exactly would that be?
I'm wired with a rebellious tendency.
I tend to act out when people annoy me.
So what are you saying?
That you should stop worrying
and be patient.
So that I'll be happy to help you out.
Be patient until then.
-You're such a--
-A jerk, right?
Yes, you're an obnoxious pig.
I see her in you.
It's raining.
Where are you headed?
To my dorm room.
Do you have an umbrella?
-No.
-I do, so let me walk you.
No, I'm good.
I need to stop by the office too.
Are you sure you're okay
with giving up this position?
Yes, I already agreed.
Nicely done, So-bin.
How did you persuade him?
I didn't--
I'll have other opportunities,
so of course, I should pull out.
My gosh, Jun.
How can you be this handsome
and super generous?
Can you put in a good word
to Professor Song for me?
Don't worry.
I won't go back on my promise
after what you did.
Also, your switch of class was authorized.
But brace yourselves.
Professor Park makes you work hard.
Do you take his class too?
You too?
Why though when you're a freshman?
I'm ambitious, you see.
This is great though.
I'll now see you every week.
Your shoulder's getting wet.
Get inside the umbrella more.
It's like a scene from a movie.
A movie?
Yes, "Bungee Jumping of Their Own".
There's an umbrella scene just like this.
In addition to that,
we both actually went bungee jumping.
You're back early.
Hold on. Didn't you have an umbrella?
You should've called me.
It's just a drizzle.
Have you eaten?
[It'll be 10,000 won for the wash,
40,000 for my time spent,]
and 50,000 for new shoes.
Here you go.
I guess you haven't.
Let me cook some ramyeon.
Koo-hyun, why don't we eat
something nice today?
Really? Is it a special occasion?
-Order what you want.
-Sweet!
Remember to chew, will you?
Is it a special occasion?
Is someone adopting me?
As if anyone would.
Better me than you.
Koo-hyun.
The deeper tone's worrying me.
-I'm sorry.
-About what?
Darn it.
You're wearing my underwear, aren't you?
-Just eat up.
-I'm right. Get over here.
-Is it my favorite?
-Stop it.
Give it back then!
Give it back.
-Soo-hyun, come on.
-Just eat.
-I know it's my favorite.
-Stop that.
I knew you had a lot of pride,
but you're actually pretty insecure.
[You're so crooked, you won't even accept
other people's acts of kindness.]
How dare you judge me?
You don't know anything about me.
What gives you the right?
I treated you like my senior
because I pitied you,
but you disgust me.
-Cheers!
Don't drink too much, guys.
Let's drink.
Unbelievable.
Wait. We're out of booze, right?
Can we have two more bottles of soju?
Stop that.
[Are you anxious?]
You need everyone to like you,
but I get on your nerves.
[The way you act like you know me
is revolting.]
That's better.
It was hard seeing you act so pretentious.
Once more. Let's raise our glasses.
-Come on.
-All right.
Cheers!
-Cheers, everyone.
-Cheers.
-Here you go.
-Stop that.
Is it a death wish you have?
-Are we out of soju?
-Stop it.
-That's enough.
-Two more bottles of soju, please.
[Alarm]
It's... It's a dead person.
We're doomed.
What do you mean?
It's our roommate.
I see she's back in a dorm again.
Young-ran.
Young-ran,
the floor's too cold to sleep on.
-Young-ran.
-I think she's dead.
Wang Young-ran,
how about a third round of drinks?
Okay, let's go!
When did you get in?
Look who it is.
It's little Ms. Kim So-bin.
Long time no see.
Be my pillow for a second.
Darn it. I have a weirdo for a roommate.
Hey, Anne.
Anne of Green Gables!
Me?
My leg.
-Cramps.
-Come over here and massage her leg.
Right there.
Higher.
Yes, right there. Harder!
Keep going!
You're doing well.
You leaving already?
-But you worked all night.
-I can sleep on the bus.
[Criminal Law Case Studies]
What's this?
-Tell me.
-It's none of your business.
Unbelievable.
We'll talk about this later.
Mom already knows.
She approved
and said I should talk to you.
I didn't
because I knew you'd be against it.
What about college?
I don't go to a fancy one like you
and can't get scholarships.
Graduating a dingy school
with mediocre grades
won't help me find a job.
The police academy is no joke.
You'll also need money for classes.
So just finish college and--
Say what you want,
but I've made up my mind.
I'm moving into a gosiwon next month.
Koo-hyun!
[This stop is
Myungil University Front Gate.]
[Myungil University Front Gate.]
[Top Thesis Award]
[Top Research Professor Award]
[Department of Business Administration
Professor Song Soo-kyung]
Kim So-bin, a junior.
Yes,
Are you aware that I had my eyes
set on another student?
Yes.
Have you ever took any one of my classes?
Yes, from introductory classes
to your advanced ones.
But I don't recognize you.
I should since you're a junior.
I'm really not one to stand out.
And only a mediocre GPA.
I'm sorry.
An apology won't cut it for this gig.
The research you'll be doing
is for an important presentation.
If it weren't for Ms. Seol,
I wouldn't have considered you.
I'll do my best.
Rather than your best,
I want the best work.
Yes, professor.
[It's not fun for either of us now,
so let's end it.]
This is me taking initiative.
I know you want to break up too.
As if you actually know what I want.
And that's exactly our problem.
It's just impossible to read you.
[Just your looks isn't enough.]
[Do you know the feeling]
[of trying to fill a tub
that has a hole in it?]
Anne, come and sit with us.
Have you lost your mind?
Alcohol is prohibited.
We could get kicked out for this.
I know it's against the rules,
but Young-ran wanted to bond.
Don't be a party pooper and sit.
-I don't drink alcohol.
-Then enjoy the food.
-I'm not in the mood.
-Then get in the mood.
♫ Anne of Green Gables,
what a cute girl she is ♫
-♫ Anne of Green Gables ♫
-Stop it.
♫ Our friend ♫
-Jun.
-Yeo Jun, open up!
Gosh, you guys must be drunk.
What have you been up to?
Don't tell me you're with a girl.
Anyway, we missed the last subway,
so let us crash for the night.
Well, I didn't get around
to cleaning it up.
As if we'd care.
Chun-guk, bring on round five!
Round five. Round five.
Check out this place.
Are you a neat freak?
It's spotless.
Hey, look. It's beer!
Chun-guk, get us some snacks.
It looks like you already had a lot,
so why don't you turn in?
And waste these hours of our youth?
We should keep partying.
Of course. Round five, here we come.
[The world doesn't want to see
what youth really looks like.]
[Nam Soo-hyun]
[It’s why we can only imitate
what grown-ups do]
[by following the rules
to a certain point]
[and not wasting our time.]
[We put on a mask
upon the mask we're already wearing]
[and try ever so hard
to keep our true self hidden.]
[Spring has always been just a rumor]
[since we're constantly stuck in winter.]
That photo you uploaded was killer.
-Really? Thanks.
-Can you follow my account?
-Me too.
-Of course.
Who did you hang out with yesterday?
-So-bin!
-My gosh.
Oh, it's you.
Why do you seem sullen today?
Did you meet with Professor Song?
Yes, I did.
You're the one
she obviously wanted though,
so I don't know
if I can live up to her expectation
especially now that
you let me have your spot.
It wasn't me she wanted.
What?
You'll do a good job, so don't worry.
-Thanks for that.
-Only in words?
We're not done becoming friends.
Aren't we quite close though?
-It is in my books.
-But you know nothing about me.
Well, you...
My gosh!
No way!
You're popular.
You have me. Just trust me.
I don't think
I ever promised you my spot
if you bungee jump.
You're hard to figure out.
How so?
You sometimes seem
like a different person.
I mean...
You're a man of many charms, that's all.
-You too.
-What?
No, there's only one side to me.
Wait, just the one?
What about you is so captivating then?
What?
Oh, it's nothing.
I didn't mean it that way.
-Tell me.
-What?
-Forget it.
-What is it?
-I told you it's nothing.
-Please tell me.
Jun, over here!
Hi.
Did you text him to get us coffee?
No, it wasn't me. Wasn't it you?
He just knows how to please, doesn't he?
Wait. Why is he sitting there?
Did Nam Soo-hyun send him
on a coffee run too?
Hey, Jun. Jun!
We saved you a seat.
Sorry about that,
but I forgot my contacts today.
It's to apologize for before.
I was out of line.
Enjoy the coffee and forget it happened.
Anyway, that's all for today's class.
That reminds me.
I forgot to mention this
during the last class,
but I'm assigning you team projects
for your mid-term evaluation.
Seriously?
Quiet!
I'll let you choose your team though
and the project can be about anything.
The team leader will inform me
of the topic you choose next week,
and we'll draw names
to determine the order of presentation.
-But Professor...
-Professor Park.
What about those
with no friends in this class?
Sometimes, life boils down
to the connections you have.
The experience
of forcing yourself to team up
with other students
who share the same goal
will become an asset.
But Professor, I'm a freshman.
-Isn't this class for juniors?
-It is.
Which is why I should be teamed up
with someone who gets good grades.
He must be referring to you, Soo-hyun.
He's your responsibility now.
-Professor, that's--
-Professor!
I'll lead Jun to a good grade.
You, Han Jung-ho?
I'm old enough to know what I'm doing.
Soo-hyun, you now have
another member on your team.
Who else? Raise your hand
if you need help getting into a group.
Right here and right now,
I'll play matchmaker for you.
You can bond over lunch...
Hey, Nam Soo-hyun.
What was with that scowl?
We may both be juniors,
but I'm a year older than you.
So what was with that scowl?
Not again. Why you--
Jung-ho, please.
We're on the same team now.
How can I possibly work with that jerk?
You have me, remember?
Right. Just take your cues
from me and Chun-guk,
and run errands.
Hye-ji, just follow my lead.
Sure thing.
Does that make me the only girl?
We're short a person.
And with Jun being a freshman...
Just a second.
-Me?
-Are you already in a team?
-Not yet.
-How about you join ours?
Well...
I need someone I can trust on the team.
Are you saying you can't trust us?
Someone who works hard.
That jerk...
I wouldn't mind having you on our team.
If this is about the team project
we did last semester, I'm good.
Did something happen between those two?
I don't get swayed by frivolous things.
I checked the file you sent
and liked your work
which is why I'm asking.
Please think about it.
What's there to think about? Just join us.
-What?
-Let's go.
Our first meeting should be held
somewhere fancy.
Let's go.
Off you go.
Really?
Hey, stop that.
-Unbelievable.
-It wasn't me though.
Come on, guys.
Are you deliberately falling behind
or do you just walk slowly?
You startled me.
I always seem to do that.
I'll notify you in advance
before approaching you.
Your number.
We'll exchange numbers anyway
since we're a team now.
Don't you think it'll be fun?
We'll see.
Think of it like bungee jumping.
It'll be thrilling
since you'll be working with me.
So what should our presentation be on?
How about success stories in marketing?
No, it's a topic easy to do research on,
so another team could beat us to it.
Can't we say that we called dibs?
No.
A common topic won't make us stand out.
We won't get good grades
even with a good presentation.
What's your idea then?
An analysis on marketing strategies
that failed.
It sounds fresh.
I don't know any better,
but it'll make us stand out.
-Don't you agree?
-What?
Is it a good one?
I don't know. You guys can decide.
It doesn't sound too bad.
Isn't it a cheap trick to go that route
just because success stories seem to easy?
The conclusion will be the same.
Something like
"Failure is the mother of success."
So-bin, what do you think?
Well...
It sounds like fun.
It's not meant to be fun.
But...
An analysis of failed marketing strategies
is a topic that covers
a wide range of views.
So just like Jung-ho said,
it could seem like
we're just twisting the words.
It’s why I think
focusing on a top-tier product
falling down the ladder
due to failure in marketing
and examples of marketing strategies
that couldn’t adjust to
the needs of consumers could be better.
Unbelievable. So-bin, I'm impressed.
I was just voicing my opinion.
Do we have our topic then?
I guess we do,
so now we should decide on team leader.
You're the oldest here, so of course
it should be you.
What? How does that make sense?
Apart from Jun, we're all juniors here,
so why does age matter?
Are you volunteering?
No, I have other team projects to manage.
What about Soo-hyun?
He seems to have the professor's trust.
Let's make this simple
and put it to a vote.
It'll be between Jung-ho and Soo-hyun.
What do you say?
Sorry? Well, I'm fine with
either of you being--
You seemed confident when
suggesting the topic,
so why not be the team leader?
What?
I vote yes.
How can she when she's mostly invisible?
I saw at the orientation
that she was hard-working
and had a good sense of responsibility.
Someone like that should be team leader.
He's right.
So-bin has that quality to her.
-I vote for her too.
-Hold on a second.
Same here.
Majority rules then.
In the next class, the team leader
will inform the professor
of our team and topic.
Are you leaving already?
The pretentious jerk.
It's impossible to like him.
Did you notice he didn't order anything?
Life would be a bore
without odd people like him.
Odd?
He's not odd.
He's just the ultimate psycho.
Do you know what happened
during my freshman year?
When I first met him, I mean.
Soo-hyun!
Can you treat us to a meal?
I'm Park Hye-ji,
a freshman in the department.
And I'm Lee Ki-sun.
So?
Sorry?
Why must I buy meals to strangers
who I haven't met before?
We're sorry.
Talk about a new kind of jerk.
What did I tell you?
He may be good looking,
but he's an annoying jerk.
Darn it.
So you're freshmen.
That's right.
How well did you do
on the language section of your CSAT?
I got a level two.
You got the subject wrong.
Sorry?
The one begging for a free meal
is the annoying kind.
-I see.
-Be a better judge of character
and figure out
who'd actually treat you to meals.
That would've been a cool sight to watch.
You can clearly imagine how Soo-hyun was.
He's not wrong though.
Seniors shouldn't have
to blindly treat their juniors.
Wait. Did you just take his side?
Of course not.
I'm just saying he has a point.
What about a senior student
stealing a freshman's job?
Are you going to keep making me
feel guilty over what's been settled?
Yes.
I must really be an easy target to you.
That's what I like about you.
Yeo Jun, I don't appreciate it all.
I can be scary when angry, you know.
Boy, I'm trembling.
Anyway, I'll see you, Scary One.
I have a call to make.
Right. Sure thing.
Hello?
It's on Friday night.
Your aunt and uncle will be there too.
Right. It's been a while
since I saw you and Father.
Do you actually miss us?
[Of course. I miss home-cooked meals too.]
Don't lie just because I can't see you.
I can hear it in your voice.
[I'm not fond of having you here either.]
[It's not like
you're someone to be proud of.]
[Since your brother's busy,
you'll have to do instead.]
What can I do
when I have a limited number of sons?
[Be here even if you don't want to be.]
Right. I'll see you then.
Don't be your usual self
and be here on time.
-Sure.
-That reminds me.
Is your hair still a mess?
[I don't want to burn my eyes out,
so clean yourself up.]
[Your brother
never had his hair like that.]
Yes, Mother. I'll do just that.
Don't you worry.
[I'm not fond of having you here either.]
[It's not like
you're someone to be proud of.]
[Since your brother's busy,
you'll have to do instead.]
[Is your hair still a mess?]
[I don't want to burn my eyes out,
so clean yourself up.]
[Your brother
never had his hair like that.]
My gosh.
Can you please get up?
[Nam Soo-hyun]
Will you drink it?
I'll take these too.
Your total is 4,400 won.
Do you need a bag?
No.
It's for you.
Please forget what you saw.
What?
It's nothing.
You work so hard. Just drink it.
-Take them.
-You're welcome.
You're here.
Got eyes in the back of your head?
I have a sharp sense of smell.
Your perfume.
Did you have a beer?
No, maybe you did.
Mi-ju, are you all right?
Yes, he's not the only guy in the world.
Oh, right. There's only one guy for you.
Did you have dinner?
Dinner?
No, I don't think so.
Do you want cup noodles?
One, two, three, four. Hold your breath!
That's it.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Exhale!
Good. One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight!
Great job. Good boy.
Who are you?
Hey, friend. Doesn't it help you
clear your mind for a moment?
-Not sure.
-Come on. I've tested it on my friend.
And? Did it work?
No, it didn't work on her.
This isn't enough for her
because she thinks way too much.
She needs me to help her
declutter her mind
by chatting her up nonstop.
You're a good friend.
What? What's this?
Are you jealous?
I can tell from that look in your eyes.
Come on. You're the one
who has the most friends!
Do you know me?
No, but I've heard a lot about you.
Yeo Jun, the most popular guy
at Myungil University!
But I don't have any good friends.
Honey, what are you doing?
Well, let's enjoy this sweet night air
together again next time.
[Rent, Books, Academy]
[Living Expenses, Phone and Internet]
[Don't lie just because I can't see you.]
[I can hear it in your voice.]
-You're already here.
-I just got here.
Hi, Soo-hyun.
Don't do things like this by yourself.
This isn't a team leader's job.
Come on. All you need to say is,
"Thank you."
You're so cranky.
He's right though.
Get me to do it since I'm the youngest.
Anyone who's here first can do it.
Did you call everyone else on the team?
Yes, they all said
they'll be here on time.
Actually, Hye-ji can't come.
She's coming down with a cold.
I guess it'll be just the five of us.
This is our first meeting
for the assignment.
Where is everyone?
Is this your first group assignment?
-Except for electives.
-Yes.
For required courses,
there are three every semester.
You'll hear all kinds of excuses.
I think there are two types of people.
Those who are responsible
and those who aren't.
Both Jung-ho and Chun-guk
aren't checking their phones.
They're not picking up either.
I should've double-checked with everyone.
I'm really sorry.
The fewer people there are,
the easier it'll be.
We're here anyway,
so let's divide up the workload among us.
Without the others?
Then what? Are we going to keep waiting?
Then I'll let them know
which parts they should work on.
Do you trust they'll do the work?
Sorry?
It's hard to forgive someone
who betrays your trust.
It's easier to just think
they were never on the team.
You're always so negative.
I'd say, I'm a realist.
If that's what it's like to be a realist,
I don't want to be one.
But it must be hard to be positive
if you're down in the gutter.
I get it.
You get it?
Do you even know what that means?
I sure do. Being broke isn't
the only reason you end up in the gutter.
I hope you're not
one of those pathetic losers
who attack innocent people
because they think no one else is
more miserable than they are
when they don't even know
others' situations.
They do that
because they have too much ego.
I'm...
I'm the team leader,
and I don't want to give up on anyone.
We'll divide it up into six parts.
If they don't do their parts,
I'll do their work.
Then I'm out.
Wait, Soo-hyun!
What do we do?
If he's out, we're seriously doomed.
Don't worry. I'll bring him back.
Chun-guk, what happened?
I called you several times.
We were playing billiards
and lost track of time.
Did you guys drink?
The loser had to buy chicken and beer.
Nam Soo-hyun, you jerk!
Hey, what did you just say about my age?
Say it again.
I said, you're 26,
and you need to act your age.
You jerk.
You think I'm a complete joke, don't you?
Because you played billiards
and drank beer,
we wasted our precious time.
What a way to set an example.
You little jerk! Got a death wish?
Look at you. You dodged it? Get back here.
Come at me, jerk. You're so dead.
Jung-ho! Please calm down.
We're at school now.
Get off of me.
Help me calm him down.
Hey, just leave him be.
-Nam Soo-hyun deserves to get beaten up.
-Chun-guk, please!
You're drunk. Please don't cause trouble.
Just leave, okay?
Have you all gone mad?
Yeo Jun, let go.
One, two...
You, Chun-guk, and I should go
for another drink. Come on.
Jun!
Jun, are you okay?
Hey, don't look down on us
just because your family's rich.
We know that you belittle us
behind our backs.
Where do you think you're going?
You little...
Don't hit him!
Just talk it out! Why must you hit him?
Don't...
Jun.
Don't hit him...
It's okay.
Just a second. It's almost done anyway.
-Here...
-I can do it.
Do you think Jun will be okay alone?
Why don't you go see him
if you're that worried?
I don't know where he lives.
I have to go. I have my shift.
Wait, Soo-hyun.
For the assignment...
Are you really going to leave the team?
You said you'd make it up to me.
Could you do that now?
Don't leave the team. We need you.
What if the team members cause trouble?
Will you cover for them
as the team leader?
No, I was wrong about that.
Everyone's grade should reflect
how hard they worked.
All right. Then I'll stay.
Really?
One more thing.
I suppose I have a lot to make up for.
You see, Jun isn't normally like that.
I don't know why he did that earlier.
Please try to understand.
So you know what he's normally like?
Jun always smiles a lot,
and he's very sociable.
I don't think he's usually that sensitive.
I guess you're right.
But I refuse to try to understand him.
I simply can't.
Okay.
Is my team going to be okay?
Get in.
You said you were headed home.
I can go by myself.
Just get in.
Mom called me first. I didn't call her.
I told you to let me know
if you were ever going home.
I don't want to do that.
Why do I have to do that?
Why do I need your permission to go home?
Because it's not your home.
So you're not my brother.
Put on your seat belt.
That mischievous rascal.
I envy you. Your younger son is adorable.
And your elder son is the youngest
doctorate degree holder and professor.
Myung-hoon, you've done a great job
raising your boys.
A man must have big goals.
I expect more from them.
Doesn't Jun-wan look more handsome
in person than on TV?
Yes, he does.
Chan-woo got into
Seoyul University, you know.
He'll attend Jun-wan's alma mater.
That doesn't mean
they're on the same level.
Jun, what are you majoring in
at Seoyul University?
I didn't get in. I'm studying Business
at Myungil University.
Oh, right!
Everyone else in the family attended
Seoyul University, so I forgot.
Sorry about that.
My school's great, Auntie.
Jun-wan teaches at my school, you know.
That's true.
I totally thought he'd get a position
at either Seoyul University or HAIST.
but you got transferred to
Myungil University?
Seoyul University,
which we graduated from, isn't that
different from Myungil University
which Jun is going to.
Not different? That's ridiculous.
Despite the standards of
Korean universities,
none of them produced a noteworthy scholar
or has an outstanding
educational environment.
We should get going. I have other plans.
-Already?
-Let's go.
Why don't you stay a little longer, Jun?
It's been a while since you came.
Come on.
-You go ahead.
-Yes, go ahead Jun-wan.
You said you had other plans.
Go ahead. Mother must've missed me.
Come out when I call you.
Are you smiling?
Is this funny to you?
You were laughing and bragging
about your school, weren't you?
How dare you mention that
trashy school during dinner?
Jun-wan is going to pick him up soon.
You're the problem!
Why did you call this
useless brat to have dinner?
Are you out of your mind?
Please stop, Father. It's all my fault.
Shut your mouth!
Get this brat out of my sight!
Understand?
Arrogant brat.
I'll get going then, Mother.
Does it hurt?
I'm fine. It doesn't hurt.
Of course, it does.
Gosh, you poor thing.
No...
It's my fault.
-I shouldn't have interfered...
-No...
It's all on me.
It's my fault for thinking
you'll behave yourself today.
No...
It's my fault for giving birth
to you in the first place.
What?
I did my best with you.
Look at your brother.
I gave birth to you both.
So why can't you be as good as Jun-wan?
I know... I'm trying my best.
At least you're good at listening to me.
Yes...
But are you really listening to
what I'm saying?
Mother...
This is why I hate you.
I told you to
dye your hair black, didn't I?
I didn't have enough time to...
Stop making excuses!
You're always like that!
I'll call the barbershop.
Go get your hair dyed now.
Okay.
Even though you're saying "okay"
I know you're thinking about
fooling us on the inside.
-Right?
-No, of course not.
Since you don't live with us anymore
I wonder how many more times
you're going to fool me.
I promise I'll go.
Which barbershop is it?
I'll go right away and get my hair dyed.
Shut your mouth.
I'll go. I swear.
Deceiving people while
wearing that fake smile is your specialty.
You think I don't know you?
[Yeo Jun-wan]
Hey. I'll head out now.
Don't make it seem obvious
that you got slapped, got it?
Yes, mother.
Mother,
please believe me.
I just turned 20.
Please have a little faith in me.
Go.
Jun-wan is waiting for you.
[Academy fee, phone bill]
[Nam Soo-hyun]
-Hello?
[-Soo-hyun.]
-Who's this?
[-It's me.]
[You know who I am.]
[You know everything.]
-Are you drunk?
[-Yes.]
[Yes, but I want to drink some more]
[with you.]
-Why would I drink with you?
[-Please don't say no.]
[If you do,]
[I'm going to kill myself.]
Jun... Yeo Jun, is that you?
Oh, So-bin. How did you know I was here?
Soo-hyun said you'd be here.
You guys must be close.
Except me...
Are you okay? How much did you drink?
Not much...
I can drink more.
Let's go drink more...
What's wrong? Wake up.
Soo-bin.
Can you please like me?
[At a Distance, Spring is Green]
It's Soo-hyun.
I'm worried he'll follow me around
[thanking me and saying useless things.]
Soo-hyun!
[Did you give me a piggyback ride?]
Oh, no...
[You're unbelievable.]
Did you say there's a guy you like?
[He did seem interested in me.]
-[Do you really hate me that much?]
-Yes.
Why? Are you going to quit?
[Your brother is out of his mind.]
Am I really your friend?
I actually thought you'd changed.
[Thanks for reminding me that
you're a psychopath.]
How about you like me instead?
[Everything panned out
the way you wanted it to.]
You made me call you
and get down on my knees.
[I'll reward you, Soo-bin,]
for dedicating your youth to me.
[-With what?
-Chicken and beer!]
[I don't know who your crush is,]
[-but you're too good for him.]
-Is it that weird?
[Chan-ki bought me this bracelet
when we were in elementary school.]
[It's totally weird.]
Five, four, three, two, one.
[Yeo Jun]
Use me. I'll be your boyfriend.