♪Waking up in a nightmare♪
♪Facing this cruel world♪
♪Whose heart is flipped♪
♪Missed farewell to lover♪
♪If the ending is tragic♪
♪Fearlessness is born in adversity♪
♪Even if the wings are torn♪
♪And fall back to the abyss♪
♪Hold your hands and move forward♪
♪Never stopping day or night♪
♪Transcending time and distance♪
♪I may be hurt and heartbroken♪
♪Yet be brave to fight on♪
♪As a hero♪
♪Looking beyond, conflicts and war never stops♪
♪Turning behind, you are always there♪
♪Lash out the curse in life♪
♪Let the story be eternal♪
♪Martial Soul surges aggressively♪
♪To embrace your lone wolf braveness♪
♪Even if the future is harsh♪
♪I will never give up♪
♪When there is no way out in reality♪
♪Hope is vexed by desolation♪
♪Yet smiling freely♪
♪Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant♪
♪The power of twin souls illuminates♪
♪Surviving in every plight♪
♪I will never give up♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
The young one with the energy
of the God of the Ocean,
let me see your power.
Top-tier level one test!
It's a once-in-a-century thing.
God of the Ocean. God of the Ocean...
She is the Grand Ocean Master, Bo Sai Xi!
Tang San,
your test
affects the existence of Haishen Island.
My guests,
please follow me into the city.
[Episode 170]
Oh! After a day of tiredness, I can finally sit down!
What?
Everyone will rest here for a while.
I still need to go back to the totems to practice.
Okay.
Thanks a lot, Senior.
Dear guests,
lunch is ready.
Great!
It's so delicious.
I didn't expect things would go
so smoothly after coming here.
Brother San,
it's all thanks to you!
We did successfully make it to Haishen Island,
but this is just the beginning.
So instead,
let's take a look at everyone's first test.
I only have a yellow level one test,
so I'm not even close to you guys.
Yellow level one test.
Accept the test of the sea beasts
at the Seahorse Totem for one month.
Xiang, it's okay.
Even if you only have a yellow level one test,
you can still take the test with us later.
[Black Level Six Test]
Look!
The first test.
Cross the Light of the God of the Ocean
and head to the core forbidden area
of Haishen Island.
Ascend the 108 steps of the forbidden place.
You may exit midway
and the time limit is one year.
I need to cross the double light
of the God of the Ocean
and need to ascend 333 steps.
Isn't it double?
How come Brother San has nearly
three times as many steps as we do?
I don't know either.
Except for Xiang and San,
our first test is all about crossing the light
of the God of the Ocean.
It turns out that I am different from yours.
I have to climb 136 steps.
This is the difference between
the top-tier level test and the black level test.
It's alright.
I'll be with you.
Xiang,
this flower is for you.
Although the first test
is to climb the steps,
we should go through the forbidden area
of Haishen Island.
A special defense.
It seems that every step we pass through
is under immense pressure.
I suddenly thought of a question.
If the Light of the God of the Ocean
will bring us pressure.
Then,
this pressure should also
stimulate our potential.
So, early tomorrow morning,
we'll officially start our training.
What do you think?
As long as I'm full first,
I can do it at any time.
Where is Xiang?
Has anyone seen Xiang?
Xiang is missing.
Missing?
Yes.
We searched the entire residence
and couldn't find her.
I know where she went.
There's no need to look for her.
Let's go.
Will she be in danger?
Yes,
but I trust her.
Grand Seahorse Master instructed
that if the distinguished guests are ready,
I will lead you to the test site.
Welcome to Haishen Mountain.
This is the forbidden area?
Yes, it is.
This is our forbidden area on Haishen Island.
The Haishen Hall to consecrate
the God of the Ocean.
In front of us
are the stairs to the island.
It is also where you need to pass the test.
There are 1001 steps in total.
Dear guests,
although the Light of the God of the Ocean
is the only test
that is not dangerous among all the tests.
But please be careful.
Make sure not to force yourself.
Also, please be careful of the Round Ocean.
(It turns out that this special defense)
(is called the Light of the God of the Ocean.)
Thank you for your advice.
Let's go!
Flying Mushroom Sausage.
Boss Dai,
let's give it a try first.
[Soul Land]
A majestic and solemn atmosphere
permeated the surroundings.
With each step closer,
this oppressive atmosphere grows stronger.
Boss Dai, let's give it a try first.
What happened?
Seems like we hit a wall full of elasticity.
As much my impact force is
and as much it directly bounced back.
The same happened to me.
It seems that
starting from the position of the stairs,
it was the range covered by
the Light of the God of the Ocean.
Boss Dai,
try firing a White Tiger Intense Light Wave
upwards at a squint angle
with a small amount of soul power.
The second soul skill,
White Tiger Intense Light Wave.
It seems that I guessed right.
The Light of the God of the Ocean is an
overbearing protective shield,
capable of reflecting any attack.
And it only bounces back to the person
who launched the attack.
San is right.
Otherwise,
the White Tiger Intense Light Wave
that I shot with squint angle
should have bounced into the diagonally above.
In this case,
wouldn't we be unable to use any skills?
This test is really sick.
So how are we going to get up there?
Our test is so hard,
then Xiang's test...
Bai Chen Xiang.
If you are ready,
please accept the test of the Ocean Delusion Beast
in the Sea Within a Sea.
I'm ready.
Then, let's get started.
There is always a way.
Let's try again and climb slowly under pressure.
Come on.
(What a strong resistance.)
(I'm like a balloon that is being
constantly squeezed)
(and about to be popped out.)
(Moreover,)
(the soul power is being consumed quickly.)
(The pressure is increasing.)
(The pressure is surging like a tide.)
(At this fifth step,)
(I'm afraid that the soul power)
(of the 30th level soul master has been exhausted.)
San.
Let's compete.
The first soul skill, White Tiger Shield.
San.
Go on!
You don't have a single soul skill,
so how did you make it?
I have three more soul bones than you.
Fifth soul skill,
Tiger Monstrous Transformation.
Thirty-four. Thirty-five.
Thirty-six. Thirty-seven. Thirty-eight.
Boss Dai!
Mu Bai!
(Can't even struggle anymore.)
He's so impressive.
I can't stop.
You should take a rest.
It's okay.
I want to see how far San can go.
Forty.
Be careful!
Don't force yourself when you are exhausted.
(Thank god)
(my bones can take the pressure.)
(This familiar crackling sound.)
(Do it all at once,)
(second time tired,)
(third time exhausted.)
San's Blue Silver Domain has increased.
Surprisingly, he can accelerate his pace.
(Forty-nine. Fifty...)
(The recovery of soul power
can't keep up with the consumption.)
Brother San. Watch out!
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 170 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1571 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2570]
[Total scene: 62447]
[Total CGI: 28524]
[Total plan of action scene: 12678]
[Total scene model: nearly 580]
[Total character model: nearly 1055]
[Total props model: 13418]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪We still have to part from each other♪
♪I'm faint-hearted to stop you from leaving♪
♪Amidst the grieving woods♪
♪Who is crying out there♪
♪I still relentlessly hold on♪
♪I refuse to accept this destiny♪
♪Desperately searching♪
♪Any signs of you♪
♪The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight♪
♪In your eyes, the world never changes♪
♪Yearning grows and interweaves with the past♪
♪Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven't told you♪
♪You are the memory I refuse to let go♪
♪And the craziness of my desperation♪
♪Can you hear♪
♪My calls♪
♪Breaking through extreme dolors♪
♪Rushing towards your embrace♪
♪You are the only one I dreamt to comb my hair♪
♪And the wish I made upon a star♪
♪One day♪
♪You will turn up gorgeously♪
♪And hold my hands♪
♪To envisage our future♪
[Next episode]
Turns out that this is to be
in an extremely difficult situation.
I must become stronger as soon as possible.
I'll protect you well.
Xiang.
Am I...
just a burden?
Wu,
don't get close to the Light of the God of the Ocean.
It will hurt you.
Are you mad?
What happened?
I'm afraid San's soul power is about to be used up.
And Wu's body...
No!
I'm suffocating.