♪Memories of the past are always vivid♪
♪They accompanied me to take every step♪
♪On the road♪
♪Going through heat and cold♪
♪The bumpy journey
has rendered my longing♪
♪Rock solid♪
♪The same moonlight
shines on our shoulders♪
♪Even if we are far away separated♪
♪We are close in our hearts♪
♪The wind blew away the past♪
♪I look for your distant location
on the starry night♪
♪In the ocean of faces♪
♪For you, my heart burns and races♪
♪Despite its turns and twists,
fate is in my hands♪
♪May waiting convert regrets
into a happy ending♪
♪May solitary figures
find right companions♪
♪And become a pair♪
=Time Flies and You Are Here=
=Episode 14=
(Dew becomes frost)
Look, this is really nice.
Not bad, Yan Boyang.
It's 20 strings of
1000 cash as you said.
Your father must've taken quite
a lot of money from others.
Pay me.
Give me the letter first.
Pay me first.
Are you out of your mind?
Why are you giving him money?
No, wait.
What are you doing here?
This is between men.
Stay out of it.
That's right.
This is between men,
right, Yu Qilin?
What? Yu Qilin?
Nothing.
What's with this letter?
Is it Yan Boyang's?
Yan Boyang wrote a lady a letter
and asked me to deliver it.
Is it wrong for me to run the errand
with a small fee?
It's okay.
Are
you crazy?
You've been trying to
cause trouble for us.
Let me tell you.
Leave the letter behind
and scram.
Yan Boyang,
if you don't pay me,
I'm going to tear this into pieces.
Don't.
Don't tear it.
Su Wei,
you'd better leave.
Come on.
Leave.
There're more interesting stuff inside.
Don't tear it.
Su Wei.
Leave quickly.
Why are you pushing me?
You're being bullied and
threatened by Xu Shu,
so I helped you. Yet you're
blaming me and pushed me?
Su Wei,
can you stop minding others' business?
Leave quickly.
Yan Boyang,
fine.
You coward.
You deserve to be bullied.
I...
Lady.
Go away.
Pay me now.
I've already paid you.
Give me the letter.
What are you trying to do now?
What's that just now?
Damsel saving the scholar in distress?
I
hate to be pointed by others
and scolded the most.
Add 20 strings of 1000 cash more
to compensate for me.
20 strings of 1000 cash more?
You're jacking up the price.
That's exactly what I'm doing.
Let's go.
Just wait and see!
Coward.
Yan Boyang!
You made me angry!
You won't even listen!
You unworthy man!
Minggu.
Yan Boyang made me so mad.
What's wrong with Yan Boyang?
He's a coward.
Don't even mention him.
What did Qiongqiong say?
Courtesan Zhu has decided
to get married.
Qiongqiong hopes that
Congwen will go and see her,
but I think
it's between the two of them
and I shouldn't interfere
so I didn't agree to it.
Look.
In the end, they'll separate anyway.
Why are things in this world
so strange?
Take Yan Boyang for example.
He usually pretends to be composed,
but he's a coward
during critical moment.
Also, Courtesan Zhu and Congwen.
The two of them were doing fine,
but in the end, they'll separate anyway.
Perhaps it's as written in the books.
"Such a trying journey,
so full of forked paths before."
Certain things
don't seem as easy on the surface.
Also, everyone thinks differently.
Since there're many forked paths,
people will gradually go separate ways.
There's nothing wrong with it.
However, think about it.
Courtesan Zhu's a courtesan.
Congwen's family
is said to be officials in the capital.
They're not destined to be together.
Moreover, Courtesan Zhu's so proud.
She usually interacts with
officials and noblemen.
How could she possibly be willing
to be someone's concubine?
That's not...
That's not what I meant.
You're right.
Forget it.
Anyway, it's not like I
can help with anything.
Let's go home.
Okay.
Your Highness,
eat first.
The dishes are turning cold.
Wait for a while more.
Your Highness.
She's back.
Lady is back.
Understood.
Go quickly.
You're back.
Come on.
The dishes are cold.
I was waiting for you.
What's wrong?
You're in a bad mood?
No.
Come on, let's eat.
I was waiting for you.
The dishes are cold.
I didn't touch any of them.
I was waiting for you.
Eat quickly.
This, too. Try it.
It's very tasty.
Today is the Ghost Festival.
I purposely booked a
decorated pleasure boat.
Later,
we'll go and watch the lanterns,
all right?
I don't want to go.
Don't eat if you don't want to go.
Guizhao Workshop is a large
decorated pleasure boat.
It's not up to you to choose.
You have to go.
Why must I go?
What are you trying to do?
I...
Anyway, it's...
I have something to tell you.
Just say it now.
I...
Certain words
must be said during the festivities,
so it'll be more formal.
Right?
Yes, that's right.
It's a gift.
Before we arrive at Guizhao Workshop,
you mustn't light it.
Come on.
Let's eat.
Why did you come back so late today?
Can I ask you a question?
Of course.
Is there a type of
relationship which family background
doesn't matter,
and the couple can be together
as long as they're in love?
Why are you asking this all of a sudden?
I
recently read a picturebook.
There's a couple in it.
Due to the differences in
their family backgrounds,
the lady is going to marry someone else.
As for the man,
he didn't get to see
her for the last time.
I just want to know
if everyone thinks
if the family backgrounds
aren't compatible,
they're bound to separate?
Of course not.
At least not for me.
I don't believe it either.
What great foundations
or large-scale family businesses
were all
earned by our ancestors.
Back then, my ancestor
wasn't a royal or aristocrat.
He established his kingdom.
Now, my entire family
is doing well thanks to him.
Therefore,
where there's a will, there's a way.
Moreover,
a man
doesn't even dare see his
lover for one last time.
This kind of man.
She'll do better without him.
What are you talking about?
If you like someone,
you must tell the person.
The picturebooks you read
tell the stories of scholars
and beautiful women.
All these scholarly officials
are wretched.
He'd risk his life to submit
a memorial to His Majesty,
but is too cowardly to meet his lover.
What is he trying to do
by not saying a word?
Does he want her
to miss him forever?
That's only causing trouble for others.
Don't believe that.
I'm not like that.
Either way, I'm telling you.
A man having a clear conscience
isn't only about serving the nation.
It's also
about his heart.
Do you understand?
Here.
Having a clear conscience here.
Well said.
Don't worry.
I...
I'm quite the man.
I'm going out.
Later, I'll go look for you
directly at Xushui.
Where are you going?
(Teachers' Office)
Congwen,
today is the Ghost Festival.
Let's go back earlier.
I'm leaving soon.
Congwen,
there's no time.
Xiaoman?
Courtesan Zhu's going to leave tonight.
It has nothing to do with you.
Go home.
That day, when I first came
to Wujiang Prefecture,
you told me to look forward
to mount the wind, break the waves,
and traverse the vast, rolling sea.
Look forward means
to make peace with
everything in the past.
Someone told me that
men need to have a clear
conscience in handling matters.
Not only is the conscience
about serving the nation,
it's also about here.
When handling affairs,
men also have to be true
to their hearts.
That's what it really means
by having a clear conscience.
Are you going to make yourself
as well as Courtesan Zhu regret?
By the painted window, I shed tears
while staring at the vermilion gates.
Things of the present are right and
wrong, leaving feelings of resentment.
Dreams of ecstasy filled
the old courtyard.
Since we last met,
how much melancholy is there?
Just listen to the raindrops
into evening.
Her feelings have been written on here.
What about you?
You don't even dare bid her farewell?
This was written by Yanniang?
That's right.
Qiongqiong came looking for me,
asking me to pass this to you.
You two haven't bid each other farewell.
She doesn't want you
to have regrets.
So,
she asked me to give you this
for you to make the decision.
What's the time now?
There's still time.
Minggu.
There's "Night Parade of One Hundred
Demons" on the Ghost Festival.
So,
if you're afraid,
stay with me
so I could protect you.
You'll protect me?
Use 20 strings of 1,000 cash
to protect me.
Minggu,
I...
Where's Xie Xiaoman?
She should be here soon.
Why isn't she here yet?
Why are you asking me to see her?
Don't you want to meet her?
Someone once told me that
while we're alive,
we mustn't let ourselves down.
You've helped me a lot.
I don't want you to
regret in the future.
Your friend
is quite straightforward.
She's here.
Courtesan Zhu.
Stop the carriage.
Take it.
Stop, Courtesan Zhu!
Congwen has a gift for you
to bid his old friend farewell.
Go quickly.
I'll buy another lantern.
Go!
I've never given you any
gift meant for a lady in the past.
My bad.
This is for you.
I don't believe you bought it yourself.
You used to blame me
for not understanding your troubles.
When I talked to you,
it's always about official affairs.
I wasn't romantic at all.
Today,
let's be romantic for once, all right?
Yanniang,
the city gate's closing soon.
Get back to the carriage.
Yanniang, where are you going?
Yanniang!
This is your romance?
That's right.
This is my romance.
This is Congwen's romance.
I can't grant you a stable life
or lifelong promise.
I can't grant you lots of things,
but I just want to make you smile.
But now,
what if I want to change for your sake?
What if I disregard everything else
to redeem you,
make you my wife,
be with you for the rest of my life,
and have our own offspring.
Just you and me.
For this entire lifetime,
we'll be together forever.
What do you think?
Congwen, you're still so scholarly.
That's good.
You're still the same,
Li Congwen, the scholar whom I like.
You've never changed once.
What had changed is me and society.
Do you think you can get away from
your family?
Li Family has been
scholars for generations.
And me?
A 24-year-old
courtesan.
I'm not good enough for you.
Don't you understand?
The Li Congwen in my heart
has high ambitions.
He's going to attend the
imperial examination in the future.
He'll become a great man and
has a bright future ahead.
He's destined to be Li Congwen
who stands at the top
instead of belonging to me.
But what if I don't want to
attend the imperial examination?
What bright future?
I don't care at all.
You have to
because the Li Congwen I love
is always the sincere Li Congwen
wishing to serve the nation.
I want to see you marry
the daughter of a noble family
which elevates your status,
allowing you to focus on
pursuing knowledge
as well as ways of handling
national affairs
and become a high official eventually
to serve the people.
What I wish to see the most
is the future Chancellor Li.
When he thinks back when he's old,
he still remembers
there was once a woman called
Yanniang at Wujiang Prefecture
who hoped that you'll advance on
the path of becoming an official.
But I
have my own path.
After marrying that man,
perhaps my life will be plain,
but one day,
when I become a grandmother,
if I think of the Li Congwen
whom I once loved
and is now well-known as an official
was willing to give up
everything tonight,
I won't have any regret.
Yanniang!
Yanniang,
where are you?
My husband's looking for me.
Take care.
Yanniang.
Yanniang!
Path of becoming an official.
Chancellor Li.
What if I don't want to?
What if all this is not what I want?
Resembling a bird locked
in a golden cage.
My robes are filled with dust.
As if I'm seeing all this from
the outside of my body.
I descended to the mortal world
for a few years.
Not long ago, eastern winds were here,
and peach blossoms are
as I remembered them.
I return to the county of Wuling.
By the painted window, I shed tears
while staring at the vermilion gates.
Things of the present are right and
wrong, leaving feelings of resentment.
Dreams of ecstasy filled
the old courtyard.
Since we last met,
how much melancholy is there?
Just listen to the raindrops
into evening.
It's strange.
Hanchen,
she might've been delayed by some stuff.
Let's wait for a while.
Come down first. Careful, don't fall.
Who cares if she's coming or not?
I don't care.
Forget it.
I'll help you to look for her.
Minggu,
I'll go with you.
No need.
Minggu.
Don't come after me.
Minggu,
don't be angry.
I know I shouted at you earlier.
I'm sorry.
Look.
Today's a festival.
If you missed this beautiful scene
because you're angry,
it isn't worth it at all, right?
Yan Boyang, do you have
nothing better to do?
Why are you so fierce?
That's how I am.
However fierce I am,
it's still better than you
being all cowardly and indecisive.
Who are you calling a coward?
If you aren't a coward,
go talk to Xu Shu
to take your money and letter back.
Walking back and forth here.
Who are you trying to
be unreasonable with?
You just dislike that
I gave Xu Shu
20 strings of 1000 cash earlier.
All right, wait here.
I'm going to take that
20 strings of 1000 cash back now.
I'll show you that
I, Yan Boyang, am not a coward.
Where are you going?
Where am I going? I'll go and
take the money back from him.
Yan Boyang!
Su Wei,
what's going on with you two?
He's going to look for Xu Shu.
Xu Shu?
Yesterday at brothel,
Yan Boyang and Xu Shu
had a conflict.
Xu Shu blackmailed him.
Just now I bickered with him,
and said he's a coward,
that might've agitated him.
And that fool
insisted to go talk to Xu Shu
to prove himself.
He doesn't have a weapon
and acts on impulse.
He's going to suffer for sure.
Zhao Xiaoqian,
why don't you go and help him?
Give me back the letter
and 20 strings of 1000 cash.
Or else, prepare to bear
the consequences.
You'll make me bear the consequences?
Boyang has toughened up today.
Let's see
how you'll do it.
Yan Boyang!
Boyang!
Hanchen,
we've found Boyang!
He's right there!
- Let's go!
This is bad.
Lanterns.
Shopkeeper,
how much is this?
10 cash.
This lantern?
Here you go.
I'll take it. Keep the change.
Lady,
I haven't finished talking!
Let me ask you again.
Are you giving it to me or not?
No.
I...
Let go!
Boyang!
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
How dare you touch my brother?
Come over here, Xiaoman!
What's going on?
Careful.
Why are they fighting?
Xu Shu
deserves it.
Hide behind my back.
Just watch quietly.
Not bad, Yan Boyang.
You called for backup.
I'm going to read the letter aloud.
Xu... Xu Shu!
What?
He wrote a letter to a lady
and asked me to deliver the letter.
Is it wrong for me to ask for some fees?
Moreover, Lady Dew
won't accept the letter.
Isn't that right, Yan Boyang?
Let me tell you.
No matter which lady
you fell in love with,
you're just aspiring after
someone you're not worth of.
It's just your wishful thinking.
It'll never happen.
Shut up.
Minggu.
I'm Lady Dew.
I'm in love with Yan Boyang.
So what?
You're in love with him?
What's gotten into you?
Yan Boyang, what are you
standing there for?
Go!
Hit him!
I...
If Lord Shen doesn't watch
his own underling properly,
and if he goes and bites others,
I'm going to teach him a lesson.
Understand?
Scram.
Scram!
All right, that's enough.
Don't watch anymore. Leave.
Leave.
What took you so long?
I've been waiting for
you the entire night.
What's going on?
Well,
I was writing my good friend a letter,
and Xu Shu saw it.
He threatened me with it.
It's just a letter.
What's there to threaten you?
I agree.
It's just a letter.
Could it be a love letter?
There is no need to choose another day.
Why don't we
ask Lady Dew out today?
Talking face-to-face will make things
clear rather than writing a letter.
Forget it. I'd better not.
You have to.
I hate fickle-minded men the most.
Moreover, Zhao Xiaoqian booked
the entire Guizhao Workshop today.
Right, Xiaoqian?
That's right.
Let's go and take a look.
I'm not going.
Come on.
Let's go.
No, but...
- Come on!
- I don't think I'll go.
- Let's go!
Later,
I have something to talk to you.
Mr. Yu Qilin.
Dew?
That's right.
Have a seat.
How is that a young lady?
It's certainly not.
Well,
have some tea.
All right.
I have something to say to you.
Follow me.
Let's go.
Well.
The moon tonight
is quite lovely.
The Ghost Festival is a good
time for viewing lanterns.
Why didn't I see the young lady
mentioned in the invitation letter?
She...
She doesn't know about my feelings yet.
You should let her know.
Yes.
Every time I see her,
I'd get very anxious.
I don't know how to tell her.
Just tell her
what you've written in the letter.
Ten thousand miles of
rivers and mountains,
you're one in a million.
And I'm the cavalry who guards
the nation's territory.
All right.
Enough.
Stop reading.
I'm going to vomit.
No, you...
Why are you staring at me?
What you told me
sounded very sincere.
How is it disgusting?
She's a very good lady.
You're very good.
Yes,
she's my ideal type.
You don't know this.
She's the only daughter in their family.
She'll become the head of the household
in the future.
Moreover,
she's bold and intelligent.
Anyway, there's nothing bad about her.
Unlike me,
I couldn't even do well in studies
and keep making her angry all the time.
That's not all.
I'd become a coward whenever I see her.
But when it comes to relationship,
there's no such thing as right or wrong.
What matters most is your
feelings at this moment
are true.
That's better than anything.
At our hometown,
there's this method.
If you're afraid
to tell her face-to-face,
you could...
Come here.
I can't hear them.
Is it nice?
Yes.
Do you like it?
Back in the capital,
during each year's Ghost Festival,
I'd always ask my brother
to bring me to the city
for lanterns-viewing.
However, we didn't get
to watch it even once.
It's all right.
We're watching it now.
Duke of Yongguo didn't get to
watch it with you,
but I can.
(We're to separate as I know you're
in love with someone else.)
Is it your lantern?
Boyang.
Minggu,
I...
(My lover is just across the river.)
Take care.
(Two days later)
(Sleeping Room)
Slowly, Your Highness.
Slowly!
Your Highness!
His Majesty is at Ruisi Palace,
checking Your Highness' homework.
His Majesty told me to
relay this message
which is, right now,
Her Highness is pregnant,
so playing a kite is unsuitable.
I even wrote the words
I want to tell my parents
on the kite.
Brother said if it's written
on the kite,
my parents will come and look
for me once they saw it,
but he won't even play with me.
Your Highness,
don't say that again.
Since you entered the palace,
you're now His Majesty's son.
Prince and Princess Consort Pu
are your uncle and aunt.
His Majesty and Her Highness
are your parents.
My parents aren't my actual parents.
You all are lying to me.
Your Highness!
The kite's flying.
Your Highness,
flying kite isn't advisable!
Your Highness!
The string snapped.
Your Highness.
Her Highness is about to give birth.
These aren't allowed within the palace
since it might distress Her Highness.
Ridiculous.
Brother!
Your Highness.
Your Highness, what's wrong?
I'm fine.
You may leave.
Shi Deng'er.
Why aren't you serving His Highness
in his room at this hour?
What are you doing here?
Mr. Ji,
what's gotten into His Highness
these few days?
He even wakes up startled at night.
Duke of Yongguo's death
anniversary is in a few days' time.
His Highness is always like this
during this time of the year.
Let me tell you. These few days,
if there's nothing in particular,
don't go near His Highness.
Do you hear me?
This memory of mine.
I forgot.
This is our academy's Dongguan Building.
Come on. I'll show you around.
Usually Jingnv Pavilion
doesn't have visitors.
You're the only exception.
There are so many books here.
Lonely Boat in the Night?
(Chapter one)
It's not worth reading.
Don't read anymore.
Wick told me that
Zhao Xiaoqian's acting
strange again lately.
Even Mr. Liangji was scolded by him.
Are you two having a fight again?
No,
everything's fine.
But ever since he came back
from the Ghost Festival,
he's been acting strange.
That one-of-a-kind temper of his
is like June's weather.
It changes so easily.
Someone must've angered him.
Oh, right.
I saw your mother this morning.
She told you to make a trip home.
She's going to nag at me again.
I'll borrow this book.
Let's go.
Let's go over there.
This book hasn't been borrowed before.
Are you sure you want to read it?
No.
You're making promises again anyhow.
Then
he's going to a wedding
banquet in the countryside.
The dishes served are
going to be unrefined.
He's the Commandery Prince.
There's no way he'll get used to it.
But,
I've already told that family.
Now, the entire village knows
you married to the Commandery Prince.
The couple
from Liu Family who is
going to get married,
Cheng and Ying,
were your childhood playmates.
They're my childhood playmates.
That's why I don't have to
put on airs in front of them.
Think about it.
Liu Family's daughter
gave you a lot of food
when you were little.
Your brother even drank her milk once.
We shouldn't be ungrateful, right?
You're the one who pretends to
be rich whenever you go home.
I don't believe Ying
would make noise just to
see His Highness.
Yes.
I'm pretending to be rich.
Are you satisfied?
Now, the entire village knows that
we came to Wujiang Prefecture.
They all know that
you married to
the Commandery Prince of Julu.
They're waiting to see how
I'll embarrass myself.
I don't care.
If His Highness isn't going,
I'm not going either.
You
didn't come back even once,
and make me angry when you do.
Your father
had come to work at
Wujiang Prefecture long ago.
I raised the three of you up
since you were little.
Now that you've grown up,
and know how to anger people,
you'll just make your mother angry.
I guess you'll be happy
when I die from anger one day.
That way, no one will nag at you.
All right.
I'll go talk to him.
But I don't know
if he'll agree or not.
That's my good daughter.
I need to return some books.
I'm going to the academy.
Goodbye.
Books.
You only know how to read books.
What's the use of reading
all those books?
Can you attend the imperial examination?
Worry about our family more.
Don't you think my mother
has nothing better to do?
She wants Zhao Xiaoqian to go
to the countryside with me
to attend the wedding banquet.
I don't know how to ask him.
Throughout her life,
she had never cared for food
or extravagant clothing.
Now that she's old,
she cares about whether it'll
look good for the family.
It's normal since you're returning
to your hometown in glory.
Besides,
her own daughter married to a royal.
Of course she's very proud of it.
Ladies.
Congwen.
Greetings, Congwen.
There's something
which I might have to tell you.
I'm leaving Wujiang Prefecture
a few days later.
About the matters concerning studies,
I've asked Teacher Liu to help.
Why?
Congwen, are you leaving us?
I've had some trouble recently,
so I'm going to meditate
at Mount Kunyan Temple.
In the prose Lang Mengzi
mentioned just now,
although it's talking about
the misery of parting,
it also mentioned "long distance
separates no bosom friends.
I'll be back after some time.
And by that time?
Will you leave again when you're back?
Ladies,
see you.
Congwen.
Are you leaving
because of Courtesan Zhu?
Have I taught you this poem before?
Life is like a journey
and I am a traveller.
Since I'm a traveller,
I'll be on the road.
A person's life journey is
ever-changing.
I've also thought before
to travel throughout my entire life
and teach students.
What about now?
Now,
I'm also confused.
Before Yanniang left, she told me
that I shouldn't remain
at Wujiang Prefecture.
I should return to the capital
for the exam.
A man should have high ambitions.
What do you think, Xiaoman?
No matter what you do,
there's a reason for doing so.
Why am I telling you all these?
It doesn't matter.
It's just that, since Yanniang left,
I'm uncertain about some matters.
About the imperial examination
and my future,
it's filled with uncertainty.
This time, I'm leaving
to give myself some time
to think it through.
No need to worry about me.
Instead,
the lantern you gave to
Yanniang in my place,
I'll ask someone to return
one to you next time.
Never mind.
Autumn season is here.
Take care of yourself
and bring more clothing.
What were you talking
to Congwen just now?
Do you know where Zhao Xiaoqian is?
They're having a chess lesson today.
He should be at Tingtao Pavilion.
How did you know
Luming Pavilion's lesson arrangement?
I copied it secretly
from Director Xu.
It's because of Zhong...
I know.
The way of chess
is between ego-centrism
and stubbornness.
Find the most suitable timing
to understand when to give up
and when to persevere.
Zhao Xiaoqian,
what opinion do you have this time?
As humans,
it's quite boring
to have nothing to hold on to.
In that case, take a look at
the set of chess before you.
Half of the black chess pieces
have been captured.
Should you give up one chess piece
or continue to break through?
What if the opponent gives up
a chess piece first?
On the chess board,
look to your own heart,
not your opponent.
Zhao Xiaoqian.
♪Ask the moon whether it has seen♪
♪The other end of the earth♪
♪Your feelings fluctuate
like the moon's wane and wax♪
♪Have they ever been the same?♪
♪Carried by misty clouds,
the moon came into your eyes♪
♪As a substitute for me, it appeared♪
♪Cast our eyes over the bustling street♪
♪Don't shed tears when we part♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪