♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
=The Eternal Love S3=
=Episode 06=
(So this is what it feels like)
(to have my lifelong dream come true.)
(I feel sorry for Eighth Brother,)
(but tonight will be a sleepless night)
(for Tan Er and me.)
Cheng Cheng?
Come on out, Cheng Cheng.
Where are you?
Cheng Cheng? Cheng Cheng?
Hiding from me, huh?
Cheng Cheng!
Come out, Mo Lian Cheng!
Mo Lian Cheng! Mo Lian Cheng!
What happened, Your Highness?
Quick, go and find him...
Find the prince consort!
Ah Gui, get some people
to find the prince consort.
Quick. You guys search over there!
Hurry, hurry! Find the prince consort!
- Prince Consort! Prince Consort!
- Prince Consort!
Mo Lian Cheng!
Come out!
Come out, Mo Lian Cheng!
Mo Lian Cheng!
Your Highness.
Why are you here?
Eldest Brother.
Mo Lian Cheng!
Come out!
(Even if Her Highness finds me,)
(I'm sure she won't do anything
with Eldest Brother around.)
(But how can I convince Eldest Brother
to let me stay?)
Don't sit...
Eldest Brother.
I can't stay in that room any longer.
Why?
It's normal to feel nervous on your wedding night.
Aren't you nervous, Eldest Brother?
All men have to go through this.
I may be nervous,
but I'm looking forward to it as well.
I'm afraid I can't feel that way.
Don't worry, Eighth Brother.
You don't have to worry about tonight.
It is me...
who will need to concentrate and ensure
that I am ready for it.
Why don't I concentrate with you?
That may make me feel better.
Eighth Brother, you don't need to do this.
Eldest Brother,
no need to be so courteous.
I am willing to do it.
Eighth Brother, Tan Er will be here soon.
Let's not talk any further.
Go back to your room and rest.
Eldest Brother, I need more time...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Why don't... both of you carry on?
Tan Er, Eighth Brother only came
to keep me company.
He'll be leaving right away.
Yes, he'll leave right now.
Go on... Go. Go!
I won't!
Go now.
I won't.
Go back.
- Go back...
- No need!
No need.
It's alright. I'm not in a hurry.
I'll leave first. You guys have fun.
Tan Er.
What about... I leave first?
I shall not interrupt your fun.
Please enjoy yourselves.
Eighth Brother, are you all right?
I'll have Yu Hao send you back to your room.
You... I...
Are you alright?
No!
What's wrong with your head?
Don't come near me, Eldest Brother.
She... She...
Don't look at us like that!
Don't think I don't know what's
going on in your mind?
Tan Er!
Eighth Brother!
What are you doing?
Because I went to your brother's room?
If so, why did you hide in his room then?
Mo Lian Cheng,
you've gone too far.
Can't you be serious for once?
If you keep thinking those thoughts,
I'll have to do something extreme
to get you to stop fantasizing.
"Fantasizing"?
Cheng Cheng, is it really you?
Still laughing?
You aren't reflecting at all.
Wait.
You realized it too?
What sort of rule is that?
You turned back the moment I kiss you.
You want to kiss me that badly?
I thought all you cared about was your son.
I wonder if Yu Er was harmed
by the Soul-guarding Bead.
What if we can never go back?
The final memories Yu Er had of us
were his parents arguing.
Would he think that we didn't love
each other anymore?
Nonsense.
Don't worry.
I will definitely bring you back.
But my current condition...
I don't know if it was caused by
the Soul-guarding Bead.
But I have memory lapses.
I can't always protect you.
Fortunately, I...
♪Carried by the wind, our love falls to the ground♪
♪As I roll up the beaded curtains,
you are the only one before me♪
♪A dream of love without worries♪
♪We share a night of happiness,
to our deaths do we part♪
Let's just take it...
that I've kissed you already, all right?
With the way things are right now...
I don't know how to cheer you up.
No way.
You have to try to overcome
the obstacles you encounter.
What's this for?
We can use this handkerchief to cover you.
That would work, wouldn't it?
This red handkerchief is just like the red veil.
Wouldn't it suit you better?
Today, you are marrying into the bride's family.
Not the other way around.
Dear husband.
Dear "wife"?
Which should I call you?
♪We search for one another, missing each other♪
♪The wheels of fate turn, in another life we meet♪
♪I still remember the vows we made,
but words would not come to me♪
♪I resent that we act as if we are strangers♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
Your Majesty has had him
become the prince consort.
Why do you have to be upset over the matter now?
It is unlike you to surmise my thoughts.
Indeed.
What matters most is the second princess
right now.
Not the eighth young master of the Mo family.
It may be more appropriate
to marry him off to the second princess
rather than have him enter the harem.
She was willing to take in Mo Lian Cheng.
That is exactly what I want to see.
Your Majesty's illness acted up again.
Was it because you witnessed
their marriage yesterday?
You mustn't allow yourself to
fall in love, Your Majesty.
There is no one that could make me fall for them.
How would I even fall in love?
However, it is hard not to think of him
when I see something like that.
Where is the Soul Parting Flute?
It's here.
This flute...
was originally a magic tool meant to kill.
But somehow it is now being used to save lives.
(Princess’s Residence)
What exactly happened last night?
How could I have...
Eighth Brother.
Eldest Brother.
Here. I prepared this for you.
Have it while it's hot.
Tonic soup?
It was your first time.
You need to replenish your body.
Eldest Brother,
after I went to your room last night, I...
I don't blame you. You don't need to explain.
Eldest Brother, I didn't...
You don't have to explain. I understand.
However, please do not
take Her Highness away by force
from my room again.
Think about what other people would say
if they caught wind of this?
Took her away from your room?
By force?
Jing Xin.
You...
Fourteenth Young Master, swords are dangerous.
You should be careful.
You... What were you looking at?
I'm having a melon.
[*Internet slang for gossip]
I asked you what you were looking at.
It means to be an onlooker. Gossiping.
It's a new word I learned from Her Highness.
What were you guys looking at?
What were you looking at?
I don't know.
What about you guys?
We're having a melon.
I'm curious as to how Her Highness
and my eldest brother
are getting along in the Frost Court?
Her Highness wasn't in the Frost Court.
What melon were you having?
She's in the Xue Court.
My young master went to the Frost Court.
And Her Highness followed him to the Frost Court.
This...
Of... Of course I know about that!
They are still in the Frost Court, right?
They went back to the Snow Court together.
And you guys don't know this too.
The main prince consort went to
the Snow Court just now too.
So what exactly were the two of you looking at?
- This...
- Mo Lian Cheng!
- You must be careful.
It's all your fault.
My back still hurts.
Your Highness, you should
take good care of your body.
Someone
should take better care of my body.
He shouldn't let it
get to his head and do something that hurts my back.
(Last night, Cheng Cheng returned to himself
when he and Mo Yan Chen)
(touched.)
(I remember that happened before as well.)
(He would react when he comes into contact
with a blood relative.)
(Could the key to turning him back
lie with Mo Yan Chen?)
(Let's give it a try.)
Are you guys having soup?
The secondary prince consort is healthy.
It'd be a waste for him to have it.
He doesn't need it.
Why don't you have it instead?
Why are you still standing there?
Bring it over.
You must be careful.
Don't spill it on the main prince consort.
I'll do it. Come on.
Cheng Cheng?
(Cheng Cheng the heck.)
(Grumpy and mean.)
(He definitely didn't turn back
into my Cheng Cheng.)
(Why did it fail again?)
Eldest Brother, it's all my fault.
I wasted the soup you made for me.
It's all right. There's always next time.
Since we won't be having the soup,
let's depart then.
To where?
Tan Er. You forgot?
We're supposed to go back to
visit our families today.
Oh, right.
I must still be sleepy.
Why don't you go back and get ready first?
All right. Please excuse me then.
Yun Ying.
Why did you trip my brother earlier?
You need evidence before you
can slander someone.
Why would I need...
See.
So you admit you were slandering me, right?
I can't be bothered with you.
Make sure you don't talk too much when we
return to the Mo Residence.
To avoid unnecessary trouble.
We're just going back to visit your family, aren't we?
I know how things work.
You better mind your own business.
And respect me.
Otherwise, you'll have to deal with your sister.
Welcome, Your Highness.
Please have a seat.
What's the matter?
Father, Tan Er accidentally
hurt her back last night.
Quick, get a cushion for Her Highness.
Yes, My Lord.
No need.
No need for that.
Why were you so careless?
To have let Her Highness hurt her back
on your wedding night.
It wasn't Eldest Brother. It was me.
Both of you better be more careful
from now on.
Her Highness is royalty.
Why wasn't Your Highness
in the main prince consort's room
on your wedding night?
Feng Yang, what does that matter?
I was the one who dragged Her Highness
away by force
from Eldest Brother's room last night.
It had nothing to do with Her Highness
and Eldest Brother.
Don't you think you involve yourself
too much, General Mo?
Please do not be angry, Your Highness.
Feng Yang has been away on the battlefield
for a long time.
She may be a bit brash and reckless with her words.
Since we're on this topic,
I'll have to make things clear.
I slept alone last night.
Without any of the consorts in my bed.
Who is it?
I should have expected this.
In the Princess's Residence,
only the princess would do such a thing.
You turned back?
I hadn't expected this at all.
Hadn't expected what?
I never expected that I would be
a victim of domestic violence!
In a matriarchal society, even.
Your Highness was the one who acted crudely first.
I didn't make the first move to kiss you!
You wouldn't believe me even if I told you.
What are you doing?
I can't walk.
Take me back to your room.
Why do you want to go to my room?
I'll have Jing Xin send you back.
How are you going to explain this to Jing Xin?
I'm not going to cover up for you.
I feel awful...
My consort
is not someone that anyone can just
criticize and slander.
Neither do they need an outsider
to teach them what to do.
Mr. Mo.
We've come to greet you today.
I will be bringing my two consorts
back with me now then.
We'll take our leave.
Seeing you off, Your Highness.
Tan Er.
(So I can get the best of both worlds.)
(She got into an argument with Feng Yang for my sake.)
(I should be nicer to her.)
(Tan Er loves me, after all.)
Here.
She got into an argument
with Mo Feng Yang for Mo Lian Cheng.
What is she trying to play up now?
Could it be that she is pretending that she is
on bad terms with the Mo family?
Pretending?
Does that mean she is trying to hide the fact
that they have formed an alliance?
Your Majesty, you mean...
I haven't sent Tan Er's wedding gift to her yet.
Why don't...
I send her a grand gift?
A pair of red corals.
A pair of silver bangles.
Six pieces of jade accessories.
Two pairs of rings.
Rolls of fabric...
What is all of this? Who sent them?
Your Highness,
these are wedding gifts sent to you
from Her Majesty.
Her Majesty has also said that
as you are newly-wedded,
there is no need for you to enter
the palace to thank her.
Her Majesty does hold Tan Er in high regard.
Her Majesty is very generous.
Yu Hao,
take inventory of the gifts.
Make a record and report it to me.
That'd make me happy too.
Yes, Your Highness.
There is also a very special gift.
Her Majesty has ordered
that I must hand it to you in person.
What is it?
Tan Er seems to like it very much.
It's nothing special.
Put it together with the other gifts.
But don't open it.
And there's no need to make a record of it.
Yes, Your Highness.
All right.
We got into an argument today.
It's been a long day.
Go back and rest.
Take a good rest, everyone.
Why are you still here?
Thank you for what you did today.
I didn't do it entirely for you either.
She was being rude.
I couldn't stand it.
So I refuted her.
Still, thank you.
Not only for speaking up for me,
but I admire your words and view as well.
If you really want to thank me,
then why don't you carry me back to my room
to show your gratitude?
I shall not bother you any further then,
Your Highness.
You won't send me back.
Are you afraid that you won't be able
to control yourself
once you get into my room?
Or that I might force you?
All right.
I am curious as well.
As to why Your Highness thinks that
I wouldn't be able to control myself.
And what you think you could force me to do.
Please.
I've sent you back.
What else does Your Highness have in mind?
Please hurry up and do it now.
The sky is still bright outside.
What are you afraid of?
Come over here and serve me some tea.
Your Highness doesn't have any new tricks at all.
You still haven't learned anything despite
having tea spilled on you many times.
You give it a try then.
If you get me wet,
I'll just have you help me change my clothes.
You touched my hand when I served you tea.
If your clothes got wet, you'd have me
help you change.
Does Your Highness intend
to push me up against a wall next?
It's a bit old-fashioned, but it's classic.
So what if I try it out a few more times?
You forgot that you aren't tall enough.
Am I tall enough now?
Your Highness, please don't waste your energy.
The problem between you and me
is truly not a matter of height.
(The imperial token?)
Does Your Highness really like me that much?
I do, but it's a waste of effort.
Ungrateful.
I'd like to tour around the lake
on the outskirts tomorrow.
Would Your Highness permit me to do so?
You'll have to bring me along with you.
Then Your Highness
will have to bring my eldest brother along as well.
We'll split up then.
And meet up at the lake.
All right.
Jing Xin, what time is it?
Why isn't he here yet?
If we had known that we'd have to wait so long,
why did we have to come so early?
I don't get it.
We're all staying in the same residence.
Why do we have to split up to come here?
You don't get it.
Waiting can be a fascinating thing.
Especially when you know
that he'll definitely come.
He's here. Here they come.
Jing Xin.
Make sure you watch me flirt with him
and learn from me.
You can use it on Fourteenth next time.
Don't talk nonsense.
Tan Er, sorry for making you wait so long.
Eighth Brother indeed did it on purpose.
Why? Are you disappointed?
(It's fine that I feel disappointed.)
(But why should I make him feel bad too?)
(It's not his fault.)
Of course not.
I invited both of you.
But he didn't come...
It must be because
he has something even more important to attend to.
But since we're here,
let's have fun and enjoy ourselves.
Let's forget about all the unpleasant things,
okay?
As long as you're happy.
What do you mean by that?
Please don't keep everything to yourself.
Say what you feel.
Do what you want to do.
Your own happiness is the most important thing.
Let's go over there and see what
fun things we can do.
Come on.
(The imperial token can allow my father
to direct the border troops)
(and do great things.)
(I'm sorry, Your Highness.)
The air is so fresh here.
Tan Er.
I'd like to show you my sword dance.
You were always so happy when you
saw me perform back then.
Seeing you being happy makes me happy.
Jing Xin, give the prince consort your sword.
He's not bad at all.
Much better than you.
I...
♪Why am I the only one to suffer♪
♪Standing alone in the wind♪
Yan Chen, you don't have to feel restricted.
Try to let yourself go. Be a little bit
unbridled and carefree.
All right.
♪The day turns to the night♪
♪A sleepless night passes by♪
♪You kept me up, tire me out♪
♪Like the wind, I♪
What are you doing?
I can tell that there is a lot on your mind today.
Didn't you tell me to let go?
To be unbridled and carefree?
Let it out together with me.
♪That's your true nature♪
Prince Consort.
Eighth Brother.
Eldest Brother.
Why are you here?
Didn't you have other important things to do?
Eldest Brother, I apologize for interrupting.
I have some things
that I must talk to Her Highness in private.
Could I...
No.
Tan Er.
Eighth Brother must have come late
because he was held up.
Since you have something to discuss,
I'll wait in the carriage.
Thank you, Eldest Brother.
Jing Xin, go with Eldest Brother.
Yes, Your Highness.
Where is the imperial token?
I pawned it.
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪The flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪the love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter what
hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have to
travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter what
hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have to
travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪