DAY 1
We have breaking news, it happened
just a few moments ago apparently...
We have very little
information available...
We are... We have I understand, an
eyewitness on the phone right now...
- Roge!
- Where are you right now?
...a loud noise, and everything shook,
I went outside.
...of the plaza at 8:52 AM.
We have limited information
at this point.
We don't know about the injuries
in the building...
What the hell happened?
A bomb.
I think.
So sad.
Roger, I gotta...
- Yeah, just go.
- Thanks.
Wanna go higher?
So, the Red Sox with two down...
- First time through the order?
- Third.
The third?
- What inning is this?
- Fifth.
Oh, boy!
Your hands are… disgusting.
Let me do it.
Disgusting?
Disgusting.
Wow!
Just breathe.
...pops out one down
the line. Come on, Beltran...
it's ducking in! It falls in...
- What's the inning of that game?
- Third.
Let's go!
Come on, Henry!
You got it, you got it.
Dive! Dive! Dive!
He's out!
Hey, how do you say, 'dive'?
- Dive?
- It's a tough one.
Come on!
Ball.
Shit.
Shit!
Check one!
It's alright.
Goddamn thing.
Check two!
Let's go.
Alright folks, that's the game.
We all head to our cars, okay?
- Okay, let's go.
- Ollie!
- Hey.
- What was that?
- I don't know.
- I don't know what that was.
- Honey, take the kids home. Okay?
Okay. Yeah. My truck's
up on main street. So...
Okay. Alright.
Everybody in. Let's go.
I'll go with Dad.
Okay. Straight home.
Lee. Lee.
- Hey, you alright?
- Yeah. Good.
Your brother say anything
going on at the base?
Not that I know of.
He just called,
let me call him back.
Alright. Yeah.
Let me know.
- My truck's up there.
- Okay.
Look out!
Don't worry.
Wait here.
Ronnie, what do we got?
We got units headed out there now.
EMS and Fire.
- Where about?
- I think up on Walker's farm.
What's wrong?
It's alright.
It's okay, honey.
It's okay, baby.
- Mom?
- Yeah.
What is happening?
Oh my God!
It's okay. It's okay.
We're okay. We're okay.
- Dad, that's dad! Dad!
- Where? Where?
Mom! Mom!
Oh my God!
- You're okay, baby.
- I'm okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
Go! Go to the buildings!
I'm okay. I'm okay.
...we were on Main Street
and then...
I'm don't...
Are you there?
Mom?
Our Father, Who art in heaven,
hallowed be Thy name;
Thy kingdom come; Thy will be done
on earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily...
There's daddy! There's daddy.
It's Dad!
Get down! Get down!
Let's go!
Subtitled by CLARITY
DAY 474
Wait here.
I'm going back in…
Stay here.
Run!
Baby, please!
Please!
Please! No!
It's okay, honey. It's okay.
It's okay.
Go!
You can't stay.
I don't know why you came all the way
up here. But you can't stay.
Up?
There is not enough food...
...water, there is not enough of
anything.
How do you know
we traveled up?
There is nothing I can do.
You won't survive.
Show me your face.
I can't help you.
Please, I can't help you.
Emmett?
Please...
Breathe baby.
How does it work?
It's three feet of concrete.
That must be right above us to hear.
What's this?
Some kind of...
...some kind of
feedback from the microphone?
It just works.
I don't know...
I've never seen one dead before.
How is he?
He's...
I didn’t reach the bone.
But that wrap won't last.
I'm sorry.
- Of what?
- The boys.
- I assume.
- That day...
And Nora?
Eleven weeks ago.
She was sick.
We held out as long as we could
in the house.
But the pain didn't.
Just when she started screaming...
we had to come here.
It was smart.
It wasn't enough.
Can I ask you a question?
When you saw the flame,
night after night,
did you know it was him?
Yes.
And did you ever think
to come for us?
No.
The people that are left...
...what they have become...
...you don't know, do you?
I knew.
They are not the kind of people
worth saving.
♪ Somewhere ♪
♪ beyond the sea ♪
What is it?
- What is it?
- Music.
♪ Stands on golden sand and watching ♪
- It's a...
- Beyond the Sea.
- Have you heard this?
- Ah. Yes.
No. Dad would've heard this.
It's the same song that has been playing
over and over the last four months.
You're lying!
My Dad used the radio every day!
What she's saying?
She thinks he would have heard it.
Who?
Lee.
It's the valley.
It's the valley, I tried the radio,
from our house too. But...
We never heard anything
until we got up here.
Your dad was never
gonna make it work.
You're nothing like him!
Does this mean that
there are more people?
- I don't know, baby. I don't...
- No!
There is nothing left.
I told you, there is nothing left.
I want you gone tomorrow.
It's not a song.
On the radio.
Beyond The Sea… Right?
It's not a song…
It's a signal.
They're telling us where to look.
I looked up the radio station.
…where the song is coming from.
It's an island!
I can follow the train tracks…
It's not even one day.
Then I can find a boat.
You can't do this.
If I can find the song.
Where it's coming from…
I can use this…
to change this…
into this!
Mom, will never… let you go.
I can save them.
I can save us.
I'll tell her.
Mom… I'll tell her.
Please don't do this!
I need to try.
Why?
Because Dad would.
And look what happened to him.
KEEP LISTENING
You have to find her for me.
She's gonna get help, and I need you to go
and find her for me, bring her back to me.
Alright, listen to me.
Please, Emmett, I am begging you!
- No, Evelyn!
- I am begging you!
We were friends, Emmett, please.
Lee is gone.
Now he's gone.
It's a shame, because
if he was here,
he'd look you right in the eye,
and he'd tell you that
his little girl is absolutely
the kind of person
worth saving.
So please go, find her.
And bring her back to me.
Alright, listen to me!
We stay here until they're
gone, and then we go.
You understood?
You can't hear?
You can't hear, shit!
I'll take you home, we'll wait here,
until they are gone.
Goddammit!
Enunciate… Remember?
I'm...
...taking you...
...back.
They heard...
...the shot, okay?
No!
You can't do this!
Help me.
Enough! Please, enough!
I'm taking you home.
What home?
You said…your wife…
Hey, don't.
Do not talk about my wife.
You said…
…that you could not do enough.
Now you can.
I found a boat.
Don't go.
I will be right back.
A matter of hours.
But the baby, I don't know how...
I showed you how to do it.
Stay calm.
You have everything you need.
Everything.
Please…
Look…
If I don't go…
Soon you'll be in a lot of pain.
And I won't know…
… I won't lose you too.
Breathe…
I'll be right back.
♪ You make me happy ♪
♪ When skies are Grey ♪
♪ You'll never know, dear ♪
♪ How much I love you ♪
♪ So please don't take ♪
♪ My sunshine away ♪
I'll be right back.
It's okay.
Hey, look at me!
Hey!
Baby! Marcus!
Marcus!
Marcus, wake up!
Oh.
Thank you.
You heard the song?
Figured it out?
She did.
- I thought she was...
- ...figured it out.
Not sure anyone here
can actually believe it.
The most people had finally
given up hope.
In a long time.
How long?
That day.
We got here the same way as you.
We were in this city.
When we heard the hurricane sirens.
Once they knew, they couldn't swim.
The National Guard were told to
start loading people on to boats.
Any boat that they could find.
So as soon as people saw
the first one got out safe,
everyone just started pushing forward.
That's when they started screaming.
They had 12 boats lined
up on the dock that day.
Only two got out.
Anyway, you're here now.
A new day.
And where are you coming from?
Ah, just over the Appalachian Ridge.
And how long did it take?
Just under two days.
That's determination!
It's necessity.
To get out?
No.
To give in.
He said he will do it.
Yes.
He said yes.
I wanted to say...
I'm sorry.
I doubted you.
I was wrong.
And you were right.
I am nothing like him.
You are.
Get inside!
They are everywhere!
Go!
Stay down!
Hey! The doors' locked,
you got a key?
Where is it?
We went too fast.
What if we lost it?
Give me the key.
Jesus Christ, it went back.
- My family.
- No, alright, listen to me.
I have to get back to my family.
♪ Somewhere beyond the sea ♪
♪ Somewhere waiting for me ♪
♪ My lover stands on golden sands ♪
♪ And watches the ships ♪
♪ That go sailing ♪
♪ Somewhere, beyond the sea ♪
♪ She's there watching for me ♪
♪ If I could fly like birds ♪
ON AIR
Subtitled by CLARITY