(All characters, locations, organizations, religions, )
(and incidents in this drama are fictional.)
(Episode 9)
Thanks for the food!
At one point, I wanted to be one of them.
- Here. - Hey, you know what?
You should try the drink.
You might like it.
All right.
You're pretty good for a first-timer.
You know?
I wanted to eat just like them.
And I wanted to fall asleep like them.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Mom! - Mommy!
- Mom! - Dad!
Daddy!
I wanted to have compassion...
and love like them.
But being one of them was impossible.
They always leave.
They always have a place to be...
unlike me.
(Bean Sprout Gukbap Restaurant)
(For Rent)
That's when I realized it.
I had no place to be.
There was no end to this life.
So I could never become one of them.
My job...
is to merely watch them.
So choose.
Choose yourself and the world.
All I can do is watch.
You darn brat! Stop right there!
How do you expect me to stop when you're running after me?
I won't stop.
You little brat.
Hey.
I'm sorry for showing up like this all of a sudden.
Who's here?
Wait for me on the first floor. I'll be right there.
Let me know if you heard that.
I'll be right back.
Here.
If you're leaving because of me, I'll leave.
I'm sorry. That's not it.
Is there something wrong?
He's here. Lee Hyun Kyu.
I'm sorry, but can you wait a bit...
before you come outside?
- I just don't want... - I understand.
I'm sorry.
She didn't have to apologize, but it does feel...
a little weird.
Who told you my address?
I asked around.
Did you think it'd be okay to just come by...
just because someone told you my address?
No.
It seemed like the wrong thing to do.
- Then why did you come? - I couldn't help it.
I missed you.
I came to Korea because I missed you.
And I went to the reunion for the same reason.
I came here to tell you that.
You always do things however you like.
- Hello. - Hey.
You just do everything however you like, don't you?
How could you not tell me that you're leaving to study abroad?
I can't believe you made me come all the way here.
- I'm sorry. - Why didn't you text me back?
Are you really going to break up?
I just felt really sorry.
Then you should've texted me back.
If you felt sorry, you should've met up with me.
I'm really sorry.
You're always like this.
I liked you first, and I like you more than you like me.
You know that. You're totally aware of it.
Forget it.
That's not it. Let me explain.
I may be going abroad to study, but I never said I wanted to end it.
Look at yourself.
You're being selfish again.
I bet you thought I didn't have the guts to break up.
You kept dragging things on,
and we eventually broke up without even talking about it.
I always regretted it.
I was too young back then.
I know how it feels to blindly wait in front of someone's house...
because I've also done it before.
You wonder what you're going to say when you meet them,
but you can't come up with anything.
But even so,
I couldn't help but just wait.
I just waited.
- Ji Na. - But you're not like me.
But then again,
I never got to meet you.
But you did.
You should've shown up like this back then.
You're too late. It's been nine years.
I know. I'm not trying to do anything. I just...
I just wanted to answer your question.
But if you think I'm only complicating things,
just forget about it.
I'm sorry. Don't let it bother you.
I can't.
You'll be on my mind for a while now that I've met you today.
Look at me now.
Even now, I'm sitting right in front of you.
Whenever I'm with you,
it takes me back to the past.
I was always wet.
The day I saw you at the pool and the day I waited in the rain.
Liking you...
felt so wet and damp for me.
Although it might've been soft and fuzzy for you.
I'm not so sure if I want to go back...
to those days.
I still liked everything about you.
Regardless of all that happened,
I still liked you.
Auntie, calm down!
- How do you expect me to calm down? - Sun Kyung, that punk.
Who am I going to blame?
Auntie.
Auntie, stop.
Auntie, wait. Wait.
- Get over here. Come here. - No, wait. Calm down.
I didn't do it on purpose.
Get over here while I'm being nice.
You're not being nice right now.
Auntie.
Auntie. Auntie, are you okay? Auntie.
- I got you. - Auntie.
This isn't fair. That's cheating.
You're the one who cheated first.
No, wait. Let me go.
- My gosh. I'm so exhausted. - Please let go.
Auntie, please!
Sit down.
I don't want to sit on the floor.
He can be very American at times.
He doesn't do it often, but he did it just now.
Let me finally introduce myself, Dong Kyung's boyfriend.
My name is Kang Soo Ja. I'm Dong Kyung's aunt.
Yes, she's my aunt, Kang Soo Ja.
"Boyfriend"?
I heard a lot about you.
You heard a lot about him? From whom?
Sun Kyung, that punk.
I'm sorry for what happened earlier.
I bet you were shocked.
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
By the way, where do you live?
It's very late.
I live...
Yes, she's right. It's really late.
- You should go home. - But you told me to sit down.
It's time for you to get up. Hurry.
What? I know, right? It's such a relief.
You can still take the bus.
You should get going now.
I'd ask you to stay and drink with me.
But as you can see, our family is going through something important.
What? You're okay?
Yes, of course. He says it's fine, Auntie. Wait.
Here. Take this.
Stop that. Get out.
Go.
Call me later.
Bye! Okay!
She's always so unpredictable.
Auntie.
I know how you feel.
So I won't get mad.
"I'll be a burden."
"I'll be a nuisance."
I know that's what you were thinking...
and that's why you didn't call me.
The color is perfect.
I bought it on sale last year. It's perfect.
I'm glad I got it.
You were like that since you were 10.
You walked on eggshells around me...
and acted like a guest.
Why did you bother?
You always did what you wanted.
So why did you bother walking on eggshells?
You create stress for no reason.
How could you not get sick?
Auntie.
How long will you be polite?
Are you a guest who dropped into my life?
Anyway... Why is this hat so big?
Is your head tiny?
I thought it would fit.
I'll give it to Sun Kyung.
Hey. I bought a few summer dresses too.
Do you want to try them on?
I bought one here and there whenever I thought of you...
when I was in Canada.
You have to wear them all.
I need to get my money's worth.
That was my intent when I boarded that plane.
So you have to get your act together.
Don't give this to Sun Kyung. It's mine.
Gosh. You're greedy about clothes just like your mom.
Do you know how much of my stuff she took from me?
That's why I didn't want to take your life from you.
You never took it.
I gave it to you willingly.
Because I wanted to.
(Na Ji Na - Did you get home safely?)
Did you get home safely?
I was too out of it earlier.
(Na Ji Na - Did you get home safely?)
- You're back. - Yes.
- Were you in the shower? - Yes.
You should wash up too.
Okay. Rest up.
Rest up.
(Ms. Soo Ja)
Hello?
Hey.
You know how to answer the phone?
- I know how to hang up too. - Hey.
I'm calling in secret,
so don't make me yell.
What are you doing? Are you home?
Why?
I'm just curious. You always slept with me.
You're hesitant only with certain words.
Otherwise, you're so free with your words.
Do I? Anyway...
Yes.
Is that all you can say?
Darn it.
Your aunt looks a lot like your mom.
They don't just look alike. They look the same.
They're twins.
I feel like I'm looking at my mom when I see my aunt.
I'd always look at her...
and think that was what my mom probably looked like.
I always thought that, but it was all I could do.
But seeing her in person, I realized they were different.
Thanks.
I didn't get to say that.
Thank you for letting me see my mom and dad.
Sure.
And I'll think hard about my wish...
for myself.
Okay.
Is that all you can say?
I can say, "Good night," too.
Good night.
This so new and awkward,
doing this over the phone.
- Bye. - Wait.
What?
You said you'd do pretty much anything for me, right?
So I was thinking...
May I ask you for a favor?
A new drug was confirmed to be safe...
and is currently in clinical trials,
and they're looking for more volunteers.
Her name is on the list,
so we're waiting to hear back.
When can we begin treatment?
We need to wait for the blood work,
so it'll take about two weeks.
If she qualifies,
she'll have to come in periodically.
See?
Let's relax and wait patiently.
Are you sure...
she doesn't need to be hospitalized right away?
Yes, I am.
You're saying there's hope, right?
Can she live?
Yes, I'm in the process of saving her.
Didn't you say yesterday that your boyfriend is a doctor too?
- Where does he work? - Him?
He works...
in the US. He's an American doctor.
I see. He's in the US.
That's why you said at times that he was American.
Yes, that's right.
Although your boyfriend is...
very slightly less attractive...
than your doctor...
He's less attractive?
Who cares about his looks?
As long as he's a good person.
Sun Kyung told me that he's a very nice guy.
But you know, I wouldn't say...
he's ugly or anything like that.
My gosh. You're totally into him.
Then, let me go, pick my Canadian husband,
and drop him off at a hotel.
Meanwhile, you can hang out with your American boyfriend.
Gosh. You guys didn't have to come back to Korea.
Don't you know how much Kevin adores you guys?
Don't say stuff like that. Kevin will be disappointed.
I could barely stop him from buying a house in Seoul,
so we could all live together.
I'll be back. I won't be gone for long.
Okay.
- I want my cell phone. - I see.
Gosh.
- All good? - Yes.
- Bye. - Where are you going?
You said you're all good.
I'm all good with the phone. And I'm not done with you yet.
Here.
- What's this? - It's a cell phone.
You've never seen one before?
- No. I saw it yesterday. - Gosh.
Come on. Take it already.
No. I'm asking you why I need this.
There might be another incident similar to yesterday's again. Okay?
I have a plan. Okay?
Or were you excited that we talked on the phone before going to sleep?
Well, that's partially true.
Who's paying for this?
That brings me to my next question. What's your bank account number?
Or tell me your card number.
Is this phone even working?
Goodness.
Here.
(Human)
(Dong Kyung)
I didn't include our last names because full names sound distant.
All right. We have each other's numbers.
What should we do next?
(Human)
What are you doing?
Answer it.
Are you free?
Isn't this the next step after getting a girl's number?
What if I'm free?
Let's hang out.
What's this? Why are we here?
What is it? Is this a present for me?
- No, that's your work. - Work?
You've gotten materialistic lately. Do you want a present from me?
Gosh.
Grandma. Then, my teacher isn't coming?
I heard that there's no boat coming to the island.
I don't think your teacher will make it today.
Then, I can't have my graduation ceremony?
You and I will have your graduation ceremony together.
You already have your diploma right here.
I want to get the diploma from my teacher.
- Sir. - Sir.
My gosh. I thought you wouldn't be able to make it.
I ought to come today. It's the school's last graduation.
Who are you?
What?
Well...
She came from Seoul to take photos today.
From Seoul? She flew here?
Yes.
I'm here to take photos.
All right. Here it goes.
In 1, 2.
(Diploma)
Then, this school will disappear?
There won't be any students coming to the school anymore.
And there aren't any teachers who would teach here.
Where's the real teacher?
He's probably headed somewhere.
- Where? Is he having a dream? - No.
He's headed to the opposite direction of life.
By now,
he could have arrived at the garden.
You know, that girl?
The girl at the garden.
I've seen her at the hospital too.
She was wearing a patient gown that time.
She's sick.
She is?
She's always sick.
She's always born sick, suffers in pain, and dies.
And she's reborn again just to go through the same pain.
Then, she dies again.
That's how she maintains the world.
She suffers in pain for all the sins in the world and dies.
That's the duty of a deity.
I saw her repeat that many times for a long time.
I thought I had the most miserable life.
My pain was nothing compared to hers.
If there was nothing in the world from the beginning,
would the world be a peaceful place?
If nothing ever happened in the world.
Don't move.
What? Why?
You didn't move for a second. And during that one second,
nothing in the world was destroyed.
It was the world you wanted.
It's odd, isn't it?
During that one second,
my time stood still.
(Kang Soo Ah)
You're still beautiful.
I'm the only one aging.
You're the one who should address me as the elder sister now.
Soo Ah.
I know you miss her,
but please be patient a bit longer.
Just a bit longer.
Let her stay here a bit longer.
I'm talking about Dong Kyung.
One thing I learned in life is...
that we can't use the word, "forever", for something...
that is still happening.
Loving someone forever is nearly impossible.
But losing someone forever is possible.
But we always live for things that don't last forever.
For example, dreams are one of them.
Two cups of latte are ready.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- This is good. - Really?
Or things like memories or regrets.
("Second First Love", Lee Hyun Kyu)
(Lee Hyun)
Or some live for love or other people.
(Human)
The Korean words, "human", and "love", look similar.
I shouldn't have given you such a name.
Come out. I want to do something with you.
Why am I here?
- I've made up my mind today. - For what?
I'm determined to spend money today.
I've never done this in my life.
So I need you.
Why do you need me?
I want you to watch me splurge.
Make it fun for me.
Give me everything...
from here to here.
You want all this?
Yes. In 270mm.
Then just up to here.
People only have two feet. Is it necessary to buy this many?
It's one for every season.
Sun Kyung's shoes wear out very easily.
There's our next stop.
Do you know what gift writers don't like to receive...
but end up receiving the most?
- What is it? - Fountain pens.
People think writers will need them,
but they rarely use them nowadays.
But they're too pretty and expensive to throw away.
So they just end up keeping them somewhere.
Then why are you buying one?
Because she's the type who lingers on the stuff she hates...
rather than what she likes.
She'll never be able to forget it.
I'd like to take a look at this one.
I'm sorry.
But we only have one left.
Can I please take it?
I waited three months for this.
I...
only have three months left.
I'm...
terminally ill.
So...
before I die,
I want to buy something for my aunt.
Stay strong.
Thank you.
Nice.
I've never shopped like this in my entire life.
I guess this is why people work so hard.
- Who's next? - "Next"?
The next person is me.
I'm going to press on this to take a photo.
I know you don't want to do this, but try to smile.
It's not that I don't want to do it.
But what's the purpose?
- What? - To look at it from time to time?
Then shouldn't I be the only one in the photo?
Humans are really weird.
Why make things like that?
You never get to see them yourself.
It's for others, not me.
I'm like that sometimes.
Who knows? I might not be the person looking at it later on.
Just do it. I'm going to take the photo now.
Smile.
Here we go.
When are you going to give everyone these gifts?
What? I don't know.
Maybe later. When I want to give it to them.
Hey, give me your cell phone.
Can't you see my hands are full?
- What are you doing? - Just wait.
Ta-da.
- Hey. - Your hands are full.
So just stay still.
See you.
Dong Kyung.
Just let it slide already.
Do we really have to fight over something like this?
As you already know, I can be pretty feisty.
I'll see you later.
Oh, later...
What? Later? When?
Hey.
What is this? Am I dreaming?
Yes.
I guess it is a dream.
You'd never take me to a place like this in real life.
What's that supposed to mean?
You said you never eat or sleep.
I'm eating and sleeping right now just for you.
Will I be able to taste everything even if it's a dream?
I won't gain weight since it's a dream, right?
- Are you happy? - No.
It'd be better if we could do this in real life.
There are some things that are only possible here.
What?
I'm sorry.
Sorry we're late.
Ji Na is such a rough driver.
Hey, shut it.
I guess I should've left you behind.
It's my treat today. Eat as much as you want.
- Thank you. - Enjoy.
What's gotten into you?
Hey, stop eating and ask for water.
- Sun Kyung, eat up. - Okay.
Eat up, kiddo.
This is delicious.
Good morning.
Hey, you're awake. Come and eat.
I called them over so they could eat with us.
Why didn't you tell me your aunt came?
So I told her instead.
Right.
Come and sit down.
Okay.
- Ta-da. - My gosh.
I haven't had a homemade meal in so long.
When did you cook all this?
This is your favorite.
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for the food.
- Thank you, Auntie. - Enjoy.
I'm getting changed.
You can talk from there.
I'm sorry I never listened to you.
I'll listen from now on.
This isn't a truce.
I'm surrendering to you.
Why?
Are you going to try and become a nice kid?
I'll give it a try.
I'll try to prevent what you're worried about from happening.
What is it that I'm worried about?
She won't abandon the world.
I'll make sure she doesn't.
That's what I want.
Also,
I've always wanted to say this.
I always felt sorry for you.
I pitied you more than I resented you.
Thanks for letting me be born.
I've been...
feeling that recently.
What do you mean, she won't renew her contract?
Tell me what you mean.
It's as I said.
She won't work with this company...
unless Dong Kyung is her editor.
Give me a break.
Tell her to kiss off.
Why is she so arrogant when she's not even popular?
Fire Lee Hyun. Hey!
Go and make it clear.
"You're not rejecting us, I'm rejecting you. Me."
That rude brat.
- Dalgona won't work with us either. - What? Why not?
Siberia and Jung Dang Myun too.
What? Why?
Same for Young Prince, whom she barely signed recently.
What? No... We can't lose him.
He's our top 10!
Did you hear them?
Mr. Cha. Do something.
You'll do something, right?
Like what?
Either bring the writers or bring Dong Kyung.
- Why should I? - What?
You should take responsibility for something this important.
What?
Are you saying I created this mess, so I should clean it up?
No. I'm saying the CEO should take responsibility...
for something this important.
At least you know you created this mess.
I thought you didn't know.
Call Dong Kyung right now.
Answer me.
You call her.
She's screening my calls...
Hey, kid. What did you just say?
Do you see a kid in here?
I assume the meeting is over, so we'll go now.
We kids have too much work piled up.
How dare he talk to the CEO like that?
(Na Ji Na - Isn't it too sudden?)
(Absolute obedience. Wait.)
(Can you come right now? I'm stuck.)
(Did you get home safely? I was too out of it earlier.)
To be honest, I didn't expect the writers to do that.
I know. I expected that from one writer, but...
Lee Hyun?
Did you get home safely?
I was too out of it earlier.
Mr. Cha, how do you know Lee Hyun?
What?
What is wrong with you today?
During the meeting too.
- What? - You've been checked out.
Where are you? Are you somewhere nice?
It's not that nice.
How do you know Lee Hyun?
Well...
I filled in for Dong Kyung once at a meeting.
- Where are you going? - I'm cutting.
- Enjoy. - Thank you.
Did you sober up?
I've never been drunk in my entire life.
I've been fine all morning.
Is that why you called me "bro" and were informal with me?
I'm sorry, sir. I think I was drunk.
My tolerance is three shots of soju.
Thanks.
For what?
For having a low tolerance?
Just something.
Oh. Hi.
- Let's talk. - What would you like?
I said let's talk.
Your CEO is at a table behind you.
Hyun Kyu.
(Push)
Look at this punk.
Do you think I put you here so you can play all day?
I have to go. The building owner just came in.
I'll call you back later.
Didn't you hear your dad?
Why are you here?
Mr. Cha.
Dad?
Father.
Come on, Father.
You should've told me you were coming.
Whom did you come with? Did you come alone?
Come on.
Hey.
Where are you rushing off to?
Come on, Father. Don't be like that...
What is wrong with you?
He suddenly showed up at my door.
Oh my gosh. Hyun Kyu?
Was he always that aggressive?
Time changes people.
That's not the point. Who told him where I live?
It wasn't me.
Who else came over besides you?
You said you wanted to talk.
Yes.
Go on.
Let's talk upstairs.
Do you know Na Ji Na?
Yes.
Is that all?
Let's talk upstairs.
I have to go somewhere.
(Fill line. Quality may decrease if you cross this line.)
(Mr. Cha Joo Ik)
(Did you leave your umbrella?)
(Incoming Call)
- Hello? - Where are you?
- Who... - It's me, Hyun Kyu.
How did you get my number?
I'll explain when I see you. Let's meet right now.
Right now?
- I'm not home. - Where are you?
I'm at the laundromat by my apartment.
- What are you doing? - Are you seeing anyone?
- What? - Are you seeing anyone?
- No. - Or are there any guys you like?
Even if there are, date me.
I don't care who that guy is. We met first.
I liked you first.
And...
I still like you.
We must put up with a lot of hassles now that we don't live together.
Right.
That should do it. Bye.
What? You don't want to let go of my hand?
If...
What if...
I wanted to live?
Can you grant me that wish?
No.
I can't do that. My job is to destroy.
I see.
I knew it.
I just wanted to ask.
You heard it, didn't you?
What everyone was thinking in their heads, right?
It might look like...
they are all smiling at me.
But...
they are hurting inside, right?
As much as me.
Or more.
Yes.
What about you?
What goes in your head when you look at me?
You think I can't see that?
You keep...
You keep hinting at me that I should live...
when I only see death in your eyes.
How do you think I feel when I see that?
You can do what you had in mind from the beginning.
It's simple as that.
Bye.
Its flowers were beautiful back in the day.
I don't see any flowers these days.
It's dying.
Just like us.
Both you and I are dying too.
That's what it means to live.
Goodness.
I thought the flowers would always be around.
What a shame now that I can't see them anymore.
Its flowers were so beautiful.
What goes in your head when you look at me?
I thought I would be able to watch people disappear...
to the end of time.
Eating,
sleeping,
feeling compassionate, falling in love,
and having a place to go...
Is this how it feels to be human?
Dissipating from the world didn't scare me.
But not being able to see you anymore scared me.
Like a fool, I just realized...
that I don't have much time left.
What's wrong? What happened?
I love you.
I am...
in love with you.
(Doom at Your Service)
I decided to date him.
Do you still feel lonely and alone?
No. You're back.
Hey, don't look at me like that.
He's been scowling at us.
You were like a puppy protecting his owner.
You glared like this.
I told Ji Na.
Don't answer it.
I need to talk to you.
Be madly in love and live.
I want to make a birthday wish.
Will you marry me?