(All characters, places, institutions, incidents,)
(and organizations portrayed in this drama are fictitious.)
Goodness, I'm coming.
- Darn you. - Shut it.
(4 years ago)
Is it the dirtbag in Incheon?
I'll go with you.
Go away, punk. You're so annoying.
What are you going to do all by yourself?
Don't you know that the award ceremony is tomorrow?
And it's been 1 year since I joined Crime Investigation Team 1.
I'm your partner.
Partner, my foot. Give me a break.
Go away.
I'll show you...
that I deserve to be called your partner.
Gosh, seriously.
Stop, you jerk!
- Hey! - Stop right there!
I told you not to follow me!
- Darn it! - Gosh.
Gosh.
Darn it.
Step back.
Darn it. Where did he go?
No!
Chul Jin!
That crazy scum!
Let go!
Let go of me, you jerk!
Chul Jin!
I said, let go of me, you jerk!
I'll never let you go!
Dong Man!
Over there!
I'm sorry that I left you behind...
when I'm your partner.
You don't have to be sorry.
Now that I have a stab wound,
it's kind of cool,
but it was really scary.
How will I ever go after a suspect alone at night?
You will never go out alone, you punk.
From now,
I'll always be behind you,
so don't be scared.
Darn it.
My gosh.
Dong Man.
The print on this laptop...
wasn't found on this remote control you brought...
but on this plastic cup.
Professor Yu.
I can't stop working on this case.
No. I won't.
You said the culprit is here.
How did you...
I must...
catch the culprit at all costs.
So that...
I can protect...
the people I love.
I've made up my mind,
so you should decide.
I must...
see the end of this case.
Dong Man.
("Defensive Tactics")
It looks like he's back, but...
Where is Sun Ho? Is he at the library to save our seats?
Everyone is there because our finals started.
Who are you? Do you know me?
I'm here to see my friend, Sun Ho.
- Please leave. - I'm leaving!
- Go! - Come on!
Sun Ho!
Hi.
Wait. That seat is reserved.
Sorry.
Where did he go to have it out with the professor?
(Stir-fried Cartilage, Boneless Chicken Feet)
Why are you drinking so much? Do you want to get drunk?
My gosh.
You go first.
Sorry?
Go ahead and explain why you think...
he's the culprit.
What? What are you talking about? Are you calling me the culprit?
I finished analyzing Chul Jin's communications data.
What?
When a burner phone that picked up a signal...
from a cell site near our school...
called Chul Jin's phone,
Chul Jin's phone picked up a signal...
from the same cell site a few hours later.
Several times, at that.
Gosh.
- So? - That means the owner...
of the burner phone called him, and he came to the school.
The calls, travel route, and the same cell site.
I kept seeing the same pattern.
What nonsense are you spewing, you punk?
Hey! This is unbelievable.
Are you certain of the causality?
Are you sure that's all there is?
Wasn't there a case where I called him,
and he came over to the school?
Your speculation lacks basis.
But that doesn't mean that it's not true.
Why did you come to our school...
when Professor Yu didn't call you?
Why is this jerk... He keeps talking nonsense.
Dong Man, it's not me.
Why would I do something like that?
Shut your mouth and follow me.
Why that little...
Dong Man, you don't believe a word he's blabbering, do you?
Dong Man. Say something!
Why did you touch Sun Ho's laptop?
Dong Man.
Are you talking about the laptop on his desk?
I just took a look because I got curious.
What about you?
Why did you dig up on my communications data?
What are you accusing me of?
We don't know if you were injured...
while carrying out a sting operation...
or if you're just putting on a show...
because you're working for those jerks.
Are you serious?
We don't know if you touched his laptop...
to dig something up from it or not!
Is that really what you think?
I've been working as your partner for six years,
and I even got stabbed!
That's why I know you well.
I know the face you make when you lie.
Just go, Chul Jin.
Sir, can you make a U-turn?
Do I make a U-turn or not?
Mr. Park Chul Jin.
You were in my car last time too.
I can't do this.
I want to stop here.
This is too much.
Seriously.
Sir, please stop the car.
I can see that you remember it.
He will call you.
(Korean National Police University)
You're almost done with submitting the exam papers, right?
Yes, except for the Investigation Studies.
I see.
Professor Yu, you must upload them to the cloud by tomorrow night.
Professor Yu?
- What? - The exam papers.
Oh, right. I got it.
Okay then. Let's wrap it up here.
- Okay. - Good job, everyone.
Do you want to go for a drive after submitting them tomorrow?
Where to?
You know. Misa-ri or Yangsu-ri.
Anywhere that ends with "ri".
Why would you go to such places?
It's dark, the roads are narrow, and accidents occur there a lot.
That's why we're going there.
It's dark and narrow, and I'm hoping for some accidents there.
What happened? Did he just turn me down?
Gosh, the deadly exams are coming up.
I've already messed up my mid-terms,
so I'm dead if I mess it up again in the finals.
Right, you're dead already.
No, it's not.
How is it going with studying? You want to grab some coffee?
Here you go.
So... Did you make up with Professor Yu?
Not yet. I think he needs more time.
But I'm sure he'll be fine soon.
From what I know, he's always like that.
I thought you were just investigating together,
but I guess you guys got close too.
We always fight.
That means you guys are close.
If not, why would you even fight? You'd just ignore each other.
So when are you going to tell me...
about that investigation you're doing with him?
Well...
We haven't had it out yet.
- I'm sorry. - What's there to be?
I'm going to have it out with you after him.
It's about time we have it out and decide what we are.
Hey, I'm not asking because I want to have it out with you.
I was curious since it seemed like it's related to my mom.
What? Why are you smiling now?
I don't have time for this.
Let's go. I'll finish it off.
You don't have time for this? Hey, Sun Ho!
(Investigation Studies Exam)
Sir, are you available now?
Gosh.
Goodness.
Since when did you know about it?
That the culprit is in the Police University.
After the sports festival.
I heard you talking with Mr. Park.
You punk. Why would you eavesdrop on grown-ups' talking?
Why didn't you tell me about it?
I wasn't so sure about it.
It could've just confused the investigation.
But still, we got the bug.
Isn't it clear enough?
Nothing is ever clear enough.
You've never done a proper investigation.
We first went after the illegal gambling gang.
Whether they are in the Police University or not,
they are close to us. That's a fact.
If Chul Jin is the culprit,
don't you think we should investigate...
how deep he is involved in,
and who is hiding behind him?
So that means you're going to do it right.
You won't back off no matter what, right?
Didn't you hear anything?
Of course I won't back off.
What do you want me to say?
You can't avoid it even if you want to.
Nothing will change if I stop.
I should at least keep going to get something out of it, right?
I don't know what's at the end of this investigation,
but we'll see when we get there.
I'll stop him from doing anything.
I'll do whatever I can...
to stop him from investigating.
I'll get it done this time.
If you give me one last chance...
(Professor's Office)
(Professor Yu Dong Man)
Why did I choose to become a police officer?
Tell me about it. If we mess up the exams...
and fail to graduate,
we won't be able to become one anyway.
Gosh, study more instead of worrying about it.
- I can't focus on studying. - Guys.
You know what this is?
- What is this? - What's that?
- Goodness! - Why?
You all know the legendary graduate...
who got straight-A in every class for four years.
The one at the headquarters now, so-called the next commissioner.
- Of course I know. - This is...
These are the sample questions that he used to study.
- Gosh. - Goodness.
- How much for a page? - Give your price first.
There won't be any negotiations, right?
Guys, we're at the Police University.
If you get into something speculative...
- Fried chicken. - Okay, fried chicken.
And pizza.
- Pizza? - And beer.
Beer?
I'm not in.
- Are you sure? - Yes, I'll be off.
- And the blind date. - Really? Blind date?
And the blind date expenses.
- Are you sure? - Yes, totally.
Stop staring at me and read your book, will you?
Okay.
Right, did the talk with your professor go well?
I did talk to him but...
Sorry.
Just until the exams are over.
After that,
you'll have to tell me everything.
Okay, I will.
Try to focus again.
Okay.
Hey, Min Kyu. Did you see this?
Give it back when you're done.
Mr. Park Chul Jin seemed to have regained his memory.
You didn't know?
(Chul Jin)
(Professor Baek)
- Hello? - Professor Yu.
I got a report from a student.
It says that the sample questions going around the students...
seem to be the exam paper for Investigation Studies.
Professor Yu, is it true?
Is it the exam paper?
Yes, it is. How did this get out?
The exam for Investigation Studies hasn't been uploaded yet though.
Did you print a copy of it by any chance?
Yes, I printed a copy last night to do a final check.
Then do you remember if anyone visited your office...
after you finished writing all the exam questions?
First, let's check the CCTV footage from the camera in the hallway.
Okay.
Yes, Mr. Hyun.
Professor Yu, can I have a word with you?
The old exam questions you were looking at this morning?
Yes. Apparently, they were for our Investigation Studies exam.
I guess they were leaked somehow.
Where's Professor Yu?
It's been reported to Asan Police Station as well.
They called and said their officers are on their way now.
I see.
Let me ask you again.
After you completed writing all the exam questions,
did anyone visit your office that night?
One of my students stopped by.
Was it Kang Sun Ho again?
Yes.
It was Sun Ho.
But we just talked. And until he left my office,
I was there with him the whole time.
The CCTV footage will prove it.
The laptop you submitted for fingerprint analysis...
is also his, isn't it?
You're not getting Sun Ho...
involved in your private matter, are you?
I hope that is not the case, Professor Yu.
You may return to your office.
Yes, sir.
You're not getting Sun Ho...
involved in your private matter, are you?
I hope that is not the case, Professor Yu.
Gosh, I have a headache now.
What is this?
What in the world...
Professor Yu Dong Man, we're from Asan Police Station.
- What's that behind you? - Nothing.
What is this?
Professor...
Professor.
Professor. Wait.
Say something! Please?
This can't be true.
- Professor! - Just a moment.
Professor Yu can get in my car. We'll follow you.
But we were told to arrest him immediately.
You don't have solid evidence yet,
so it's unnecessary to do this in front of the students.
From the tone of my voice, I'm sure you can tell...
that I'll take issue with this if this conversation drags on.
And from the look on my face, you can tell...
that I want to wrap up this talk if you got my point.
You know where Asan Police Station is, right?
(Stop)
You didn't have to do this.
I said we should go for a drive.
Although it's not dark yet, and we're driving on a wide road.
But there has been an accident indeed.
A case, not an accident.
It is an accident.
An accident that was sprung on you out of the blue.
Did this happen because I didn't step on the brakes?
I wonder if this was done to stop me...
because I wasn't going to stop.
(Korean National Police University)
I'm not sure if this is an appropriate analogy,
but there's a day I regret the most in my whole life.
That day, I had an awful dream.
So I told my husband to skip work for just one day...
and go to the beach somewhere with me.
But he was adamant about going to work no matter what I said.
He was like that. Regardless of what I said,
he remained stubborn and did everything his way.
If I knew we'd never be able to go to the sea again,
I should've stopped him at all costs.
I should've done everything I could to stop him.
I should've done something at least.
I regret it every day.
You need to stay alive...
to forgive and make up.
Don't you think so?
[VIU Ver] KBS E08 'Police University'
"The Culprit"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
(Lee Ju Won)
He can't deny it.
They even found an envelope of money in his office.
But I find it suspicious.
They found the evidence too easily. It's strange.
That's true.
He was once called a legend of Investigation Studies.
I don't think he'd have been this sloppy.
Exactly.
He doesn't seem like the type to receive bribes either.
- Right? - You never know.
He'll either be dismissed or fired.
Do you think they'll fire him?
So that means you're going to do it right.
You won't back off no matter what, right?
Of course I won't back off.
What do you want me to say?
Hello.
Sun Ho.
All right. Thank you.
They're starting his investigation now.
Why won't they let us see the surveillance camera footage?
Take a careful look.
Someone turned the surveillance camera,
so it caught nothing.
Tell me about it.
Seeing how he knows the angle, it must be someone from inside.
Who's your accomplice?
Whether it's a student or not, you must've done this...
so that it wouldn't catch you accepting the 10,000 dollar bribe.
Someone from inside.
Professor Yu, why don't you just confess?
They're analyzing the footage now,
and the arrest warrant will be issued soon.
Dong Man!
Gosh, why are you here? This is humiliating.
You brat!
You know this is humiliating, don't you?
I know you're a nutjob,
but you wouldn't do something so low.
You punks!
I know, right? Why is he doing this?
What did you say?
If he wanted to frame me, then he should've done a better job.
You know who did it, don't you?
Who is it? What's this about?
Did he do this to stop me from investigating any further?
Tell me what this is about. It's frustrating.
Captain, I have a favor to ask.
Here, have some tea.
The night before the exam paper was leaked,
you were with Professor Yu in his office, right?
Yes, I went to talk to him for a second.
May I ask what it was about?
I was stuck while studying Investigation Studies,
so I wanted to ask him.
Just this month alone,
you visited Professor Yu's office more than ten times.
Were you there to ask questions on Investigation Studies?
You shouldn't make that face when the police ask you a question.
Let me see.
He was arrested without a warrant,
so Professor Yu will be detained...
for about 36 hours.
If you want to prove his innocence before he's cornered,
you'll need to hurry.
You may leave.
Yes, sir.
(Forensic Science Room)
You are behind this, aren't you?
Just go and study for your exams.
I'll make sure...
to find evidence on you.
I'd love to see you try.
Although I'm not sure if a greenhorn like you is capable of doing that.
Sun Ho!
It's really strange though.
Why did the culprit share the paper when he could've had it for himself?
The police are investigating it,
so wouldn't they find it strange too?
An envelope of money was found during their investigation,
so they'll investigate based on the evidence,
not the circumstance.
Then they'll miss the golden time.
Still, I think the police...
will find a suspect from the students first.
I think so too.
And that'd be me.
What?
What? It's you?
I went to see Professor Yu...
in his office the night before.
What?
But still, you didn't leak the paper.
Of course he didn't.
Professor Yu didn't do it either. He's being framed.
I must catch the culprit.
Speaking of which,
can you guys help me?
Never mind. It's exam week.
I'll get going.
Kang Sun Ho!
What do you think you're doing?
Of course we must help you when you're in trouble.
Exams? They're not important at all!
He's right. Sun Ho, I might not be of much help,
but I...
want to help you too.
You would've done the same if this happened to me.
That's right, brother. Don't underestimate us.
We're friends, after all.
You guys...
Hey, don't get emotional. We're running out of time.
You're right.
Don't get emotional. We're running out of time.
What shall we start with?
It looks like the kids from our year bought the leaked paper.
Then Bum Tae and Jun Wook, you should start with questioning.
Question those who didn't buy the paper like I did,
or those who borrowed it.
And those who didn't buy it when they're likely to do so.
Let's narrow down suspects by questioning them.
Also, find out Dong Gu's alibi since he sold the paper.
- Roger that. - Roger that.
What about us?
We must go to the crime site first.
Evidence and clues are always left at the scene.
Let's go.
They haven't caught the culprit when there's a camera right here?
We'll know who did it if we can watch the footage even just once.
Then let's see if we can do that.
No.
Those at Asan Police Station believe that this case...
could have been an inside job,
so even the professors aren't allowed to access it.
Then can we take a quick look at it here?
Goodness. I already said no.
Get out.
We're asking because I think I saw someone...
fiddling with the CCTV camera in front of Professor Yu's office.
You saw it?
Was it a man or a woman?
That I don't know. It was too dark.
Get out. Go.
- Please... - Go, get out.
(Situation Room)
That sure is your specialty.
I'm impressed.
The other guys must've finished their job by now. Let's go.
Can you let go?
Right.
Shall we?
- Let's go. - Okay.
(Exam Leak Case, Park Dong Gu)
Dong Gu got his hands on the exam paper...
on Monday, around midnight.
He found it on top of the printer in the Residence Hall.
According to him, that was when he printed copies of it.
There are seven students who didn't buy those copies.
Dong Gu, the seller, Kang Hee, Jae Kyung,
Sun Ho, Min Kyu,
Sung Soo, and Hae Ju.
Wait.
Cha Sung Soo and An Hae Ju didn't buy it?
Right?
Those two, of all people,
must have bought it.
What's more shocking is that...
over 80 percent of the students bought the copy.
That's right.
Park Dong Gu should become a salesman, not a cop.
So we have two suspects.
I'll talk with Hae Ju.
Jun Wook and Bum Tae, you two talk with Sung Soo.
I'll see if we can get our hands on the CCTV footage somehow.
(To be continued)
We'll be able to save...
Professor Yu, right?
Mr. Yu, are you going to keep up this uncooperative attitude?
Mr. Yu Dong Man!
Goodness.
(Forensic Science Room)
I talked to An Hae Ju.
She said the one who left the print room before her...
was wearing a neon watch.
Check Cha Sung Soo's watch.
If it's a neon-colored watch, he's the one who found it first.
(Investigation Task Force, 4 Members)
It's exam time. Shouldn't you be studying?
I have somewhere to be.
Let's talk another time.
What about me?
"Another time", again?
I...
like you.
I don't expect you to give me your answer now.
I'm just telling you how I feel.
Okay, I see.
Then let's talk another time.
(The 41st Chungram Sports Festival)
(Women's Residence Hall)
Okay.
Let's just talk now.
Min Kyu, there's someone I like.
I can't afford to worry about how upset you are...
because I'm so worried about him right now.
Who is that?
Is it Kang Sun Ho?
I have to go.
You'd like to see the CCTV footage?
Yes. I know that I'm not allowed to view it,
but I figured you probably can access it.
That's a lot to ask.
Right, I apologize.
I'm aware that it's a lot to ask, but I wanted to give it a shot.
Why is that?
Because trying is better...
than not trying at all.
There are times when doing nothing is better for your own sake.
I've got nothing to lose,
and nothing will change if I stand still and do nothing.
When you're investigating a case,
you must keep pushing forward to find clues.
That's what Professor Yu taught me.
I'm worried you'd trip and fall if you kept pushing forward.
But that's not a failure.
Wouldn't it be a process to learn to walk straight?
I still remember what you told us...
when we went to the shooting range for the first time.
You said we as police officers must pick up guns...
to protect and save lives, not to kill.
Would you hand me a bullet,
so I can protect Professor Yu?
At three o'clock. A neon watch, confirmed.
At eight o'clock. Also confirmed.
What are you guys doing?
No matter the angle,
it is indisputably neon.
What?
I heard the CCTV footage shows...
the person who first found the exam paper.
Hey, what do you mean? There are no cameras there...
So it was you.
Cha Sung Soo.
You may refuse to give an incriminating statement.
Don't move!
You'll be given a chance to explain yourself...
and have the right to an attorney.
You may request the court to review the legality of this arrest...
- That's not right. - What?
Take it up with the Leadership Room, not the court.
- Stay still. - Let me go, you crazy jerks.
Hey, you'll break my arms!
(Forensic Science Room)
- Hey, Bum Tae. - Sung Soo found it first.
But someone was in the print room before he got there.
What?
Can we talk?
If you've got something to say, just say it and leave.
I told you.
I will find evidence to prove...
that you did it.
I have Cha Sung Soo's statement...
that he ran into you in the print room...
the night the exam paper got leaked.
Such statements or circumstantial clues...
cannot serve as admissible evidence.
Which is why I'm planning to secure physical evidence as well.
So that...
I can save Professor Yu,
your supervisor.
I'm going to save him.
Do you...
really think saving Dong Man from this case...
is a good thing for him?
This time, it was only an exam paper.
Aren't you scared that something worse...
might happen to him next?
No, I'm not scared.
That must be exactly...
what they want.
Us getting scared because of this incident...
and stepping back...
so that...
we stop investigating any further.
Both Professor Yu and I...
will never give those jerks what they want.
Are you sure...
you can handle this?
Do you think you can...
stay next to Dong Man until the end without running away?
Yes.
He's better than me.
Have you checked on it, Captain?
Chul Jin did withdraw 10,000 dollars.
What on earth is going on?
Did he get blackmailed or something?
Okay, Captain. I'll call you again.
Can I make another call?
Hello?
It's me.
Goodness, we have all the witness statements,
but we don't have the final blow.
That hurt.
Where did Sun Ho go?
Let's find the last piece of evidence.
- What is that? - What is it?
- What is that? - What is that?
Did you find anything?
Yes.
I have something to report.
Pause it.
What? Only his hand was caught.
Wait. I'm sure it's a man's hand.
The culprit is a male.
I don't think we'll be able to tell who turned the camera.
What are you doing?
I can see something!
We got him!
Hey, but isn't he...
the new professor?
He is. It's Professor Park Chul Jin.
Let's go.
Did he get blackmailed or something?
Sir.
- All right. - Let's go.
There are only two.
No!
It still hurts on rainy days.
And I still turn around in panic mode,
thinking someone might attack me from behind.
- So please... - I'll never let you go!
Chul Jin!
Dong Man!
Don't leave me alone.
I'll show you...
that I deserve to be called your partner.
My gut feeling tells me that this case is dangerous.
I was appointed as a professor at Korean National Police University.
- What? - Chul Jin asked for it,
saying he wants to work by your side.
From now, I'll always be behind you,
so don't be scared.
You will never give up, will you?
You'll never give up...
on going after those jerks, will you?
Let's...
start with the report.
Are you serious?
I got the permission slip to go out from Professor Seo.
The taxi is here. Let's hurry.
Hello. This is Seo Sang Hak.
What did you say?
An exam paper was leaked right before the exam...
at Korean National Police University.
The cradle of justice, Korean National Police University.
KCS will report thorough coverage on the corruption case...
that overshadows the school's philosophy.
It hasn't been a year since Professor Yu...
was appointed to this school,
but he leaked an exam paper of the subject he's teaching.
According to the Asan Police Station,
Yu denied all charges at first,
but he ended up admitting them during the investigation.
Why did he admit them all of a sudden?
He didn't do it.
Sir, could you speed up a little?
Sure.
The police are suspecting him of solicitation,
and they will investigate further...
to find the illegal dealings made.
This is Im Hyun Seok of KCS.
It's still under investigation, so we're not sure...
There's nothing we can say.
- I'm sorry. - That's...
Where is Mr. Park Chul Jin?
Who gave you the money?
I have no idea.
I heard I'd get paid in cash if I handed over the exam paper.
I thought you wanted us to start writing a report.
What is this?
Gosh.
(Friendly police of the citizens)
What are you talking about?
Hello?
It's me.
I was wondering if you were doing okay.
Seeing how you picked up, I guess you're fine.
- That's all I needed to know. - Dong Man.
How can you worry about me...
in this situation?
I told you that I'll protect you.
That darn promise.
I'm finally keeping my word, you punk.
I was the one...
who leaked the exam paper.
Hey, what are you doing?
You should've been the one to cuff me.
Hey, Park Chul Jin!
I was just trying to make some money on the side...
but ended up coming this far.
Hey, you idiot!
You should have given up when you found the bug.
What was the point of me acting like I lost my memory?
You just wouldn't step on the brakes.
You jerk! Shut your mouth!
Senior Inspector Yu Dong Man.
My supervisor.
You no longer need to have my back.
You crazy idiot!
(Police University)
I didn't come here to learn from someone like Yu Dong Man.
Who sent a tip to the news?
If you did it because of me, don't do it ever again.
- How dare he touch her? - She smiled.
Don't smile!
So you didn't do it?
If this turns out to be a lie, I will cut all ties with you.
I want to investigate the case with you.
And I like you, Kang Sun Ho.
What you saw and learned isn't a proper way to do things,
- so forget all about it. - No, I don't want to.
I went through hoops to learn them. Why should I forget them?
Okay, fine.
The burner phone is on.
It was you?