fTiming and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ No longer panicking on the night of the blackout ♫
♫ You're by my side, illuminating a beam of light for me ♫
♫ Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet ♫
♫ Your breath brushes up against my cheek ♫
♫ With you warming up the stage,
happiness never comes to a close ♫
♫ Boring jokes add some sweetness to the dinner ♫
♫ Daily life is even more like a comic than comics themselves ♫
♫ Happiness and sadness ♫
♫ Make up the moments of life ♫
♫ Rainy days become very special because of you ♫
♫ Picked up a pitiful youngster off the street ♫
♫ No matter when and where, you always appear ♫
♫ Holding me tightly and spinning in circles ♫
♫ Rainy days make me so nostalgic because of you ♫
♫ Becoming some part of the memories ♫
♫ Walking down a street with lights lighting up
one after another ♫
♫ Warming up the whole world ♫
[Please Feel at Ease Mr. Ling]
[Episode 17]
♫ Carelessly picked up love ♫
♫ You were so cold, and unapproachable ♫
These are the limited editions of comics.
These are super hard to find.
♫ Carelessly picked up love ♫
Do you like this?
I do.
Welcome home.
Welcome Home]
What's in that box that you've been holding all this time?
Youyou gave it to me. She said it's some sort of roommate's gift.
Some important equipment; I don't know what it is.
- For a game?
- Probably.
It's the strongest outfit.
Why don't you try it out?
Why don't you try it instead?
It suits you.
I'll tell you. Since we're living together now...
however...
Are you hungry?
I'll go make something good to eat.
No need. We can go to the convenience store to get something.
My treat.
Okay.
Buy two, get two.
There are exactly four.
The expiration date is okay.
You look around here; I'm going over there.
Go on.
[Chewing Gum]
[Strawberry Flavored Condoms]
The room's password is 0411.
If that isn't easy to remember, you can record your fingerprint.
It's convenient.
Why is that the password? It's not either of our birthdays.
Could it be his mother's birthday.
All of this was bought at the convenience store?
Yes. What do you think? It's can almost be a Michelin chef [Michelin: ratings for food]
From now on, I'll make dinner at home.
Just give me half of the money for Michelin-rated restaurant.
Economical, right?
Tell me, between money and me, which do you love more?
Probably...
maybe...
it's probably you.
Where did you learn all this?
My brother taught me. I used to make it at home often.
Because it's so convenient.
The flavor is just average.
Average?
No way. I just mentioned my brother.
And suddenly, he leaves the table in a pique.
Let me look; where did it  burn?
Clumsy. It's turned red.
Should I add some vinegar in your sukiyaki?
I could tell you really like to eat.
- No need.
- Yes, there is.
- Yes, there is
Hello.
Youyou.
Ansheng.
Do you want to hear about An Xin?
And I want to know how you are too.
Don't worry; we're all good.
Anxin is very comfortable.  She and Ling Yue are living together.
Did I say something wrong?
They're living together?
Great.  Great.
Hearing it personally, I can relax.
Then, we'll leave it there.
I have to get to work; contact me anytime.
- Bye-bye.
I heard everything.
I'm still just a replacement for An Xin?
Xin'er, the matter between you and Yue Ling doesn't have anything to do with Anxin.
Nothing to do with her?
If it wasn't for Anxin,
Brother Ling Yue and I would have been together a long time ago.
Then, there's you.
Brother, you're so outstanding.
how many girls pursue you?
Why are you so stubborn and keep lying to her?
What about you and Ling Yue?
Without Anxin,
Ling Yue and I wouldn't be the way we are today.
Xin'er, that's not love.
It's refusing to face it.
It's not use trying to work up those sentiments.
I'm an example of failure.
I won't fail.
I believe in Ling Yue.
I also believe in all the years of affection between us.
He will come to understand who stands by him;
who has the qualifications to be by his side.
That person is definitely me.
Xin'er.
Feelings aren't a matter to be measured by time.
I won't give up.
Hello.
Who's he calling behind my back? He's still not totally open.
Now that we're living together, anything that makes you fill uneasy,
just tell me.
It's not the first time we've lived together, what is there to feel uneasy about?
Of course, you've experienced it once;
it will get better now.
What you gave me wasn't an experience.
That was called experiencing an evil spirit.
Then let's say that I didn't do that well.
I didn't finish it.
I'll make it up to you. Okay?
What is this?
This is a heart sensor.
Putting this on guarantees your safety while you sleep.
If something unusual happens,
it will contact your close contact.
So my close contact person is you?
If something abnormal happens to both of us, then what?
Then it will contact the hospital.
Why is your heart rate so fast?
Are you okay?
You can't think be thinking of all kinds of R-rated thoughts, could you?
I'm not.
I...I'm not.
What are you thinking?
Can't you trust your man a little,
Miss Gu Anxin?
Then, from now on,
could you trust me more?
Give me a feeling of security, but not this kind.
Okay. Go to sleep.
[Courier package from Gu Xin'er]
Anxin, who is it?
This...I'll put your delivery in the entryway.
Okay. Thank you.
What delivery needs to be returned home?
No. We just got rid of the misunderstanding.
We said to trust each other.
You say, what kind sort of furniture we should go for?
The ones that are the safest.
We should buy the ones that are pretty and the cheapest.
Do we need to take a look of the double bed?
Fine.
What are you doing, little girl?
I am measuring.
You don't need to measure; I am double of you.
How do you feel?
This bed, would it be too small?
No, it is just right size.
I move around a lot while sleeping,
You might not be able to catch me.
Then, let's try it.
Mister, if you like this then I can ring it up for you. All you have to do is sign it.
Just pick the style you like; I already finished measuring the sizes.
This one is very comfortable, you and your wife will definitely love it.
Please send it using the fastest method.
Got it, there won't be delays.
Let's start.
You're haphazardly placing them and not being sincere.
You have to make the paws move.
If it doesn't move how will it attract fortune?
Over there.
Okay.
You can pray now.
You're actually going to pray?
Yes.
We are finally done.
Seeing all this, it feels like I'm going back to the beginning.
Just without a limp and big cockroaches.
But you have a good boyfriend who you can trust.
- What is this drawing of?
-Qiu Yu.
I mean this guy.
Is it not obvious, it's you.
Me!
Do I look that bad?
Please, the way it's tuck on the couch looks so similar to you.
Qiu Yu is so cute, just like you.
It tucks itself into a little ball whenever there's danger.
Let me use your phone for a little bit.
Sure.
Why you don't have a password for your phone?
Why would I need a password?
If I lose my phone someday and a stranger picks it up, they'll know who to call.
No password is risky.
What if your credit card number or other information gets leaked?
Then, you set one for me.
And you...
...do you have a lucky number or a date you like?
Let's use 0411.
Okay.
[Password 0411]
Senior Iron Wall Man.
Anti-finger hearts? I like it.
April 11th...Gu Xin'er's birthday is...
[Good luck in your work]
Thank you.
To celebrate your return,
Zhao Lei did what has never been done before and used company funds to buy this cake.
In your opinion, if a man uses a woman's birthday
as his password, what does this mean?
Then he must like her a lot.
- No...
- Why are you acting weird?
If he has dating history that I don't know about,
then am I waiting for the day his ex comes back
and obediently give up my position to her?
True.
Exes are the most troubling people on earth.
Actually, I'm not sure whether or not it's true,
but... I rarely see him using that tone when he's calling
so gentle and with a smile.
Pressure him. You have to ask him!
But what if I get an answer that disappoints me, what do I do?
I'd rather keep it to myself. Everyone has a past, right?
Since you have doubts, you should be more determined and protect your love.
Really.
Am I being too persistent about his past?
Indeed I am so afraid.
What if he thinks that we are unfit after we officially start dating.
Everyone knows that you two are together, who would try to sabotage?
Even if they try, we will fend them off.
No matter who tries to sabotage, I will never back down.
[GB.Boxing]
Hello.
Why you are here?
I came here for you.
Don't I look oddly handsome without my white robe?
Then I hope after the team practice,
you can maintain this unique handsomeness
We will now talk about footwork in boxing.
Maintain your balance, slide your feet out to strike.
Only when you are well acquainted with your footwork,
can you move your energy to your waist area.
- To us, the waist area is very...
- Hey, coach
You say the waist can exert power,
but why can I never feel it?
- Is it here?
- Yes, this area.
Yes.
Why can't I feel it?
Is it in the front or the back? Is it here?
Here? Why can't I feel it then?
What are you doing?
Who are you, you little punk? Who do you think you are? You have to guts to push me?
Why do you care about who I am, you creep?
Don't you dare touch Ai Li again.
I touched her, what are you going to do about it?
Coach, I ask for a practice round.
Okay.
Didn't I say it before? I will protect you.
Coach, I ask for a practice round
Xiao Yishan? Xiao Yishan?
Get up.
Sorry, I still didn't win him.
Winning or losing is not important. Why do you have to fight with him?
Do you know that you only trained twice?
There's a great chance that you could've gotten hurt badly.
I wanted to win him. I had to win him.
- Why are you so persistent?
- I did it for—
I did it for you.
For me?
I am just an amateur. But you are over-the-top.
If I don't do boxing, how do we find thing in common.
And you only like to box.
Like. Who told you that I like boxing?
You... you don't like boxing.
This is the job.
Expertise and liking something is totally different.
Why didn't you tell me—
Why didn't you tell me that earlier?
Do you despise me?
Today, you are the most awesome fighter
on the six-meter square boxing ring.
No matter what,
I must apologize to you. Apologize in front of everyone.
Otherwise, I will not give up.
Thanks.
You're suddenly so gentle that
I'm not quite used to it.
What are you thinking about?
I'm thinking,
your reckless behavior today, comparable to smashing a rock with an egg,
might be true bravery.
Even though what you're saying is the truth,
but you can slightly—
Slightly be more euphemistic.
You should stop moving.
Isn't that the loser?
Coach Xiao Ai, why are you rubbing him?
Help rub me too.
You're right.
Right that those who show no respect
should be taught a lesson.
Why are you hitting people, Coach?
Now, I'm neither in the arena or in the training center.
So, I'm not your coach.
I'm just a normal person harassed by you.
That was so handsome.
Wasn't that super satisfying?
You should be like that in the future, do whatever you want.
If anything makes you unhappy, lash it out.
If you really don't want to talk about it, there's still me.
I'm willing to be your trash can 24/7.
It is so satisfying. Just a little regretful.
I should've beat him harder.
Don't worry. I'll do it next time.
Help me.
Here.
- Boss Gu.
- No.
I didn't even say anything yet.
- Usually things that start with a title have no good purpose.
- No.
Listen to me. I've signed a big deal for our studio.
A big company is secretly recruiting company image designers.
Boss, I have a pile of work unfinished here.
You must be trying to hollow me out.
Listen to me. If this order is fulfilled,
Not only will there not be a person earning the difference in prices,
it will allow our studio to achieve at least half a year of milk tea freedom.
Will do. Go for it.
- Working makes me happy. Overtime makes me prettier.
- Nice.
You both can make earning money sound so refreshing.
Don't drink the milk tea.
- Boss Gu, in a moment—
- I can't.
No, listen to me.
What I mean is when you meet Party A,
don't let the surprise make you dizzy with success.
It's just a human. Perhaps, he has three heads.
The big company you're talking about...
It's New Way.
The big boss you mentioned?
- Young President Ling
- Then why didn't you say that earlier?
- No.
- I was afraid that you'd avoid it.
- I—
In the case that you run from it, then our sales performance this month will be a zero.
Even if it's said that avoiding rousing suspicion will create troubles
but let me tell you, this is too big.
No, let's leave now.
Boss Gu, Boss Gu.
We're already here. And I did some research for you.
For this company, those who know your relationship with young President Ling
isn't even enough to count.
- Really?
- For real.
So, just think of the milk tea.
And the money.
- For the money.
- For the milk tea.
How cold, how ruthless, how charming.
He rarely likes to smile too.
Forget it that there are no bevy of young women.
Even if he's so gorgeously dressed, he doesn't have any rivals.
Mr Doom doesn't just distance himself from women.
He's even more decisive towards men.
Which mysterious person can make our Iceberg Prince surrender?
Who is he waiting for?
No, it's the strange woman.
It's her. Give advance warning about a dangerous person.
President Ling, please take good care of me in the future.
If there are opportunities, we must collaborate more.
She's just a vendor.
Look at her. From top till bottom, nothing seems right about her.
Her make-up and dressing are full of flaws. The probability as a rival is zero.
That's right.
Zhao Lei tricked me into coming here.
I didn't know this work is related to your company.
I wasn't aware of this too. This collaboration is purely coincidental.
That's right. President Ling didn't arrange this.
Anyway, I don't want anyone know I am your girlfriend.
I don't want others to say that I used connections to be here.
I don't want you to be partial to me too. Understand?
Thank you, President Ling.
This way, please.
President Ling.
Control yourself.
What if I can't control myself?
Work hard to control yourself then.
Stop it.
The unique feature of our company is comics. However, in the current market,
internet companies and comics can have collisions of ideas and create sparks. This is rarely seen.
We have done many investigations in this case study.
If there's a need, I can do some analogies for your reference.
President Ling.
Frankly, you don't need to participate in this kind of small project sign-ups.
I'm here to spot-check on the work of the Marketing department.
What's wrong, any problem of this?
No problem, no problem.
Miss Gu, if there's no problem with the contract,
we will follow up with the proposal after the advance payment is made. This is normal procedure.
Okay, fine. We look forward to our collaboration.
Thank you.
Wait.
Are you Director Gu?
Yes.
You come to my office.
I have some ideas to convey to you privately.
We have never seen President Ling being so serious in our work.
You must do a good job.
Otherwise, we will die because of him.
Don't worry. We don't die.
What are you doing by calling a woman into your office?
You didn't even call Zhao Lei.
Director Gu, close the door.
What are you doing?
Miss Gu, how's my performance?
You...you performed well but if you do this,
it's easy to be discovered.
Don't scream.
If you scream, all previous efforts will be wasted.
What are you doing?
I can't control myself.
What do you mean? Don't scare me.
I can't control myself anymore.
♫ You are cold and unapproachable ♫
Okay. If there's no one around, you don't need to control yourself.
♫ Carelessly picked up love ♫
♫ It's love ♫
[Cai Niao Station]
Did you return this
or did Anxin return this?
Xin'er.
What's up?
Do the boss of an entertainment company need to come personally to discuss the endorsement?
You are Party A for this.
Looks like we don't need to discuss the collaboration.
Don't we already have the spokesperson?
Who is it?
Do you think there's someone more suitable than you?
Endorsing Cai Niao Station? Mr Sheng, you must be joking.
Xin'er, do you know?
The florist told about the language and name of these flowers.
It's White Rose, I'm good enough for you. I hope we can have a good collaboration.
As for me, I finally have the chance to spend the nights and days with you.
Seems like you are going to take full responsibility
for this endorsement activity.
For now,
I can only return the invitation to you for next month's anniversary celebration.
If you didn't mention this,  I would have forgotten about this.
What is this?
Is he worth it?
You won't understand.
Why won't I understand?
Haven't I always been waiting for someone?
I hope that, one day, she can turn back and look at me.
If she doesn't know how to turn back?
I will keep standing behind her to protect her.
I will keep waiting.
By the way,
what should we have for dinner?
Xin'er,
I just want to tell you, I will love you all along.
I can keep repeating this confirmation to you.
I'm hungry. Let's go for dinner.
Let's go.
You are still here?
You are here alone. Why did you switch on all the lights?
My water bills, electricity bills...
Mike found a girlfriend.
Well...
you still haven't gotten over him?
I'm performing the exit ceremony.
I liked him for 7,421 days.
How could I simply forget this?
Everything fine. You can use my stuff anytime.
Stop crying.
What are you talking about? Whether it's online or in person,
no matter how much I invest in it, there's no result at all.
This is...
No.
I think you are great.
It's true.
There may be some small errors in the way you worked for it
but in fact,
you are worth being loved by someone.
Really?
Definitely so. It's my real sentiments.
BBC today produced a documentary on Rebuilding Notre Dame de Paris.
This is a collaboration with France, United States, Australia
and completed by many agencies.
The video has a strong sense of reality.
Please enjoy the short excerpts.
Older Brother, what brings you here?
I got your address from Youyou.
I have these daily necessities for your temporary stay here.
I didn't managed to deliver these to you.
In fact, you didn't need to trouble yourself.
When did you start to be so formal with me?
About what happened in the past.
I'm sorry.
When it comes to feelings,
there's no right or wrong. Let bygones be bygones.
Let's be just like in the past.
The Rose Window in Notre-Dame was burned. The raging fire lasted for twenty fours.
The monument stood for 850 years.
There are nothing that always stays the same.
Did you hear that?
Notre-Dame de Paris was badly damaged too.
If...
Quasimodo didn't hide his feelings,
the story could have been different.
Would Esmeralda be touched?
I don't know.
But, there is not many 'if' in this world.
Everything must go forward, Older Brother.
My Anxin has really grown up.
Don't be burdened by what happened in the past.
Let's go back to the way we were.
I have something to do, I leave now.
Bye.
You are back. I will heat up the food I cooked for you today.
Who was here before?
Noone.
Gu Ansheng, right?
How do you...
You knew it and why you still asked.
I didn't tell you because I worry you are upset.
How would I be unhappy?
What's wrong? Your older brother is worried about you?
No. He delivered the stuff I left at his home.
Isn't there a courier?
I knew you would be like that.
Ansheng is just my older brother and nothing more.
I am really tired today.
I have so many work to do and prepared the meal for you.
Not only you didn't praise me, you threw tantrum at me too.
You delivered this cake that fast as an apology?
I'm not like some little monster without any conscience.
I'm the one without any conscience?
What's wrong? Ran into some problems?
It's common to hit a plateau for creativity.
Hence, this cake came in time.
Take it slow. You will find the solution.
In future, you meet your brother, don't hide from me.
Not right, you don't meet him at all.
Then, I should see him or not see him?
Anyway, you cannot hide from me.
Fine.
Now that we are talking about this,
I will make a confession.
There are certain things I wonder whether I should ask.
Please talk.
Who has been calling you every evening?
[Xiao Yishan]
Xiao Yishan?
Why is he calling you?
He wants me to help  him to pursue Ai Li.
- Hello.
- Help me, help me. I'm hanging up.
I'm hanging up.
I hurt my back. I even pulled off the handle of the door in the toilet.
I'm being locked up in the toilet now.
I'm going to grow old with the toilet.
Shouldn't you call 120110 for the retirement center? Why call me instead?
Why are you so heartless?
Didn't I leave a spare key with you?
Insert the handle in the doorknob again and try if you can open it.
I'm going to try.
It's opened. My brain has short-circuited.
Isn't this normal?
This is the first time in my life that
I feel so miserable. Really miserable.
You shouldn't give me your spare key. You should give it to your girlfriend.
It's not like I didn't try leaving it with Ai Li.
But what can I do now?
Go and find your Ai Li.
Well...
Okay then. It's rare to come up with such a good solution, buddy.
By the way, when you go to work tomorrow,
check your back and then, do a brain scan too.
Get your brain checked.
So, you are saying that,
you happily call every night because
you want to continue to laugh at him?
Yes.
Xiao Yishan likes Ai Li
but he's abnormal. Why would he find you for this kind of stuff?
There are normal people who falls in love.
Who are you scolding?
You.
Don't change the topic.
Also,
let me tell you first. I'm not prying on your privacy.
I merely helped you to get your courier package.
When I took the package, I accidentally
took a glance and saw that it was from Gu Xin'er.
I returned it.
What's in there? So secretive.
I have no idea too. I didn't care.
Should have told me earlier.
If you told me earlier, I could have opened it to take a look.
What if it's something expensive? What a waste. It's not cost-effective.
Since I'm with you, I must draw the line with other women.
One last question.
Why is the password 0411?
You really don't remember?
What?
0411 is our first anniversary.
[April 11, 2011]
Little Green Bean.
I will come back to find you.
0411 is our first anniversary.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Memories are soaked in rain ♫
♫ Fate works bizarrely ♫
♫ The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly beats abnormally ♫
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Obviously, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness, for it has always been you ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Yet the longing has never been able to stop ♫
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Using all of my most beautiful adjectives ♫
♫ Is still not enough to describe your name ♫
♫ Our story is exclusively ours ♫
♫ Our palms hold onto the key to the future ♫
♫ Using love to slowly open up a lifetime ♫