♪Waking up in a nightmare♪
♪Facing this cruel world♪
♪Whose heart is flipped♪
♪Missed farewell to lover♪
♪If the ending is tragic♪
♪Fearlessness is born in adversity♪
♪Even if the wings are torn♪
♪And fall back to the abyss♪
♪Hold your hands and move forward♪
♪Never stopping day or night♪
♪Transcending time and distance♪
♪I may be hurt and heartbroken♪
♪Yet be brave to fight on♪
♪As a hero♪
♪Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops♪
♪Turning behind, you are always there♪
♪Lash out the curse in life♪
♪Let the story be eternal♪
♪Martial Soul surges aggressively♪
♪To embrace your lone wolf braveness♪
♪Even if the future is harsh♪
♪I will never give up♪
♪When there is no way out in reality♪
♪Hope is vexed by desolation♪
♪Yet smiling freely♪
♪Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant♪
♪The power of twin souls illuminates♪
♪Surviving in every plight♪
♪I will never give up♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
I can't go any further under such pressure.
I'm fine.
You should all have a try.
The Light of the God of the Ocean
is the best catalyst for our growth.
Is that the Ocean Delusion Beast?
Oh no,
it saw me!
Made it!
Everyone is doing their best
to pass the challenge.
I can't fall behind!
This time,
I have to awaken her soul.
You're always worried about me
but what about yourself?
No!
Don't die!
[Episode 172]
(He's recovered from the injury long ago, hasn't he?)
(Is it...?)
(I should have noticed it!)
(I couldn't breathe in the sea)
(but Fatty could talk to me.)
(This is the true challenge
from the Ocean Delusion Beast.)
(It's an illusion.)
(I didn't lose to the Ocean Delusion Beast)
(but my own weakness and fear.)
The things shown in the illusion
changes with the thoughts of the test taker!
The illusion created by the Ocean Delusion Beast
is like a chess game.
When faced with it,
Bai Chen Xiang conjured up unconsciously
what makes her feel secured the most.
And now,
she has realized what she's truly facing.
Her mind has matured
and the situation is changed.
Don't be afraid, Xiang.
I will protect you.
The more I'm envious of your talents,
the more I'm hindered.
What I have neglected is
that you guys work much harder than others.
So all I have to do
is putting much more effort into it than you do.
I know no matter what kind of danger I'm in,
you will definitely come and protect me,
just like you did last time.
But this time,
I have to fight on my own.
Xiang.
Now it's time.
First Soul Skill. Delusion!
I'll show you how fast
people from the Tribe of Agility can be.
Yellow Level One Test is not difficult.
As long as she manages to
remove the inner shackles, she will make it.
Surprisingly,
Bai Chen Xiang used her wits
and advantages
to make up for
what a soul master of the Agility Branch lacks.
Is this also part of the influence
of Tang San and his friends?
His soul power...
This is too hard.
I only made it to the 31st step.
Zhu Qing to the 32nd.
I just reached 27th.
Rong Rong couldn't pass the 20th.
Without any social skills,
we can hardly move.
Ao and Rong Rong
are not strong enough physically.
Even with the enhancement of their martial souls
and their soul skills,
it's harder for them than for us
to go through the Light of the God of the Ocean.
Moreover,
Rong Rong must reach the 136th
in a year.
I'm afraid...
There's a loophole in this test.
Just now, I found
that I could use my domain
to help Wu climb.
Are you saying
if we concentrate all our strength
on one person,
the test can be passed?
Ao's sausages,
your Jiubao Amber Pagoda,
and my domain
can all enhance people's ability.
Boss Dai boasts three enhance skills himself.
With our help,
he should be able to finish it right away.
What are we waiting for?
Let's go now.
Easy.
You can't be the first to finish the trial.
I have to think carefully
about the order.
We have to think about the order?
The more of us finish it,
the easier things will be, right?
I don't want us to relax too soon.
Black Level Test is so cruel.
It takes an ocean soul master 10 years
to pass one challenge.
Yet we only have a year.
But the God of the Ocean wouldn't assign
a mission impossible to us.
A key lies in the first test
which can help us pass the rest.
I think you feel it too.
Confronting the high pressure of
the Light of the God of the Ocean
can increase our ability to withstand pressure.
The flow of our soul power
runs more quickly than usual
and the efficiency of the cultivation
is also improved.
So,
we have to postpone the day
to the last day permitted
to make the most out of
the Light of the God of the Ocean
so we can stand a chance
to pass the following tests.
[Soul Land]
You've found the true mystery
of the Light of the God of the Ocean so quickly.
No wonder the God of the Ocean chose you.
But this time I came
mainly for you.
For those who are going to take
a Black Level Test or above,
when they are stuck for the first time,
they will be given a soul ring by the God
without the need to hunt a soul beast.
The God-given Soul Ring will equip you
with the soul skill you need.
And it will be a soul ring of the highest level
that you can bear.
Giving people soul rings directly?
Is this something that can be done by humans?
Each person only has one chance.
Feel it carefully
and embrace it with your utmost tolerance.
I'll be here, guarding you,
until you finish the absorption.
The pain of skipping levels
and absorbing soul rings
is almost unbearable.
Let alone it's Fatty who is always carefree.
Fatty has really changed a lot
after meeting Xiang.
He can surely make it!
Phoenix Piercing Strike!
What an awesome skill!
It's as powerful as a soul ring formed
in a four-decade millennium soul beast.
Thank you, Senior.
When another person is stuck,
I will show up again.
Make hay while the sun shines.
Let's continue with our cultivation.
Use every bit of your strength when you climb.
Retreat when you can't stand it
and feel the relaxation of your body.
This kind of tension and loosen-up
can bring out the best effect.
If only Xiang can see how charming I am now.
(Could it be...?)
(Deep Sea Jellyfish
is the true Ocean Delusion Beast!)
(Bai Chen Xiang,)
[Bai Chen Xiang, Sharp-tailed Swift]
(your Yellow Level One Test)
[Soul Sect of the Agility Branch]
(is accomplished.)
[Soul Power LV. 48]
(Reward,)
[Soul Power LV. 49]
(one level up in your soul power.)
Passing the test in 27 days,
as a land soul master,
you're not bad.
It's almost been a month?
In the colorful mist
created by the Ocean Delusion Beast,
the passing of time can hardly be perceived.
Go and find your friends.
Although
I may not be as good as you are in this life,
Well...
Fatty,
Xiang's well-being is in your hands.
If you didn't catch me in time,
I would be dead now from the fall.
So
we will face
whatever lies ahead together.
Even if it will cost our lives,
we will never give up.
In this case, your destinies
will be decided by the God of the Ocean.
However,
my destiny
is in my own hands.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 172 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1585 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2600]
[Total scene: 63039]
[Total CGI: 28673]
[Total plan of action scene: 12792]
[Total scene model: nearly 580]
[Total character model: nearly 1055]
[Total props model: 13419]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪We still have to part from each other♪
♪I'm faint-hearted to stop you from leaving♪
♪Amidst the grieving woods♪
♪Who is crying out there♪
♪I still relentlessly hold on♪
♪I refuse to accept this destiny♪
♪Desperately searching♪
♪Any signs of you♪
♪The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight♪
♪In your eyes, the world never changes♪
♪Yearning grows and interweaves with the past♪
♪Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven't told you♪
♪You are the memory I refuse to let go♪
♪And the craziness of my desperation♪
♪Can you hear♪
♪My calls♪
♪Breaking through extreme dolours♪
♪Rushing towards your embrace♪
♪You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair♪
♪And the wish I made upon a star♪
♪One day♪
♪You will turn up gorgeously♪
♪And hold my hands♪
♪To envisage our future♪
[Next episode]
-Brother San.
-San.
What a pity, Tang San.
Your rival won't stop right there
and wait for you to be strong.
Descendants of Angels.
The test is falling upon you.
Having broken down one time after another,
yet you still managed to go on.
For Wu,
you can't let this chance go.
My body is being suppressed by a stream of power.
I have to try everything I can
to push myself to the limit.