[Myungil University Awaited You]
[Department of
Korean Language and Literature]
[Do you like basketball?]
[2021, Welcome Freshmen]
[Friends? I have many.]
You're so handsome!
[Official Account for Yeo Jun's Fans]
[And I have even more online.]
[Yeo Jun]
[I love you!]
[Crazy good looking]
[I attended the freshman orientation]
[and got myself a fan club.]
[So handsome]
[It's the easiest thing to do, right?]
[Making friends, I mean.]
[Conveyor Belt Sushi Buffet: 13,000 won]
-How about a sushi buffet?
-But I want dakgangjeong.
I'd rather have sushi.
[Dating?]
[Leisure?]
[Conveyor Belt Sushi Buffet: 13,000 won]
[Those are a luxury for people like me.]
[Because those who barely scrape by...]
[don't have any free time.]
[TOEIC Vocabulary]
[TOEIC Reading]
[My high school homeroom teacher
once said that]
[the hours you study
determines your grades.]
[So what now?]
[All I knew how to do
was put in the hours,]
[How to get a good score.]
[but that won't cut it anymore.]
[I hit rock-bottom.]
[The world tells me
I'm physically an adult,]
[but that's not how I see myself.]
[They say this is our youth,]
[but we can't quite call it that.]
[Youth, the green spring of one's life.]
[As if.]
[Spring is only green at a distance.]
[At a Distance, Spring is Green]
[Episode 1]
He's absolutely stunning!
-Can you believe it?
-Is he that freshman?
-It's Yeo Jun!
-So cute!
-It's time for your coffee infusion.
-No way.
You just have to be this generous,
don't you?
Latte with two pumps of syrup, right?
Giving us the card would've sufficed.
You didn't have to buy these yourself.
Is there anything you're not good at?
I don't know. Maybe you could guess.
Let me see.
Just leave him be.
But the professor is here.
It's best not to get on UP's nerves.
Is that UP? Jun, he saved you just now.
UP?
UP as in Ultimate Psycho.
That's Nam Soo-hyun.
No one in this school
has ever seen him smile.
Eerie, right?
I'll now call attendance.
-Lee Won-jun?
-Here.
-Han Woo-hyun?
-Yeo Jun?
-Here!
-Kim Jae-han?
-Here.
Nam Soo-hyun?
Soo-hyun?
Nam Soo-hyun.
I'm sorry.
I'm present.
Your health is most important,
so don't wear yourself out.
It'll cost you more than you earn.
I'm on mute again, aren't I?
Whatever.
When I was your age--
-You were the same!
Exactly. So keep that in mind.
Soo-hyun!
I'm sorry about earlier.
I hope the coffee didn't burn you.
-I'm glad.
-You're glad?
I don't mean
I'm happy about what happened.
Anyway, I apologize.
You should probably get that washed.
I'll feel guilty
if you just leave like this.
-100,000 won.
-Sorry?
It'll be 10,000 for the wash,
40,000 for my time spent,
and 50,000 for new shoes.
Here you go.
Unbelievable.
Sorry?
You're the school's ATM.
-But it was my fault--
-I know.
But I did too, so we're both responsible.
[50,000 won]
What did I tell you?
If you're curious about
the school's psycho?
Turn to Nam Soo-hyun.
If you want a beating laid on you?
Then get in Nam Soo-hyun's face!
He's never once
lost out on the scholarship
which means he's quite smart.
Not even once?
The guy's relentless
which makes him seem like a robot.
Anyway, we human beings
should grab a bite to eat.
I need to get changed first.
Seriously. What you wear doesn't matter
since you're pure gold itself.
It's not like you to dish out compliments.
Birds of a feather flock together.
I'm golden which makes him golden too.
-Then I'm golden as well.
-Not you.
Anyway, let's go.
Come on.
Me too.
[Welcome to the Dormitory]
[Basic Principles of
Business Adminstration]
I pray to all deities.
Please send me kind, hardworking,
and generous roommates
[who are not too much of a loner
but also not too much of a chatterbox.]
[I also want whoever it is to be tidy,]
[but not on the verge of having OCD.]
And here's my last request.
[Someone too stunning
will only disrupt our harmony,]
[so please send someone]
[only a little, just a little,
prettier than me.]
Hi.
Talk about a crappy view.
I'm Kim So-bin,
a junior majoring in business.
Does that make you 22?
Yes.
I'm Gong Mi-ju,
a sophomore majoring in design.
We're the same age, so speak casually.
What?
Oh, sure.
Can I help you with that?
Will you?
[Welcome to the Dormitory]
Are these all yours?
I heard the room was small,
so more was left behind.
Unbelievable.
[Welcome to the Dormitory]
Seriously?
Were you that unsatisfied with my prayers?
Cheers.
-Come on!
-Cheers!
What are you doing here by yourself?
Care to join us?
I prefer to observe.
I see.
How about I take a break too?
Hey, Jun!
Can't you see me working my butt off?
Come on.
Darn it.
-All right.
-That was fun.
How about round two?
Are you willing to treat us?
Of course... I can't.
I even look broke, don't I? Right, Jun?
-It'll be on me.
-I knew it.
-Jun's the best.
-Of course.
Jung-ho, Jun paid for the entrance fee
and all the drinks we had.
He also bought lunch today.
You guys should treat us this time around.
What's so bad about a rich boy paying?
If you're born into money,
you should give back to society.
It's called trickle-down economics.
You're applying that
to who buys the drinks?
She's right.
You can't freeload all the time.
Aren't you his senior too?
You were fine letting him pay.
Guys, cool down.
Why ruin a sweet night, right?
I will but only because you asked.
As if you have the right to say that.
The next round will be on me too.
But how about a detox drink first?
-Count me in.
-Really?
I'll get those for you.
Here.
Hey, Hye-ji. Thank you for this.
You're being too formal with me.
Just consider us as friends.
We can be even more than that
when it's just you and me.
-Really?
-Of course.
Hye-ji.
-I'm afraid I can't.
-Why not? I'm fine with it.
But Jung-ho has feelings for you.
Who is he kidding? He's not my type.
I want to be on good terms
with all my seniors
and I don't want to cause any trouble.
You know what I mean, right?
Yes, I do.
-Even if I don't, I'll say I do.
-You're adorable.
If only someone like you
were my girlfriend.
[Nam Soo-hyun]
Darn it!
So here's where you work.
-Were you watching us?
-That'll be 28,000 won.
You should've said something.
Do you have a membership card?
You're good at ignoring
people's words, aren't you?
When do you get off?
We're going to get more drinks.
You should join us.
Did you think I'd go?
No. It's why I want you to join us.
If money's the issue, don't worry.
Your time and the drinks you have
will all be paid
by Myungil University's ATM.
I just want to get to know you better.
I'm more decent than you think.
Maybe that's how you want people
to see you.
I don't intend to get to know you,
so get going.
You're still in those pants.
You should've just taken the money.
I intrigue you, don't I?
Anyway, I'm freshman Yeo Jun.
-Why are you smiling?
-Why aren't you?
Get going already.
The others are probably awaiting
your gold card.
Crack a smile for me
the next time we cross paths.
It's not like that costs money.
Hey, Jun. How about a round three?
[Mapo14: End of the line]
Jung-ho, you're drunk.
Besides, Hye-ji's heading home too.
Hye-ji? Wait, I should take her home.
You should worry about
getting home yourself.
Hye-ji, our bus is here.
Jun, I had a blast today.
-Let me take you home!
-Get home safely.
I'll take you home.
Jung-ho, you'll trip at this rate!
Jun.
Jung-ho's too wasted.
Let's head to your place instead.
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but I still live with my parents.
I move out next week.
What? Are you kidding me?
We only drank past our limit
thinking we had a place to crash.
You should take Jung-ho home. This way.
Here.
[Why do I smile, you ask?]
For the cab ride.
-Darn it.
[-It's to get closer to people,]
[-but not too close.]
-Good night!
[This smile]
[hides who I really am inside.]
Greetings.
[Seoul]
Back gate of Myungil University, please.
A short distance ride at this hour
is a waste of my time.
I'll pay triple the fee.
[Seoul]
I'm surprised you didn't bother
to persuade me.
It's easier this way.
[Unprotected left turn]
[Seoul]
[Department of Business Administration]
[Student Assistant Scholarship
for Professor Song Soo-kyung]
[Students like you are tricky to consult.]
[Employment Support Office]
You have mediocre grades
and aren't licensed to do anything.
Have you won any contests
in or out of school?
I'm only a junior--
Students start building their resumes
in their freshman year.
What about you?
Did you party up until now?
No, I tried, but--
You’ll find corporate-funded projects
at the department office.
Apply and do well on them,
and get good grades.
"Better late than never" means that
you’re truly far behind.
[Professors]
[Song Soo-kyung]
Aren't you going to bed?
Did I wake you?
Please don't tell me...
you're nocturnal.
I can't have you tossing in bed
on your phone.
I only sleep well in complete darkness
being sensitive and all.
Sorry about that.
I'm all done and will turn in now.
We'll have to come up
with a roommate agreement first.
-So-bin.
-Yes? What is it?
The lamp.
My gosh!
I guess I startled you.
Could you at least withdraw your hands?
Oh, no. My gosh!
I'm really sorry.
I never intended
any inappropriate physical contact--
You're in the department, right?
I'm Yeo Jun, a freshman.
Oh, right. The popular freshman.
-Anyway, I'm Kim So-bin.
-I see.
I'll see you around, So-bin.
Please, I've never asked you
for anything like this before.
Just give me this one chance.
Not everyone can do the research
for Professor Song.
It's why I'm begging you.
Put in a good word for me.
An assistant like me
doesn't have that kind of power.
I'm a junior with nothing to write
on her resume.
If I graduate in this state,
I'll be seeking for jobs my whole life.
Even if I could help,
someone beat you to it.
-What?
-That freshman who just walked out.
Yeo Jun.
Professor Song already chose him.
A freshman got to be
her research assistant?
Either he has connections or he's smart.
Anyway, he's no ordinary freshman.
My gosh!
What kind of a freshman is he then?
I'm not sure.
If you really need this job, go to him.
Ask him to give up his slot.
Jun? Yeo Jun?
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
-Do we load these on the bus?
-Yes.
Make sure it's the one for our department.
-Sure.
-Got it.
[Myungil University]
If Jun gives up the position,
I could put in a good word for you.
Really?
The student body has asked departments
to bring some juniors and seniors
to the freshman orientation.
Only one has volunteered in our case
in exchange for exemption
on the student union fee.
So you're asking me to...
Please say that's not it.
This is unreal!
A junior is headed on a trip
to clean up after freshmen.
Keep it down, will you?
When they throw up
after drinking too much,
catch the vomit in your hands.
Look, there go the freshmen.
Chirp, chirp, chirp.
Chirp!
What can you do though?
Enjoy whatever you can't avoid.
I should avoid what I can't enjoy,
but it's all for my resume.
Chirp.
At least get yourself
a young freshman to date
and let me have my freedom. Chirp!
You've been gum on my shoe for 14 years.
Is that so?
Am I keeping you
from getting your first boyfriend?
If only I knew!
Let me see if you still have the bracelet.
I should go.
So-bin.
Enough. I've had it with your nonsense.
It's not too late to back out.
Isn't that Nam Soo-hyun? Why is he...
So-bin, my friend of 14 years,
I hope you survive the trip.
Why don't you come with me?
No thanks. I have a date.
Bye! Chirp!
-Hey.
-See you.
-Hey!
-Chirp, chirp!
Traitor!
You promised to always be by my side!
[Freshmen Orientation]
Freshmen at the Department of BA,
gather around.
-You'll now board the bus. Come on.
-Okay!
[Freshmen Orientation]
I'm sitting in the back.
Let's hop on.
Hurry up.
Fine.
Hi,
I'm Kim So-bin, a junior,
and I'll be chaperoning this trip.
Let's check the attendance list first.
I'll take Bus One, you take Bus Two.
[Department of BA, Freshmen Orientation,
Student List]
I'd rather take Bus One...
[Department of BA, Freshmen Orientation]
-It's hot in here.
-Tell me about it.
-I get it though.
-Right?
Let me take attendance.
Hi, Soo-hyun.
Are you joining us on this trip?
We leave in ten minutes.
I must take attendance, so please sit.
Don't bother. I already checked.
-Oh Young-seok?
-Here.
-Kim Ki-hyun?
-Kim Jung-hyun?
-Here.
-Chae Bin?
-Kim Myung-bin?
-Here.
-Jung Min-sung?
-Jun, here you go.
Thanks, Eun-young.
You remember my name!
Of course.
As if I'd forget one of a friend.
You're still
just as popular in college too.
-Kim Ye-jun?
-Do you want it?
-Park Da-som?
-Here.
-Park Min-sung?
-Is he our group leader?
-Here.
-Kim Jae-hyun?
-I doubt he volunteered.
-Kim Young-bum.
-Maybe he's getting paid.
-Here.
-Why that psycho of all people?
-Lee Sun-hwa.
-Group Two's leader is a cutie.
-Cho Seo-yeon?
-Here.
-Lee Han-woo?
Stop that!
Please sit so that I can take attendance.
-Guys, I must take attendance!
-Sweet, right?
Department of BA freshmen!
I'll now take attendance.
[Business Administration
Freshmen Orientation]
Hello, I'm Yoon Se-young, a freshman.
It's nice to meet you all.
Hello, I'm the goofy guy
in Business Administration.
I'm Kim Dong-min. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you!
You're handsome!
Hello, I'm a freshman as well
and a sexy girl!
I'm Ha Se-mi!
Hello, I'm Han Ji-won, a freshman.
It's nice to meet you all!
It's your turn.
Well...
I'm not a freshman.
I'm Kim So-bin, a junior.
-You're so cute!
-You're pretty!
[Freshmen Orientation]
It's okay. I got this.
Just go to the girls' room.
Soo-hyun.
Can I ask you something?
We were on the same team
for a group assignment last year.
Do you remember?
That course... What grade did you get?
Don't get me wrong.
I always have to ask when I'm curious.
-I'm sorry.
-You want to know how well I did?
No, it's not that.
Never mind.
I am curious.
You were the team leader,
and you practically did
the assignment by yourself.
The other team members were useless.
I got an A plus.
Let's drink more! Come on, let's go!
Goodness.
Just leave him. I'll take him to his room.
I got it.
I'll do it.
Come on. I'm stronger than I look.
Get up.
They're gone.
Oh...
I can carry him.
Why don't you carry me
if you're that strong?
Oh, sure.
What? Do you want to show off how strong
you are in the middle of the night?
I keep catching you
stealing glances at me.
It makes my heart flutter.
Well, I was just...
Do you have a crush on me?
-Well...
-What? For real?
-No, I meant...
-Then what?
Jun!
-Yeo Jun!
-Jun, he's calling you!
You barely got to drink,
looking after them.
Let's have a drink, just us.
This is mean, don't you think?
I'm hovering around you
because I want to be your friend.
Shouldn't you at least try to be nice?
-Are you anxious?
-About what?
You need everyone to like you,
but I get on your nerves.
You don't need to be anxious.
Befriending a guy like me
won't help you anyway.
Even if we're not friends,
your college life won't be affected.
I knew you had a lot of pride,
but you're actually pretty insecure.
It can make life miserable for you
and everyone around you.
What?
Relax. Don't be so guarded.
I like being guarded.
Soon,
you'll let your guard down
and feel comfortable, around me at least.
I'm really good at that.
Hey!
I told you to stay away from that psycho.
-You're still up?
-Let's have a drink, just us.
You shouldn't drink more.
I'm not drunk at all! I'm totally sober.
I need your advice on something.
All right, let's drink until we drop.
Let's drink until we drop!
♫ Today, we're going to have a blast ♫
Let's clean up together in the morning.
I want to make sure no one's passed out
outside before I go to bed.
Hand over the flashlight.
No, it's okay.
You're doing all the work here.
I'll go check.
All right, then.
Can I
ask you one more question?
I'll go first.
Why must you always ask questions?
That's...
I think too much, that's why.
I'd wonder why someone did certain things
and keep thinking nonstop.
Then eventually,
I'd feel like my head is going to explode.
Then ask away, before your head explodes.
Why didn't you
read my e-mail when we were working
on the group assignment?
I'm not trying to interrogate you here.
I worked hard on the research
and sent you everything,
but you didn't even open my e-mail.
You're Kim So-bin, a junior, right?
-Yes.
-I didn't get your e-mail.
What?
Then...
I guess it's my fault. I'm sorry...
That may not be the case.
Maybe it was my mistake.
You'd never make such a mistake.
And you would?
People who think a lot
tend to make fewer mistakes.
[You have mediocre grades
and aren't licensed to do anything.]
["Better late than never" means that
you’re truly far behind.]
[I guess it's my fault. I'm sorry...]
[That may not be the case.]
[People who think a lot
tend to make less mistakes.]
Don't you lie to my face, jerk!
You obviously know
that I have a crush on Mi-ra.
How could you do that
and still call yourself my friend?
Did she say that she and I dated?
That's right, jerk.
I heard about everything at the reunion.
I had planned to tell her how I feel
that day.
But she kept crying
and talked about you nonstop.
Got anything to say?
She wanted to go to the movies
on her birthday, so we did.
We had dinner, and I took her home.
That's all.
Then why didn't you tell me?
Because it wasn't important.
You have a crush on Mi-ra?
I told you back in 10th grade.
I told you to stay away from her
because I like her!
You betrayed my trust, you jerk.
You're really drunk.
Where do you think you're going?
Go to bed.
Watch out!
What the...
Let go! Get off of me!
I will kill you all!
Darn it!
Get him out of here.
You're bleeding.
You know where the first aid kit is?
-Yes.
-It's okay.
No, it's not okay.
The team leader will be held responsible
if freshmen cause trouble.
I was touched for a second,
thinking you were worried about me.
Let's go.
You're so dead.
Where do you think you're going?
Well...
It might scar. Make sure
you go see a doctor, just in case.
Will do.
[Ointment]
Why did you guys fight?
We didn't fight.
I was just trying to handle
a drunk friend.
He seemed really angry though.
You see, being nice to everyone
can lead to misunderstanding at times.
Popularity comes with a price.
Wait.
I know this isn't the right time
to bring this up, but...
What is it? Just say it.
That's why you've been
stealing glances at me.
What? How did you know?
It shows on your face.
Well...
If I say this,
you may think that
I risked my life to protect you
because I had a hidden agenda,
but that really wasn't the case.
I did that without hesitation
because my protective instincts kicked in.
Okay, just relax and get to the point.
The research gig for Professor Song.
Can't you please let me do it?
That's why you didn't hesitate
for a second to come to my rescue.
No, it's not that. Trust me.
Sorry to disappoint you,
but I don't want to do that.
Then, let's pretend
you didn't hear what I just said.
Not for free.
I'll think about it
if we can become close.
That's it?
Then you'll let me have the position?
My goodness.
Don't think it'll be that easy.
Being my real close friend,
not a fake one...
It's really hard.
I'll do my best. What should I do first?
We'll take things slow.
[Inbox]
[Spam]
[Kim So-bin]
You know where the first aid kit is?
-Yes.
-It's okay.
No, it's not okay.
Befriending a guy like me
won't help you anyway.
Even if we're not friends,
your college life won't be affected.
[I like being guarded.]
What are you looking at, all spaced-out?
Do you want to try bungee jumping?
I'm afraid of heights.
Then it'll be even more thrilling.
If you do it,
you'll realize it's no big deal.
Do you want to try?
I'll do it with you. It'll be fun.
Just hearing about it makes me queasy.
You'd better do it
if you want to be my friend.
What?
You should be a little adventurous
if you're that desperate.
Why don't you just do it?
Can you spare me a moment?
We're leaving
at noon, right?
I was mistaken.
-Pardon me?
-Your e-mail.
I found it in the spam folder.
It must've ended up there because of
the spam trigger word in the subject.
-Then...
-It was my mistake after all.
But you're partially responsible too.
-Sorry?
-You should've asked me right away.
There's nothing I can do now
because the semester is already over.
I couldn't bring it up
because I was intimidated by you.
You never listened to the team members.
-What I'm saying is...
-You suffered because of my personality.
I'm sorry.
I'll make it up to you
if the chance arises.
No, it's okay.
He apologized to me,
so why do I feel so awful?
What's awful?
Oh, when did you get here?
Let's go bungee jumping.
Can you give me some time
to think about it?
How much time? Three days?
Not a chance. Let's go!
Gosh, my stomach is upset.
Then I should just keep the job.
Hey, wait up!
You're already here, you know.
I really can't do this. Just keep the job!
Some people just hover over what they want
and always hide or run away
when they have to make a decision.
Then they'd regret it over and over.
But you're not a coward like that.
You know what though?
This may be the last chance
for you to trust someone
and just let yourself go.
You'll feel differently after you jump.
-But...
-You have me.
Just trust me.
Can I
really trust you?
Ready to jump?
We're going to jump together.
I can't do this. I'm out!
Then I'll jump alone.
You came to my rescue last time,
so I wanted to do this with you
and keep you safe.
I really can't jump. I'm not doing this!
-That was nice.
-What?
Hey, do you want to grab
a drink next week?
-How about a cup of coffee?
-Sure.
-Alright. I'm going to take off.
-Bye.
Oh, hello.
Have you been to the department office?
What?
Did you tell them that you quit
the research gig for Professor Song?
Oh, I forgot.
You didn't tell them yet?
But I don't think
Did we make a proper deal
for the position?
- What?
- I mean, I am the one who brought it up,
but you're the one who jumped.
I don't think
I ever promised you my spot
if you bungee jump.
Yeo Jun! You said you'll...
Okay, fine. I was just joking.
I'll go to the department office
right now and tell them. Okay?
But you have to keep your promise too.
-What promise?
-You promised
we'll be close friends
if I gave you my spot.
We became close
through bungee jumping.
No, that's not going to cut it.
Have lunch with me sometime.
Bye.
Jun-wan.
-Are you here to see me?
-Like that'll ever happen.
Figures. There's no reason
for you to come see me.
I've been transferred here.
I'll start giving lectures next week.
Pretend like you don't know me.
Give me a pack of cigarettes.
Which brand would you like?
Can't you tell which one I smoke
just by looking at me?
Just give me my regular.
How dare you look at me like that?
How are you planning to keep your job
if you don't even know that?
I'm telling you, kids these days
are out of their minds.
No, not that one! The one next to it.
No. The one below it.
Yes, that one.
I told you I wanted that one
a million times!
Gosh, you... You studying English?
Give me cigarette.
I'm asking you to give me a cigarette.
Keep the change.
What are you, blind?
Did you just hit me?
What did you say?
You're the one who shoved me first!
The part-timer who works here
saw everything.
Do you want me to call the police?
Hey.
Where did a brat like you come from?
And where did a jerk like you come from?
What? Gosh...
I'm letting this slide because I'm a man.
Hey, man!
You want a piece of me?
Where are you going?
Should I call the police?
Maybe I'll let it go
for your sake.
[Nam Soo-hyun]
- How rude.
- Soo-hyun,
please buy this rude girl a drink.
Young-ran wants to drink.
Hey!
What brings you here?
I came to water your cactuses.
I don't want them to dry up.
If not for me, who will water them?
Eat.
I'm good. You eat up and go home.
Come on.
If I don't come see you at work,
I never get to see you.
I'd prefer to be left alone.
So you're saying I interrupted
your sweet break time?
Drink. All you need is alcohol, isn't it?
I'm only drinking
because you're here with me.
Stop making excuses.
[Alarm]
[Myungil University Shuttle]
[Class cancellation notice]
Soo-hyun!
Gosh, if I had known I would've slept in.
Right?
Now that I think about it,
I've never really thanked you.
I could've gotten into big trouble
that night if it weren't for you.
Thanks for helping.
I get that you're used to
people being kind to you
but I wasn't trying to help you.
You have an overinflated ego.
Then were you helping So-bin?
Gosh, how annoying.
The way you look at me
as if you know everything...
It's revolting.
You're so crooked, you won't even accept
other people's acts of kindness.
How dare you judge me?
You don't know anything about me.
What gives you the right?
I treated you like my senior
because I pitied you,
but you disgust me.
That's better.
It was hard seeing you act so pretentious.
[At a Distance, Spring is Green]
-I must really be an easy target to you.
-Yes. That's what I like about you.
[So what are you saying?]
[That you should stop worrying
and be patient.]
[-The group project sounds--]
-so why not be the team leader?
[Kim So-bin, a junior.]
Are you aware that I had my eyes
set on another student?
[It's hard to forgive someone
who betrays your trust.]
You're always so negative.
[But it must be hard to be positive
if you're down in the gutter.]
[I hope you're not
one of those pathetic losers]
[who attack innocent people]
[because they think no one else is
more miserable than they are]
[when they don't even know
others' situations.]
Just talk it out! Why must you hit him?