fTiming and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ No longer panicking on the night of the blackout ♫
♫ You're by my side, illuminating a beam of light for me ♫
♫ Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet ♫
♫ Your breath ♫
♫ brushes up against my cheek ♫
♫ With you warming up the stage,
happiness never comes to a close ♫
♫ Boring jokes add some sweetness to the dinner ♫
♫ Daily life is even more like a comic than comics themselves ♫
♫ Happiness and sadness ♫
♫ Make up the moments of life ♫
♫ Rainy days become very special because of you ♫
♫ Picked up a pitiful youngster off the street ♫
♫ No matter when and where, you always appear ♫
♫ Holding me tightly and spinning in circles ♫
♫ Rainy days make me so nostalgic because of you ♫
♫ Becoming some part of the memories ♫
♫ Walking down a street with lights lighting up
one after another ♫
♫ Warming up the whole world ♫
[Please Feel at Ease Mr. Ling]
[Episode 13]
We're also searching for a camping spot!
Let's camp together?
So many?
Do you like it?
Why is my brother's car here?
He's asleep?
-Why are you here?
-Anxin...
You're saying that's the dude with amazing visuals?
That dude?
A man like you can be called "that dude".
A man like...
Ansheng can't be referred to that way.
He's not that handsome. Look at that facial hair.
Not as fine as me.
I'm joking. I'm joking. Just saying it for fun.
-Why did you come here?
-What does it have to do with you?
Why are you here?
A single man is camping out my girlfriend's house.
How does that have nothing to do with me?
Also, this house is mine.
What's wrong with coming to check out my house?
Brother, why are you here?
-I...
-My brother came to pick me up!
I'm sorry. I had some business at home,
so I had my brother come pick me up.
You guys have fun. Let's hang out next time.
I'll be leaving first.
Let's go.
Brother...
You really waited for Anxin the whole night?
-I didn't.
-If you didn't,
then how could someone as clean as you,
not even shave?
I lost my razor.
What's wrong?
You really can't lie.
Why are you so stupid?
Suffering a whole night for Anxin.
I don't want to talk about that right now.
Brother, we aren't kids anymore.
Anxin is also an adult now and doesn't need you to watch over her everyday.
Don't you think your kindness is already a bit over?
-It's not like a brother to a sister, but like-
-How is it not like a brother to a sister?
Am I not good to you?
It's not even close. Hurry and shave after going back.
Don't let mom see.
I know.
As a new person, you've already achieved such great results.
Did you foresee this beforehand?
Absolutely not.
Actually I only have a pure love for cartoons,
and simply drew the world I saw in my heart to share to my readers.
To receive so much attention and love, I actually...
feel quite overwhelmed and flattered.
You've been called the future of chinese cartoons.
The readers' expectations for you are much greater than before.
Would you have a lot of pressure?
Right now, compared to creating alone in the studio,
I definitely lack a lot of freedom.
There's definitely pressure as well.
But more importantly, I don't want to let down the people who like me.
I will try my best to turn pressure into motivation.
Alright. Then our interview
-will end here today. Thank you for your cooperation.
-Thank you.
Then I will look forward to a happy ending for "Accidentally Picking Up a Prince".
-I will keep reading.
-Thanks for the hard work.
Good luck.
Drive safely.
It's getting late. I'll be leaving first.
You've finally come back so stay for a few more days!
You've lost weight.
How can that be? I've gained weight.
Nonsense!
Wherever you gain weight on your body,
I can see it all clearly.
No, no, no. We must speed up
-finding a girlfriend for you.
-That's right!
I've never seen brother bring a girlfriend home.
Mom, don't worry about this matter.
What do you mean don't worry?
Look at your sister. Isn't she doing well with that Ling Sheng?
No, Mom! There's nothing between Ling Sheng and I.
-I just see him as a little brother.
-Arguing again.
Little brother? His eyes are almost grown on you!
You still deny it?
Oh, right! That Anxin and Ling Yue are pretty good as well.
Only you!
There's not even a hint of someone.
Do you have any friends that are possible?
Your Dad and I went from friends to husband and wife.
Mom, I'm really not interested in girls right now.
Not interested in girls?
You aren't...
No...
-What are you thinking?
-Then why aren't you looking for a girlfriend?
Aside from Anxin, I've never seen you be close with another girl!
You can't possibly date her right?
Mom! Brother's just returned from overseas. He still needs to adapt to life here.
Also girls from overseas and here act differently.
I know you are in a hurry for a grandson,
but you have to give him some time.
Xin'er is right.
I don't care.
Your brother's dating life can't keep dragging on like this.
I'm looking forward to being a grandma one day.
Last time, the Aunt Chen who did nails with me
has a daughter that also studied abroad like you.
She's really beautiful!
I have her picture on my phone. Do you want to see?
I really don't need to Mom.
Just stop rushing me, alright?
I don't care! You must find time to meet her.
Hello?
Youyou, I've planned a date for you.
You must go this time.
I don't want to go...
If you don't go, I'll end our mother and daughter relationship!
Mom!
Move, move, move.
Ever since my mom thought I broke up with Xiao Ba,
my phone's been ringing nonstop!
Anxin, can you do me another favor?
The one in gray sitting there.
That's him.
Youyou, he actually seems alright to me.
Why don't you go try it first?
What can you see from here?
Anyways, what age is it now to still have parent's decide your marriage?
I'm telling you that I'm definitely not going.
Isn't everything still planned out clearly for you?
Or else you wouldn't have come to us for help.
Let me tell you. We'll proceed with the plan in a bit.
Once I walk over,
sit down, and pick up the water cup,
you guys will head out.
Ok. Don't worry, Youyou.
We'll definitely make him feel...
excited.
Ye!
I've come!
-Youyou?
-It‘s you?
You're Aunt Chen's daughter?
The young talent my mom was talking about is you?
I, Youyou's, spring is here again! I love arranged meetings!
Thank god it's you today, or else I wouldn't know what to do.
Then since we've already come, let's just continue with this arranged date.
What do you like to do normally?
Just photography, traveling, and cooking.
I also like photography!
Let me tell you, I normally take photos for-
Hurry and go!
Xu Youyou!
Didn't you say you were on a business trip?
You're going behind my back to go on a date with this wild man?
What do you take me for? A green turtle? You must give me an explanation today!
It's not!
It's my turn, my turn!
If you don't give me an explanation, I'll end myself here!
-Sir, put down that spoon first, and let's talk peacefully.
-Sir? Who's your Sir?
Sit down first. I'll take it out on you later.
Xu Youyou!
How can you do this to me-
-Anxin?
-Brother?
Don't you understand our signals?
It's not that. Didn't we agree that when you raise your glass, we should rush over?
I gave new signals to you behind my back. So many times.
'No', 'no', telling you not to come over.
I thought you were intentionally encouraging us as part of the act.
Besides, Ansheng doesn't look much like he used to.
So that's how it is. That's fine.
Before, I was worried about what I would tell Mom and Dad about this.
If it''s Youyou, it's easier to handle.
Since neither of us wants to do blind dates,
each of us can have our own reasons and it will be fine.
This is a cooked duck that's right in front of me
but it can't fly.
Sister, you have to think of something.
Nevertheless, I think that you and Youyou have some destiny together.
This has brought us together. Isn't that right?
It is indeed quite a coincidence.
Brother.
How do I say this...Youyou is a high quality, outstanding woman, right?
How about...
Don't meddle in this.
He must be shy.  Be mild and tactful.
Use outflanking tactics.
Received. Over.
I suddenly remembered something.
You are both being pressured to get married. If this goes bad,
you'll surely be back at the mercy of your parents, right Youyou?
I've thought about it.
Why don't you collaborate a little.
Why don't you just go through with it and have an open marriage?
- What kind of collaboration?
- Pretend to be sweethearts.
That's not really fair to Youyou.
That would be great.
No; what I mean is
if you will help out, I won't have to be tormented by my parents anymore.
Then...
- What do you think?
It's excellent.
Okay.
So it was you.
[Mom]
Hello.
Yes, Mom. I'm with Youyou.
As soon as I got together with Youyou,
I felt that
love had arrived.
Yes. Don't worry, Mom.
Okay. I'll talk to you when I get back.
Okay, I'm hanging up.
Perfect. Thank you, Brother.
I also need to send this to My mom's Moments [Chinese Facebook] so she can see it.
You have to send one of those posts parents like the most.
Like those with expressions like this....
smiling and that kind of thing.
- Roses?
- That works.
Hurry up.
Brother, I've just remembered that Zhao Lei and I have something to talk about.
Why don't you help us and see Youyou home.
What thing?
Don't we have a project to discuss?
Yes. A project.
= You guys go on ahead.
- Anxin.
You've gotten thinner again. Are you not eating well?
I am eating well.
I'm a take-out delivery girl. How could I not eat well?
Hurry and go. Hurry.
Is eating take-out good enough?
Brother, don't go on like a broken record. Worry about the important things in your own life.
Hurry. Go on.
Are you really so interested in matching Youyou and I?
I do want to make that match.
Every windy, moonless night, when I think about my perfect brother,
a person in utter isolation,
my heart aches.
Hurry up and go. Go on.
Bye-bye.
- Go for it.
- I'm afraid.
What's there to be afraid of?
Isn't that Looking Northwest Into Chang'an?
(T/N Her username)
It really is. I've seen everything. Heavens.
It's Looking Northwest Into Chang'an!
Can I get your autograph? I just love your cartoons.
Me too.  I love them too.
Okay.
Sister Chang Anxiin, could you do more?
It's definitely not enough.
Exactly; you can't leave it unfinished.
Nonsense. How could it go unfinished?
After the new technology was released, in as short as three months.
The revenue for Cai Niao Station increased up to four points.
Cai Niao Station continues to use the most advanced technology.
To focus on improving the experience for customers.
Our courier station started from zero and got to where it is now.
Xing'er, this is the result of your efforts.
Dad, it's all because you had the foresight.
It's also thanks to New Way's advanced techniques
combined with Cai Niao Station's original techniques.
The feedback from our customers is also very good.
We are continuously gaining users.
This means Ling Yue
is pretty capable.
Chairman. Isn't out company planning to create a payment software?
Why don't we connect with some of the resources Xing'er has.
Xing'er. I only want to ask you one question.
Is the data base of this in your own hands?
It's in the hands of New Way.
Those resources are so valuable. I'm afraid
he won't hand it over to someone easily.
The resources are indeed valuable.
But it's still not as precious as my daughter.
I deeply trust the place Xing'er has in his heart.
Give him a call. Tell him
he can require whatever conditions he wants.
Dad. This...
Why are you embarassed? I'll do it!
Hello, who is it?
President Ling, I'm Xing'er.
Gu Group wants to talk with New Way
about the facial recognition collaboration.
This isn't an area included in our collaboration.
Dad. I don't think the timing is right.
Xiao Yue. I'm your Uncle Gu.
Listen carefully. What Xing'er just said
is what I want. The business sector our families maintained all these years
has always been on good terms.
We should be helping each other out.
How about this. As long as you hand me the resources,
no matter what conditions you make I will be willing to negotiate.
-What do you think?
-Apologizes, President Gu.
The information of customers isn't something that can be measured using other conditions.
I am still quite busy so I won't continue to bother you. Goodbye.
Ling Yue is so disrespectful.
Dad. I'll tell him in person later.
No need!
He really doesn't take his opportunities and likes to do things the hard way.
I will wait until the day he begs me.
Ask the Technology Department to strengthen the security  these coming days.
Understood.
[Galaxy cool man]
Big sister Chang An, can you update the cartoon? There's not enough to read!
That's right! The ending can't be bad!
What are you saying? How could the ending be bad?
You're being called the future of chinese cartoons.
The readers' expectations for you are much greater than before.
Would you be feeling a lot of pressure?
What's wrong, Miss Main Author? You still don't have ideas?
I really don't know
what choice she should make.
It's alright. Take your time.
Oh, right. Your draft fee
should already be deposited. Go check it.
Ones, tens, hundreds, thousands...
Oh my god! I've never made so much money before!
If it's too much, why don't you return some to me?
Thanks, Boss.
How is it, Miss Main Author?
I think I've already reached my limit.
No way, let me see.
I'm telling you. It's because you're hungry.
Eat some fruit.
How are you so caring?
I'm telling you. Ansheng sent all these to me.
It's not fruit I'm eating, it's another couple's affection.
My parents also said that there's destiny between us and look like husband and wife.
He's already met your parents? That fast?
Opportunities must be grasped early.
Why are you staring at me? I know I'm pretty.
Ansheng...has handsome features
with a straight nose and striking looks.
You...with 400 degrees eyesight and dead fish eyes.
Husband and wife...well if you think so.
What do you mean?
I'll stop talking. I value my life.
-You better speak clearly!
-I won't!
-Speak!
-No!
-No, speak clearly!
-You're letting me speak?
Speak!
Abstract.
You look way to abstract. There's no word to match in the dictionary.
Zhao Lei! You-
I'll stop! But you're the one who told me to talk.
Stop, stop, stop. I was wrong.
I really like Sister Chang An!
These few chapters are dragging on too much.
She can't be too busy with interviews and not want to update, right?
I think Sister Chang An drew it well.
Isn't it tiring to update everyday? Can everyone be more understanding?
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
You can't be looking at something embarrassing, right?
Looking at what?
We're all adults. I understand.
What do you understand now?
There's no need to...clarify, right?
I don't need that.
Really? Oh, I see.
You're aware of my ability, right? It seems it's been too long, and you've forgotten.
Should we review?
It's the middle of the day. Don't say something so embarrassing.
So don't you go encouraging me in the middle of the day.
Oh, right. Send me your Alipay account.
Why?
Don't I still owe you 82,000 Yuan? I can pay you back now.
Because right now, I count as
a small, small, small upstart.
So I can pay you back what I owe.
I'm not in a hurry about the money. It's not like you're going to run away.
That can't do! I need to get rid of my poor identity as soon as possible.
How are you poor now?
I can't just always not repay what I owe.
If possible, I want you to owe me for your entire life.
What did you bring me here for?
For a date.
A date? At such a hardcore place? It...doesn't really suit me.
Let's go. You'll find out soon.
This is where I first established New Way.
At the time, no one had high expectations for New Way.
In order to increase productivity and improve technology,
I remained here without sleep or rest for a long time.
But I still failed at the time.
Failed?
Because I overestimated the market's needs at the time.
So all the products I made couldn't be sold.
The company had to pay for the losses.
But you still succeeded.
Or else how could there be the New Way of today?
Have you ever thought about
how if everything went smoothly for me then,
I would definitely would have been delighted over my own talent.
And wouldn't have the New Way of today.
Every failure brings seed for success.
Any wrong step you take isn't necessarily correct or incorrect.
As long as you stay true to your heart,
then all the failures will be your treasures in the future.
I won't give up.
President Ling, the technical division has a problem.
President Ling, this time we've learned from past failures
and added multiple layers of succeed to the facial recognition system.
Since you think you're not at fault,
then speak louder and clearly.
Yes, President Ling.
The loophole that the internet refers to doesn't exist.
We've already added multiple layers of security to the facial recognition system as per your orders.
We've created a detailed inspection report.
Do you think we should publicize the results of our inspection report?
Or else if this continues, I'm afraid it will
affect our first year anniversary celebratory event.
Immediately publicize the inspection report. Other publicity methods will proceed at the same time.
Go work with the property manager and obtain security camera footage.
Yes, sir.
Has Cai Niao Inn made a move?
No.
It seems this matter...is connected to the Gu Group.
Immediately cut off all informational routes with the Gu Group.
Yes, sir.
President Ling, there's trouble in America.
Speak.
The brands that were to attend our preparatory anniversary event and already signed contracts
have just claimed they no longer wish to support New Way.
How can they do that?
There's no loophole. Who reported that?
Also, the Gu Group suddenly decided to hold a website banquet.
Apparently, they have already made contact with America.
We haven't even started investigating,
yet that old fox has already shown his tail.
Hello.
Hello, please give me a vanilla creampuff.
Alright.
[Strong Start]
[Loophole found in collaborative technology created by Cai Niao Inn and New Way]
What's going on with New Way?
Immediately send an announcement denying it.
Boss, the Chairman said we aren't allowed to respond to this matter.
Alright. I understand.
Then what should we do now?
Listen to the Chairman's orders for now.
Yes, ma'am.
Nice ball!
How's it going with the Second's matters?
The Second's fallen pretty hard this time due to Gu Yuanchao.
I'm afraid he won't be able to recover.
Who said you can call him Second?
Isn't President Ling-Young Second Master Ling's fall
exactly what you wanted to see?
We can simply sit and wait for profit as those two dogs to
fight it out.
Turn around.
Turn around!
Is there something behind me?
Who are you calling a dog?
If he's a dog, then what am I? If he's a dog, then what am I?
President Ling, you've misunderstood! I don't mean it that way!
No! I don't mean it that way!
-You're still explaining?
-Please listen to me!
If he's a dog, then what am I?
First, we need to stabilize things in America.
Ling Yue brought the promotional record to me for free. Why wouldn't I use it.
Our activities still have to be released as planned.
Yes. Don't worry. We are not only willing to invest money for them, but will also pay liquidated damages.
There won't be a second company that offers this treatment.
Come in.
Chairman, then I'll take my leave.
Dad.
We took a big blow for our focus on New Way this time.
Should we clear up stating that there is nothing wrong and think of another solution?
Xing'er, you've been treated unfairly.
I know your station has been very successful.
It's very outstanding in many aspects and got involved unwillingly.
But this is what it looks like on the outside.
The key to a successful enterprise
is to think long-term.
Think about it. New Way isn't just a company Ling Tian favors.
It might me the key to the future development of Ling Group.
If we sacrifice a small station to knock him down.
Do you think this sacrifice is worth it?
-Dad.
-Don't say anything.
I know you're here to speak for him.
I'm not here to speak for him. I'm here to discuss business with you.
What business?
Haven't you always wanted to take down New Way?
Rather than killing 1,000 enemies with a sacrifice of 800,
why don't we think of a new plan?
Continue.
The best way is to unite with Ling Group through marriage.
Last time he didn't try to give you face.
I think his heart already belongs to someone else.
That's not important. What's important is
that he can't ask anyone for help now.
That is true, but doesn't he still have that Old Man Ling Tian?
He has always wanted to escape from the control of Uncle Ling.
So he definitely won't ask him for help.
What's wrong? Are you okay?
Don't look, don't look.
Let's go.
Thanks, brother.
Why don't we call the police?
Forget it.
I don't want to cause a ruckus.
Do you know who did it?
I think it should be crazy fans.
I've stopped working for too long.
They must be using these methods to rush me.
Why don't you move back?
It's too unsafe to live alone.
Don't worry, it's really fine.
Right, why did you come over today?
I called you so many times and you didn't pick up. I thought something happened to you.
Sorry, since I've been quarantining, I've turned off all my notifications.
Quarantine?
It's to...find inspiration.
You look exhausted. Have you eaten yet?
I've eaten.
You...Have you not been eating on time?
It's not too late to eat now.
What do you want to eat? I'll order our takeout together.
Okay, stop ordering takeout.
I'll make some food for you.
What do you want to eat?
Anything.
Okay.
Brother
What happened to New Way?
Being targeted by business rivals is very common.
Don't think too much.
You can't tell Ling Yue what happened today.
I don't want to cause trouble for him.
Why would you...
be a bother?
New Way
Why is she here?
In times like this, Miss Gu dared to come to New Way.
I've heard that Cai Niao Station has taken a blow because of her.
This President Gu. In order to beat us, he's willing to do anything. That's too overboard!
Didn't she have an ambiguous relationship with President Ling?
It can't be that this time...
That's hard to say.
President Ling, can we talk alone?
Regarding New Way's current problem, I have a solution.
Why are you helping New Way?
Your surname is Gu, so shouldn't you be on the side of Gu Group?
Anxin's surname is Gu too.
Why don't you suspect her help at all?
Anxin is different.
My identity now is not part of the Gu family,
but an entrepreneur that you've helped before.
Things about Newbie Station is a mutual collaboration that doesn't talk about helping or not.
Other people don't understand you, but I do.
You won't invest in a company that you haven't researched at all.
Did you really not know Cai Niao Station is my company
before investing a lot of money in it?
What I saw was its business value.
No matter what, you've helped me before.
So this time, I won't just stand by and watch.
What is Gu Yuanchao's condition?
Marriage.
Why will the marriage of our two families be useful for you guys?
Not only can it free New Way from the current stock situation.
We can create an e-commerce platform in the future.
Why wouldn't I support this win-win situation.
Boss has been talking for a long time.
I don't even know what he's talking about.
A man and woman alone in an office, what can they talk about?
But it wouldn't be bad if the boss is with Ms. Gu.
Then we wouldn't have to worry about the danger of the company.
Ms. Gu...They couldn't be talking about Gu Xin'er right?
If you're worried about hurting Anxin,
I can tell her clearly that this a plan for the two wins of our companies.
That this is just a publicity engagement.
When this is over,
we will go back to before.
Brother Yue, your tie is crooked.
Ling Yue!
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Soaking the memory wet ♫
♫ Fate works bizarrely ♫
♫ The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly beats out of normal ♫
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Obviously, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness,
for it has always been you ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Yet the reminiscing has never been able to stop ♫
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Using all of my most beautiful adjectives ♫
♫ Is still not enough to describe your name ♫
♫ Our story is exclusively ours ♫
♫ Our palms hold onto the key to the future ♫
♫ Using love to slowly open up ♫
♫  a lifetime  ♫