Cheng.
One last question.
Go ahead.
You've been ignoring me
for the past few days.
Is it just because you're angry
or because of something else?
Because I was afraid.
I was afraid I'd go soft-hearted.
(Anyone)
(will inevitably have to make sacrifices)
(for the things they love.)
(Be prepared.)
(This is just the beginning.)
=Falling into Your Smile=
=Episode 19=
(Obsidian has arrived near the monster.)
(There they've found
ZGDX hitting the monster.)
Cat, hold on!
Clear the line.
Clear the line on the top lane.
ZGDX.
Destroy the top turret.
Go up, go up. Get in there.
Controlled.
Hold on, hold on.
(ZGDX gets the monster)
(Killed Off the Monster)
(And have taken advantage of it.)
Nice!
(Defeat)
(The team fight isn't over yet.)
(Double Kill)
(Okay, ZGDX)
(has taken the victory in the team fight.)
Lu Yue, go.
(Defeat)
Coming.
(Rampage)
(Obsidian is unstoppable.)
(Defeat)
(ZGDX continues to chase after them.)
(Another kill.)
Nice!
The last team fight.
- Here we go.
- Copy that.
Go, go, go.
Fight! Fight! Fight!
(Perfect Power)
Watch out, watch out!
There's another one behind us. Hurry.
Chase.
Spread out.
(God's Envoy)
Give me room for my attack damage.
Chase! Chase!
(Unstoppable)
(Chessman continues to chase after them.)
(Nice! He killed another one.)
(Chessman completes a double kill)
(God's Envoy)
He's still chasing.
(Triple Kill)
(Nice! Chessman has got a Triple Kill.)
(This looks like
a good chance to win the fight.)
Nice!
(Let's congratulate ZGDX)
(for winning the game.)
(Let's congratulate ZGDX.)
(Thanks to NongFu Spring)
(for your support of this season!)
(Let's get back to the point.)
(ZGDX's performance in this game)
(was really surprising.)
(Especially when it came to player Lv)
(who did a good job too during the match.)
(He got the MVP.)
(To be honest,)
(when even a substitute can play so well,)
(I think maybe the other teams)
(need to reevaluate)
(ZGDX's overall strength.)
(That's right.)
(What's Lu Yue's treat for dinner tonight?)
I'm telling you, Lu Yue.
You can eat whatever you want tonight.
Good for you.
Yes!
Awesome.
Lu Yue.
You played well.
MVP.
It feels like after this game,
you'll gain 300,000 more fans.
What did you say?
What did the water dispenser do to you
or are you planning to retire?
Cheng, what did you say to Shorty?
She seems to
have had some kind of breakdown.
It's delicious. Let's go eat that.
All you care about is eating.
Don't talk nonsense, okay?
After this game,
our team still holds the record
for winning every single match.
Did you see the fans in the audience?
The glow sticks they waved for your victory
were all based on my previous performance.
Yes, your brilliant performance.
And then you slapped it away
with a loss of 120,000 yuan.
I'm praising you.
Do you know how to be grateful?
What a mean guy.
That was a good game.
Very good.
Am I right?
Why do you two have so much to say?
What time will they be out?
Who knows?
- Just wait for them.
- We've been waiting for so long.
They're coming out.
Coming. Come on, come on.
Hello.
Thank you. Thank you.
Let me get by. Let us get by.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Look over here. Look over here.
Please look over here.
It's quite crowded.
Hello. Hello.
Tong Yao.
May I ask you a question?
What do you think about this ban?
I deserved it.
Do you feel particularly aggrieved?
Rumor has it that you did it
to protect your teammates.
I'm not aggrieved.
Are you worried
that you'll be replaced by Lu Yue?
I'm only banned for one game.
Why did you hit her?
Didn't you know
it would stain your image?
Or did you know
every move you made
would be noticed by the public,
being the only female competitor.
So you couldn't help but do this
so as to gain attention.
That's pretty much of it.
How do you expect her
to respond to these questions?
Which media are you in?
That's exactly the way it is.
She became the starting player
without any practical training.
I heard that she signed a contract before.
Yes, even if she is really good,
she didn't turn on the camera
during her previous live streaming.
Who knows if she played by herself or not?
The club signed the contract
with her just like that.
According to Article 246
of the Criminal Law
of the People's Republic of China,
whoever publicly insults others
by violence or other methods
or fabricates facts to slander others,
if the circumstances are serious,
shall be sentenced to the fixed-term imprisonment
of no more than three years,
detention, control,
as well as deprivation of political rights.
So,
think twice before you say anything.
Don't go.
That's right.
Is what Cheng said true?
Do you think my brother studied
at the University of Political Science and Law for nothing?
(Lv.)
(How does it feel to be back
after such a long time?)
It feels pretty good.
That's why I picked
my newly trained shikigami today.
(Yes, Lv picked Enenra)
who doesn't really
match his style of play today.
It's a surprise.
Did you get prepared in advance?
I don't think it was prepared in advance.
It's just our coach.
Yes, our coach, Ming.
He said that a Chinese midsolo
must be able to command this shikigami.
It's a bit embarrassing if not.
So I practiced her in advance.
So Smiling can play Enenra too?
She's very good at Enenra.
In fact, I think she's good at
every shikigami.
At first, she didn't play well with Higanbana.
But later on,
she also gained good command of her.
It seems that the relationship
between the starting player
and the substitute of ZGDX
is not so tense.
There's nothing to be tense about.
We have different styles
and different patterns of play.
Whoever should go play in the game
will go play.
But as things stand right now,
she's more suitable than me
to be the starting player.
But I will become stronger afterwards.
That's for sure.
It seems that Lv is responding to
some of the doubts
about ZGDX on the internet.
I trust the judgment of my teammates.
If there is something I want,
I'll go for it myself.
So you do have a conscience.
You actually knew how to compliment me.
Don't take it the wrong way.
I was defending my brother's team.
That's all.
Brother protector.
Come inside, please.
This restaurant is so good.
What's wrong? You've got a limp?
It's a scrape.
Be careful.
Wait for me.
You didn't even tell me
your feet were scraped out.
Are you mute?
I'll go to the store to buy a band-aid.
It'll be fine.
Come on, Dragon.
Let's take a picture.
Okay.
Me too. Me too.
- Come on, look at me, let's take a picture.
- Come on, cheers.
Okay.
See how good this filter looks?
Don't move. One more picture.
This little brat
is always surrounded by women.
Tong Yao?
What do you think?
Look at it. Does it look good?
This one's not bad.
Why are you here too?
I came to eat.
I was live yesterday.
Someone in the live room
said bad things about you.
I cursed them.
I told them not to say that about you.
You're very nice.
Thank you.
But don't do that next time.
They will scold you too.
I'll get you into trouble.
Get me into trouble?
I don't understand.
Cheng, what does it mean?
You're childish.
Yao, you're so cute.
You're so cute even when
you're cursing someone.
Today, I told Tae-lun,
you're funny.
Tae-lun said he thinks you're funny too.
Hello.
(Jungle player, ID: DQ.Five_Dragon)
(Hsu Tae-lun, Jungler)
Come on.
I said no.
This is the girl of another brother.
And even if she's technically not,
I still rank second.
Daydreaming.
What does "daydreaming" mean?
The same as before.
Cheng.
You are not cute at all when cursing others.
Yao.
I'm going to eat first.
I'll contact you later by WeChat.
Watch your feet.
That Tae-lun he…
What Tae-lun?
Do you know him well?
He looks familiar.
Another jungler!
Tong Yao, what's wrong with you?
I always feel like I've seen
this Tae-lun somewhere before.
We've seen
DQ.Five's game videos before.
No.
It was in some other place.
Don't think about it, just eat it.
Have one.
I remember now.
What's wrong?
I've seen Tae-lun somewhere before.
I saw him on Ning Jiaqi's live stream.
What's their relationship?
Boyfriend and girlfriend?
You don't know?
Shorty.
Eat the meat.
Grow taller.
Excuse me, pull over along the street ahead.
Cheng, what are you doing?
Going to buy something.
You don't have to wait for me.
Biscuit.
Let's go eat.
Let's go. Let's eat.
Bye-bye.
What?
Tong Yao, come on.
This.
What's wrong?
This…
Why are there only
two of Cheng's goldfish sons left?
There were three before we left
for the afternoon match.
You must have made a mistake.
No way, check it out for yourself.
Biscuit!
(Cheng 2020.01.25 - 2020.08.12)
Hurry up and figure out a way.
Otherwise, when Cheng comes back,
you and Biscuit will both be killed.
You see?
How about this?
Do you think Cheng is stupid?
He may not even see it.
The colors are different.
What are you doing?
Cheng, your son ate randomly,
and ate himself to death.
I'll help you destroy the body.
I thought it over that
I haven't thanked you
for educating me before.
What you taught me was so meaningful.
It was as if I got a new set of parents.
You're so kind-hearted,
like a bodhisattva.
You're full of love for all living things.
You abide by the laws
of cause and effect in nature,
and the laws of the food chain
pertaining to the weak and the strong.
Tong Yao.
Say something I can understand.
My cat
ate your fish in accordance with
the laws of jungle found in nature.
I screwed up.
Be optimistic.
Think about it this way.
Maybe it's your goldfish son
grew wings and flew away.
There is a fish in the north,
and its name is Kun.
The Kun is too big to be stewed in one pot.
Band-Aid.
(Jinyang)
Hey, Jinyang.
You're in such a good mood!
Of course, I am.
It's a beautiful day.
So of course I'm happy.
Is it?
It's a cloudy one for your captain.
What do you mean?
Your captain
isn't playing the game
as he should be in the live room.
He's searching for a live baby piranha.
Ai Jia just transferred the link to me.
I'll send it to you.
I'm hanging up.
I won't keep you from
enjoying your captain's heroics.
(Cheng, you can't buy a baby piranha.)
(Search for something else.)
I don't know why,
all the search results are Venus-Flytraps.
But thinking about it.
The effect would be about the same
if I were to put one next to the fish tank.
So I bought one.
(Cheng, what's the effect?)
Anyone who tries to
tease the fish again will be bitten.
(A Venus-Flytrap?)
(No way!)
(It's not going to eat my Biscuit, is it?)
(Biscuit, I'm sorry.)
Biscuit!
Biscuit?
Biscuit.
Don't move.
Otherwise, get lost.
Lu Sicheng, I'm not…
Let go of me!
You...
Cheng, why are you still awake?
I...
I must be sleepwalking.
(Oh my God.)
(What did I just see?)
(I'm going to go blind.)
(I didn't know
you were that kind of captain.)
(It's my fault for being so naïve.)
(Why did I have to see that?)
(Why did I have to see that again?)
(There are 365 days a year.)
(I only get up early
for no more than five days a year.)
(Why did you choose these days)
(to blind my eyes?)
(Or do you two actually…)
(I want to call the police.)
What's up?
Why do you look like you're in shock?
What are you doing?
Getting so close to me while I'm sleeping.
I came down from upstairs.
I wanted to see if my cat is still alive.
How can a good healthy cat just die?
If you want to make an excuse,
please think up a new one.
It's all because you said
you wanted to buy that flytrap yesterday.
I just wanted to see if my cat is alive,
or if you strangled her
and flushed her down the toilet.
But then
I came down to find you asleep in the game.
Then out of kindness,
I was afraid you would be cold
so I found you a blanket.
But you just pressed my head
against your stomach for no reason,
and messed up my hair.
How is that possible?
You thought I was Biscuit?
How… How could…
Anyway, the final scene was seen by Chubby.
(Calling "Roly Poly")
Hey, Chubby, you got it wrong.
We didn't do anything.
If we were about to do anything,
why would it be in the living room?
You're a fool. I'm not.
If you didn't sound so aggressive,
you'd have been a little more convincing.
Now even I think
you're just throwing us for a loop.
So what do you think
Chubby thought we were doing?
Cheng.
Today is Tuesday.
There is no training match.
I thought since
we have nothing to do today anyway,
then why don't we go to the flower,
bird and fish market?
I'll get you another goldfish.
But you stayed up all night
playing games.
So I guess it's better to just forget it.
Okay.
Let me take a shower and change my clothes.
Please wash your hair too.
Let's go.
Okay.
Chubby.
You haven't reached
your live performance goal, right?
I have.
That can't be true.
I think you've reached
your eating performance goal.
If you do this again,
your salary will be deducted.
What's going on?
Tong Yao looks especially alluring today.
Excuse me?
Why do they have to
choose the same brand of shoes?
What's the situation?
What do you mean "what's the situation"?
Where are our two carry players going?
They said they were going to
the flower, bird and fish market to buy fish.
Going to the flower, bird
and fish market to buy a fish.
Is it the flower, bird and fish market
next to the Civil Affairs Bureau,
or is it the Civil Affairs Bureau
next to the flower, bird and fish market?
Spring is here.
It's the time of the year
when the animals are in heat.
These two people are too blatant, right?
Although it's not prohibited in the club,
this is…
I suddenly feel very angry.
These days dysgnosia people
and elementary school students
can go on a date.
While our Cat,
as such a normal person is single.
All he can do is to
grab iron shafts all by himself.
Strong.
(Dutch Flower Town)
Cheng.
What?
You look good in a necklace.
Why don't you wear it at the base?
For whom would I wear it at the base?
Who are you wearing it for now?
The fish?
Aren't you wearing a dress too?
Who are you wearing it for?
The cats?
Have you stared it long enough?
Shorty.
Are you an adult or not?
Why?
You don't even know how to wear high heels.
Why are you pretending to be an adult?
Cheng, how many do you want?
Whatever.
What color do you want?
Black.
The red ones are so pretty.
Look at their tails,
they're like little umbrellas.
Is that so?
I want a black one.
Red is so festive.
Look how it's bouncing around.
It looks like it's going to live a long life.
If my fish
wasn't bitten to death by your cat,
it would also have lived a long life.
I told you I wanted the black one.
You can't judge me.
I'm in charge of my own fish tank.
Since you don't like red so much,
don't take the Fire Kirin anymore.
Give it to me.
Don't you dare touch my Fire Kirin.
If you are so capable,
why don't you let the game designer
design a Black Kirin for you?
Just say you like it.
"No rebuttal accepted.
I'm in charge of my own jungle.
That's how dominant I am."
You're way too talkative.
Handsome.
I suggest you just listen to the girl.
What's the point
of fighting with your girlfriend?
If they get angry,
we are the ones who suffer in the end, right?
Next month when you want to hold her hand
and she slaps it away,
then brings this up with you,
that's when you'll regret it.
Sir.
You've got it all wrong.
We are not in that kind of relationship.
How much is this fish?
One yuan and a half.
One yuan, is that okay?
Hello?
You drive an Aston Martin
and now you're bargain with
a stall owner for 50 cents?
Are you even human?
My wife is the same as your girlfriend.
Willful.
We're really not…
Pay up.
Here is the fish.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Take care.
What are you looking at?
Let's go.
This place will cost me three years of my life
every time I come here.
If you want me to die early,
let your cat eat my fish again.
Shorty.
You're always taking advantage of me today.
It's not appropriate, is it?
So cute.
Ma'am, how much is it?
3,500 yuan for this cat.
Are you kidding me?
It's not enough for you
to have the one fat cat?
You still want another one?
What a cute kitten!
Hello.
Dragon, give me this.
I want this kitten.
It can keep me company when you're not there.
I saw this first.
Let's go.
Okay.
Is he Chessman?
Ma'am, how much is it?
I saw the cat first.
It's enough that you have that one fat cat.
You still want to get another one?
There are already
two annoying little creatures at the base.
I reject keeping a third one.
How come there are two?
You and the cat.
That cat was so cute.
It's like the brother of Biscuit.
Wait a minute.
Isn't his girlfriend Ning Jiaqi?
Then that one just now is…
Maybe she's a fan of DQ.Five
or maybe she's a staff member.
What the hell?
He's cheating?
I feel embarrassed for you.
First Li Hengshuo and then Hsu Tae-lun.
You're never able to see through people.
Keep your mouth shut from now on.
You didn't tell me before.
Would you believe me if I did?
You'd say I made
an unfounded attack upon them
out of envy and jealousy.
The car is here.
Please.
I'm a little hungry.
What would you like to eat?
Noodles.
Noodles?
I thought girls all favored
Japanese food or something like that.
Girls?
What're those?
I want to eat the noodles
with hot soup, meat and eggs.
If there is someone of a certain gender
who loves noodles,
I must be of the same gender with him.
Mr. Li, sorry.
I'll have to change the destination.
Okay, received.
Please follow the navigation
to the destination.
What do you want to do later?
Go back to the base for gaming.
There is no training match today.
I don't want to play games.
Why don't we go to the movies?
I've already bought the tickets.
You'll go with me.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
You're acting like a thief.
If I get caught, then...
You've already played
a third of the tournament's finalists.
You're still not used to the fact that
you have to show up in public a lot
being a public figure?
The first time I asked you to hide behind me
was because you just joined the team.
The second time, you won't be so lucky.
Why?
You have to learn to adapt yourself to it.
This is the most basic requirement.
Adapt to being a public figure first,
then adapt to not being manipulated
by public opinions.
Isn't your education policy
to be well behaved and cause less trouble?
That's what you taught me before.
Even if you make it,
there will still always be
someone discussing you.
Yesterday, someone said you've gained weight
during the live stream.
Really?
See, you're being manipulated
by public opinion again.
Can't you get on the scale yourself?
When you're able to
you're not fat and it's just they're blind,
that means you've graduated.
How come it's so tiring
being a professional player?
If you want to wear a crown,
you have to bear its weight.
You brought the kitten in?
It's cold in here.
Kittens get sick easily.
If they get sick,
there will be a lot of trouble
to take care of them.
Enjoy the movie.
Hsu Tae-lun is so cunning.
He ran away before the movie was finished.
There seems to be fans there.
I have to go to the bathroom.
You really haven't grown up.
Hsu Tae-lun must have known there were fans,
setting you up on purpose.
I'll hide first.
I told you this wouldn't happen again.
Cheng, are you dating with Smiling?
Why is she here?
Or is your whole team there?
Why is she hiding?
Is she shy?
Oh my God, you're not really dating, are you?
I didn't believe
what was on the Internet at first.
I thought so too.
Hello, everyone.
I'm ZGDX's midsolo, Smiling.
Her standard lines when receiving
MVP interviews.
Don't laugh.
She gets shy easily.
I had a hard time convincing her
to watch the movie with me.
Cheng, are you two together alone?
Yes.
I think it's definitely…
I've seen people talking about you two
all the time on the E-sports Industry Farm.
So you two are really together?
We are…
We are harmonious teammates.
It's just a coincidence
that we went out to see a movie together.
Teammates.
What did you do today?
We bought the fish.
Bought fish for a whole day?
Do you really think I'm stupid?
Oh, right.
We did go to a movie.
It's Black Widow, the one you like.
Spoiler alert?
No.
Come on.
No, no.
Don't spoil my Scarlett Johansson.
Kitten?
Yeah, from a fan.
It's so cute.
(DQ.Five_Dragon)
Thank you.
(So cute. A warm guy.)
I'll take good care of it.
Cinema?
Watching a movie?
You must have mistaken someone else for me.
(Just returned to the base?)
I just returned to the base with the kitten.
(It doesn't seem to be true.)
(I feel like it's not the truth.)
I've been playing games
with another account this afternoon.
(Ask your teammates if this is the case.)
If you don't believe me,
ask my teammates.
(Dragon, be composed,
continue to make up lies.)
(I saw him at the cinema today
and he said he didn't go there.)
(Lying)
(The teammates are also telling lies.)
Yes.
(I saw him too)
He's been playing games
at the base this afternoon.
(You're lying.
I don't believe you're telling the truth.)
(Your teammates are lying too.)
(Are you going to
keep lying to us like this?)
Besides, the cinema is so cold.
The kitten would definitely catch a cold
if it was there.
(Whoever has a kitten must be kind.)
I can't do that.
Civet Cat.
Go and turn off the air conditioning
in the base.
The kitten will catch a cold
if it is blown with too much cold air.
It's okay.
He probably feels a little cold
for being exposed to too much cold air.
Isn't this Hsu Tae-lun from DQ.Five?
Why are you watching his live stream?
Aren't we playing with them next week?
I'm getting to know
the opponent's tactics in advance.
What's wrong?
This Hsu Tae-lun is really annoying.
He's not a good guy.
I hate him.
You guys who play e-sports
are all bad.
Are you out of your mind?
What does it have to do with me?
(Douban Group)
(Jungler Dragon from DQ.Five)
(dated with a woman
other than his girlfriend.)
(Dragon wasn't wearing the same clothes)
(as in the photo at all.)
(So the person who was caught
on camera this morning)
(is definitely not Hsu Tae-lun.)
(ZGDX_Smiling)
2 p.m. at Wantai Cinema.
- I ran into Smiling and Chessman.
- What were these two doing alone?
- Isn't that right when…
- The photo of his back.
- The one who saw Hsu Tae-lun.
- The photo is also…
- Wantai Cinema.
- Went to that movie.
(the time of the electronic clock on the wall
can also testify that.)
Cheng and I went to buy goldfish.
We went to see a movie after that
since there was plenty free time.
No one has made a rule that
only couples can go to the movies.
If there was really something
going on between us,
who would so openly
go to the cinema
and wait to be gossiped about by you?
As for the other team's jungler
you were talking about,
I don't know anything about that.
After all, there were
so many people in the cinema.
But
there were indeed a few people
who came in the dark
after the movie had started.
As for who they were,
why don't you ask him yourself
if you're so curious?
(Smiling is good at being sarcastic.)
(Obviously she's implying Dragon.)
(I bet she and Cheng must have an affair.)
(She's using Tae-lun
to draw attention away from herself.)
(Group Match of Group A, The Third Game
ZGDX vs. DQ.FIVE)
(Dear users of Onmyoji Arena,)
(and those of you
who are watching the live stream.)
(Hello, everyone!)
(Welcome to the scene of)
(the Onmyoji Arena Pro League, 2020.)
(I'm the host, Xizhe.)
(Today's teams are)
(ZGDX and DQ.Five.)
(We can say)
(they're equally strong.)
(Who will be the winner?)
Let's wait and see.
(Once again let's welcome them)
(with a warm applause.)
(All right, please take your seats.)
Let's be careful in this match.
I just feel a little bit nervous.
I don't know why.
You're nervous when looking at anyone.
Is your Zodiac a rabbit?
(ZGDX vs. DQ.FIVE)
(Well, the lineups of both sides
have been determined.)
(Let's look forward to the following match.)
(The game has just started.)
What are they doing?
Where are they?
I don't know.
Probably in a meeting somewhere.
Come on, let's get ready to kill Tong Yao.
- I know.
- Coming.
(They're about to start a fight)
(while Smiling is still
unaware of it at this time.)
Go. Now.
(Suddenly, they've come to the middle lane
to attack Smiling altogether.)
(Smiling can't fight back at all.)
(Her teammates can't make it to support her.)
(First Blood)
Smiling was killed in seconds.
(- First Blood.)
(- DQ.Five took the first blood.)
Tong Yao, you poor thing.
These five people picked a team fight
in the middle lane right at the beginning.
What was that about?
(They have contained the middle lane
in the early stage.)
(Is this some kind of new tactic?)
♪You say the world
is always not gentle enough♪
♪Fortunately, you're free,
the most special player♪
♪Invite me to be your number one teammate♪
♪So I had my first encounter with my dreams♪
♪You said you'd always be behind me♪
♪Rumors ran to me and hurt you♪
♪How long will it take
from now to the future♪
♪You're love that never needs a reason♪
♪I want to be close to you,
a little closer to you♪
♪You can be expressionless
and pretend to be calm♪
♪The rhythm of your heart is the best proof♪
♪You never say anything,
your eyes send a message♪
♪You and I are the only ones
in the world who understand each other♪
♪The moment you think of me♪
♪I happen to be thinking of you too♪
♪I want to be closer to you,
a little closer to you♪
♪You can be expressionless,
pretending to be calm♪
♪The rhythm of your heart is the best proof♪
♪You never say anything,
your eyes send a message♪
♪You and I are the only ones in the world
who understand each other♪
♪The moment you think of me♪
♪I happen to be thinking of you too♪
♪You never say anything,
your eyes send a message♪
♪You and I are the only ones in the world
who understand each other♪
♪I like in every season♪
♪I'm at the top of your list♪