=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 31=
Father. Please come.
Houchi, what makes you so happy?
These are made by hand,
not by immortal skill.
You haven’t eaten dishes
of the human world for long, right?
Please sit and try it.
You made all these dishes?
I didn’t make the dishes.
But they contain my goodwill.
Qingmu made all these for you.
The fish is very fresh.
He caught it himself.
The fruit wine was brewed
by him from the plums
on the back mountains.
It took him a whole day
to finish all these dishes.
Please don’t give him
the cold shoulder again.
Houchi.
He made all these? Is it true?
Yes.
Have a try.
I may only eat
a meal he cooked once in this life.
Forget it.
Father.
If you like the meal,
Qingmu can cook it for you every day.
Lord Qingmu.
Yes?
Please be at ease.
Only if you are at ease,
I will feel at ease.
Yes.
Chang Que.
Yes, Your Grace.
Go bring ten
ten-thousand-year luminous pearls
as gifts for North Sea Lord.
Yes.
You made me a meal.
I give you ten luminous pearls.
I believe it’s fair to you.
Now it’s late.
I’m sorry we can’t keep you staying.
Please return to the North Sea early.
Fengran.
See our guest out.
Father.
Houchi.
God Gu Jun.
I love Houchi deeply
and sincerely hope
I can marry her.
Your Grace, why do you
insist on refusing?
Lord Qingmu.
You saved her many times.
We have a great appreciation for it.
You are a great one
from the Immortals.
But my daughter is too naughty.
She isn’t a good match for you.
Your Grace, you keep refusing.
Why are you so dissatisfied with me?
The only reason
is I don’t want
my precious daughter to leave me.
I disagree
with
your marriage.
Father.
Fengran.
See him out.
Yes, Your Grace.
Lord Qingmu, please.
Excuse me.
Qingmu.
Qingmu!
Father.
Father!
Father, why do you hate Qingmu so much?
I’ve said
it’s because I don’t want you to leave.
Since when you became so unreasonable?
All in the Three Realms look down on me.
But Qingmu never does.
He’s sincere to me,
always makes me happy,
and protects me with his life.
He’s willing
to be against the whole
Three Realms for me.
Why did you refuse him
with such a perfunctory excuse?
I didn’t mean that.
I have my reason.
It’s not up to me.
Why?
Because of my lot?
I always wanted to ask you about it.
I wasn’t given birth by Wu Huan,
and I have no blood of the flood dragon.
You didn’t take me back from somewhere.
I always thought
I couldn’t cultivate my spiritual power
because my spiritual veins
hadn’t been unleashed.
But Jingyuan told me
there is a powerful seal in me.
It suppressed my spiritual power.
I know he didn’t lie.
Because I often see
memories that don’t belong to me.
I even saw memories about the God Realm
when I was in the Pilgrimage Hall.
Father.
Why is it that I can see
memories about the God Realm?
Why is it that I can absorb
the Pilgrimage Hall’s spiritual power
that even the Heavenly Emperor can’t?
Houchi.
You’ve grown up.
I can’t keep hiding your lot from you.
Actually, the spiritual strength
of a Goddess is sleeping soundly in you.
And you
are her.
You mean
a Goddess from the God Realm?
The Tribulation of Chaos occurred
60,000 years ago.
Devils came to attack us.
Gods and Goddesses fell.
You once helped me a lot
with my cultivation.
I kept a little of your
spiritual strength
with all my God power in the calamity.
But it’s too weak.
So, I went to the human world
and cultivated it in the Huajing Pond
for thousands of years.
Then you were born.
How about Boxuan?
Is he from the God Realm as well?
No.
He’s just a usual immortal
in the Three Realms.
I helped him when I went to
the Immortal Realm.
In order to repay me,
he agreed to stay in the Qingchi Palace
to take care of you.
The spiritual strength in you
was sealed by Boxuan and me.
Father.
I still don’t understand.
She helped you.
Why didn’t you wake her up
after saving her?
That’s her last wish.
As a Goddess,
she would have to
be responsible for all beings.
She couldn’t master her own destiny.
When she died
in the Tribulation of Chaos,
her last wish was...
Wish I wouldn’t be a Goddess
in the next life.
If there is the next life,
she wished never to be a Goddess.
Even if she lost her memories,
she is still the most honorable one
in the Three Realms.
So,
I’m really not your daughter.
I’m just from some spiritual strength.
Boxuan and you are good to me
only because of
that spiritual strength in me.
In order to fulfill her last wish,
you sealed my spiritual power
since I was born,
in spite of making me a laughing stock
across the Three Realms.
Houchi.
It’s not what you think.
Is she Chief Goddess Shanggu?
How could you know that?
I saw her when I devoured
the Pilgrimage Hall.
She looked the same as me.
Father.
Before, I thought
I was abandoned by my mother,
but
Father and Boxuan loved me.
Now I see.
I just exist
for fulfilling another one’s wish.
Since the body shouldn’t belong to me,
why did you give life to me?
I...
never really owned anything.
Identity. Family.
Nothing belongs to me.
Houchi.
Boxuan and I just hope you to be safe
and live a carefree life.
I don’t want to hear that!
I don’t want to hear
any of your explanations.
You both care about her only.
Houchi.
Houchi!
I’m sorry.
Houchi.
What is it?
What happened?
Are you angry with your father?
Silly.
Now that he refused me this time,
I can just try harder.
He’s your father,
the one who loves you the most.
You shouldn’t be mad with him for me.
You don’t understand.
He’s not...
Not what?
What happened exactly?
Qingmu, do you like me?
Of course.
Am I really the one you like?
Me, Houchi?
Of course, it’s you.
Who else could it be?
I’ve told you
that it’s destiny that tied us together.
When I saw you for the first time,
I found you very familiar.
I felt that
we had been acquainted for eons.
In fact, I knew you
earlier than you thought.
A thousand years ago,
I woke up in the North Sea
without any memory.
But I kept dreaming of a girl.
What girl?
She’s in a dark black ancient robe
and stands in the thunder.
For eons?
Do you like me
or the one you’ve been missing
for eons in your dream?
It’s you who’s in my dream.
No, it’s not.
She and I
aren’t the same person.
I never wore a dark black ancient robe.
And I was never in your dream.
She is not me.
Qingmu, answer me.
If you didn’t see
the bracelet on me
on that day when we met
for the first time on Mount Lookout,
or feel
I’m the destined one for you,
would you still have gone to the Demons
with me,
protected me with your life,
and fallen in love with me?
I...
I see.
You are all the same.
You protect me and are good to me
with your life because of
the spiritual strength in me, right?
What spiritual strength?
I don’t understand, Houchi.
The one you like
is in my body.
One body can’t have two souls.
She would devour me.
Or she might completely vanish.
I wish I could be with you
not as a god
in the next life.
Shanggu.
I won’t allow you to die.
If only one can survive,
which will you pick?
Don’t hurt her!
Don’t hurt her?
Leave.
I don’t want to see you ever again.
No, Houchi.
I don’t know why I said so.
Listen to me.
Qingmu.
I’ve told you
not to stay at Qilian Mountains.
Your Grace.
After getting Houchi back,
I will come to apologize.
You are not clear about your feelings.
Even if you get her back,
it will be meaningless.
What do you mean?
Houchi just asked you
which you would pick if only one in her
could survive.
You even couldn’t answer.
How could you say you love her?
I...
I don’t understand.
The spiritual strength in her?
What does it mean?
Houchi
was not my daughter.
She was cultivated with
the spiritual strength of Shanggu.
The spiritual strength is very powerful.
Once it wakes up,
Houchi will lose her memories,
which means she won’t exist anymore.
Qingmu.
Houchi is not a normal immortal.
You two being together
will only lead to a bad ending.
End your relationship early
so that you won’t get hurt
in the future.
No.
I won’t give up Houchi.
Haven’t you ever doubted?
You feel familiar with her.
You value her.
Is it just because she’s Houchi?
If you even haven’t figured out
who you are exactly,
how could you marry her?
Isn’t it too early?
Excuse me,
but Your Grace,
do you mean True God Bai Jue?
Seems you’ve got an answer.
Boxuan.
Did you take care of me
for requiting favors of Father?
Why do you all protect me?
All for her, right?
Boxuan.
I’ve made up my mind.
I will leave the Qingchi Palace
and travel around the Three Realms.
Father.
Jingjian.
What’s that?
I received a Chihe Jade recently.
Hope you will like it.
Jingjian.
You’ve always been obedient.
As early as your mother
was in the God Realm,
she liked jade from Chihe in particular.
How about giving it to her?
No problem, Father.
Report!
Your Majesty.
Information from the Demon Region!
Go ahead.
The Demons attacked
the Demon Region again.
Prince Jingyang asked
if you could reinforce
to help him fight back
or even merge the Demons.
Let Jingyang only defend the barrier.
If the Demons don’t attack us,
never send an army into the battle.
Yes!
Father.
If the Demon God attacks,
I’m afraid Jingyang will...
It seems
I need to visit the Qingchi Palace
in person.
Your Highness.
I’ve taken away the heavenly guards
according to your order
and framed the Demons.
It caused conflict as expected.
Information from the Demon Region
said Prince Jingyang
had asked for reinforcements.
What did His Majesty say?
His Majesty only wants peace.
He didn’t permit any counterattack.
Sure enough.
Fengnyu,
assign forces
to the Demon Region to help Jingyang.
Remember.
Secretly help him instigate rebellion
within the Demons.
If His Majesty knows this,
he will blame you.
There’ll be deaths in any battle.
The Demon Region will have
much pure evil
that I can use.
Comparing with that,
it doesn’t matter even if I’m blamed.
Let go of me. Let go of me!
Don’t move!
Let go of me!
Kid!
If you keep being disobedient,
I will swallow you right now.
Immortal Miss, help!
Immortal?
How bold you are!
The Immortals and the Demons shouldn’t
intrude into the human world.
How could you snatch a mortal in secret?
Who are you?
How dare you intervene!
I work for the Three-head Fire Dragon.
This girl is an oblation for him.
You’d better get lost.
If he is displeased,
he may destroy your monastery.
My monastery?
If he dares to come to Qilian Mountains,
I will warmly welcome him.
Are you... Goddess Houchi
from the Qingchi Palace?
Let’s go.
What’s your name? Where do you live?
My name is Bai Shuo.
I live in Dibei Town.
How were you taken here?
I don’t know.
I found myself caught once I woke up.
Immortal Miss,
I want to go home.
Don’t worry.
I’ll take you back right now.
Houchi doesn’t want to be
in the Immortal Realm
(Travelling the Three Realms. By Houchi)
or go to the Demon Realm.
She’ll only go to the Human Realm.
Dear,
don’t cry.
I’ve sent the guards to look for her.
It’s useless.
Children got missing one after another.
People say it’s the demons who did that.
I’m afraid Shuo was also taken away.
No, it can’t be.
Shuo!
Dad.
Shuo, where have you been?
Dad,
I was caught by the demons.
It’s Immortal Miss who saved me.
Thank you for saving my daughter.
That’s nothing.
Don’t mention it.
I’ve set a barrier out of your mansion.
No demons can come again.
Dear,
leave with Shuo.
All right.
Here’s the thing.
I’m the master here.
Many demons have come to
the town recently.
I assigned many guards to patrol.
But there’re still lots of kids missing.
Now
I really don’t know how to protect
the people in the town.
You are powerful.
Please stay
and defend our Dibei Town, will you?
I will check it right now.
Thank you.
Hey.
Her Grace has left.
But His Grace doesn’t
worry about her at all.
How do you know he doesn’t?
What’s more,
Lord Qingmu has gone to look for her.
They will return very soon.
It isn’t that easy.
I heard
His Grace and Her Grace
had a fierce quarrel.
Her Grace left in tears.
You saw it personally?
No.
Then why did you talk nonsense?
His Grace doesn’t like talking.
But he loves Her Grace the most.
How would he quarrel with her?
Her Grace had been waiting for
her father for long.
Now that she left home.
I’m sure she was heartbroken.
Stop talking nonsense.
If His Grace heard this,
he would feel very sad.
Don’t you have anything to be busy with?
- Your Grace.
Your Grace,
I will prepare some herbs.
Please excuse me to leave.
Come on!
Your Grace,
please don’t mind their nonsense.
Houchi is just angry temporarily.
She will come back
after she calms down.
Houchi is in Bai’s Mansion
in the human world with Lord Qingmu
protecting her.
Don’t worry.
You may go rest.
You’ve known it?
(Travelling the Three Realms.
Don’t look for me. By Houchi)
Since the body shouldn’t belong to me,
why did you give life to me?
I...
never really owned anything.
Identity. Family.
Nothing belongs to me.
You both care about her only.
Houchi.
I hope that day
would never come.
Let’s go.
Stop!
Let go of the kids!
Houchi...!
If she doesn’t want to see me...
Please spare us! Please!
Who is your master?
How dare you snatch kids here!
We work for Three-head Fire Dragon.
He ordered us to come to the human world
to get boys and girls
for his cultivation.
Please spare us!
We did this by order.
Three-head Fire Dragon?
Go back to the Demon Realm.
If you invade the human world again,
I will let you vanish.
Yes! Yes!
The Heavenly Emperor and the Demon King
made an agreement 60,000 years ago.
Neither the Immortals nor the Demons can
invade the human world.
How come Three-head Fire Dragon
is so bold?
Maybe
something happened to the Demons.
Go to the Xuanjing Palace
and tell Jingyuan
that I’m waiting for him in Dibei Town
in the human world.
I need to protect the people here first.
It’s been 60,000 years.
The Qingchi Palace hasn’t changed.
Gu Jun.
It was my fault
that I didn’t protect Houchi well
on that day
on the Green Dragon Platform.
Let bygones be bygones.
I don’t think you are here
for a general talk, right?
Gu Jun.
Tell me the truth.
Is Houchi Master Shanggu?
No.
If not, how could she
get into the Pilgrimage Hall
and inherit the Power of Chaos in it?
Houchi could get into
the Pilgrimage Hall
all because of an opportunity.
She was lucky.
Forget it.
If you don’t want to mention it,
I won’t ask.
I believe you’ve known
that the Demon God appeared.
Unexpectedly,
he hides in the Demon Realm in the name
of Demon Lord Ziyue.
He’s patient enough
for appearing till now,
given his temper in old days.
The Demon God is ambitious.
He tried to become the God of Chaos
with the lives of the Three Realms.
Now he’s back.
Surely he would do the same thing again.
We need to find a way to stop him.
Only the three True Gods
could stop him at that time.
Now, all of them already fell.
Nobody can stop the Demon God
if he really wants to
destroy the Three Realms.
He used his power
at the Heavenly Palace last time.
I could feel that his power
as a True God hasn’t recovered.
Even so,
I’m not sure if we can kill him
with the power of us three.
But if
we can restart the God Realm
and wake up the sleeping Gods,
maybe we can stop him.
Restart the God Realm?
It won’t be that easy.
If only we get
the four weapons of True Gods,
we can restart the God Realm.
Now the Taicang Spear
has chosen its master.
The Twin Spear’s buried near the barrier
between the Immortal and Demon Realms.
Once we find the Ancestral Sword
and the Purple Moon Whip,
it won’t be hard to restart
the God Realm.
The Purple Moon Whip disappeared
during the Tribulation of Chaos.
I’m afraid the Demon God already got it.
So, we need to
find out the other three weapons
before his power of True God recovers.
In that case,
we will have a chance to win.
Gu Jun.
No matter how hard it is,
we have to try.
Master Zhiyang
left the Three Realms to us.
We can’t just watch it
being destroyed by the Demon God.
It’s about the beings.
I shouldn’t refuse.
We’ve tried last time,
but we couldn’t open the Skyreach Pillar
and get the Twin Spear.
That’s why I’m here today.
I want you to take Qingmu with you
to go to the Skyreach Pillar.
Both the Taicang Spear
and the Twin Spear
were made by Ancestral God Qingtian.
Maybe
Qingmu can take back the Twin Spear
with the power of the Taicang Spear.
After getting the two weapons,
even if we can’t restart the God Realm,
we can restrict the Demon God at least.
Okay. I will do it.
Fengran, go take Qingmu back.
Yes, Your Grace.
He must have returned to the North Sea.
Immortal Miss.
What is it?
Immortal Miss,
whom are you missing?
I’ve been calling you for a long time.
What’s the matter?
Could you play with me?
Okay. Let’s go.
You really aren’t clear about your mind?
I only love Houchi.
How could you say so?
It’s just that I dare not see her.
I worry that our happiness
won’t last long.
Why not long?
If you are determined,
how could it end in a flash?
No matter what, it’s about Houchi.
I have to think it twice.
By the way,
God Gu Jun wants to see you.
God Gu Jun wants to see me?
Maybe I can’t
help clear up your confusion now.
But when you go back,
you may win
that picky old man’s favor.
Your Majesty.
I just came back
from the Parasol Forest.
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
What happened to the Feng Clan?
A group of phoenixes will pip.
Phoenix’s pipping is a major event.
I’m the leader of the Feng Clan.
How could I not be there?
So, I stayed in the Parasol Forest
for a few days
and attended some affairs.
Huan.
Just ask Fengnyu
to deal with the chores.
You don’t need to work so hard.
Elder Feng Yun appointed me
as leader of the Clan before his death.
I can’t betray his trust.
You are already occupied with
managing the Heavenly Palace.
I just hope you can be
a little light-hearted.
Forget it.
Let’s not talk about it.
Do you like
the Chihe Jade?
Very much.
That’s nice.
Your Majesty,
I don’t think you asked me here
only for this.
The Immortals and the Demons
are fighting in the Demon Region.
Did you send reinforcements
for Jingyang?
The Demons always want a fight.
Now that the battle has started,
how could they stop easily?
You ordered Jingyang not to attack.
He has no helping hand
in the Demon Region.
If anything happens to him,
what should I do?
Jingyang is always impatient.
This is a chance
for him to practice.
Do you remember the peace
of the Three Realms
before the God Realm was closed?
But now, the Immortals and the Demons
don’t get along.
We don’t live up
to Master’s expectation.
You are the Heavenly Emperor.
You can ignore Jingyang’s safety
for the Three Realms.
But I’m a mother.
I can’t leave my child alone.
Huan.
I know you worry about him.
But as for increasing forces,
I hope it won’t happen again.
Your Highness.
It’s the critical moment to increase
my God power.
Nobody can stop me.
Kill those who have a big mouth.
Yes.
(Qingchi Palace)
The Demon God is still alive?
God Gu Jun.
True God Bai Jue
killed the Demon God at that time,
didn’t he?
Nobody can figure out
his thoughts.
Four True Gods were like brothers.
Maybe True God Bai Jue
wasn’t that hardhearted.
A God who tried to
destroy the Three Realms.
I don’t think mercy was necessary.
You are young.
You may say so.
I called you here because
I want you to help the Heavenly Palace
restart the God Realm
to defend the Three Realms.
God Gu Jun, please rest assured.
I’ve got the Taicang Spear.
Even if you didn’t ask me to,
I would not allow the war between
the Immortals and the Demons to begin.
Good.
In this case,
you may take a break today
and go with me
to the Skyreach Pillar
for the Twin Spear.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪