=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 32=
I called you here because
I want you to help the Heavenly Palace
restart the God Realm
to defend the Three Realms.
God Gun Jun, please rest assured.
I’ve got the Taicang Spear.
Even if you didn’t ask me to,
I would not allow the war between
the Immortals and the Demons to begin.
Good.
In this case,
you may take a break today
and go with me
to the Skyreach Pillar
for the Twin Spear tomorrow.
Yes.
Go ahead.
Come out.
Why are you here?
I’m having a rest here
and you happen to be here, too.
A coincidence again?
You think I can’t sense you?
Was the one in Dibei Town
also you?
Yes.
Why are you so furtive?
I...
What?
I’m here to apologize.
For what?
For many things.
What my mother and brother did
and what happened
on the Green Dragon Platform.
Those things have nothing
to do with you.
How are you
recently?
Not bad.
I’m at leisure in the Heavenly Palace.
If you need any assistance,
you can call me upon.
No need.
You have nothing else to say?
I’m going back to
the Qingchi Palace then.
Why do you follow me again?
We’re going the same way.
The Heavenly Palace and the Qingchi
Palace aren’t in the same direction.
My father is in the Qingchi Palace now.
I will go back with him.
The Heavenly Emperor
has gone back already.
He has?
What on earth do you want?
Nothing.
Inexplicable!
I miss you!
Catch up.
Zihan,
I’m going to the human world.
You tell Sen Jian,
he can make decisions about
the war situation in the Demon Region.
Yes.
Master, where are you going?
Houchi asked me to meet her
in the human world.
Everyone in the Three Realms
has known your reappearance.
I think she’s already known
your identity.
She makes an appointment with you now.
Is it that she’s remembered something?
I hope so.
How’s it?
Perfect.
Even Sen Yun couldn’t defeat me
back then.
If you surrender now,
maybe I can let you go.
How arrogant!
I’ll kill you with my sword today
to offer a sacrifice to my brother.
Let’s go! Hurry!
Come on!
Run!
(Bai’s Mansion)
Come on! Hurry!
Mother!
- Come on.
- Run!
Run!
Water! Come on!
Hurry!
Here!
What strong fire!
Is it the Immortals and the Demons
are fighting at the Demon Region?
Goddess,
the disaster
is striking Dibei Town.
Please save us!
Mr. Bai,
my Immortal Shield
can’t protect the town long.
Lead the masses to leave here
as far as possible!
Darling.
Take care of the kid.
All right.
Guys!
Yes!
Evacuate the masses.
Let’s go!
Congratulations, Your Highness!
You finally reached
the highest level of a Goddess.
The Sky Bow
is really a treasure
for gathering evil force.
It’s very beneficial to cultivation.
But I heard
His Majesty had ordered Prince Jingyang
to defend only, instead of attacking.
I’m afraid the Immortals and the Demons
will resume peace soon.
Without the innocent dead,
how can you get enough evil force
for cultivation?
It’s not enough
by capturing only one heavenly guard
to trigger the war against the Demons.
It seems
I should do something.
Your Grace,
aren’t we going to take the Twin Spear?
Why did we come here?
You don’t know,
when the God Realm was in disaster,
Master Zhiyang threw the Twin Spear
to the Three Realms,
which turned into the Skyreach Pillar,
as the boundary
of the Immortals and the Demons.
You mean,
the Twin Spear
is inside the Skyreach Pillar?
Why didn’t you and the Heavenly Emperor
get it for all these years?
Leaving the weapon here
may offer an opportunity for the Demons.
Even Demon God Tianqi
can’t take it away.
How can the other demons make it?
Except Master Zhiyang,
the only one who can get the Twin Spear
is you.
Go ahead.
Take it now!
Master Bai Jue?
Your Grace,
on the Green Dragon Platform back then,
what the Heavenly Empress said is right.
I do have some demon power in my body,
which makes me lose control sometimes.
When I took the Twin Spear just now,
the demon power appeared again.
I don’t know
what on earth is going on.
You’re born outstanding.
If the demon power
can help you with your cultivation,
you needn’t get to the bottom of it.
The Twin Spear guarded the boundary
for tens of thousands of years.
It naturally has some power
from the Immortals and the Demons.
Maybe that power entered your body
and impacted you.
Your Grace,
I have a request.
Keep the Twin Spear well.
It’ll be useful in the future.
Go back to the North Sea now.
Qingmu,
you’re the one
selected by the Taicang Spear,
and the only one who can
get the Twin Spear in the Three Realms.
Listen to me,
the affections between you and Houchi
are just temporary.
Your Grace,
now that I got the Twin Spear,
I think I’ve known my origins.
I’ve been thinking it over recently.
I’m afraid I can’t follow your will.
Since you’ve known it,
why do you still choose affections?
Maybe Houchi and I
will both be replaced by the True Gods,
but the affections between Houchi and me
are sincere,
and even more important than my life.
If I give up now,
I’ll surely regret it one day.
Please agree to our being together.
Stand up.
If you don’t agree,
I won’t stand up.
You’re threatening me?
I have no other choice.
I’ve reasoned with you,
tried to stop you,
and even scolded you.
I have no other way.
Thank you, Your Grace!
I didn’t agree.
It’s you who insisted on this.
Don’t blame me for it in the future.
Please rest assured.
I promise I will protect Houchi well.
Take good care of her.
Treat her well
every day.
Fine.
Let it be.
Your Grace, bad news!
What is it?
The Immortals and the Demons
are fighting at the Demon Region,
which is a disaster for the human world.
Houchi went to stop the fight alone.
He has two weapons of True Gods
with him.
They’re enough for him
to deal with the fight
and protect Houchi well.
Follow me to another place.
Where?
The Heavenly Palace.
What strong fire!
Goddess Houchi,
what are you doing here?
Your fight
has involved the human world
and the mortals.
Dibei Town under the Demon Region
has become a hell now.
If you don’t stop now,
I will kill all of you.
The lives of the mortals
is not as important as
our immortals’ peace.
Protecting the human world
is your responsibility.
As a prince of the Heavenly Palace,
how can you ignore human lives?
For the past tens of thousands of years,
many heavenly guards died or wounded
for protecting them,
while your Qingchi Palace
stood by and did nothing.
How can you
give me a lesson here?
I’ll give you a good lesson
for the Heavenly Emperor today.
Houchi,
you really want to help the Demons?
I won’t help any side.
If you stop now,
I’ll leave here immediately.
No way!
Houchi.
Mother.
Greetings, Your Highness.
You do collude with the Demons.
No wonder the Demon God made trouble
in the Heavenly Palace for you.
I should have killed you
on the Green Dragon Platform.
Greetings, Master.
Master?
Isn’t it the form of address
used for a True God?
I went to Dibei Town to meet you,
but you
came to the Demon Region.
Jingyuan hasn’t regained
the power of True God.
I’ve reached the highest level
of a Goddess.
I’d better take this opportunity
to kill him,
solving the trouble forever.
Wu Huan,
I’ve warned you.
If you dare to hurt Houchi again,
I’ll wipe out the Heavenly Palace.
Demon God,
you’re deeply guilty
for hurting the Three Realms.
Everyone should kill you.
I won’t be threatened by you.
You’re the Demon God?
Houchi,
don’t pretend here.
The Demon God protected you many times.
How could you not know his identity?
I will take both of you down today,
so that you won’t hurt
the Three Realms anymore.
Until now,
you’re still turning the facts
upside down.
60,000 years ago,
it’s you who made Yue...
- Go!
- Come on!
- Leave here now!
- Go!
- Come on!
- Hurry!
Hurry up!
Go!
Come on!
Forget it!
- Go!
- Thank you.
Come on! Go!
Go!
Let me go!
- Come on, leave here!
- Let me go!
Come back!
Kid.
Whose kid is she?
Come on.
Thank you!
- Don’t be afraid.
- Dear!
Thank you.
Dear.
Darling.
Father.
Dear.
Leave here with the kid first.
No!
Let’s leave together.
Leave now!
- No!
- Come on!
Let’s leave together!
Shuo!
Father!
Dear! Dear!
Dear!
Father!
Heavenly Empress!
A lot of people live
under the Demon Region.
The fire’s falling down
will kill all of them.
So what?
To kill demons like you,
we have to sacrifice something.
We’re demons?
As the empress of the Heavenly Realm,
you ignore people’s life.
You’re the evilest demon!
Sharp-tongued.
What?
With the protection of the Demon God,
you dare act recklessly.
Do you really think
he can protect you today?
Of course,
I can protect her.
Tianqi,
as a superior God
for tens of thousands of years,
you should know
the feelings of being inferior today.
Low-born phoenix,
what unlawful and tricky ways
have you used in your cultivation?
How come your power improved so much?
Now, do you still think
you can win?
Fine.
I’ll find another opportunity.
Qingmu,
you stole the Immortals’ treasure
and collude with the Demon God.
The Heavenly Palace won’t forgive you.
How are you feeling? Are you injured?
At 3:00 PM,
I’ll meet you outside Dibei Town.
Okay.
Master,
I felt the Purple Moon was shivering
in the Third Heaven.
Are you all right?
I’m fine.
Is it Qingmu who
caused you to shiver the Purple Moon?
No.
It’s Wu Huan.
Really?
How come she has
that strong spiritual power?
Did you get hurt?
How could I
be hurt by that low-born phoenix?
But her power has improved
so much in such a short time.
There must be something fishy.
Sen Yu,
go back to the Third Heaven
and tell Sen Jian
to guard the Demon Region in person.
Yes, Master.
What about Three-head?
After his spiritual power
was weakened by me,
I didn’t expect that he would
use an evil way for cultivation.
Hadn’t I
been to Dibei Town,
I would still be kept in the dark.
He should learn a good lesson this time.
Listen, everyone,
I’m going to Dibei Town now.
Before I come back,
follow whatever the Demon King says.
Yes, Master.
Father!
Darling!
Immortal Miss!
Immortal Miss,
you’re an immortal.
Please!
Please save my father!
My father was hit by fire
when protecting me.
Please! Save my father!
Immortal Miss!
Shuo.
Even I’m an immortal,
I can’t bring the dead back to life.
I... I can’t save your father.
Miss, please save my father!
Father,
open your eyes
and look at your daughter.
Darling!
Father!
Shuo!
Make way.
Houchi,
even the Demon God can’t defeat her.
You can do nothing
even you go to the Heavenly Palace now.
Because she’s the Heavenly Empress,
I can’t accuse her
of killing these people?
In her eyes,
mortals are like ants.
Ants?
They’re living people.
I don’t believe
there is no justice in the Three Realms.
Calm down!
Think about God Gun Jun.
Do you want him to lose his beloved
like Bai Shuo?
I’m useless.
I can’t protect them.
Are you really the Demon God?
Who I am
depends on you.
If you like me to be the Demon God,
I am Tianqi.
If you like me to be Demon Lord Ziyue,
I am Jingyuan.
Why?
You’re scared of me?
Even you think the Demon God
is unpardonably vicious?
You saved me several times.
I never think so.
But you shouldn’t have
allowed the Demons to fight.
The Immortals asked for it!
Jingyuan,
your fight with the Immortals
will not only kill your people,
but also the humans.
Why must you start the war?
I just return like for like.
If they continue fighting,
the hatred will become
increasingly deeper.
Jingyuan,
countless people have died.
As the Demon God,
ask them to stop, will you?
Fine.
I promise,
if only the Immortals
won’t offend us again,
I can stop the fight.
Except this,
I have another request.
Please help break my seal.
Why so suddenly?
Didn’t you refuse me in the Qingchi…?
For them,
I’d like to break it.
I want to have strong power.
Them?
Who are they?
The people in the town,
the human world,
and even the Three Realms.
Do you think
I’m boasting
by mentioning
protecting the Three Realms?
Before,
I didn’t know
what it means to be an immortal,
always idling away my time in pleasure
in the Qingchi Palace.
Time flies.
60,000 years have passed.
Hadn’t I come to the human world
accidentally,
I wouldn’t have learned
that immortals can
have another way of living.
What way?
As an immortal,
I should protect the lives
in the Three Realms.
But I can’t protect anyone,
because I’m too weak.
Now the Demons and the Immortals
always fight.
Both sides can’t live well,
even bringing disasters
to the 60,000-year-old human world.
If I want to protect the lives
in the Three Realms
with my power,
I have to own stronger power.
That day, you refused me
so decisively and clearly.
But now, why?
You have quarreled with Qingmu
and don’t want to stay with him,
living your happy life together
in the quiet Qingchi Palace?
It has nothing to do with him.
Aren’t you afraid the Spiritual Strength
in your body would awaken
and devour you?
No, I’m not.
I’ve been existing for 60,000 years.
No one can obliterate this fact.
All right.
I agree to help you.
But I’m afraid
not today.
Why?
My power as a True God hasn’t recovered.
If I want to break your seal,
I’ll have to use my Purple Moon Whip.
But the Purple Moon Whip
has turned into the Purple Moon
which is supporting
the whole Demon Realm.
Before we stop the fight,
I can’t take it back.
Okay. I’ll wait.
Let’s go.
North Sea Lord, what are you doing?
You needn’t worry about
Houchi’s affairs.
How could you
decide it for her?
We’ll get married soon.
So, of course, I can decide.
Qingmu.
You’ll get married?
Did Gu Jun agree?
Of course,
Gu Jun has agreed
the marriage of Houchi and me.
How come my father...?
Do you know whom you’ll marry?
Of course, I do.
No matter in heaven or on the earth,
or across the Three Realms,
she’s the only one.
So what if Gu Jun has agreed?
I disagree.
North Sea Lord,
thank you for helping us today.
Go back to the North Sea now.
Demon Lord Ziyue,
please don’t forget your promise today.
Please go back as well.
Master,
if Master Shanggu and Master Bai Jue
be together again...
It won’t be that simple.
In the Demon Region,
Qingmu helped me
in front of so many people.
Wu Huan is suspicious.
The Heavenly Palace will no longer trust
the North Sea and the Qingchi Palace.
It will try every method
to cope with them.
But if Houchi’s seal isn’t broken,
with limited spiritual power,
she’ll be in danger.
Let her stay in the Human Realm now.
After I have dealt with Wu Huan,
I’ll help Houchi break her seal.
Your Majesty,
North Sea Lord Qingmu and Houchi
have betrayed the Immortals
and colluded with the Demon God.
Please issue an edict to arrest them.
Mother,
Qingmu is the best Lord
among the immortals
and Houchi is the daughter
of God Gu Gun.
Is there...
Is there any misunderstanding?
Misunderstanding?
In the fight in the Demon Region,
they helped the Demon God
in front of the two armies,
witnessed by so many people.
How could they be misunderstood?
Father...
I witnessed it with my own eyes.
Hadn’t Mother arrived in time,
I would have been killed by Houchi.
Please make a wise decision, Father.
Your Majesty.
Qingmu has not only the Taicang Spear,
but also the Twin Spear.
If we can’t get him back
to the Heavenly Palace
before he becomes a God,
he will become a big trouble
for the Immortals in the future.
Your Majesty.
Messenger!
Send my edict.
Report!
God Gun Jun is here!
Greetings, God Gun Jun.
Gu Jun,
why are you here?
If I didn’t come here,
you would have issued an edict,
and my Qingchi Palace would be charged
of colluding with the Demon God
and hurting the Three Realms.
Gu Jun,
there hasn’t been a conclusion.
I’m just going to ask them back
to make it clear.
Don’t bother.
It’s me who asked them
to go to the Demon Region.
It’s also you who asked them
to collude with the Demon God?
If I wanted to collude with
the Demon God,
I wouldn’t have waited until now.
I would have wiped out the Immortals
with him 60,000 years ago.
God Gun Jun, you mean
you want to be an enemy
to the Heavenly Palace
and betray the Immortals?
Wu Huan,
you’re talking nonsense.
Gu Jun,
I never suspected
your intention.
But why did you ask them
to help the Demon God
at the Demon Region?
They went there
not to help the Demon God,
but to stop the fight
between the Immortals and the Demons.
Your fight with the Demons
can’t involve the human world.
That is the rule made and publicized
by the Heavenly Emperor
and the Demon King back then.
Hadn’t
Qingmu and Houchi arrived in time,
the human world
would’ve had more than one town ruined.
If the Immortals are defeated,
the Demons will become
the scourge of the world.
Will the human world be peaceful then?
The Immortals should
protect the human world.
That is the iron rule
made by True God Zhiyang.
If you don’t fight with the Demons,
the whole world will be in peace.
I asked Jingjian to make peace
with the Demons,
but the Demon God went back on his word
and started the fight.
If we don’t fight back,
we’ll follow the same
old disastrous road.
Gu Jun,
I asked you
to take Qingmu to get back
the Twin Spear
in order to collect all the four
Weapons of True Gods
to reopen the God Realm
and restrict the Demons.
No matter why
Qingmu did so in the Demon Region today,
he did help the Demons.
If you want me to believe
he’s still loyal,
he must return the Twin Spear
to the Heavenly Palace.
I’ll give you three days.
Fine.
It’s a deal.
No wonder you’ve been merciful
towards Houchi and Qingmu.
Turns out you still want to
reopen the God Realm.
Houchi.
Houchi!
Why did you stop Jingyuan
to break my seal?
Because I don’t want to lose you.
But the one you really love...
I love you.
That day, you asked me
when we met for the first time
on Mount Lookout...
If you didn’t see
the bracelet on me
on that day when we met
for the first time on Mount Lookout,
or feel
I’m the destined one for you,
would you still have gone to the Demons
with me,
protected me with your life,
and fallen in love with me?
My answer is yes.
I don’t care who you were,
or who’s in your body,
for me, you’re Houchi,
the only one in the whole world,
and the one I love with my life.
So, I don’t want you
to become anyone else.
If you lie to me...
If I tell any lie to you,
I’m willing to be stricken by
49 thunder strikes.
Thunder strikes won’t kill you.
That vow is not effective.
Then... turn me black.
Houchi,
I dare not lie to you.
Losing you is more terrible than death.
I know you felt sad,
and you didn’t know whom to tell
and what to do.
But don’t worry.
No matter what happens,
I will always accompany you
and protect you.
I couldn’t save Shuo’s father.
If I were a little stronger,
she wouldn’t have lost her father.
It’s not your fault.
Don’t worry.
One day,
we will return to the Ninth Heaven
and let justice prevail
for what happened today.
(Bai’s Mansion)
(Memorial)
- Shuo.
- You like her?
Hadn’t I met this family,
I might still blame my father.
God Gun Jun is not your birth father,
but he treats you better than
your birth father.
I didn’t realize it before.
It’s said the dead mortal
will be led to the immortal river
by heaven lanterns,
hoping to become an immortal
in the next life,
not to be shackled by the mortal life.
But they don’t know
even Gods
can’t do everything they want.
Houchi, it’s not your fault.
Don’t blame yourself.
Qingmu.
I want to break my seal.
It’s not an act on impulse.
Now the Immortals
and the Demons are opponents,
and the human world is suffering.
The world is no longer peaceful.
My father is old.
And he has old wounds.
I can’t let him face the disputes
among the Three Realms alone.
You have me.
I’ll protect the human world
and the Qingchi Palace.
On the Green Dragon Platform that day,
I told you
that I wouldn’t let you
face any danger or difficulty alone.
I want to be the one
who can fight with you,
instead of standing behind you
and letting you protect me.
Don’t worry.
Even I have broken my seal,
I will still remember you
and what happened between us.
No matter what you do,
promise me
you won’t leave me.
The fight between the Immortals
and the Demons has ceased.
Dibei Town has no danger now.
Let’s go back to the Qingchi Palace.
God Gu Jun has been waiting for you.
What’s wrong with you?
Since I got the Twin Spear,
my spiritual power has been turbulent.
I saw him.
Who?
Boxuan.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪