=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 25=
Master,
aren’t we here to celebrate
the birthday of Her Grace?
Why don’t you go to her?
Zihan.
We’ve been in the Qingchi Palace
for a while.
There are still many things
I need to deal with
in the Demon Realm.
Let’s go back.
Sen Jian will take care of it.
We can stay in the Qingchi Palace
for a few more days.
Wu Huan knows who I am now.
The Demons will be prepared.
Your Highness, you brought these
heavenly soldiers to the Qingchi Palace.
What do you mean by that?
I’m here to bring the edict
from the Heavenly Palace
to Qingmu.
Please let us in, Lady Fengran.
Since it’s the edict from
the Heavenly Palace,
you can go inside, Your Highness.
But it’s the rule in the Qingchi Palace
that people with no fixed duties
are not allowed to enter.
The carriages should be left outside.
You shall wait here.
Yes.
Why did the Heavenly Palace
order you to come here
with heavenly soldiers?
To pressure or to provoke us?
Is it because you think you can
push us around in the Qingchi Palace?
If God Gu Jun were here,
how dare you run wild here?
Calm down first.
Let’s talk inside.
I won’t.
Then let me ask you,
where is Qingmu?
Answer my question first.
Why do you want to see Qingmu?
Fine.
Since you won’t tell me,
I’ll ask someone
to poke the hornet’s nest
in front of the mountain.
We will see how your
heavenly soldiers are going to suffer.
Do you have a problem with it?
I dare not.
It’s totally up to you
whether to poke the hornet’s nest
of the Qingchi Palace or not.
I’m glad you know it.
After you vent your anger,
I’ll give them some plasters
to relieve swelling and pain.
You are going to suffer
if the Queen of Heaven hears that.
As long as you are happy.
Forget it.
Those heavenly soldiers
just take orders.
They shouldn’t be punished.
The one who should be punished
is you.
Yes, yes.
After this is over,
you can do whatever you want to do.
You are even more stubborn
than stone.
Huan.
What are you thinking about?
You’ve been unsettling recently.
What’s on your mind?
What else can I think about?
It’s still about our child.
Is it for Jingzhao’s marriage?
Jingjian has gone to see Qingmu.
He will give us his answer.
What if he rejects it?
Qingmu were close to Houchi
when they were on Mount Lookout.
I’m afraid
he has feelings for her.
Your Majesty!
Jingzhao is infatuated with him.
But if Qingmu doesn’t love her,
we should just let it go.
Looks like I worry too much about it.
What do you mean?
Qingmu has the Taicang Spear.
If he can’t be used by us,
I’m afraid it will remain
a distant possibility
to reopen the God Realm.
Just tell us.
What exactly does
the Heavenly Palace want?
Are you here to get back at Qingmu
for hurting your younger sister
on Mount Lookout?
Jingjian.
You and Qingmu are close friends.
You can’t just turn your back on him.
Fengran.
His Highness said
the edict from the Heavenly Palace
is for Qingmu.
Since it’s between them,
I don’t think we should intervene.
Don’t make it difficult for him.
Houchi.
I know it’s improper to bring
those heavenly soldiers,
but my mother ordered me to do it.
Since it’s her order,
you don’t need to explain it.
I don’t want
to hear a word about her.
What’s going on here?
Ask him.
Weren’t you on good terms yesterday?
Why are you being so cold today?
We are never on good terms.
Qingmu.
It’s serious. Don’t make jokes.
I need to have a word with you.
Just stay.
Fengran, let’s go somewhere else.
What puts you
in a spot like this?
You can be frank with me.
It’s not that I don’t want to be frank.
I just don’t think
you are going to like it.
My father and mother
want you to take over
the Commander in Chief
and command 100,000 heavenly soldiers.
Because of the Taicang Spear?
Yes.
I don’t like constraint.
You know it.
Just turn them down for me.
It would be easy
if that was the only reason I’m here.
I also brought Father’s edict to you.
He asked me to come to
the Qingchi Palace
and grant a marriage
to you and Jingzhao.
What did you say?
You know that Houchi is the one I...
Qingmu.
Calm down.
How would I not know your feelings?
It’s just...
You should take the whole situation
into consideration this time.
Although you were possessed by
the remnant soul of the True God
on Mount Lookout that day,
you still fought with me and Jingzhao.
Firstly, it undermined
the prestige of the Heavenly Palace.
Secondly,
others will be suspicious of
your true intentions.
Thirdly,
you also entered the Qingchi Palace.
So they want to tie me up
with this marriage?
Although my father and mother said
they just wanted you to come over
to the Heavenly Palace,
they ordered soldiers
to follow me here.
I’m afraid
it’s not just about
granting you a marriage.
To intimidate the Qingchi Palace?
If you turn them down,
I’m afraid...
The Heavenly Palace is overbearing.
There will only be more troubles.
I don’t mind it because I’m all alone.
But God Gu Jun is not here.
Houchi is in the Qingchi Palace
by herself.
She will be in danger.
I’ll go to the Heavenly Palace
with you now
to end this thing.
Okay.
Qingmu, are you really going to
hide it from Houchi
and not say goodbye to her?
I can’t let Houchi know it.
I need to go and return quickly
and turn down this marriage.
Qingmu!
I know it already.
I heard your conversation with Jingjian.
Don’t worry.
I won’t marry Jingzhao.
I’ll turn down the marriage granted by
the Heavenly Emperor right now.
Then what?
Then...
Then I’ll come back here
to protect you and stay with you.
I won’t leave you again.
You also know it’s not that simple.
We just got together.
I don’t want you to leave,
but I don’t want you
to be in danger either.
You must be
cautious in your words
and deeds this time.
The Heavenly Emperor
only wants your Taicang Spear.
As for the marriage,
he can’t tie you up.
He would be like a bandit
in the lower realm in that way.
But just in case,
if he is really going to hurt you,
don’t act recklessly.
You still got me.
Are these words
really from Goddess Houchi
who has always despised me?
And also,
when you are in the Heavenly Palace,
you mustn’t look at Jingzhao
or talk to her.
You are mine now.
If there is any rumor coming out,
do you know the consequences?
Of course.
Not to mention Jingzhao,
I won’t look at any woman.
When did you two get together?
I’m really happy for you.
Houchi.
You and Qingmu truly love each other.
It’s really enviable.
Don’t worry.
After we arrive at the Heavenly Palace,
I’ll defend Qingmu
and remind him all the time,
helping him express
his thoughts to Father.
Thank you, Your Highness.
No need to call him “Your Highness”.
Just say his name.
Don’t worry.
I’ll be back soon.
Let’s go.
Master.
I’ve followed your instructions
and secretly summoned the demons.
As long as Wu Huan takes any move,
we will declare war on
the Immortals immediately.
It’s no hurry.
Muguang wants to find
the Purple Moon Whip through you
to reopen the God Realm.
Wu Huan is not that bold
to start a war between
the Immortals and the Demons
and enrage Muguang.
I was going to help you become a God.
But after some thought,
I still think it’s improper.
You are the Demon King.
If you become a God on top of that,
I’m afraid it will attract
the fear of the Immortals.
Wu Huan might take that opportunity
to start a war between
the Immortals and the Demons.
Then it’s not worth it.
You’ve done a lot to protect the Demons
for tens of thousands of years.
I understand it.
I remember
the Three-head Fire Dragon
in the Abyssal Ridge Swamp
has strong spiritual power.
If we help him become a God,
firstly,
we can threaten the Immortals.
Secondly,
we won’t cause much trouble.
This is a ray of pure spiritual power
I drew from the Purple Moon.
Take it to Three-head Fire Dragon
and help him become a God.
If we have one more God
among the Demons,
I think Wu Huan dare not act rashly.
Yes, Master.
Greetings to Your Highness.
North Sea Lord does have
an extraordinary bearing.
No wonder Jingzhao likes you.
Don’t feel constrained.
Have a seat.
Thank you, Your Highness.
I heard from Jingjian
that you are here today
because you have something important
to tell me.
Your Highness.
I’m here
for my marriage with Princess Jingzhao.
Marriage is too important
to be treated carelessly.
I don’t have
any affections for Princess Jingzhao.
There is someone else I love.
I won’t accept this marriage.
Please take back your order.
Since Jingjian is willing to
make friends with you,
I guess you are a smart person.
This marriage is
not just about affections.
Do you understand?
Yes, I do.
You understand it
and you still turn it down.
You are a young hero indeed.
High-spirited and vigorous.
But you are still too young.
You are impulsive
and you forget to weigh
the pros and cons.
Your Highness.
I’ve made up my mind.
It’s not an impulsive decision.
I’ll just forget
what you said today.
Go back and think about it.
Fengnyu.
Walk North Sea Lord out.
Excuse me, Your Highness.
Mother didn’t get mad at you.
That’s strange.
I also think it’s strange.
Today I bluntly turned her down
and told her I love someone else.
But the Queen of Heaven
didn’t get angry
or allow me to turn the marriage down.
I really can’t figure out
what she is thinking.
Mother has always
loved Jingzhao the most.
Could it be...
...that she doesn’t want to
see Jingzhao sad
and she thinks there is room
for maneuver?
In this case,
I might as well give the Taicang Spear
to the Queen of Heaven.
The Spear can recognize its owner.
Do you think you can
give it away that easily?
Besides,
such a big thing happened
on Mount Lookout that day.
It’s got the True God
and the Devine Beast involved.
If you really want to give it away,
you need to find an excuse.
In my opinion,
we need to give the matter
further thought.
Further thought?!
I’m afraid if I don’t solve it now,
Houchi will only get
more worried and upset.
They all say that a grown-up girl
can’t be kept at home.
I think
you are the one who can’t be kept.
You are really clingy.
I’m clingy indeed.
Why am I telling you that?
All right.
I’ll wait for a while.
Although I’m not in the Qingchi Palace,
I have a lot of ways to be with her
and make her think of me every day.
Have you heard about it?
I begged Father and Mother for so long
and they finally agreed
to let me marry Qingmu.
But Qingmu turned it down.
As the Princess of the Heavenly Palace,
I condescend to marry him,
yet I still can’t move him.
What is it that I’m not
good enough for him?
My sister is good enough
for any man.
But love is the only thing
that has no criteria.
It can’t be forced.
It can’t be forced...
Jingjian.
Be frank with me.
When Mother sent you
to the Qingchi Palace that day,
you didn’t want to go at all.
Is Houchi the one
whom Qingmu has feelings for?
I knew it.
That woman in the Qingchi Palace
must have bewitched him!
Jingzhao.
Jingzhao!
Clear my mind
and let the energy flow.
I got a great book.
Merry Immortal and Pretty Lady.
Their love
is heart-stirring and moving.
Houchi, take a look.
Let me try again.
And this one.
Fox Tantalizes the Immortal.
It’s a love story of an immortal
and a demon.
It’s really interesting.
Houchi, I promise you will like it.
Fengran.
Recently, you’ve been bothering me
every time I cultivate myself.
Is there nothing else you can do
in the Qingchi Palace?
It was my fault before.
I only focused on your cultivation.
I didn’t expect you
to be so boring and dull now.
You just fell in love.
You need some skills.
Let me explain it to you.
You should keep these books.
I have other things to do.
Houchi.
Let’s share the books together.
Just read them.
She would meditate
at the bottom of the pool
or cultivate herself every time
she gets something on her mind.
I don’t know whom she got it from.
Looks like I have to
use the second trick.
Why do you want to see me
in such an urgency?
Well, Your Grace.
I know our Qingchi Palace
usually doesn’t receive guests.
But think about it,
when the holiday comes, or when it’s
someone’s birthday or any baby is born,
you’ll have to
make social visits.
What’s more,
you will be in charge of
the Qingchi Palace one day.
Why don’t we
start with identifying all those people?
Why are you bringing this up
so suddenly?
Don’t worry about that.
This is the first disciple of
Lord Jinyao on Mount Nanxian,
Lady Yuehua.
Your Grace,
do you know her?
I don’t care whether she is
Yuehua or Xinghua.
She looks like a one or two
thousand years old junior.
Why should I know her?
Your Grace.
You must not underestimate this woman.
She is gentle
and elegant.
She also has a great reputation
all over the world.
The most important thing is
she declared one hundred years ago
that she would only marry Qingmu.
Do you feel threatened?
And this one.
The Princess Royal
of the Dragon King of the West Sea.
I heard that she and Qingmu
knew each other early in the North Sea.
She claims that they are
childhood sweethearts.
It is inevitable that you will meet her.
You must be on your guard.
Chang Que.
What’s this about?
Your Grace.
To be honest,
before Lord Qingmu left,
he asked us to find some ways
to make you happy
or make you think of him.
We can’t let you
worry about him too much.
And you can’t
hold everything back to yourself.
What kind of method is this?
You are making me
flustered and anxious.
And I’m feeling very insecure right now.
Your Grace.
It’s all my fault.
I swear
I won’t upset you
with these portraits again.
Fengran, come in.
Stop eavesdropping on us.
I mean,
there are all kinds of
things Qingmu can do.
But he prepared those portraits
of beauties for you.
I mean,
what is he thinking?
He is dumb but cute.
He doesn’t know how to please girls.
Then what do you like about him?
I like his integrity and sincerity.
He is stupid, cute, and impulsive.
I like everything about him.
Why am I telling you this?
My good lady.
You finally have some energy.
Since Qingmu left,
you’ve been frowning all day.
You barely smile.
Do you see my belly?
I ate two steamed buns today.
I haven’t digested them yet.
Do you know why?
Why?
Because I’m feeling peaceful
like still water.
Your Grace, something happened!
Jingzhao came to our Qingchi Palace!
She handled herself over.
I’m going to teach her a lesson.
Looks like you are filled with anger.
Is this how peaceful you are
like still water?
I’m peaceful.
I’m very peaceful.
Your Grace.
Are you going to meet her like this?
Go back to my room with me.
Yes.
(Qingchi Palace)
I’ve been waiting for some time.
Why hasn’t anyone come out to greet me?
Is this how they treat
their guest in the Qingchi Palace?
Your Grace, don’t be impatient.
Don’t forget what
the Queen of Heaven said.
We have our own ways
to treat guests in the Qingchi Palace.
If you want to horse around,
just go back to your Heavenly Palace.
Besides, you are not
a guest of my Qingchi Palace.
Houchi?
You are not Houchi.
Or did you use any witchcraft?
You Grace, you know the best
whether she is Goddess Houchi or not.
If you can’t remember it,
Goddess Houchi can summon
a few more thunder strikes
to strike some sense into you.
How dare you!
You are just a nameless immortal,
how dare you be rude to me!
Save it, Jingzhao.
You made a big deal of coming here.
What are you up to?
Your Grace.
I was young
and thoughtless before.
I offended you many times.
I hope you can forgive me.
I’m here today
to send you the invitation.
My mother’s birthday is coming soon.
She wants to meet you.
Blood is thicker than water.
I hope you can come
for the sake of your relationship.
Princess Jingzhao.
Please go back and tell your mother
that the Qingchi Palace wants nothing
to do with her.
We hope she can leave us alone.
How is that going to work?
Aren’t you Qingmu’s friend?
If you don’t come to
the birthday banquet,
how are you going to see
my engagement ceremony with Qingmu?
What did you say?
Goddess Houchi.
North Sea Lord has accepted the marriage
granted by the Heavenly Emperor.
He doesn’t want to destroy
the harmony between the two palaces.
He hopes you can let go of the past
and don’t be stubborn.
How is it possible?
Qingmu loves Houchi.
How would he marry you?
Qingmu only stayed in the Qingchi Palace
for a few days.
How come you have
such a misunderstanding?
Right,
you always covet what I have.
Qingmu is no exception.
This time we are going to
become an immortal couple.
Are you still going to pester him?
What a joke.
If I want someone,
do I even need to pester him?
Not to mention
you are the rival.
What do you mean?
I mean
if you don’t get out of
the Qingchi Palace now,
don’t blame me for letting you
feel the thunder strike again.
You… You are threatening me!
It’s not a threat,
but a punishment.
To punish you for having no respect
for your superior, being ignorant
and trespassing the Qingchi Palace.
These three sins can
get you punished hard.
With your little power,
I don’t think you can take
these few thunder strikes.
Your Majesty.
I’m here this time
to give you the spiritual power
of Demon Lord Ziyue
and help you become a God.
This is of great importance
and you mustn’t make any mistake.
Your Majesty, please rest assured.
I’ve been cultivating myself here
for tens of thousands of years.
This day is what I’ve been waiting for.
With the help of Demon Lord Ziyue,
I’ll become a God in one fell swoop.
That’s good.
It’s the people
from the Heavenly Palace.
The First Prince, Jingyang?
He got the nerve to come.
Hold on.
The Heavenly Palace
has noticed something.
Before becoming a God,
you mustn’t get yourself exposed.
You are right, Your Majesty.
I’ll start cultivating myself right away
and not let the Heavenly Palace
take the lead.
Your Majesty, you must be busy.
Please go back.
Remember,
look
before you leap.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Please.
Prince Jingyang.
I remember
he led the heavenly soldiers
and had a big fight with
Sen Yun in the Abyssal Ridge Swamp.
He treated me like dirt.
I’m about to become a God anyway.
Would I be afraid of
the Heavenly Palace?
I have to avenge myself.
How can there be divine weapons
on such desolate land?
They still insist that
I search this place.
You guys.
Take a quick look in the forest.
Yes!
Jingyang.
Long time no see.
Who is that?
Three-head Fire Dragon.
It’s you old brat.
I didn’t kill you
when you were cultivating yourself
in seclusion.
You got the nerve to
seek your doom again.
All right.
I’ll give you a quick death today.
It has been tens of thousands of years,
but you are still using
the same old moves.
Jingyang.
Even you are not bored,
I’m bored of it.
I’m not going to walk anymore.
What on earth is this place?
They don’t even have a chariot.
I have to walk down the mountain.
Your Grace.
The rules of the Qingchi Palace
have always been like this.
No matter who,
the guards must be left
outside the palace
and no chariot can enter.
This is still the land of the Immortals.
Why should I obey the rules
of the Qingchi Palace?
Your Grace, just hold on for a while.
We are going to leave the palace soon.
I don’t care.
Do whatever you can
to get a chariot for me.
Yes.
Are we really going to do this?
This princess is ill-tempered.
If we get caught...
What are you afraid of?
We are at our Qingchi Palace.
She got the nerve to run wild here.
We can’t just let it go.
You bold birds!
I’m a Gold Dragon.
How dare you tease me!
You are asking for your death!
What did you say?
Jingzhao went to the Qingchi Palace
and told them
that I had agreed to marry her?
Did Houchi buy her words?
She kicked Jingzhao out?
This is the woman I fall for.
It’s the signal
that Father convenes a meeting.
Something happened to
the Heavenly Palace.
Let’s go take a look.
Let’s go.
What did you say?
Your Highness.
We lost the track of Prince Jingyang
and the heavenly soldiers
after they entered
the Abyssal Ridge Swamp yesterday.
There is still no news about them.
How come?
Father, please try to tell
if Jingyang is in danger by telepathy.
I’ve checked it.
Jingyang’s spiritual aura is weak.
But he is safe now.
Your Majesty.
Prince Jingyang went there
for the divine weapons.
Now he is missing in
the Abyssal Ridge Swamp.
It must be the Demons who did it.
Lord of Wind,
that’s not necessarily true.
The Abyssal Ridge Swamp was abandoned
by the Immortals and the Demons.
There are both immortals and demons.
And most of them are rebels.
Even if it’s the Demons who did it,
even the powerful Demon King
can’t take away so many people
without anyone noticing it.
As for whether
it’s the Demons who did it,
I need you to find it out
at the Abyssal Ridge Swamp.
That’s right, Your Majesty.
It’s imperative
to rescue Prince Jingyang first
lest a long delay may cause trouble.
Father.
I know who can do it.
Jingjian, what are you doing?
Don’t worry. I’ll let you
get what you want.
Father.
I think
Qingmu is perfect for this task.
Lord Qingmu has
the True God’s divine weapon,
the Taicang Spear, to fight with them.
He is the best choice.
Lord Donghua.
North Sea Lord is not from
the Heavenly Palace.
He isn’t holding any post
in the Heavenly Palace.
I don’t think it’s proper to let him
take on such an important task.
Lord of Wind, do you mean
you are willing to
lead the army and go there?
My ability is limited. I’m afraid...
Father.
Since no one in the Heavenly Palace
can take on this task,
it’s better to let Qingmu do it.
I’m willing to go with him
to rescue Jingyang.
But it’s extremely dangerous.
And this is the first time for Qingmu
to enter the Heavenly Palace.
If he can rescue Jingyang,
the Heavenly Palace must give him
a generous reward.
Of course.
Qingmu.
I promise you a generous reward
if you can rescue Jingyang.
Are you willing to do it?
Your Majesty.
Of course, I am.
But I don’t want any generous reward.
I only have one condition.
How dare you, Qingmu!
You are just a little immortal
in the North Sea.
Why do you think you can
bring terms to His Majesty?
Your Majesty, don’t worry.
What I want
is not about the Immortals
or the Heavenly Palace.
It’s a private matter.
If Your Majesty can promise me,
I will head for the Abyssal
Ridge Swamp immediately
and bring Prince Jingyang back safely.
Okay.
I grant you one promise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Houchi.
Are you still angry at
Jingzhao’s tricks?
It’s not about Jingzhao.
She came to cause a scene.
Looks like Qingmu has difficulties
in turning down the marriage.
I’m worried about Qingmu’s safety now.
But I’m afraid it’ll intensify conflicts
if I go to the Heavenly Palace now.
I’ve never
hated my incompetence so much.
There is nothing I can do
to help him.
Jingjian asked someone
to send us a message
that Qingmu just got a chance
and he might be able to break it off.
He asked us to wait for their news
and not to worry too much about it.
What... What chance?
Is it safe?
Don’t worry.
But there is another news.
Do you want to hear it?
News?
It must be good news.
I notice that you haven’t found Boxuan.
So I asked my former friends
to look out for him.
Did they find Boxuan?
A little demon told me that
there was a sign of a Demigod becoming
a God in the Abyssal Ridge Swamp.
I suspect that the Demigod
is probably Boxuan.
The Abyssal Ridge Swamp?
I’ve been looking for him for so long.
But I overlooked a few
dangerous places left over
from ancient times.
If the Demon King becomes a God,
there should be a big scene about it.
But the Immortal Realm
and the Demon Realm are peaceful now.
Maybe it’s really Boxuan.
That’s right.
Instead of filling your head
with foolish notions,
you’d better go out and look for Boxuan.
Okay.
Let’s set off immediately.
This place is really unique.
The spiritual power is so thin here.
I once cultivated myself here
when I was young.
There is biogas everywhere.
Those who stay here are mostly powerful
and brutal demons.
We must be careful.
Have you been here before?
I’ve not only been here,
I almost died in the mouth of the demons
when I was young and overconfident.
There is a sound.
Come on.
My good goddess.
Let me ride with the wind
next time, all right?
I’ve never been good at flying.
I just wanted to practice it.
Houchi?
Let’s go.
Let’s take a look ahead.
Why are you stopping me
from seeing my wife?
She’s not your wife yet.
What do you mean?
You two haven’t met for days.
You must miss each other a lot.
Well,
I’ll draw Fengran away later.
Good idea.
Not only that...
Okay.
Let’s go.
The Power of Rules here
is quite confusing.
What would Boxuan be doing here?
This is just the periphery
of the Abyssal Ridge Swamp.
By the way,
you have to put
your immortal power away later.
Don’t let someone else notice you.
Someone else?
There are many demons here.
There must be a lot of demons
who have the power of a lord.
When I was thrown here back then,
if it weren’t for
the old Tree Demon’s care,
I would have died many times.
Is there any powerful figure
in the place we are heading for?
I can handle
most of them.
But there is a Three-head Fire Dragon
from ancient times.
He got some serious power.
Although he doesn’t like immortals,
he is not bloodthirsty.
As long as we don’t cause any trouble,
we will be fine.
Jingjian.
Why are you here?
Something happened to Qingmu.
Qingmu is also here?
Qingmu and I were ordered to
look for some people.
But we got surrounded by
a group of demons
just as we arrived here.
Qingmu gave cover for me to leave.
I’m afraid his life is in danger now.
Fengran.
Please go with me to help.
I’m going with her.
Your spiritual power is weak.
Stay here to protect yourself.
All right, we are far enough.
We won’t disturb them now.
You found it out?
With your exaggerated performance,
if it wasn’t because Houchi was worried,
she wouldn’t have fallen for your lie.
Lady Fengran, please don’t get mad.
Who is that?
Who is this immortal?
You got some nerve
to trespass on this land.
I... I didn’t recognize the road
and I strayed.
Please show some mercy
and let me go.
How can I let you go?
I haven’t eaten any immortal
for thousands of years.
Finally, there is
such a beautiful immortal.
How can I let you go?
Just eat me.
I’m not afraid.
However, can you let me
send an instruction feather
to the man I love
and tell him my last words
before I die?
The man you love?
What are you going to say to him?
You are unfaithful!
You betrayed me
and chose Princess Jingzhao!
I don’t love you anymore.
I didn’t choose Jingzhao.
You are the only one I love.
Untie me now.
Jingjian said you were in danger.
Luckily, you are fine.
I was so worried about you.
But you still made fun of me.
All right.
It was my fault.
I shouldn’t have listened to
Jingjian’s bad idea.
He asked me to scare you first
and then come to your rescue.
I won’t listen to him anymore.
This is all Qingmu’s idea.
He asked me to draw you away,
so he could stay with Houchi alone.
He is stronger than me.
I had to do what he asked me to do.
Please don’t blame me.
Your Highness.
We haven’t met for only a few days,
but you have become much bolder.
Now you even dare to lie to me.
I listened to you
to let them bond tighter.
When did you ever
listen to me like that?
When have I not
listened to you?
I’m glad you get the point.
Then let’s wait here.
Let’s not be the third wheels.
Did you and Qingmu follow us
to the Abyssal Ridge Swamp?
Of course not.
We are here...
Lady Fengran.
It’s my father’s edict.
It’s a secret of the Heavenly Palace.
Sorry that I can’t tell you about it.
Forget it.
I don’t care that much
about the Heavenly Palace.
Where are you going?
It’s a secret of the Qingchi Palace.
I can’t tell you.
All right.
We are even now.
Since you won’t tell me,
I’ll just follow you.
But this place is very dangerous.
You should be careful
and stay alert, Lady Fengran.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪