=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 26=
Where are you going?
It’s a secret of the Qingchi Palace.
I can’t tell you.
All right.
We are even now.
Since you won’t tell me,
I’ll just follow you.
But this place is very dangerous.
Lady Fengran.
You should be careful and stay alert.
Your Highness.
I grew up
in the Abyssal Ridge Swamp.
You should take care of yourself.
Fengran, where is this place?
Old man.
I’m back to see you.
Don’t worry.
I’m living a great life now.
I eat well and drink well
at the Qingchi Palace.
There is also a little stubborn girl
keeping me company.
Don’t worry about me.
Fengran.
This is...?
This is the one who died
at the hands of Sen Yun and Jingyang.
He was also the only family I got.
I was born ominous.
Before I opened my eyes,
I was left at the Abyssal Ridge Swamp.
When the old Tree Demon found me,
I was barely alive.
The demons in the Abyssal Ridge Swamp
said that I couldn’t be saved.
But he wouldn’t believe it.
He used his demon core
to warm my body for three days
and three nights.
Then I started to come back to life.
I asked him
why a demon like him saved a phoenix.
He said
he never left the Abyssal Ridge Swamp
in his life.
Now he was too old
to travel far.
He hoped I could
take him to travel around
the Three Realms
and see the world outside
when I grew up.
But one day,
the Immortals and the Demons started
a war above the Abyssal Ridge Swamp
and the creatures there were
plunged into an abyss of misery.
When Sen Yun and Jingyang were fighting,
I was hiding under the tree.
In order to protect me,
the old Tree Demon was burned
to death in the heavenly fire.
Help! Help!
Grandpa, no!
Grandpa!
Grandpa, no! Grandpa!
Grandpa...
Fengran.
I’m willing to pay for
my brother’s mistake.
The old man’s body and spirit
were exterminated.
How are you going to pay for it?
I know my life can’t
undo the damage my brother caused.
But if you want my life,
I won’t complain.
You are you.
Jingyang is Jingyang.
I will end my feud with him
in person.
Please rest assured.
I will take good care of Fengran.
Old man.
Don’t worry.
One day,
I will make the person who killed you
pay for what he did.
Old Dragon.
How dare you treat me like this!
I’ll flatten
your Abyssal Ridge Swamp!
You led the heavenly soldiers
and occupied our land
of spiritual power,
making me cultivate myself
in these disgusting methods.
Today,
I will suck all the spiritual power
out of you and those heavenly soldiers.
You immortals deserve it!
My Lord, the immortals are here.
I advise you to release me now.
If my father comes here,
he will take your life.
You talk too much.
Who are they?
My Lord,
they are four young people.
Judging by their cultivation,
they should be upper immortals.
Bring them here.
I want to meet them.
Yes.
You guys, come with me.
Have you turned down the marriage?
Don’t worry.
I’ve figured out a way to make
the Heavenly Emperor take it back.
The Four Seas and the Three Realms
all know that the Heavenly Emperor
granted you a marriage.
Can you turn it down that easily?
Jingyang and a group of
heavenly soldiers
went missing here not long ago.
Jingyang’s spiritual power is not weak.
But he just vanished.
Jingjian and I speculate
that he was caught by
the Three-head Fire Dragon.
So I volunteered to come.
The Heavenly Emperor said
that if I could bring Jingyang back,
he would promise me one request.
By that time,
I’ll ask him to take the order back.
I feel a little uncomfortable.
Why?
Do you still remember what happened
in the Xuanjing Palace?
Do you know
why Fengran killed the Third Prince
of the Demons, Sen Yun?
Even if Sen Yun deserved death,
he is still the Third Prince
of my Xuanjing Palace,
and my... favorite son!
During the battle between
the Immortals and the Demons,
Sen Yun and Jingyang accidentally
killed the old Tree Demon
when they were fighting.
In order to avenge
the old Tree Demon’s death,
Fengran set herself against
the Immortals and the Demons.
She can’t wait to take Jingyang’s life.
But now you are going to save Jingyang
and use it as a bargaining chip
to turn down the marriage.
I just wanted to break it off
as soon as possible.
I didn’t know Jingyang
killed Fengran’s family.
I was thoughtless.
It’s not your fault.
I didn’t tell you before.
No matter what,
we can’t ignore Fengran’s feelings.
Let me figure out another way.
What about you?
Why are you here?
Fengran said that there were signs
of a Demigod becoming a God here.
I thought Boxuan might be here.
So we came here.
Who are so bold
as to break into
the Abyssal Ridge Swamp?
You toyboy.
Are you the rescuers of the immortals
from the Heavenly Palace?
What immortals?
Who are you?
We are the subordinates of
the Three-head Fire Dragon.
Are you afraid now?
The Three-head Fire Dragon captured
the immortals from the Heavenly Palace.
Take them both.
Yes.
- Hurry!
It’s the Spirit Gathering Array.
The Three-head Fire Dragon
goes against the heavenly principles
and sucked the spiritual power
of the heavenly soldiers.
The evil power is strong here.
I’m afraid those from
the Heavenly Palace have been killed.
We underestimated the power
of the Three-head Fire Dragon.
I’m afraid he will become a God soon.
You are going to die.
And you are still concerned with
love and romance?
What a pair of brave lovebirds.
You sucked so much spiritual power
from those heavenly soldiers.
Aren’t you afraid of
the Heavenly Emperor’s punishment?
After Lord of Dragon becomes a God,
your Heavenly Palace
will be ours sooner or later.
A few immortals mean nothing.
Hurry.
- Come on.
- Go.
Qingmu?
Jingyang?
Well, Jingyang.
You were also caught by the Three-head
Fire Dragon as the sacrifice.
Heaven is fair.
You took advantage of your identity
as a prince of the Heavenly Palace
and took my fiancée from me.
I’m going to kill you today.
Chanyu, go to report to His Lordship.
Tell him
that we have caught
the immortals who broke in.
Ask His Lordship to come back
for the sacrifice ceremony.
I’ll stay here.
Yes. Let’s go.
Either you die or I die today.
Your Highness.
It was an imperative situation.
Please forgive me.
With your spiritual power,
will you be afraid of those pawns?
I know you just wanted to embarrass me.
After I return to the Heavenly Palace,
I will tell my mother about this
and punish you for offending me.
You are already in such bad shape.
But you are still so imposing.
It’s not easy.
Qingmu.
Father has betrothed Jingzhao to you.
Why are you still with her?
Do you want a wife
and a concubine to serve you
so that you can enjoy the happiness
of having two women?
Why should we save this kind of person?
Just let him be the sacrifice
of the Fire Dragon.
Qingmu.
You...!
It won’t work.
The Three-head Fire Dragon
has reached the peak as a Demigod.
You can’t break his barrier.
We need to figure out a way to get out.
I have an idea.
But Prince Jingyang
will suffer a little.
You don’t get along well
with my Qingchi Palace.
If you want us to save you,
this is the only way.
What is it?
The Three-head Fire Dragon
is about to become a God.
I think he has been
waiting for his thunder trial.
If there are thunder strikes
in the cave now,
the Three-head Fire Dragon will believe
that it’s the thunder trial
for him to become a God.
In order to enter the cave
to pass the trial,
he will open the barrier first.
I guess the prestigious
Princess Jingyang
hasn’t received the blessing from a God.
You are so lucky.
That’s a great honor.
I wouldn’t give my blessing
to any ordinary person.
Fengran.
Do you remember you once saved...
The thunder trial?
I’ve been waiting for this day
for tens of thousands of years.
Thunder strikes?
How could there be thunder strikes
in the Abyssal Ridge Swamp?
Is the Three-head Fire Dragon
going to become a God?
No, it’s Houchi.
Not good.
My blessing contains
the charm of heaven and earth.
You must cherish it.
The first blessing is,
may Your Highness
marry a violent and ruthless
beautiful wife soon.
Looks like you really like my blessing.
The second blessing is,
may Your Highness
be surrounded by your children
and may you never have peace
in your family.
As for the third blessing...
It’s not a festal occasion
for Your Highness to prostrate yourself.
I won’t feel at ease taking it.
But I won’t take advantage of
Your Highness.
As for the third blessing,
I’ll just return your prostration.
Thousands of years ago,
the flame flowed down
and the old Tree Demon was burned alive.
Compared with what you did
in the Abyssal Ridge Swamp that day,
what I did today
is too merciful for you.
Who are you?
How dare you tease me!
Qingmu from the North Sea
greets Lord of Dragon.
The Taicang Spear?
How could you have the Taicang Spear?
Leave the Spear
and I can spare your lives.
Three-head Fire Dragon.
You sucked the spiritual power
of the immortals to enhance your evil power.
You don’t deserve
to touch the Taicang Spear.
Just a few immortals.
What’s the big deal
that I swallowed them?
However,
I’ve shown you a way out.
If you don’t take it,
then you can’t blame me.
After I kill you,
the Spear will still be mine.
You little girl.
Your spiritual power is not that strong.
But your physique is quite special.
You two
will be my sumptuous meal for today.
Houchi.
Did he hurt you?
I’m fine.
It’s you.
How dare you fight with me!
Now you have no one to protect you.
Lord of Dragon.
Houchi is my best friend.
I must take her out safely today.
Please be merciful and let us go.
Houchi?
The daughter of Gu Jun.
The fourth God in the Heavenly Realm.
You made friends with your enemy.
I’m quite impressed.
Jingjian.
Why are you with this demon?
From today, the Heavenly Palace and
the Qingchi Palace are at daggers drawn.
Jingyang.
Watch your words.
Jingjian,
is this the secret of
the Heavenly Palace you talked about?
Step aside.
Fengran.
We’re here to save Jingyang
because Qingmu needs to
use my brother’s life
to break off the engagement
with Jingzhao.
If you kill him,
Qingmu can’t break it off.
What should Houchi do then?
Fengran.
I didn’t know
that Jingyang killed your family.
I feel guilty.
If you want to
take revenge on him today,
I won’t stop you.
You ungrateful brat.
The Heavenly Palace treats you well.
But you take the side of that demon!
Little girl.
Don’t forget
the old Tree Demon
was burned alive by Jingyang.
Have you forgotten
the vengeance for his death
and become a lackey of
the Heavenly Palace?
That’s impossible.
Good.
If you wipe out these immortals for me,
I promise
I will let you skin Jingyang alive
in person
and break his soul into pieces.
Houchi.
Don’t let Fengran keep making mistakes.
Fengran.
No matter what you do,
I’ll support you.
One day,
I’ll take vengeance on him in person.
But today,
I have to take Houchi away.
Wrong choice.
I’ll show you what I got.
I’ll eat you down
and become a God.
You want me to pass the trial now.
How blind you are!
Let’s go now!
What are you waiting for?
After he becomes a God,
none of us can escape.
Once the Three-head Fire Dragon
becomes a God,
the Baili Palace in the Abyssal
Ridge Swamp will be destroyed.
Houchi is right.
By his very nature,
he will go on a murderous rampage.
I’m afraid even the Heavenly Emperor
and Queen can hardly kill him.
Houchi,
do you want to stop him
from becoming a God?
No, it’s too dangerous.
Fengran, leave with Houchi first.
I’m gonna help him.
You’d better stay here.
Your spiritual power
is too weak to help them.
He failed to become a God.
He won’t let us go.
Fengran,
you grew up here.
Is there any other place we can hide?
There is a place
even the Three-head Fire Dragon
doesn’t dare to go.
Come with me.
Today,
none of you can escape!
Fengran, is this where
the Destruction War took place?
What Destruction War?
It’s said that 60,000 years ago,
Demon God Tianqi set up the Destruction
Formation in the Lower Realm,
attempting to engulf the Three Realms
and become the God of Chaos.
True God Bai Jue led other Gods
to the Lower Realm and killed him.
That’s how the catastrophe
was prevented.
That’s right.
This is the place where the Demon God
attempted to destroy the world.
I grew up in the Abyssal Ridge Swamp.
Neither the immortal nor the demon
dare set foot in this place,
not even the Three-head Fire Dragon.
There is the True God
guarding in this mist.
We will die if we stay here.
Let’s go out.
You can go out by yourself.
The Three-head Fire Dragon
is waiting to kill you
at the gate.
Don’t panic.
Maybe I know how to handle it.
Before we left, Lord Donghua said
that your divine weapon
could cope with the remaining influence
of the formation.
I didn’t expect
that it could be used here.
The Land of Destruction?
It’s just a broken altar.
What’s so scary?
It was still easily taken care of
by our immortal.
A second ago, someone was too scared
to think clearly.
He even wanted to leave here.
Why don’t you leave now?
- You...!
- Jingyang.
Ease up a little.
Jingjian.
What kind of drug
did this witch give you?
Why do you protect her like that?
Fengran.
My brother is the prince
in the Heavenly Palace
and the future lord of the Feng Clan.
You are just a demon
in the Abyssal Ridge Swamp.
You don’t even deserve
to be a maid of him.
Just give up pestering him.
Jingyang.
Fengran.
Jingyang got injured.
Don’t take it personally.
The prince in the Heavenly Palace.
The lord of the Feng Clan.
I should have thought of it.
There is no difference
between you and Jingyang.
I didn’t kill him today
for the sake of Houchi and Qingmu.
But I will kill him in person one day.
If you dare to stop me at that time,
don’t blame me for being ruthless then.
Jingjian.
There are so many good girls
in the Three Realms.
Why do you have to...?
Stop it, Jingyang.
Fine.
If Fengran comes to
take my life one day,
what will you do?
If there is such a day,
I will use my life
to end your grudge.
Jingyang’s fault
still implicated Jingjian.
I don’t see a future
for him and Fengran.
Jingjian and Fengran...
He treats Fengran very differently.
Is there any way
to end the feud?
I’m afraid it’s hard.
Jingyang killed her family.
I know Fengran well.
Once she makes a decision,
she won’t change it even facing death.
Qingmu.
We owe it to Fengran today.
Shanggu.
Shanggu?
What’s wrong?
I saw some strange images.
What did you see?
I saw...
Then you will understand
what Bai Jue’s remnant soul said
was true
when you were on Mount Lookout that day.
You should have been
the most respected one in the world.
Nothing.
I just feel she is very sad.
She seems to be waiting for something.
Here are the remains
of the battle of the Gods.
This stone statue must be
a Goddess in the God Realm.
Although she is dead,
her thoughts are enough to move people.
You are still alive?! Prepare to die!
Be careful.
Fengran, take Houchi away.
Let’s go!
Are you all right?
I’m fine.
Jingyang!
Go!
The power of the True God.
You can actually master
the spiritual power of True God Bai Jue!
I’ll cut your divine vessels
if you don’t leave now.
You will never be able to
run wild again.
Qingmu.
Qingmu, are you all right?
I’m fine.
Now you have saved Jingyang.
Go back to the Heavenly Palace now
and break off the engagement
with Jingzhao.
Fengran.
I won’t use Jingyang
as a bargaining chip.
I’ll figure out another way to solve it.
Tell me what the other way is.
I understand the good intention
of you and Houchi.
I’ll take revenge on him
sooner or later.
But that can wait.
Being used as a bargaining chip
is a good deed of Jingyang.
Since the Heavenly Emperor
has promised you,
you should go back
to the Heavenly Palace
and turn down the marriage.
Only you and Houchi
have no worries about the future
can I feel at ease.
Since Lady Fengran said that,
Qingmu,
don’t refuse it.
Fengran.
I’ll remember what you did for us today.
Thank you, Fengran.
Houchi, there is no need for that
between us.
As long as you two are happy,
it will be the best thing
you can do for me.
Houchi.
Go back to Qilian Mountains
with Fengran first.
After I report this
to the Heavenly Emperor
and break off the engagement
with Jingzhao,
I’ll go back to the Qingchi Palace
to see you.
I don’t trust the Heavenly Palace.
I’ll go with you.
No!
Qingmu is going there
to break off the engagement.
If you go with him, the Queen of Heaven
won’t tolerate you.
This is between me and Qingmu.
I can’t let him bear it alone.
Houchi.
My father is not unreasonable.
Now you have saved Jingyang,
he will keep his promise.
I didn’t save Jingyang
to break off the engagement.
If it weren’t for the cruel
Three-head Fire Dragon, I wouldn’t
get myself involved in the disputes
between the Immortals and the Demons.
Considering what Jingyang did back then,
I should have killed him.
There is no reason to save him.
Never mind.
You are not Jingyang.
You are also implicated by him.
I shouldn’t have given you
that attitude.
Fengran, go back to
Qilian Mountains first.
I just said no.
Those in the Heavenly Palace
are cunning.
I can’t let you go there by yourself.
Before you two
have solved your problem,
I won’t cause you any trouble.
Fine.
In this case,
let’s go back to
the Heavenly Palace together.
Three-head Fire Dragon.
I gave you the purple fire.
How did you fail to become a God?
If it weren’t for Qingmu’s
sneak attack on me
while I was about to become a God
and he let the divine thunder
strike one of my heads,
I would have become a God now!
It must be because you coveted
Jingyang’s spiritual power
and brought those immortals there.
How precious is
the divine flame of Master.
You wasted his efforts.
Becoming a God is risky anyway.
You can’t convict me of another crime
just because I failed to become a God.
Your Majesty, please punish me.
Master thinks highly of you.
It’s not my turn to punish you.
I just feel that it’s a pity.
Your Majesty, don’t feel pity about it.
Although I failed to become a God,
that brat didn’t get anything good.
He inhaled my dragon breath.
He is just an immortal.
The dragon breath will invade
his spiritual veins sooner or later.
The North Sea Lord
only has a few more days to live.
Qingmu caught your dragon breath?
Three-head Fire Dragon.
Don’t tell Master about it.
Qingmu has never stepped in the fights
between demons and immortals all along.
We’ve never been enemies.
But he broke into the Demon Realm
and saved Fengran last time,
and he prevented you from
becoming a God this time.
Obviously, he has turned to
the Heavenly Palace.
He seems to have
an acquaintance with Master.
Now he is the owner
of the Taicang Spear,
the first immortal
in the Immortal Realm.
It’s good for us
if he dies.
Your Majesty, rest assured.
He prevented me from becoming a God.
I wish he died sooner.
I won’t tell Master about this.
The Zisong Hall is ahead.
Qingmu and I are going to
report to Father first.
You two rest here.
Just tell the Attendant Immortals
if you need anything.
Your Highness, don’t be humble.
It’s such an enchanting place.
What else can we need?
Let’s go.
Please.
There will be ample time.
I also went through a lot
when I pursued Houchi.
My own brother
killed her family.
I’m afraid it’s even harder
for Fengran and me to be together.
Don’t talk about me.
Since we entered the Heavenly Palace,
you seem to be worried.
What’s wrong?
I’m worried
that Houchi will get in trouble
in the Heavenly Palace.
Jingzhao is a little spoiled.
But if Father issues an edict,
she won’t keep pestering you.
Hope so.
Qingmu.
I hope you can do me a favor.
What is it?
Breaking off the engagement
will hurt Jingzhao.
She has always been arrogant and proud.
I hope you can show her enough respect
when you tell Father that you want to
break off the engagement.
Of course. Don’t worry.
Okay.
Let’s go.
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
Let’s go.
I know there is a problem
between you two.
But Jingjian also means well.
Have you forgotten
that he also protected you
in the Abyssal Ridge Swamp?
I’m grateful to him.
But he is still Jingyang’s brother.
I’d better keep some distance from him.
I think it’s her.
She should be Goddess Houchi.
Who is there?
What are you whispering?
Get out!
- Greetings, Goddess Houchi.
- Greetings, Lady Fengran.
We are fairy maidens
in the Heavenly Palace.
What are you doing here
in broad daylight?
For your information, Lady Fengran,
we are here to see Goddess Houchi.
Me?
You are the supreme Goddess,
but you seldom appear in public
in the past 60,000 years.
Ridiculous!
What do you think Goddess Houchi is?
A rare beast?
Sorry, I didn’t mean to offend you.
Please punish me.
Don’t panic.
Now that you came to see me,
and you have seen me,
you may leave
if there is no other business.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪