fTiming and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ No longer panicking on the night of the blackout ♫
♫ You're by my side, illuminating a beam of light for me ♫
♫ Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet ♫
♫ Your breath ♫
♫ brushes up against my cheek ♫
♫ With you warming up the stage,
happiness never comes to a close ♫
♫ Boring jokes add some sweetness to the dinner ♫
♫ Daily life is even more like a comic than comics themselves ♫
♫ Happiness and sadness ♫
♫ Make up the moments of life ♫
♫ Rainy days become very special because of you ♫
♫ Picked up a pitiful youngster off the street ♫
♫ No matter when and where, you always appear ♫
♫ Holding me tightly and spinning in circles ♫
♫ Rainy days make me so nostalgic because of you ♫
♫ Becoming some part of the memories ♫
♫ Walking down a street with lights lighting up
one after another ♫
♫ Warming up the whole world ♫
[Please Feel at Ease Mr. Ling]
[Episode 21]
There are so many words that aren't clear.
I'll help you read them.
I'm just finding out
that she tried to look happy
so she didn't affect me.
If she hadn't met my father,
would she have not had to suffer this much?
Would she have been happier?
At least, the heart-felt smile here can't be faked.
Auntie experienced happiness.
At least, you have some shared memories.
In the future, I'll do my very best not to bring work home and spend more time with you.
How can that be good. You need to do good work.
Isn't there a saying that says, 'A man who works earnestly
shines and touches others'?
If...if you can shine more warmly, that's even better.
How's this?
Not just towards me.
You should be that way towards everyone around you.
For example...Ai Li.
For example...Xiao Yishan.
- For example...
- Xiao Yishan?
Forget about Xiao Yishan.
He's a dynamo.
Hello. Do you want to have dinner together with Xiao Ai?
Excuse me. Wait just a second.
It's not too convenient today; some other day.
Look how much genuine sincerity I'm showing in bringing all this.
You couldn't be so heartless as to leave all this outside your door.
I still have work to do today.
Hello, President Ling
Okay. I'll do that right now.
You can't disturb your employees after work hours.
Are you with Xiao Yishan?
- I'm sorry, President Ling. Actually...
- I won't bother you two.
Just look at this room.
It's really unique.
It's all Ling Yue's fault. He's worked you so hard
you don't even have time to keep your house in order.
You go ahead and go back to your room and work.
Leave this to me. In half an hour,
I'll change this into a new world.
What do you think? Am I amazing?
Last time I was at your house, I thought it was so empty.
So this time, I brought Xiao Ai's luxury house
and decompression toys.
At the same time, I've been able to display my cooking skills.
And I bought some cooking utensils for you.
I don't cook at home. I can't use these cooking tools.
Can't I just come often, then?
Don't move your hands and feet.
I'm not that used to
- being too close and touching other people.
- Aiya.
We're one family; why look at me like an outsider?
Don't be like that.
If you keep that up, I'll become a disabled person. Fortunately, I'm a doctor and I can save myself.
Eat.
Try it.
How is it?
Is it delicious?
I just don't like to waste food.
Last time, you said you didn't like boxing.
Then what do you like and not like?
I...like going to work.
I don't like getting off work.
That's all because of that unscrupulous Ling Yue. What ordinary person wants to go to work?
So what sort of private life, circle of friends do you have?
I'm not very good at socializing.
- What about your family?
- My family are all abroad.
And, I don't really have any close relatives now.
Since you lack family here, can I look after you?
Actually, after I twisted my back last time,
and you came to take care of me,
A lot of images were in my head.
I suddenly wondered
whether the life of two people together
would be much more lovely than a single person?
So, will you allow me to enter your life,
let me spend my time with you?
Could we...truly be together?
I'm sorry.
- I'm still not...
Enough! Stop. I got it.
Don't tell me anything like, 'don't love me'.
We haven't reached that yet.
You haven't every done that; so how could you reject it?
It's fine. I'll wait for you.
Eat.
[Galaxy cool men]
- You've worked hard.
- No problem. It's my duty.
- I'll be going.
- Okay.
When you come back, I'll open these 2  up.
We can expand the size of our work room.
What are you doing?
Isn't that obvious enough?
The tears in this large pair of eyes
are all admiration of such narcissism.
Careful with your words. This isn't narcissism.
It's exceptional talent.
Seems like you are going to be the junior boss.
Your speech is speech is very systematic, coherent and logical.
Of course.
Youyou.
Thank you.
Thank you for staying with me while I do what I've always wanted to do
and never did.
Really.
I have to take another client to dinner tonight.
Huh?
Then, I'll go with you.
Don't drink too late and feel bad and be in pain again.
No need for that. I don't want you to drink.
Just stay at home and wait to count the money.
Wait a minute.
Take this with you.
Apple vinegar.
When necessary,
you can mix this with the real stuff.
Don't worry. I can do this.
But, I don't want to go.
Why?
I want to finish watching the meteors with you and then go.
Why do it seem like you're getting cuter and cuter?
Really?
According to experts, this year's meteor shower will be on the 18th, at 10 PM Beijing time,
Don't all meteors fall?
How come this one is rising? What is "rising" meteor?
Rare indeed.
Ai Li, is this a harrassment call?
If it is, I can pick it up for you. This serial caller keeps on calling.
It's Xiao Yishan.
Did he make you angry?
during work is difficult to answer the phone
it's not work time, you can answer
just sometimes... the call... he...
if she picks up it will never end
you guys know he is like that
he says alot but never gets to the point
he likes you so he talks to you
just like Lingyue
he feels lonely
and really stubborn about it
Aili you can spend more time with him
no I can't be distracted. my job is to protect you
but this is your happiness you got to protect it too
I was thinkin of adding a screen
and a tatami for resting
and let me know the sizing needed for the screen and sofa
thank you
Aili you don't have to keep following me
President Ling said reconstruction is dangerous
He's just too stressed from the work
why don't you go back and take care of him?
no, he will scold me
scold you? then hit him back
your fighting is really good you don't need to be scared of him
don't say it like that
If it wasn't for President Ling, I wouldn't be who I am today
actually I know you guys have a story just to embarrassed to ask
why don't you share with me today
Good! Go!
Yes! Hit Him!
Great! Fight!
This is our most
promising fighter
He can for sure protect you
I'snt my recommendation good?
What did you do? What did you do?
Doing this on purpose? This pay check
and your doggy bonus is gone
I pick her
are you sure?
I have so many better than her
From now on you can work for me
Lucky, you got yourself a owner
Thats not her name
Her name is...
Aili
If president Ling didn't save me...
from that place
then I would not be here today
I understand how you feel
some scars don't heal
when you feel you have more happiness
then you will have more fear of losing it
you will want to avoid
keep a distance from them
but it's because you value them
Aili when I met LingYue
I never thought I would be this happy
But accepting someone isn't this difficult
I can and you can
I'm driving President Ling to a dinner banquet.
I am with President Ling
I'm helping President Ling with official duties.
Did she hire a robot to reply you?
She's extremely cruel online and offline.
In fact, with the emotional stage you both are in now,
you don't need to sound each other out any further.
You just need to give her a clear answer.
to dispel the doubts and worries in her heart.
Give her a sense of ritual that belongs only to her.
In this way, she will know that she's being loved.
Alright.
Why it is you, what are you doing here?
This is the first place where we met Xiao Ai.
In a blink of an eye, a long time has passed.
Yes, it is the same.
So...
our relationship,
is that more closer?
Maybe.
Ai Li,
I want to tell you.
First time I met you.
I like you.
I first thought we would just be a friend.
when I feel myself
expose all my shortcomings to you,
there will be no escape from fate.
Hence,
will you hand over your Achilles Heel to me
and stop being the invulnerable Ai Li?
Let me protect you.
The trajectory of the meteorite is, in fact, very light.
During that period of time,
it seems like it's going to fly out from the sky.
However, from the start till the end, it's attracted by the gravity of earth.
And will eventually approach earth.
Just like you and me.
I met you.
Idiot.
I just told you.
You really forgot what it's said.
Promise me that
we will be together.
Yes, I promise you.
Xiao Yishan,
I don't want you to protect me.
Because I am capable of protect myself.
But
I am willing to try to be with you.
Yay!
I'm sorry, were you waiting long?
No
I was just thinking about, the last time watching shooting stars
was back in high school
that time I was there, in front of the school fields
But I'm an adult. This is the first time I believe in this kind of wishes from meteorite.
why do I feel like you don't believe in wishes
after meeting you I believe now
what wish did you make?
Lingsheng
are you a simple or complex person?
why do you ask?
In front of you I am as I am
Then how did you know I was at Dongjiao Tower
Did you ask someone to spy on me?
I was worried something might happen to you
nothing happened
I was afraid you might get hurt
I hoped I could be there to protect you
just see it as just a caring act
but Xiner I did not have other intentions, please believe me
Okay, I believe you
Xiner I have a special present to give you
Present!
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Soaking the memory wet ♫
Xin'er,
Will you be willing to be my girlfriend?
♫ My heart suddenly beats out of normal ♫
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Obviously, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness,
for it has always been you ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
Yes
♫ Yet the reminiscing has never been able to stop ♫
'smooch sounds"
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Yet the longing has never been able to stop ♫
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
Did you see that?
Look.
Look!
Quick! make a wish!
Your wish is also my wish
If I had 100 wishes ill give you 50 of mine
I'll give you my 100
♫ Using love to slowly open up a lifetime ♫
My wish comes true.
♫ Our story is exclusively ours ♫
♫ Using all of my most beautiful adjectives ♫
♫ Using love to slowly open up a lifetime ♫
Dad?
Dad, are you alright?
Why are you looking at me like that
Dad
I feel at ease (he says Anxin)
Dad i'm Xiner
Oh Xiner, when did you come home last night?
Don't come home so late anymore it made me worry
I understand, Dad
Ansheng, this is my accounting records
can you give them to Manager Zhao
Alright, don't worry
[Records of payment]
"Yuguo?"
I got news she is alone
The timing is perfect invite them over
For this competition our class only has one position
Gu Anxin's grades are above yours
so we decided to pick her
"remember to use this color"
Oh im so sorry
Are you blind? you did this on purpose!
It was an accident
Accident?
Accidentally got the scholarship
Accidentally got the competition opportunity
Pretending to be a good person?
I think you did on purpose, you have the most ulterior motives
I didn't do it on purpose...
I got your clothes dirty let me repay you
Okay, if it was on accident
then I accidentally bumped into you too
is that okay, I'll bump you right...
Yuguo
"It was her"
"she took away what you deserve"
"ruined your ability"
but child, don't be afraid
from now on I am your family
the way I care and help you
not for you to repay me
is for you to get revenge
one day you can fight for yourself
slowly don't rush
the person that harmed you will get what she deserves
What do I say to her?
I need to teach you what to say?
Hello
Anxin, is that you? I'm Yu Guo.
Yuguo?
Where are you? looked for you for so long
I left the country for a while
Yuguo, are you doing well?
I want to see you
Of course
I'm really worried about you
I want to see you alone for the last time
Yuguo, please don't
wait for me... hello?
Miss Anxin?
Let Yuguo find a secluded place and keep Anxin hidden
you must watch her carefully, don't let anyone know. especially Ansheng
and when Lingyue comes and you get what you need
let them meet properly
and don't make mistakes
'I'm at the bottom of the building, come alone'
"the number you have dialed...'
Presinent Ling? the chair meeting will start soon
the other members are here now
let them know meeting is canceled
Anxin
Anxin! Where are you?
Tell him to come here
Anxin!
Anxin
Anxin? Where are you?
Mr. Ling, i'm over here
Lingyue don't come here
Go! don't come here
Leave
Leave!
don't hurt her
what ever conditions you want
Ling I prepared something for you
go take a look
for this?
sign it
don't sign it, Lingyue don't do it
stay where you are
stop wasting time! sign it now!
Okay, i'll sign it
Don't sign.
'Ling Yue'
Here
Are you alright?
Lingyue, watch out!
Hello?
Yes I know, sent me the location
Lingyue
are you alright?
please, tell me your fine
i'm fine
i'm sorry... i'm sorry
In a moment you won't be fine
Yuguo, this is against the law
Mind your own business
i'm alright
then good, I'm done here
whatever happens next
is up to you
what do I do with those two
with just a fire
it can look like an accident between a lovers quarrel
then everything can looks like a secret taken to the grave
don't you hate her
heres your chance, don't waste it
why did you become like this, Yuguo?
Its because of you
If you didn't push me
would I be like this?
It wasn't like that
You losing your ability
is because of abutilon poison
You mistakenly swallowed alprazolam. That's why you are in this condition.
I have the medical records, I can show you
Please believe me
No way, I don't believe it
this many years you didn't have any evidence
when you are pushed to your death, now you do?
This is a misunderstanding between us
please let him go
he is without blame, let him go
if he is blameless, then i'm not?
did you know how hard was it for me to recover
when i think you get to live
then I'll let you live in pain
what happened
now it's exposed we need to contact the police
if I have to die then let's die together
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Memories are soaked in rain ♫
♫ Fate works bizarrely ♫
♫ The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly beats abnormally ♫
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Obviously, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness, for it has always been you ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Yet the longing has never been able to stop ♫
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Using all of my most beautiful adjectives ♫
♫ Is still not enough to describe your name ♫
♫ Our story is exclusively ours ♫
♫ Our palms hold onto the key to the future ♫
♫ Using love to slowly open up a lifetime ♫