♪Following the way she walked through♪
♪He searches for every piece of memory
that he had with her♪
♪An unexpected encounter in the crowds♪
♪Was the start of their
destined journey♪
♪No one can tell the end of the story♪
♪Since every heart is overloaded♪
♪The dream about blooming
flowers is illusionary♪
♪Painful yet addictive♪
♪Love is too wild to be reined♪
♪Too deep to be forgot♪
♪The pain will forever stay
with the scar on the chest♪
♪He wants to linger in his dream♪
=Tears In Heaven=
=Episode 26=
Lei Yuzheng.
Sir, please follow that car.
You have drunk a lot.
Please stop drinking.
You again?
You've been following me all the way.
Just leave me alone.
I'm worried about you.
I don't want to see
anything happen to you.
Let's go home.
Let go of me.
Lei Yuzheng, you just...
just came back.
What did you say just now?
What did you want to say?
Fresh out of prison, right?
You don't think prison is a good word.
You care about my feelings,
right?
Du Xiaosu, I hate you!
I hate the way you're looking at me now!
What's that?
Sympathy?
No, pity me, right?
I don't sympathize with you.
I don't pity you either.
I just care about you!
Because in my heart,
you are still Lei Yuzheng as before.
Are you the Virgin Mary?
Don't waste your time on me.
Why are you doing this?
Why do you treat me like this?
You were like this
when I went to see you.
Now you still treat me like this!
Is it so hard for you to accept my care?
Du Xiaosu.
Your care
for me
is superfluous.
OK. You don't have to accept it,
but I'm going to take care of you today.
Go home.
Go. Stand up!
Have you met my dad?
Who's responsible for
the illness of my dad?
It's me.
I made my dad get sick.
Can I go home without being guilty?
I've already told you
that's because of
the aftereffects of stroke.
You know that
this disease is hardly curable.
Go.
Getting drunk or not is
none of your business. Leave me alone!
Lei Yuzheng, you feel so sad,
guilty, and wronged.
I can understand.
But you're a man,
and you have to take
that responsibility.
Your father is in illness now.
You're here
complaining about everything.
Will it work to blame yourself?
Will your father get better?
Yes, it's hard for you right now.
But every family or every person
in the world
has their own difficulties.
You want to drink, right?
I'll drink with you.
You are crazy.
Aren't you crazy, either?
If you want to be crazy,
let's be crazy together.
Du Xiaosu.
You still don't get it.
I'm doing it for your own good.
I'm always unlucky.
I bring misery to all who come near me.
Before, it was Zhenrong.
Now, it's my dad.
Go, and leave me alone!
I'm not leaving,
unless we go together.
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
What? Are you scared?
Du Xiaosu.
Now, I am not
Lei Yuzheng of the past.
♪Between us♪
♪Dreams have never been this quiet♪
Now, I can do anything bad.
♪Your love weeps for a withered soul♪
♪That teardrop of sadness
brings extreme beauty♪
♪Indulged in the black
whirlpool of your eyes♪
♪Dreams have never been this quiet♪
No matter what you become,
and no matter what you want to do,
I'm here for you!
(Nanpu Bridge)
Dad.
Dad, let's have dinner.
Please have some.
Don't bother me. I'm watching TV.
Dad.
Get out of the way.
I have cooked for you.
Please have some.
Who are you?
Dad, I'm your son.
Let me tell you.
My son is Lei Yuzheng.
He is abroad.
Don't bother me.
Have some, dad, please.
You're not supposed to bother me.
Go away.
If you do this again, old man,
I won't take care of you anymore.
I'm not asking you to take care of me.
I'm your son.
I'm your son, Lei Yuzheng.
Dad.
Son?
You're Yuzheng?
Yes, I'm your son, Lei Yuzheng.
You are really my son?
Yes, dad.
You're back at last!
Dad.
Yuzheng, Yuzheng, you finally come back.
Where is Marshmallow?
Would you like to eat marshmallow?
Nonsense.
You cannot eat Marshmallow.
If you eat Marshmallow,
who will play with me?
Here is the candy, Mr. Lei.
Marshmallow, marshmallow?
Dad,
don't you have it in your hand?
Yuzheng, Marshmallow that
Mr. Lei mentioned
is Miss Du.
Wait, Xiaosu.
What's the matter?
I'll talk to you when I get back.
I'll go and see Mr. Lei first.
Xiaosu, I've been holding it for days.
I have to tell you today.
If you don't care anymore,
our studio is really going to
be shut up.
Shut up?
What do you mean?
The real estate market
hasn't been good lately.
No one bought apartments,
and no one needed decoration.
If we cannot sign a new contract,
we will run out of money.
How about Mr. Liu?
Have you got the money from Mr. Liu?
Mr. Liu is always very picky,
and the scheme provided to him
has never been passed.
Let me check it out.
Yuzheng, you don't know.
When you were not here,
Miss Du took care of Mr. Lei.
She always bought candy for Mr. Lei.
So Mr. Lei gave her a nickname,
Marshmallow.
Uncle Duan, I'm back now.
For this matter,
you don't need to bother Du Xiaosu
anymore.
OK.
Please rest assured.
Yuzheng, my son,
come here.
Look!
Lollipop, marshmallow.
They are all for you. Do you like them?
Last time,
when I was back from business trip,
I forgot to buy you candies.
You cried,
and almost rolled on the floor.
-Dad.
-It is dad's fault.
They are here.
Dad's fault.
Dad should buy you candies.
I can make it up to you
with these candies.
Try it.
Hurry up. Have a try.
It is about to start.
What is about to start?
News.
(Jiangsu TV. Jiangsu News Watch)
Dad,
it is late.
Can we turn it down a little bit?
I am watching news.
As an enterprise president,
we have to keep abreast of current news.
You're right.
But the news has been replayed
many times.
So many times.
You should go to bed.
I have to attend a meeting.
Meeting?
You're right!
The meeting is important.
OK, now stop watching.
Turn off the TV.
Come on.
Let me take you to your bedroom.
Why are you looking around?
I only look for someone.
Uncle Duan?
Why do I look for Uncle Duan?
I am looking for...
I forgot...
OK, dad.
I can't sleep unless I find her.
Dad.
Check it out.
Are you looking for them?
Grandpa and grandma?
Him, or him?
These were your friends when you
worked in the countryside.
Dad.
Who are they?
Why don't I know anyone?
Wanhua.
Yes, I'm looking for Wanhua.
You still remember her?
Wanhua is my spouse.
I lost her. It's my fault.
I have to get her back.
Dad.
You know what time it is?
It's been many years since she left.
Why do you want to look for her?
Nonsense!
She was here a moment ago.
She just disappeared in a twinkling
of an eye. Let's go.
Dad.
I need to find her.
Where can you find her?
Mr. Lei.
What happened?
Marshmallow, Marshmallow!
Take your time.
OK, take it.
See?
Marshmallow is nice to me.
You have to take off your glasses.
You annoy me all the time.
Fine, dad.
I promise that I will never
annoy you again.
Good night.
When did you get married?
Why didn't you tell me?
Dad, you misunderstood.
Xiaosu...
Marshmallow is my friend.
She is not married.
Not married?
You haven't got married yet?
Why does she always stay in our home?
This is not good.
If you don't hurry up,
and fail to marry such a good girl,
I'll blame you!
Why don't you go?
Where?
You just said you have a meeting.
You are not the same as me.
In those days,
I worked and lived in the company
every day.
So I can make Yutian
become a large company.
No company president can be
as relaxed as you are.
You're right. You're right.
He is...
He's leaving soon.
Dare not listen to
what I say...
Please lie down.
If he bullies you in the future,
just let me know.
I'll scold him!
OK.
Well, it's time for you to sleep.
Close your eyes, please.
Good.
You must be very tired today.
It's difficult for you.
It doesn't matter.
That's what a stroke patient
looks like.
Sometimes he is clearheaded,
and sometimes confused.
And,
he also loses his temper
for no reason.
These are normal.
So you have to be very patient.
You have to be mentally prepared.
My dad is everything to me now.
He's the only family member I have left
in the world.
I have to take care of him
no matter what.
Is she your mom?
Your mom is so pretty.
She should be a lady of a big,
noble family,
and she is very graceful.
I just heard that
my grandpa's family was well-known
in the south of the Yangtze River.
My mother is
the apple of their eye.
When my dad met my mom,
he was a poor student.
Their marriage
was strongly opposed by
my grandpa and grandma.
Your mother must love
your father deeply.
This is how it was at the beginning,
but as my father became increasingly
busier at work,
they started to quarrel.
More and more terrible quarrel.
Forget it!
Let's not talk about this.
In fact, the younger generation like us
is hard to judge the love of
the older generation.
Who would ever think,
Aunt Shao was my father's first love.
Thus, she was so against
me and Zhenrong.
But to be honest.
I never blamed her.
I can only say that
the destiny makes fool of the people.
For the past,
we didn't know everything well,
and the future is difficult to control.
So it's better to be optimistic
at the moment,
and take good care of the people
around you.
Sorry for saying too much.
Your studio just opened.
You must have a lot of work to do.
You don't need to worry about my dad.
Lei Yuzheng.
I don't like what you just said.
I am willing to take care of Mr. Lei.
Tomorrow, I
will still come over to see Mr. Lei.
I have to go.
Mr. Lin.
Look at He Qunfei.
I didn't expect that
the former president's assistant
would end up like this.
Lei Yuzheng is in such a situation.
I think he should regret it very much.
That's why he would rather
work here as a cleaner
than leave.
It's good to have him around.
I want He Qunfei to know that
I'm now
the real person in charge of Yutian.
I agree with you.
Wait, Qunfei.
This place is quite spacious.
Your work is not busy.
Clean it up, Qunfei.
Sort these items out,
and clean them up.
Remember to clean them up!
Qunfei, when you were with Lei Yuzheng,
I think you are very good.
Reliable, hard-working
and uncomplaining.
You'll only be a cleaner for a while.
I'll assign you decent jobs.
But don't worry.
I will not waste your talent.
Yes, Mr. Lin.
As you said before,
if Qunfei can work for us
someday,
that would be perfect.
Now, it comes true.
Mr. Lin and Mr. Xie,
I never fear hardship.
You let me clean the bathroom.
No problem. I will do it.
I also promise to do better than others.
But if you let me enter
Mr. Lei's office.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
I'm sure Mr. Lei will come back
one day.
Now, I, He Qunfei,
submit my resignation.
He Qunfei, think it over.
If you leave Yutian
and want a new job,
it would not be easy.
Qunfei,
I didn't know why I had offended you.
Now that you've decided to go,
I will not stop you.
I've always treated you as my buddy.
If you want to come back one day,
you're always welcomed here.
Mr. Lin,
rest assured.
Even if I become a beggar,
I won't come back.
Here comes the stuffing.
In such a short time,
you've already rolled
so many dumpling wrappers.
Great.
Look,
you have to press both ends,
wrap around here and squeeze it.
Like this.
Marshmallow, are the dumplings ready?
Very soon.
Dad, please wait.
A watched pot never boils.
I don't want to eat the dumplings
made by you.
I want to eat the ones
made by Marshmallow.
Lei Yuzheng,
Mr. Lei favors me more.
You said I was messing them up.
I call it icing on the cake.
I don't even know why my dad is
so biased towards you.
Lei Yuzheng, how
a rich boss like you
can roll dumpling wrappers
and make dumplings.
I learned it from Aunt Shao.
My father loved eating dumplings
at that time.
But he was too lazy,
and he can't make dumplings.
So I stayed in Aunt Shao's home
every day.
And,
please don't call me boss again.
That was before.
I just want to live a peaceful life now.
Cure my dad.
Be a dutiful son.
Excuse me.
Who are you looking for?
Why you walk in directly?
I'm a friend of Mr. Lei.
I want to know how he's getting on.
I just come and have a look.
You have to go.
Don't make me hurt you.
Lei Yuzheng.
That's how you treat the guest.
I came to see you today
to apologize to you.
From your attitude,
I know I flatter myself.
But,
I still need to remind you.
You are nothing now!
Hot, be careful, please.
Eat slowly.
Cool it. Cool it.
OK, now.
You can go now.
Lei Yuzheng, why are you so mean?
I helped you make the dumplings.
Now it's finally cooked.
I don't even take a mouthful of soup.
You're asking me to leave?
Even capitalists won't treat employees
like you, right?
Mr. Lei, look at him.
He's going to kick me away.
You should decide who is right.
How dare he!
Ignore him. Let's have dumplings.
Have a seat.
OK, just ignore him.
We'll have dumplings.
Be careful. This is hot!
Take it slowly.
Du Xiaosu,
thank you for coming to help my dad
during this period.
At this home,
you are not needed now.
Lei Yuzheng,
did I say anything that
offended you?
I'm telling you.
You are burning the bridges,
and getting rid of me.
Marshmallow cannot go.
You can go.
Go.
Go away!
Let's eat dumplings.
Eat dumplings.
Lei Yuzheng.
Lei Yuzheng, what are you doing?
Lei Yuzheng, what's wrong with you?
What are you doing?
Lei Yuzheng, you really think
you are a rainy day like your name?
Sometimes it is sunny and
sometimes gloomy.
Du Xiaosu, you must go today.
What are you doing, Lei Yuzheng?
Your dad is sick and so are you?
Lei Yuzheng.
Lei Yuzheng, what is wrong with you?
What have I done to you?
Lei Yuzheng,
why did you turn against me?
Open the door.
Did you hear that?
Brat.
You bring me back Marshmallow.
Lei Yuzheng, I know I offended you.
I can change if I offended you, right?
You have to be concerned about Mr. Lei.
Mr. Lei is really upset.
Don't you feel bad about
making him unhappy?
Open the door, Lei Yuzheng.
I still have to remind you.
You are nothing now.
Do you still want to compete with me?
I know you can hear me.
I left the medicine in the doorway
for you.
Don't forget to let Mr. Lei take it.
I'll see you tomorrow.
♪The dream about blooming
flowers is illusionary♪
(Vertigo Relief Tablets)
♪Painful yet addictive♪
♪Surging love raises a storm
in the city♪
♪The world is deceived while a true
heart would not be cheated♪
♪Frantic pursuit of the marks
on the chest♪
♪The one and only in destiny♪
♪The pain on the back and the marks
on the chest♪
♪Continue to indulge in the dream♪
Welcome. Miss Zou.
Look at our new season's bags.
You really have a good taste.
This is made from
African ostrich skin.
It is Designer Limited Edition
that has just arrived.
Isn't it a little old-fashioned?
Look at some others.
Let me check out other bags.
Show me the red one.
Sure.
You really have a good taste.
This red color really suits your
skin tone.
Your skin is white.
This color is good.
Yes, looks bright.
Please try it!
Looks good?
Really good.
You are elegant in this bag!
Well,
you're so sweet.
Wrap it up.
Sure.
I'll wrap it for you.
By the way,
your husband is very kind to you.
The pink bag of the new season
hasn't cleared customs yet.
He has ordered it for you directly.
Really?
Show me.
Why didn't I know that?
Sure.
Also, I need to confirm with you.
For the lock here,
is it right to write Meimei?
What?
Maybe we made a mistake.
(Meimei)
Let me show you the purchase order.
Pack it up.
Sure.
Have a nice day.
Leader.
How is it?
What do you feel wearing this dress?
Good.
I know you used to be with Lei Yuzheng,
and spent a lot of money here.
But as the circumstances change,
you have to get used to it.
If you really can't do this service job,
just bring it up early.
There are plenty of people
who want to take this job.
You can rest assured.
I can do it.
All right. Then work hard.
Buddy, I owe you money?
No.
How could I possibly owe someone money?
You owe me money?
You are not for money. Then for what?
Woman?
You just get it?
Tell me.
Who?
Lily? Amy?
Or Meimei?
That's a lot.
Qunfei,
as a man,
how can you say that?
Moreover,
I don't steal,
rob or cheat.
It's all up to free wills.
I'm not forcing anyone.
Tell me.
Who have I offended?
You know who you have offended.
He.
Shut up.
Mr. Shangguan.
I'm sorry.
It is the first day he starts work here.
Please forgive him
if there is anything wrong.
I'm telling you.
If it isn't for Lei Yuzheng's sake,
today, I...
What are you going to do today?
I'm telling you.
You don't have to be
for the sake of anyone.
Come on.
Let's have a fight!
He, are you crazy?
You know who this guy is?
You want to be fired?
I want to quit.
That's it. I've had enough!
He.
I also want to tell you.
If you dare hurt Siqi,
I'll let you know
what is being clingy
and haunting.
Mr. Shangguan.
It's OK.
Go.
Siqi?
Si... Siqi.
He Qunfei.
Why are you here?
Shangguan is also here, right?
Shangguan?
No.
We haven't seen each other
for a long time.
Shall we have a dinner?
Is it in this room?
Siqi.
Isn't...
Isn't this my bag?
It arrives so soon.
Who is she?
My friend.
You have a lot of friends.
Siqi. Siqi.
Why are you here?
The money in my card is used up?
Here you are.
Buy whatever you want.
Shangguan Boyao.
What do you take me for?
Girlfriend.
Girlfriend?
I think I am just one of your girlfriends.
Siqi,
you've been with me for so long.
I think we
should have a tacit understanding.
What kind of tacit understanding?
What do you mean?
I...
I'm not like other kinds of boyfriends.
I can provide you a lot of things.
But,
I can't give you a promise.
I think our
relationship
should be simpler
and we should have more freedom.
Tell me.
You are not happy with me now?
Happy.
Very happy.
I just knew you would understand.
Go. Let's go inside.
Sorry.
I'm a neat freak.
I think you should
keep having fun with others.
Siqi.
Come on, buddy.
Freedom?
He only made an excuse for a playboy.
It was really difficult for him.
Why are you following me?
You want me to talk about you too?
What are you doing here?
Give up the work in Yutian?
Yes, I gave up.
I don't want to be annoyed
by Lin Xiangyuan.
That's better than working in this KTV.
Serving people with tea and water.
You used to be
an assistant of a president.
You don't have to worry about me.
I'm fine.
But you...
What?
Siqi, I saw everything.
You see what?
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle in
pain and delight♪
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle in
pain and delight♪
♪Your love weeps for a withered soul♪
♪That teardrop of sadness
brings extreme beauty♪
♪Indulged in the black
whirlpool of your eyes♪
♪Dreams have never been this quiet♪