♪Following the way she walked through♪
♪He searches for every piece of
memory that he had with her♪
♪An unexpected encounter in the crowds♪
♪Was the start of their destined journey♪
♪No one can tell the end of the story♪
♪Since every heart is overloaded♪
♪The dream about blooming
flowers is illusionary♪
♪Painful yet addictive♪
♪Love is too wild to be reined♪
♪Too deep to be forgot♪
♪The pain will forever stay
with the scar on the chest♪
♪He wants to linger in his dream♪
=Tears In Heaven=
=Episode 25=
Mr. Pan, for the details of
our cooperation,
I will ask Manager Xie
to email you by then.
Mr. Lin is really a quick doer.
Having your words, I feel relieved now.
I heard before that Mr. Lei from Yutian
is a very able man.
But I didn't know that
there is always someone better,
until I met Mr. Lin today.
You're flattering me!
Happy cooperation!
OK. Happy cooperation!
OK.
Come with me, please.
Xiangyuan?
Are you Lin Xiangyuan?
Who are you?
You didn't recognize me?
I can tell now.
Who am I?
Mengnan, Li Mengnan!
Oh, my goodness.
What brings you to shanghai?
I'm here for business.
Come, come, come!
I'll take you out to dinner!
OK.
I haven't put my suitcase down yet.
Mrs. Fanlv, when I was doing laundry,
I found this in Mr. Lin's pocket,
wondering if Mr. Lin still needs it.
(Customer Information. Lin Xiangyuan)
(Li Mengnan)
Not bad.
This is my husband.
A technician from IT field.
When I arrived in Tianjin,
he started going after me.
Next to him is my son.
He is five years old
and his name is Dudu.
You're so happy. Such a perfect match!
And you also have a lovely son.
No need to be envied.
Didn't you get married
and have children?
Xiangyuan.
Xiangyuan,
you are asked to send some photos.
Your wife's photos.
What happened?
You are not married?
My wife is from Shanghai
and her surname is Jiang.
She is just pregnant.
Her dad and I work in the same company.
He is the chairman of the company.
Chairman?
Until now, I just figured out that
you're working for your father-in-law.
Well, not bad, Lin Xiangyuan.
Not only earning money from Shanghai,
and even married with
a wealthy fair belle from Shanghai.
We are really proud of you!
OK, let's not talk about this.
How long are you planning to
stay in Shanghai this time?
How about I take you around in Shanghai?
If you need any help in Shanghai,
just feel free to let me know.
Well, I really need your help now.
This time, I came to
Shanghai from Tianjin
for business.
But I don't know their boss very well.
So, I want you to go with me and
give me some advice.
OK, no problem.
It's my pleasure.
-Thank you.
-Cheers!
This way, please.
OK, thank you.
Please wait here,
and our president will come very soon.
OK, thanks.
(In the Meeting. Keep Quiet)
Mr. Shangguan, I'm Li Mengnan.
Nice to meet you.
We talked before over the phone.
Nice to meet you, Ms. Li.
Nice to meet you.
Sorry, this is?
This is my friend, Lin Xiangyuan.
He is the president of Yutian Group.
Oh, Mr. Shangguan.
You are a big shot and
I guess you wouldn't mind
I bring my friend here
to give some advice.
President of Yutian Group.
He should be the big shot here.
He's more than welcome to be here.
Right, Mr. Lin?
Nice to meet you.
Then, let's start now.
Please introduce the project, Ms. Li.
Sure.
(Slow Enough, Beautiful Enough)
Siqi, why are you still there?
I'm waiting for Shangguan
to pick me up.
You go first.
Will Shangguan drive Mercedes
or Land Rover today?
You are out of date.
I saw it last time.
Shangguan just changed to a new Volvo,
and took Siqi out for a drive!
Really?
Volvo?
(Home Magazine)
I've never been in a Volvo.
Maybe I was wrong.
I just saw a woman on passenger seat,
also with short hair.
The car was very fast.
I thought it was you.
Well, I'm leaving now.
Bye.
Bye, Siqi.
This idea is ultramodern.
(Zou Siqi)
Glass curtain wall with the steel frame
structure as the main structure
coupled with the curved and
variable bending shape,
undoubtedly adds a strong modern style
to the entire Shanghai architecture.
Taking the advantage of Huangpu River,
geography and shape,
the building will
leave a very strong stroke.
Mr. Shangguan.
Mr. Shangguan?
What do you think?
You're done?
I think this project is very good.
Personally, I'm very satisfied with it.
But I have a little question.
During our cooperation this time,
will Mr. Lin join in?
To tell you the truth,
Xiangyuan is really a business expert.
I'm about to invite him to our project
and give some advice.
Really?
Yes.
That's great!
But... if this is the case,
I have to reconsider
the cooperation between us.
What do you mean?
Lin Xiangyuan, Mr. Lin,
I've heard of his name for a long time.
In the beginning,
he was sent by Boyuan Company to
Yutian as an outside help.
But during that period of time,
he replaced Lei Yuzheng.
And by pestering again and again,
he finally got Miss Jiang.
In the end,
he suddenly changed his identity
to the president of Yutian.
Such scheming mind and means
are really admirable.
Mr. Lin, how did you make it?
Teach me.
So, Ms. Li,
if Mr. Lin is also involved
in this project,
in the end, I may be
kicked out unconsciously
as well.
Who am I going to cry to by then?
Ms. Li,
you have to be responsible to me then.
Excuse me,
Lei Yuzheng?
Who is Lei Yuzheng?
I didn't get you.
Shangguan,
don't get other people
involved in our feud.
I can promise you that
I won't interfere in this cooperation,
if you cooperate with Mengnan.
Now, you start being
kind and nice to friends.
But it's a pity.
I know what kind of person you are.
I knew it long time ago.
Ms. Li,
I can't trust this person
and I also advise you
to stay away from him.
Be careful. Otherwise,
you may be betrayed someday
and won't even be aware of that.
Mr. Shangguan,
if you do not have confidence
in our cooperation,
Wenxing won't force it.
But,
please respect my friend.
Thank you.
Xiangyuan, let's go.
Bye and take care.
Xiangyuan,
why did Shangguan Boyao
judge you in that way?
Who is Lei Yuzheng?
Mengnan,
I haven't had the time to tell you.
Lei Yuzheng is the former president
of our company.
Because of a case,
he is in jail now.
At that time, the company was a mess.
I was entrusted at that time,
and became the president of the company.
Shangguan and Lei Yuzheng
grow up together.
He thinks I robbed
Lei Yuzheng's position.
So, no matter what I explained,
he still doesn't buy it.
He is too bully!
Lei Yuzheng went to prison.
You became the president instead of him.
That is because you have the ability.
Mengnan,
I'm sorry to let you
come here for nothing.
Why not you give me
your project proposal?
I'll help you figure out a solution.
I have said it's fine.
Don't be so fussy.
What are you doing as a big man?
OK.
How about this?
You take me around in Shanghai
these two days,
since now I have nothing to worry about.
Sure.
Let's go!
(Zou Siqi)
Hello. What do you mean?
Why didn't you call me the whole day?
I'm sorry, Siqi. I'm very busy today.
Again? Are you too busy
to even make a call?
Shangguan.
Hang up?
I'm here today to tell you that
I helped you out!
What happened?
The story goes like this.
There is a lady,
who looks pretty by the way.
She wants to cooperate with our company.
But she came with Lin Xiangyuan.
Guess what?
Can I pass up such an opportunity?
Right in front of this lady,
I gave Lin Xiangyuan a horrible meal.
In the end, I decided to
terminate the cooperation.
She has no rancor against you.
Why did you do that?
Because she is a friend
of Lin Xiangyuan.
How unlucky she is!
Buddy, after all,
what I can make now
is only small troubles
I'm waiting for the day you come out.
Let's do something big.
Stop it.
Don't say that again in the future.
I'm now a prisoner
and have no plan for the future.
And Shangguan,
here is not a good place,
don't come to see me
in the future anymore.
When I'm out, let's get together.
I'm leaving now.
Buddy.
Go.
Go back.
Xiangyuan, thank you these days
for taking me around.
It must waste you a lot of time.
In fact,
I should thank you.
I have been working in Shanghai
for such a long time
and these days are
the happiest and most relaxed moments.
If it wasn't because of you,
I have almost forgotten
what smile should be like.
Xiangyuan, in fact, there's a question
I always wanted to ask you.
How are you doing in Shanghai?
Mengnan, I remember
we met each other
in a townsmen gathering.
I remember that day
we talked until very late.
You said that, after you graduate,
you want to get married
and become a mom.
You want a family.
I said I must stay in Shanghai
after I graduate and
work in the best office building.
I must be a successful person
and have the best things in the world.
Then...
Then marry your most favorite lady.
Actually, I still remember
the way you said that.
There was light in your eyes.
Since then,
Xiangyuan,
I have been having the faith that
you will definitely be successful.
Mengnan, I want to ask you.
What is success?
Look at me now.
I am rich. I have a nice car,
a nice apartment,
and a rich wife.
These are what other people dream of.
But to be honest,
I'm not happy at all now.
Sometimes, when I stay with her,
we even have no common topic.
I also feel pretty boring.
But now, we are going to have a baby.
There is hope in life.
Then life has to go on.
Xiangyuan, do you know
what is the most terrible thing?
That is to keep looking  back
when moving forward.
OK, let's drop it.
Just let bygones be bygones.
Everything will get better.
Let's sit here.
It's really tiring
after shopping for a whole day.
Fanlv, you are pregnant now.
Still going out with us?
Your husband didn't stop you?
Did he? He treasures you so much.
If Lin Xiangyuan blames us,
you have to speak for us.
Can he control me?
Why hasn't Shasha come yet?
She leaves us alone again?
Let me call her.
It's late. Let me send you back.
Let's go.
Wait a minute.
What happened?
Sands are in my eyes.
Look!
Check out who that is?
No way!
It is really him.
What are you looking at?
Nothing. The environment
is quite nice here.
Really?
Why didn't I notice?
It's pretty good, very affectionate.
Fanlv, still awake?
Aren't you the same?
Still be out there messing
around in the midnight.
Who is messing around?
A work meal and I was held back.
At this moment,
you're still trying to cheat?
Opening a room in a hotel
during the Spring Festival.
Not bad, huh?
You asked me to go home with you
so eagerly for the Spring Festival.
I thought how filial you are.
You are really good!
No, I didn't go home
during the Spring Festival
and opened a room in a hotel.
I can explain.
Explain what?
Stop pretending!
I saw it clearly this afternoon.
In broad daylight,
you were with a lady and
had very close physical touch.
I cannot imagine
how many shameful things
you have done in private.
You mean Li Mengnan?
Please speak with respect.
Angry now?
Are you serious to that home-wrecker?
Could you just stop it?
It's really a shame!
Dad, he did this to me.
We are done.
What did I do? That's my fellow.
You can embarrass me deliberately.
You can also pour dirty water on me.
But please don't insult my friend, OK?
Your friend?
So affectionate.
Lin Xiangyuan, if you are a man,
stop taking advantages of both sides.
You can't have your cake and eat it.
Enough!
Does that sound good to you?
What happened?
Have you been unfaithful to her?
Dad, Li Mengnan came to Shanghai
for business.
As a fellow and a host,
I just accompanied her around.
Do you think I believe you?
That's right.
I don't need to explain at all.
Because even if I explained,
you won't listen.
From the day we got married,
have you treated me well?
Have you ever regarded me
as your husband?
Jiang Fanlv,
don't you wish I had
some affairs outside,
so that you can directly
divorce with me?
Dad, I don't mind how Fanlv
is usually wayward,
and how she loses her temper.
I can try my best to bear all.
But she cannot just fabricate this
to force me to divorce.
Nor can she make fun of my friend.
My friend is innocent.
You have to be fair.
Fanlv,
Xiangyuan is not unreasonable.
How about you both calm down first?
Fanlv,
did you really misunderstand him?
(Eight Months Later)
Lei Yuzheng.
Come out and go through
procedures with me.
Congratulations, buddy.
Free again.
Yes, free again.
I've never expected
"freedom" can be
so luxurious like now.
Well, you don't want to leave?
To some extent, you are right.
Yes, kind of.
Suddenly free again.
In the rest of my life,
I will never forget this place.
No matter what,
this is just a place you stopped by.
You can take it as a suffering,
or a practice.
But no matter how you take it,
when the time comes, you have to leave.
Move forward.
Money Game.
Bye.
Take care.
Remember,
after you go outside that door,
don't look back.
Live a good life after going out.
When you have any difficulties,
just call me.
The door here
is always open.
But hope you'll never come back.
Thank you, Officer Liang.
You're welcome. This is my job.
Didn't you inform your family?
No, it's not a glorious thing.
I didn't tell them.
Let bygones be bygones.
Don't think too much.
There are still more days to come.
Here. Just go.
This place is a bit remote.
If you don't leave now,
you will miss the bus.
Bon voyage.
Goodbye.
(Jiangkan Detention Center)
Who is this?
Didn't recognize her?
Wanhua.
Yes, it's her, Wanhua.
Yuzheng is not at home.
But where did Wanhua go?
She also went abroad.
She's worried about Yuzheng.
So, she went with him.
Go to the door to check
if they have come back.
There are so many things that
haven't been done abroad.
They will be back
after they finish them.
No, you have to go and check.
Maybe they're back now.
Go, go, go. Hurry up.
OK, then.
I will go to check.
Hurry up.
Stay here.
I'll be right back.
He's back. He's back.
Yuzheng,
you are back.
This is really magical.
Mr. Lei asked me to check the door
just at the right time,
neither too early nor too late.
If it is not the telepathy
between a father and a son,
what else it could be?
Kid, you're back!
Uncle Duan misses you so much!
Uncle Duan, where's my dad?
Mr. Lei!
Mr. Lei, check out who is back?
Yuzheng is back.
Dad,
I am back.
Dad.
You're back?
You finished all matters abroad?
It's all done, dad.
Mr. Lei.
Dad.
It's OK. It's so far away.
Are you hungry?
Yuzheng is hungry.
Start the meal, Duan.
OK, start the meal now.
Let's open a bottle of red wine.
Let's celebrate.
And Yuzheng's favorite, crystal shrimp.
I am going to prepare now.
Great.
About that matter,
although dad is willing to believe you,
ins and outs,
you have to make it clear as well.
You said that you went home
for the Spring Festival,
but it turned out that,
you were in a hotel room.
No wonder Fanlv doubted.
Dad, I was planning to.
I already drove to the airport.
My mom called and scolded me,
saying that I had to take my wife home,
or I couldn't go home.
I was also very embarrassed.
If I went back, how could I
explain to my mom?
If I stayed in Shanghai,
how could I face Fanlv?
I really had no good idea in the end.
So, I opened a room in a hotel
to calm myself down.
As for Li Mengnan,
Jiang Fanlv was catching at shadows.
For this matter, I'm all to be blamed.
For the Spring Festival,
your mom wants a family reunion.
This is human nature.
But Fanlv
was spoiled since she was a kid.
She didn't want to go back with you,
and I could do nothing about it.
But we ignored your feelings,
and hurt you.
But when there is a problem,
we should solve it together.
Not like you and Fanlv.
You clamored to get a divorce,
whenever something happened.
This will only hurt your relationship.
Am I right?
Dad, I didn't demand a divorce.
I want to live a good life.
But Fanlv doesn't give me the chance.
I really can't do anything about it.
Don't worry.
Although Fanlv is wayward,
she is not bad in nature.
Find a chance to explain to her,
and she can figure it out naturally.
As for your mom,
when it gets warmer,
bring her to Shanghai.
She raised you up alone
and suffered a lot.
You and Fanlv should do your best
to take care of her.
As for Fanlv,
ask her to apologize to
your mother sincerely.
Xiangyuan, just do me a favor.
Dad,
I am sorry.
I'm the one who had you suffer.
I will take care of you from now on.
Why should you take care of me?
I am very well. You don't need to.
Work harder.
Yutian is such a big company.
Don't you need to take care of it?
My son can tell jokes now.
You take care of me?
Am I a three-year-old kid?
Eat, eat.
Dad.
Come, let's wash feet.
Hot?
Dad,
I won't go anywhere anymore.
I'll stay at home with you.
When I was little,
you took care of me.
Now, I should take care of you.
What happened?
You are not my son. Who are you?
Dad, I am Yuzheng.
No, you're not Yuzheng.
You don't look like my son at all.
This is when I was a kid.
I'm grown up now
and look different from before.
No, you're not Yuzheng.
You must be a liar, a liar.
You are a liar, a liar.
Dad.
You said that, when I was young,
my nose looked exactly like yours.
You can touch and feel.
Just touch it.
There are so many noses
that look similar.
Dad.
Drive away the liar.
Mr. Lei.
What's wrong, Yuzheng?
Uncle Duan,
my dad suddenly doesn't recognize me.
Mr. Lei, why are you confused?
You look forward to seeing your son
every day.
Yuzheng is back now.
He is standing in front of you.
Why can't you recognize him?
Nonsense.
He is not Yuzheng.
How come…
Definitely not. He is a liar.
You drive him away.
Dad,
I know I did something wrong.
I'm the one who had you suffer.
I'm the one who destroyed Yutian.
You can beat me and scold me,
and I won't have any complaints.
But, please don't disown me.
Lei…
Lei Yuzheng?
Great, it's really you.
You are back. You are finally back.
What happened to you?
Did you see your dad?
Did
your dad kick you out?
Actually, you were not the first one
who was kicked out.
He kicked out many people.
Qunfei, Uncle Duan,
and me.
I'm his son.
You can't blame him.
He is clear sometimes.
Sometimes, he doesn't remember anything.
This is caused by his illness.
Please stand up.
It's quite cold outside.
I can't go inside now.
You neither.
Maybe when he sees you back,
he will be happy and…
Uncle Duan is there. That is enough.
Why?
I don't want to irritate him.
Xiaosu,
thank you for coming
to my house every day
to take care of my dad
during this period.
But I'm back now.
I think I have the ability to
take care of him by myself.
Well…
Do you understand?
Lei Yuzheng!
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle in
pain and delight♪
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle in
pain and delight♪
♪Your love weeps for a withered soul♪
♪That teardrop of sadness
brings extreme beauty♪
♪Indulged in the black
whirlpool of your eyes♪
♪Dreams have never been this quiet♪