=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 18=
You should be watching Qingchi Palace.
What are you doing here?
We received an invitation
to this birthday party.
My lord is away.
As the chief of Qingchi Palace,
it’s my courtesy to come with blessings.
What?
Do you, an immortal of Heaven,
want to take the liberty
of throwing me out in front of the host?
What’s wrong with being an immortal?
Let me tell you.
Lord Donghua is also an immortal.
It’s our rightful place
to govern Daze Mansion.
By despising me,
you’re challenging the Heaven.
Are you from Qingchi Palace
all so defiant?
My lord, my lady.
Please calm down.
Lady Fengran comes with blessings
from Qingchi Palace,
hence an honorable guest.
The presence of Heavenly royals
also proves your appreciation.
In Lord Donghua’s eyes,
your blessings are equally appreciated
and valued.
Alright.
Lord Ziyuan,
just a cup of wine for the new guest.
We have to show God Gu Jun, if not her,
the respect.
Your Highness,
it’s just
something I found
has been bothering me.
I should report it to His Majesty,
but since Your Highness is here,
I’d like to subject it to you.
Lord Ziyuan,
what’s been bothering you?
Your Highness,
a few days ago, I found
someone among us
colluding with demons.
Who is it?
You mean...?
It is Fengran.
Your Highness,
my friends,
she’s working with demons
on a conspiracy against us.
Guards.
Take Fengran down.
Wait.
Princess Jingzhao,
Qingchi Palace is independent
from the Three Realms,
including the Heaven.
Even the Heavenly Emperor himself
would have to ask before arresting me.
Do you want to skip the questioning?
It’s unreasonable and unfair.
As you all know,
demons and we are contradictions
of ice and fire.
I cannot turn a deaf ear
to your suspected
collusion with the demons.
It’s my duty to keep our world pure.
Well said.
I indeed came
from Abyssal Ridge Swamp.
But Qingchi Palace severed
my past with demons.
Do you have proofs
of my collusion with demons?
Your Highness,
my friends,
a few days ago, my disciples
were wounded by a demon
in Qingchi Palace
on an errand
to Qilian Mountains.
What’s more, the demon
snatched
a precious Fire Coral, the present
I prepared for Lord Donghua.
As you all know,
God Gu Jun has been traveling far away.
The young heiress is wet
behind the ears.
For the last tens of thousands of years,
the whole Qingchi Palace
follows your lead, right, Fengran?
Now a demon is found in Qingchi Palace.
You tell me.
Who is the traitor?
Nonsense!
There’s no demon in Qingchi Palace.
Your retort will come to no avail.
Wu Wang.
Yes!
This is the wound left by the demon.
How can you prove the scar
is left by a demon?
Even if you’re right,
how can you prove
its connection with us?
Well, how can you prove your innocence
against my accusation?
This is nothing
but his groundless talking.
Is he fanning hatred?
Fengran,
if Qingchi Palace is independent
from the Three Realms,
you should stay out of our fight
with demons.
I think my father has been merciful
to Qingchi Palace,
which makes your sabotaging collusion
with demons
behind God Gu Jun’s back
more unacceptable.
Merciful?
As existences of equal standing,
when do we require mercy from you?
Jingzhao,
do you plan to bully us
while God Gu Jun is away?
It’s such
a despicable thing to do.
This is insolent!
Go back home before you put on airs
as a princess.
Alright.
Fengran,
you deny it, don’t you?
I knew you wouldn’t admit it.
Never mind.
But let me be frank.
I had a tracking mark
on the Fire Coral.
As to whether it is you people
snatched it,
all we need is a test.
See?
Fengran,
what do you say now?
Well,
I’m also here to confront you.
Your disciples stole
from the Spiritual Spring.
The Fire Coral is the evidence.
It just surprises me
you thieves distort the truth.
Lord Ziyuan,
seize her.
Yes,
Your Highness.
Let me see
if the carefree North Sea Lord
can be wayward anymore.
What is she doing now?
Petty, he straps me to the main hall.
No.
My power is weak.
My presence will add
to Fengran’s trouble.
In case of danger,
fill power in this bracelet
and it’ll greatly ramp up your power.
It won’t last long,
but enough for you to escape.
(Eternal Heaven and Earth)
The Empress’s Phoenix Feather Fan?
Jingzhao,
you have no shame.
People like you
can’t be reasoned.
Years ago, for the sake of a demon,
you almost got my brother killed.
Today with the collusion,
you cannot be spared.
Lord Ziyuan,
seize this woman for me.
Yes, Your Highness.
Princess,
Fengran is the chief of Qingchi Palace.
Even if the collusion is real,
I’m afraid you can only punish her
after it’s reported to God Gu Jun.
God Gu Jun has been traveling
for tens of thousands of years.
It’s related to the demons,
and thus should fall into our hands.
Your Highness.
There is the young goddess.
Xianshan,
you can’t be
talking about that loser
of Qingchi Palace.
I heard she’s even weaker
than mortal priests.
Such immense power.
I find the power familiar.
How could we let a weak girl
make such a big decision?
Hold your defying words
against the goddess of Qingchi Palace.
You’ll be dead soon, so stop blabbing.
Fine.
Let me put an end to your misery.
Why does she become a different girl?
So much like the goddess in my dream.
- Master!
Who are you?
How dare you break in Daze Mansion,
hurt an immortal from Heaven
and disturb the birthday party?
Broke in?
Lord Xianshan, look.
(Invitation)
Is this
your master’s writing?
I’m invited.
What do you mean by “broke in”?
Welcome, Lady Deity.
Jingzhao,
you hurt my chief.
But I merely punished an immortal
of yours.
You are Houchi?
That’s impossible.
Houchi doesn’t have so much strength.
Greetings, Goddess Houchi.
Goddess.
Greetings, Goddess.
You said my power is too weak
to make a decision.
No, no, no.
No, Goddess.
I never said that.
I... I didn’t know you’d come.
Please, for the sake of the Heaven...
The Heaven?
You were accusing
my chief of colluding with demons.
Have you forgotten?
I was talking nonsense.
Nonsense.
Houchi,
Fengran’s collusion has been proved.
Even though in front of you,
I must bring her to trial in Heaven.
Really?
Are you two going to confess?
Or should I explain for you?
Mercy, Lady Deity.
Mercy.
I dare not lie.
He was wounded in Qingchi Palace.
Are you kidding me?
What are you afraid of?
I won’t allow her
to distort the truth.
He wasn’t wounded by a demon.
It’s a kind of magic potion
that transforms wounds.
Qingmu.
You mean...?
The magic potion
is made of scales of Illusion Fish
inhabiting at the bottom of the West Sea.
Apply honey from Feihong flowers on it,
and the wound will change back.
We have the honey in our mansion.
Lord Donghua likes it to go with
tea and desserts.
I’ll send someone to fetch some.
I deceived you.
Mercy.
You two,
be honest with it.
How were you wounded?
It... It was ourselves to be blamed.
These two sneaked into Qingchi Palace
to steal from Spiritual Spring
and was found.
Her Ladyship didn’t punish them
for they’re both young.
Well,
we forgave them for thievery
and they bit back
by framing collusion with demons on us.
Now it seems they
told a lie for fear of being punished
for losing the Fire Coral.
How dare you deceive me!
I’ll kill you.
Don’t be so rush with killing.
Give it back.
Goddess.
It’s no big deal.
If you like it,
keep it.
I have better ones at home.
I was too careless
and fell for their lie.
Please forgive me.
Of course, they are to be punished.
But you ran your mouth on us,
which is more intolerable.
This
is for your defiance of me.
is for the insult to Qingchi Palace.
And this
is for backstabbing Fengran years ago
at Abyssal Ridge Swamp.
Goddess.
Mercy.
Please, Goddess.
For the sake of Prince Jingyang,
please spare me.
Jingyang?
I almost forgot.
The Princes and Princess
are your supporters.
If I insist on punishing you,
even their father won’t say anything.
Houchi,
don’t insult my father.
Jingjian,
she hurts
me and Ziyuan.
Who is this?
Your Highness,
this is Goddess Houchi
of Qingchi Palace.
Oh, Goddess Houchi.
I wonder what Jingzhao and Ziyuan did
that incurs such punishment.
Jingjian.
Prince Jingjian, I’m impressed
by your timing.
While you were not here,
Jingzhao ordered Ziyuan to defame us.
Now when Goddess Houchi
is punishing the despicable man,
you decide to deliver justice.
I...
You misunderstand.
Your first visit coincides
with such a fuss.
As the host,
I apologize for the inconvenience.
Prince Jingjian,
given what Ziyuan did today,
I wonder if it’s necessary
to keep the eternal friendship
between Heaven and Qingchi Palace.
Jingzhao made a reckless mistake.
Ziyuan cannot represent the Heaven.
Please do not misunderstand.
Please ask His Majesty, Prince Jingjian,
what punishment he’ll inflict on Ziyuan
according to the law of the immortals.
Houchi, you...
Rest assured, Goddess.
I’ll report what happened to my father.
Let’s go.
Wait.
I have a matter of grave importance
to ask.
Can we talk in the back of the hall?
No.
Qingmu.
Hurry.
Let’s go to Boxuan’s bamboo hut.
I can’t hold it any longer.
What was going on?
My power...
You again?
Lord Qingmu,
you keep pestering us.
What is your intention?
Lady Fengran,
I mean no harm.
Lord Qingmu,
I didn’t punish you
for your impertinence.
Yet you follow us here.
Goddess Houchi,
I came after you to ask a question.
I lived in solitude in the North Sea
for thousands of years.
I don’t remember meeting you.
But why did I find you familiar
when I met you?
Pervert!
Will you stop it?
I just want to figure out why.
This is ridiculous.
How could I know why you had
that feeling for me?
Alright.
What about my sword then?
I smashed it into powder.
Wasn’t it burnt?
Yes, so what?
You may not know.
But that sword is a precious
object to me.
However precious it is,
it’s nothing but a sword.
I will forget
that you offended me.
Don’t push your luck.
Stop following us.
What is it that you want?
I just want to take my sword back.
I think I get your point.
Lord Qingmu,
these pearls can buy you a good sword.
I just want mine.
You’re being utterly absurd.
Your power...
Houchi, what’s wrong with you?
Fengran,
let’s go.
What was going on?
Nothing. I’m fine.
It just hit my nerve a bit.
I saw Ziyuan was going to harm you.
It was urgent.
So I used this bracelet.
But you’re even weaker
than magical beasts.
How did the bracelet help you push off
the Phoenix Feather Fan?
Besides,
Boxuan is just an ordinary immortal.
Where did he get
such a powerful halidom?
According to Boxuan,
the bracelet can greatly
ramp up my power.
It was the first time I used it.
In merely a quarter,
I begin to feel overwhelmed.
It’s true
that no pain, no gain.
By the way,
why is North Sea Lord
pestering you?
He drove a flying sword after me
and slashed my robe.
I was so angry
and burnt his sword to ashes.
Lord Ziyuan,
you’re an immortal from Heaven.
My father doesn’t even punish you.
Why are you still on your knees?
Get up.
Common trick.
Jingzhao, no!
The Lord of Thunder must be so bold
to strike Daze Mansion at this moment.
Those idiots.
It was you?
I cast a restriction
on Ziyuan.
The first to break it by force
will be struck by lightning.
You did it on purpose, didn’t you?
Who else in the hall except for Jingzhao
would be the first to try
to lift the restriction?
She attacked you behind your back.
How could I let her go unpunished?
Right now, I find
being a goddess is handy.
Well, you’re the most
loyal friend.
I gained some strength.
Let’s go find Boxuan.
Come on.
Jingjian.
Jingzhao, are...?
Are you alright?
The young heiress
does have immense power
to activate lightning by restriction.
Lord Donghua,
Jingzhao is young and wayward.
I apologize
for her imperti...
Princess Jingzhao
is just straightforward.
Never mind.
Lord Donghua,
my power is weak.
Would you please free him?
You can’t break it, either?
Sure I can break it.
But Goddess Houchi
cast a strong restriction.
Given my power,
if I break it by force,
I’m afraid I can only keep half
of Lord Ziyuan’s current power.
You’re one of
the most powerful immortals.
If you can only keep
half of his power,
no one could do better.
I have to bring Ziyuan to trial
by my father.
Please help us break the restriction.
Alright.
- Master!
Lord Donghua,
with such an emergency,
I cannot stay.
I’ll take Ziyuan
back to Heaven now.
Hold on.
I have a question,
if you may give me the answer.
Yes, please.
I never met North Sea Lord before.
How did you get to know him?
Qingmu and I once subdued
a demonic beast in the North Sea.
We often compete and exchange views.
Gradually, we become friends.
Does he have any family or friends?
Qingmu has no parents
and lives in solitude.
I don’t know he has friends.
It seems
you’re particularly interested in him.
Not really.
I just think
he’s great as a young man
and want to know more.
You should head back to the Heaven.
Do visit Mount Lookout on another day.
We’ll have a hearty drink then.
Good-bye then.
Master.
What’s on your mind?
The young heiress of Qingchi Palace
and North Sea Lord
remind me of some old acquaintances.
Do you find the young heiress
resembles God Gu Jun a lot?
No.
She’s more like someone else.
Well, what about North Sea Lord?
It’s a big area back here. We still
couldn’t find the bamboo hut.
Didn’t you and Boxuan often come here?
Boxuan flew us here each time.
As for the exact location,
I have no idea.
This is too slow.
I’ll go up and look around.
Wait here for me.
Why is there the swish of swords?
This is...
Why is there a massive grave of swords?
You again?
I saved your life just now.
Shouldn’t you be grateful?
You want me to be grateful?
Alright.
Thank you for saving my life.
I appreciate it
and will repay your favor
on another day.
Happy?
No.
What do you want?
I had been wondering
why you look so familiar.
Now it seems
I found the answer.
Do you want to tell me
it’s fate?
Do you feel the same?
What you said and did
only convince me
that you’re a shameless man.
Except for that, I can feel nothing.
For so many years,
you’re the only one
who can see the grave except for me.
It’s the same old cliché, right?
The grave is huge.
Everyone can see it.
You’re hilarious.
I’m honest.
At the first time, I found this place,
Jingjian was right beside me.
But he couldn’t even hear the swish.
Perhaps it’s some sort of restriction
that only destined ones can see.
You said it yourself.
Only destined ones can see it.
We’re destined to be together.
I mean I’m destined to come here,
not to be together with you.
So quit following me.
I shouldn’t have driven a sword
after her.
My image is damaged forever.
I was gone for a while.
Where have you been?
Don’t bring it up.
Lord Qingmu is haunting like a ghost.
He isn’t so annoying to me.
Why do you dislike him so much?
He’s Jingzhao’s Prince Charming.
I don’t want anything to do with
anyone related to Jingzhao.
By the way,
I found the bamboo hut.
Let’s go.
Looks like it’s been deserted
for a while.
Come.
Let’s get in.
Maybe there are signs of someone
boarding here.
I didn’t know
there is such a hut on Mount Lookout.
Who is Boxuan?
She’s here for that man.
Would Boxuan have been cultivating
through his tribulation here?
This is the only place I know
where Boxuan has been
except for Qingchi Palace.
If he’s not here,
where could he be?
Someone was drunk here.
In regardless,
there are signs of someone living here.
Never saw Boxuan used this fan.
Watch out.
Are you alright, Houchi?
Yes, I’m fine.
Purple Moon Fan.
Do you know this fan?
This is Demon Lord Ziyue’s halidom.
Demon Lord Ziyue?
Who is he?
He’s the most mysterious demon lord
in the Three Realms.
And he’s as powerful as the Demon King.
Ziyue is a mysterious man
in the Demon Region.
He helps them with their cultivation.
Therefore, many respect and admire him.
By naming himself after the Purple Moon,
he must relate to it somehow.
That I don’t know.
But I heard he wears a mask
all year long.
No one knows how he looks.
He wears a mask all year long?
Could he be...?
You mean
the Demon Lord is Boxuan?
Boxuan never took off his mask
in Qingchi Palace.
But Boxuan practices for immortal power.
No.
It doesn’t make sense.
They have a lot in common.
Demon Lord Ziyue is a mystery.
So is Boxuan.
Fengran,
I don’t know
where else
we can find Boxuan
except here.
Why don’t we go visit
Demon Lord Ziyue?
After all, the fan he left here
points out a direction.
I must find Boxuan.
I want to know if he’s safe.
Alright.
I’ll go with you.
Come.
For his violation
of Heavenly laws,
Lord Ziyuan
will be banished to the mortal world
and never become immortal again.
No!
Your Majesty,
please spare me this once.
I’m sorry, Your Majesty.
For the sake of
my service
in the last years,
please forgive me.
You framed the leader
of Qingchi Palace up
and offended their goddess.
That almost ruins
our eternal friendship
with Qingchi Palace.
How could I keep you around?
Guards!
Take Ziyuan away!
Your Majesty!
Prince Jingyang!
Prince Jingyang, help me!
Your Highness, speak for me!
Prince Jingyang!
Father...
- Jingyang.
- I saved your life!
- Prince Jingyang!
- Step back.
Speak for me!
Your Highness!
His Majesty issued a Heavenly Edict.
He’s really flared up.
Ziyuan has always been unbridled.
Now he’s the victim
of his own evil deeds.
Jingyang.
Father,
I just want to ask one thing.
Houchi insulted us in Daze Mansion,
yet you punished Ziyuan.
Aren’t you fanning her arrogance
and deflating ourselves?
If it goes on,
how can we lead the Three Realms?
Why don’t you get it?
Ziyuan provoked Jingzhao’s conflict
with Houchi,
which nearly evolves into a conflict
with Qingchi Palace.
The punishment
is merciful.
But Houchi hurt Jingzhao.
Why didn’t you say anything about it?
Jingzhao hurt Fengran, didn’t she?
Father,
Jingyang is just upset
that I was hurt.
Jingyang,
it’s written in the law
that no gods or goddesses
should be offended.
We’re in the wrong.
So don’t make Father angry.
Whose side are you on?
Ziyuan saved my life.
Your judge is fair and just,
which will win your compliments.
I’m just wondering what the fighting men
in the Demon Region see of this?
The Heaven
won’t even protect
the eldest prince’s savior.
If such a rumor spreads out,
I’m afraid no one will fight for us.
Insolent boy!
Guards!
- Yes!
Make Jingyang kneel three days
outside the Heavenly Hall.
Let the immortals see
how he bends the law for selfish deeds.
- Yes.
Hold on.
You’re unbelievable.
This is not the general assembly.
Why cut up rough about our son?
Jingyang is a loyal friend and brother.
His friend is punished
and his sister hurt.
He couldn’t swallow the insult
and made a mistake.
When he comes around,
he will put
the general interest first.
Father,
Jingyang has been in the garrison
in Demon Region for long.
He might catch up with something
from soldiers.
Please don’t be angry with him.
Father,
don’t blame my brother.
He’s defending
the interest of the Heaven.
Do you know why you’re wrong?
Jingyang…
I’m sure he does.
Go back to your hall.
Stay in unless
I command otherwise.
Yes, Father.
This massive pillar
has been standing here
guarding the barrier dividing immortals
and demons
since the Human Realm came into being.
It can sense the power of every being
and rank them.
It seems
my name isn’t on it.
It’s not accurate.
Just in rumors.
The Demon Lord Ziyue is famous.
We don’t see his name on it, either,
do we?
(Qingmu)
Did you follow us?
I wouldn’t say that.
I’m just passing by.
Lady Fengran.
Houchi.
Are you alright?
Yes, I’m fine.
Thank you.
Where did you get the bracelet?
That’s what I have been wanting to ask.
Our bracelets
were made by one person.
Do you know an immortal named Boxuan?
Is he the man you’re looking for?
Who is he to you?
Do you know him?
No.
Did you lie to me again?
No, I didn’t.
Are you alright?
Lord Qingmu,
what can we do to make you
stop following us?
Lady Fengran,
what can I do to make you allow me
to go along?
That’s impossible,
unless I’m not around.
Sorry.
Oh no.
If we don’t go through together,
we’ll end up in different locations.
You’ll go
all extremes to reach your goal.
I’m not that kind of person.
I really want to know the man
who gave you the bracelet,
Boxuan.
For your temperament,
I don’t want you to come along.
The Red Blood Forest is the most
dangerous place in the Demon Region.
Without me,
how are you going
to find Demon Lord Ziyue?
You eavesdropped on me and Fengran?
Shameless.
You’re waiting for her?
Don’t you know
if you don’t go through
the barrier together,
you won’t land at the same spot?
She isn’t here yet.
Maybe she’s not coming.
You intentionally separated me
and Fengran.
I had no choices.
Young heiress,
don’t you feel
anything different when you see me?
Yes.
Do you find me familiar?
With a medicine.
What do you mean?
A clingy patch.
You were good-mannered
in front of Jingzhao.
Why do you keep blabbing
shamelessly with me?
I don’t speak to female immortals.
But I don’t know why
I’m so interested in you.
How unfortunate!
Whatever you say.
But if we find Boxuan
who proves that we’re not destined,
I will apologize to you
for
offending you.
We don’t need Boxuan.
I can prove that we’re not.
The road is wide.
You go that way.
And I go this way.
Are you convinced I’m not a good man
no matter what I do?
Alright.
No more concerns.
Abyssal Ridge Swamp?
I’m back home.
No.
It’s too far from the third heaven
where Demon Lord Ziyue lives.
I have to find Houchi
as soon as possible.
Are you looking for me?
If you allow me
to come along,
I’ll get you out.
How is that?
It seems your bracelet
can’t protect you every time.
Crisp skin and tender flesh,
which is the most tasty.
I’m sorry
for just now.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪