=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 17=
The birthday gift from Zijin Mansion
is indeed impressive!
This Fire Coral is even
more exquisite than the ones kept
in the East Sea Dragon Palace.
Looks like Jingyang is very
grateful to his benefactor.
As a former unidentified immortal
in the Lower Realm,
it took that guy only less than
10,000 years to become a Lord
in the Heavenly Palace and
an important guest at Mount Lookout.
But that Ziyuan is way over the line.
He hurt you badly back then
by a sneak attack,
and now he even sent
his immortal servants
to our Qingchi Palace at will.
The Mount Lookout
also sent us an invitation
for the birthday banquet
of Lord Donghua of Daze Mansion.
Your Lordship,
Lord Donghua is an important
official of the Immortals.
Many people will go
to celebrate his birthday.
Why don’t we take this opportunity
to tell Ziyuan off?
We can’t.
With his status getting
higher and higher in the
Heavenly Palace these years,
Ziyuan is more arrogant than ever.
If we tell him off,
it’ll humiliate our Qingchi Palace.
But our Qingchi Palace
is on an equal footing with
the Heavenly Palace!
Even though God Gu Jun isn’t here,
Little Master is also a God.
No matter how powerful
the Heavenly Palace is,
they can’t ignore what she has to say.
Chang Que.
Unlike Jiaye, you know everything.
How could you make
such a ridiculous suggestion?
Didn’t you see what happened just now?
So you lied when you said
her immortal power had got stronger?
Chang Que,
do you know
what I saw this month?
After that day,
I went to the Spiritual Spring
for 10 days in a row,
and I saw that she practiced every day
from sunset to sunrise.
Chang Que,
we’ve been with her for
tens of thousands of years,
but we’ve never really understood her.
Unbelievable! I made it!
I’ve practiced for so many years.
Why did I make it only this time?
Is it because
practicing by the Spiritual Spring
made a big difference?
If that’s the case,
does it mean
I can travel around with Boxuan
and go through tribulations with him?
Houchi was born
with closed spiritual veins.
God Gu Jun spent 40,000 years
helping her break out of the shell.
She was weak and sickly,
and she’s got unstable spiritual veins.
Even her mother dislikes her.
The Three Realms all know about it.
On account of the reputation
of our Qingchi Palace, Houchi
seldom left the palace
for the past 20,000 years.
I feel
so sorry for her.
Chang Que,
can’t you learn a few jokes
and make her laugh?
Please give me a break.
Since Lord Boxuan left,
God Gu Jun
has been traveling all over to find
herbs for Little Master.
Even the spiritual aura in our
Qingchi Palace is decreasing.
Quite a few people have left
the Immortal Cave down the mountain.
God Gu Jun will be back sooner or later.
When I was rejected by both
the God and Demon Realms,
God Gu Jun took me in.
I have to protect Houchi
while he’s gone.
Your Lordship,
even a small favor
deserves to be repaid big.
So, shall we go to the Daze Mansion
for the birthday banquet?
Forget it.
Tell them we won’t go.
Qingchi Palace and Heavenly Palace
have nothing to do with each other.
It’ll always be that way.
Yes.
Hurry!
Are you sure this is where Lord Ziyuan
dropped his Fire Coral?
I’m sure!
I’ve told you many times!
If we hadn’t come to the
Spiritual Spring of the Qingchi Palace,
we wouldn’t have made
such a big mistake!
Lower your voice!
The people of the Qingchi Palace
may hear us!
Who are you?
What are you doing here
on our back mountain?
Oh, a fairy maiden.
I’m a disciple
of Lord Ziyuan of the Zijin Mansion.
I was passing by Qilian Mountains
and I got thirsty,
so I came here to drink
some spring water.
You made it sound so reasonable.
There’s a barrier in our Qingchi Palace.
How did you get in?
I’ll tell Lord Fengran,
the Master of our palace.
What… What barrier?
Everybody knows
that the Qingchi Palace is a wasteland
in the Heavenly Realm.
I wouldn’t
come even if you
invited me over.
Do you think
she’s the one who took the Fire Coral?
Did you steal
Lord Ziyuan’s Fire Coral?
What Fire Coral?
I’m afraid I’ll hurt you
if you don’t tell the truth!
Boxuan...
Houchi,
are you alright?
I’m fine.
How dare you guys from the Zijin Mansion
break into our Qingchi Palace!
She’s that phoenix!
Let’s go!
- Okay!
- Wanna leave?
Fengran, let them go.
It’s better to stay away from trouble.
And they didn’t hurt me anyway.
I’m glad you are fine.
What should we do?
We offended Fengran,
and lost Lord Ziyuan’s Fire Coral!
The Qingchi Palace may be declining,
but it’s still God Gu Jun’s residence.
If Fengran looks into it,
we’ll both be in big trouble!
I told you to lower your voice!
Stop yelling!
I bet it was your loud voice
that caught their attention.
It’s not the time to scold me!
You are a quick thinker.
Would you think of an idea first?
Fengran holds a grudge
against His Grace.
The Qingchi Palace has little contact
with the Heavenly Palace.
And God Gu Jun is originally
from the Abyssal Ridge Swamp.
What are you doing?
It hurts!
Look.
Does it look like a wound caused
by the Demon Power?
It does!
Where did you get the spiritual water?
I bought it from an underground market.
It can forge the nature
of the wound immediately.
The war between the immortals
and the demons has lasted for so long.
Such a thing like this is always needed
by those coward deserters.
If Lord Ziyuan finds out,
you’ll…
I just bought it for fun.
Who would’ve thought
that it’d be useful today?
No matter what,
we’ll be in trouble,
so we may as well just try our luck.
Where’s the invitation
from Lord Donghua?
I have it.
Have you changed your mind?
I don’t care if Ziyuan insults me.
But I can’t stand that his people
broke into our palace
and attempted to hurt Houchi!
I’ll teach him a lesson
at the birthday banquet!
But the Zijin Mansion and
the Heavenly Palace are quite close.
If the Heavenly Palace takes their side
and helps Ziyuan…
It doesn’t matter.
Chang Que,
prepare a gift for Lord Donghua.
Yes.
Your Lordship,
the Daze Mansion put God Gu Jun’s name
on the invitation.
If you take his place to go,
Ziyuan will use it against you.
God Gu Jun is not
the only God in our Qingchi Palace.
I may not be qualified to go,
but someone is.
You mean Her Grace?
If you are in danger,
inject your Immortal Power
to this bracelet,
and it’ll enhance your
cultivation base right away.
Although it won’t last for long,
it’ll be enough for you
to get out of the danger in time.
Don’t use it too often.
It’ll harm your Spiritual Strength.
Your Grace.
What are you thinking of?
You look so serious.
What brings you here?
Donghua will hold his
70,000th birthday party in a few days.
He asked his disciple
to send us an invitation
to his birthday banquet.
Shall we make a trip
to the Mount Lookout?
The Mount Lookout?
I’m not going.
Although I haven’t been
acknowledged yet,
I’m still at the rank of Goddess.
Why would I go to
an Immortal Lord’s birthday banquet?
Donghua is the Lord
of the Mount Lookout.
His status in the Immortal Realm is
only second to the Heavenly Emperor.
If we don’t go,
people would think we are conceited.
He’s about the same age as me,
and quite influential.
How about this?
You can go with Chang Que.
I think that’ll be plenty respectful
if you go there in person.
That won’t work.
The invitation is for you
and God Gu Jun.
Chang Que and I are only Lords.
How can we take your places?
I won’t be able to go.
I do want to,
but
I need to practice the immortal
techniques in the ancient books
that Boxuan left me every day.
If I go on such a long trip,
it’ll delay my cultivation.
And I’ll fail when you
test me next time.
Your Spiritual Power is
already at the bottom,
so why care about the delay?
With my immortal foundation,
I can’t afford missing
any cultivation day.
And you saw
that I had mastered the Control Spell.
Do you think you did that?
Actually, it was me…
You what?
Did you help me in secret?
So I made the Control Spell work?
You know already?
I guess
you saw my cultivation
and you were worried that I’d lose
my confidence if I failed the test,
so you put on a show for me, right?
How did you find out that?
Houchi,
how did you grow to be this insightful?
I guess you cultivated your brain
instead of the Spiritual Power.
Fengran,
I do want to go,
but
before my father left,
he told me
that I wasn’t allowed
to leave the Qingchi Palace
until I mastered the Immortal Power.
Don’t worry.
Since God Gu Jun let me
be in charge of the Qingchi Palace,
I think I have the right
to send you to the birthday banquet.
Then…
Then what if he finds out about this?
I’ll take full responsibility.
Deal?
Deal!
Okay!
Wait!
Her sly look
reminded me
of the fox on the back mountain.
No. Houchi!
Houchi!
Boxuan,
it’s been 10,000 years since you left.
When will you be back?
♪Time disturb my feelings♪
♪Like you do♪
♪Hold tightly with your warm hand♪
Boxuan,
I also want to learn magic techniques
and fly like them.
♪Your tall figure♪
Your Spiritual Strength is unstable.
You need to establish the foundation first
to stabilize your spirit.
♪I save some time♪
Take the medicine.
Can I skip it?
The medicine put me
into sleep for a whole winter last time.
I even missed the snow scenery.
Snow scenery? That’s easy.
Take the medicine,
and I’ll make it happen.
♪To have the next life♪
♪When we meet again♪
Now, do it!
I’m tired of the view here already.
It’s said the scenery on the
Mount Lookout is quite beautiful.
Let’s go there!
But…
I have you protect me. I’ll be fine.
Come on!
♪And get close♪
♪For a little talk♪
♪If it’s such a good time
and such a beautiful scenery♪
♪Hope♪
♪Go with me♪
It’s such a lovely place!
I like it here!
If you like it,
I’ll bring you here again in the future.
You are so nice!
♪Time disturb my feelings♪
♪Like you do♪
♪Hold tightly with your warm hand♪
Boxuan,
I wanna hear a story.
About what?
♪Your tall figure♪
About…
the God Realm.
About how the God Realm was closed
and the falling of Gods.
♪To exchange it for you♪
Nobody’s ever told me that story.
♪Every second sounds so sweet♪
Gods…
Gods live as long
as the mountains and rivers.
♪Until I meet you♪
They can control the world
with their minds.
They are the strongest existence
in the Three Realms.
Beyond Gods
there are True Gods,
and beyond which,
there’s a Chief God,
who
is the ruler of all living beings.
She lives as long
as the Three Realms.
♪Listen♪
So the Chief God is immortal?
Yes.
She is immortal.
♪And get close♪
Then how come I’ve never met her?
Not even heard of her name?
Because
she did something
she had to do.
♪Hope♪
♪Go with me♪
♪I am so sure♪
Boxuan,
♪To have you with me♪
it looks like the mask
is part of your face.
I’m so curious to know
how exactly you look like.
♪Going forward in fear♪
No hurry.
One day,
I’ll show my face to you.
♪Listen♪
Houchi,
no matter what, promise me
that you’ll never take off the bracelet.
♪And get close♪
So that
I can find you
wherever you are.
♪For a little talk♪
No worries.
I won’t take it off.
I need it when I get into a fight.
♪If it’s such a good time
and such a beautiful scenery♪
♪There’s you♪
♪And me♪
Where are you?
Where are you going?
Why didn’t you say goodbye to me?
I’ll have a tribulation to encounter.
But don’t worry.
I’ll be back in 10,000 years.
Will it be dangerous?
When I’m back,
I’ll go with you anywhere you want,
let alone the Qingchi Palace.
Houchi,
just enjoy
your life and have fun.
Stay healthy.
Don’t get hurt
while I’m gone.
But
10,000 years is way too long.
Can I go with you?
Your Spiritual Power is still weak.
It’s dangerous for you
to go with me.
It’s all because I was born sickly.
I can’t be of any help to my father,
and I’ve become a burden to you.
I left without saying goodbye
because I didn’t want to see you sad.
I will do my best
to gather my Spiritual Power
and learn the magic techniques.
If you want,
you can take some time and practice
the immortal techniques in the
ancient books I left you,
so that you can travel
around with me in the future.
10,000 years.
I promise
I will be back in 10,000 years.
And I will find you
no matter where you are.
I’ll do my best to cultivate myself
and learn the techniques.
Although no one knows
where my father is,
he’d sometimes send
an instruction feather
and ask how we are doing.
But you…
You don’t even send a letter.
If you find out my Spiritual Power
hasn’t improved at all
after you are back,
would you laugh at me like
the others in the Three Realms do
that I only have an empty title
but no Spiritual Power at all?
You care about me so much.
You will never laugh at me.
Fengran decided to take a trip
to Mount Lookout.
And I can take this chance
to try to look for you there.
I hope you won’t encounter any danger
when you go through the tribulations.
You won’t! Definitely not!
You are blessed.
You’ll be safe.
You are saying that someone
in the Qingchi Palace
hurt you with Demon Power
and took away
the gift I prepared for Lord Donghua?
The Qingchi Palace has been
closed for 10,000 years.
Why would someone there
hurt you for no reason?
Your Lordship,
Wu Wang and I
passed by Qilian Mountains
and bumped into a fairy maiden
of the Qingchi Palace.
She knew that we are your disciples,
so she broke out into curses and said
you were evil and despicable.
It angered us,
so we argued back.
Then she suddenly attacked us
and took away the gift.
She… She almost killed us!
Is it true?
I dare not lie to you!
Look!
This is a wound from her attack!
It really is a burn wound
caused by Demon Power.
Since someone in the Qingchi Palace
cultivates Demon Power,
then I can’t blame you
for losing the gift.
I’ll just confiscate
one immortal sword from each of you.
- Thank you, Your Lordship!
Besides,
you two just stay in the mansion
and get recovered.
In a couple of days,
I’ll take you to Lord
Donghua’s birthday banquet.
Yes.
How dare you, Fengran!
I haven’t got even with you
for what you did back then!
There’s a mark of Zijin Mansion
on the Fire Coral.
Just wait and see!
I will make you pay for it!
Wu Xu,
though His Lordship didn’t
ask about the details,
I still feel quite uneasy about it.
Do you think…
I heard it’s been 10,000 years
since God Gu Jun left to find
herbs for her daughter.
I guess
he wouldn’t be interested in going
to Lord Donghua’s birthday banquet.
But there’s another God
in the Qingchi Palace.
If she stands up for that fairy maiden…
Her Spiritual Power
is even weaker than that
of the lowest-level Earth Deities.
She’s got nothing but an empty title!
She and Princess Jingzhao are both
the daughters of the Queen of Heaven.
The latter has been respected by
the Three Realms since she was born.
Yet I heard
that young Goddess was born
with blocked Spiritual Power.
What a poor girl!
Stop talking!
Princess Jingzhao hates it
when people compare her
with the young Goddess
of the Qingchi Palace.
If she finds out,
our entire Zijin Mansion
will be punished!
Qinglian,
I heard that His Majesty
invited the young Goddess
of the Qingchi Palace to come
to the Heavenly Palace and celebrate
the Her Highness’s birthday.
Really?
The guard of the Xuantian Hall told me.
It must be true.
People say that Princess Jingzhao
is the prettiest in the Three Realms.
I wonder how that
young Goddess looks like.
Which one do you think
is more beautiful?
It’s said that the young Goddess
is hideous
and super tall,
but she seldom gets out
of the Qingchi Palace.
I think it’s just a rumor.
Since she and Princess Jingzhao
were born to the same mother,
I’m sure she’s also a stunning beauty!
- Greetings, Your Highness!
How dare you compare me
with that nothing girl!
(Jingzhao)
Flog them 100 times.
- Your Highness, please spare us!
Whoever dares gossip again will be
banished from the Heavenly Palace
to the Lower Realm forever!
Yes.
Heavenly Father.
Heavenly Mother.
You just punished two
fairy maidens, didn’t you?
How did such a small matter
reach your ears, Heavenly Father?
As fairy maidens,
they gossip all the time
instead of minding their own business,
so of course I’d punish them.
Jingzhao.
Immortal Cultivation is a tough journey.
They just
gossiped a little bit.
You could’ve verbally disciplined them.
Why did you have to flog them?
Heavenly Father…
Enough.
Jingzhao,
just listen to your Heavenly Father.
Your Majesty,
you have something
to tell Jingzhao, don’t you?
In a few days,
it’ll be Lord Donghua’s birthday.
Your eldest brother is on an
inspection tour in the Lower Realm.
I want you and your second brother
to go to the Mount Lookout
on my behalf to celebrate his birthday.
I’m not going.
Why would I go to a
mediocre Lord’s birthday banquet?
Jingzhao!
I heard that your second brother
invited the North Sea Lord
to go with him.
If you are not going,
I’ll send another
immortal official to go.
Okay! Okay!
I’ll go!
I’ll go back and get ready now.
Jingzhao.
I’ll take my leave.
Jingzhao is too
arrogant and bossy.
I’m afraid she’ll get in trouble
in the future because of it.
Jingzhao has been pampered
since she was little,
so she can be a little spoiled.
You don’t have to be too hard on her.
She’s the only Golden Dragon
besides me in this world.
I hope she can be
more mature.
Otherwise, how can she lead
our dragon clan in the future?
Your Majesty,
Jingzhao is still young.
We’ll teach and guide her along the way.
Why do you keep staring at me?
This is the first time you’ve got out
of the palace for all these years.
How come you stay so quiet?
It’s not even like you.
What’s this?
You tricked me!
So you agreed to come because
you wanted to look for Boxuan.
That’s not true!
I agreed to come because I wanted to
accompany you to the Mount Lookout
and help you punish
that villain Ziyuan.
You are lying!
I begged you so hard yesterday.
You had already…
Houchi!
I’ll see you at the top
of the Mount Lookout!
This girl!
She actually brought the Spiritual Talisman
that God Gu Jun gave her!
Let’s see how far you can get!
I may as well find an Earth Deity
and ask him first.
Earth Deities know the
Mount Lookout very well.
They may have seen Boxuan before.
Had enough fun?
I just knew that you couldn’t go far.
Yes, enough.
Definitely!
Don’t fly around anymore.
Go to the bamboo cabin on
the back mountain and find Boxuan.
I’ll go meet you there
after I have dealt with Ziyuan.
I heard
that Jingjian will also
be there at the banquet.
Try to stay away from him.
Such an incompetent
won’t be a threat to me.
Don’t forget that I once
defeated his elder brother.
Alright.
Don’t worry about me.
Be careful.
Come and take a look!
It’s a once-in-100-year event
in the Immortal Realm.
Don’t miss it!
Miss,
you are too late.
The Pictures of Lords have been bought.
Would you like to check
out my other paintings?
Not right now.
Is there really such an
ugly person in the Immortal Realm?
It’s a picture of the young Goddess in
the Qingchi Palace used to avert evil.
Who is it?
Houchi, the young Goddess
in the Qingchi Palace.
It’s said that she’s ten meters tall
and as strong as a bull.
She may be ugly,
but for the immortals who
are down on their luck,
they often use her picture
to drive away evil from their houses.
It’s very popular!
If you want it,
it’ll only cost you
a low-class Spiritual Bead instead
of a magic treasure.
Who told you that the young
Goddess looks like this?
Her picture has always been like this
for over 10,000 years.
Miss, you look upset.
Have you met
the young Goddess before?
Met…
Think about it.
God Gu Jun is dashing and handsome.
So his daughter should be pretty, too!
Sure! Sure!
If you want a female immortal picture,
I have a lot of them.
Look.
This is a picture of Princess Jingzhao,
used for praying for good luck.
Three high-class Spiritual Beads,
and you can have it.
Praying for good luck?
With that ugly face?
Even the young Goddess
is prettier than her!
I don’t want it!
Miss,
I’m just running a small business.
I didn’t mean to offend you!
As an immortal, you should
focus on cultivation
instead of scamming people
with a bunch of garbage.
Your business should be banned!
Miss, here’s the thing.
The stands here are all set up
by the unidentified immortals
of the Lower Realm.
It hasn’t even been 100 years
since we became immortals,
so our Spiritual Power is very weak.
Neither can we go up
to the Mount Lookout
nor become Lord Donghua’s disciples.
We can only sell some small goods
in exchange for magic treasures
to assist the cultivation.
Please have mercy
and don’t ruin my business!
Thank you, Miss.
How dare him draw such
an ugly picture of me?
I’m ten meters tall
and as strong as a bull?
That’s nonsense!
And I’m only worth
a low-class Spiritual Bead?
How ignorant they are!
Aside from the second Prince Jingjian
and Princess Jingzhao,
who else will go to
Lord Donghua’s birthday banquet?
Who?
Just spit it out and tell us!
- Tell us!
- Who is it?
Just tell us!
Jingzhao will also be there?
- Who?
- Tell us!
- Who else is coming?
Qingmu, the North Sea Lord.
Qingmu?
Really?
I heard that the North Sea Lord
has never shown up in public before.
But if it’s possible,
I’d really love to have
a competition with him,
and see if he’s really
as good as the rumor says.
What a big talk!
I…
The North Sea Lord Qingmu has been
the best ever for the recent 1,000 years
among the immortals.
It only took him 1,000 years before
he reached the peak of the Lords.
He defeated all the North Sea demons
with only one single sword strike.
The Heavenly Emperor
has tremendous respect for him
before even meeting him in person,
and has conferred him
the North Sea Star Lord!
Star Lord?!
After he was conferred,
he got many dissenters,
who all went to the North Sea
to challenge him.
And you know what happened next?
What happened next?
- What happened next?
- Tell us!
They were all beaten up like a dog
by Lord Qingmu!
Nonsense!
Even my father spent 10,000 years
cultivating in the
Abyssal Ridge Swamp before he
was conferred Lord.
It’s impossible for one to reach the
peak of Lords after only 1,000 years.
It’s said that the North Sea Lord
is very close to
Their Heavenly Highnesses.
He’s especially admired
by Princess Jingzhao.
Oh!
In my opinion…
It’s a good thing!
…Lord Qingmu
will become His Heavenly
Majesty’s son-in-law!
Admired by Jingzhao,
he’s got to be a dandy
with a hollow fame.
I’ve used all the flying talismans.
High-speed talisman…
Alright. Better than nothing.
Lord Xianshan.
So many immortals have
come to Lord Donghua’s birthday banquet.
It’s Master’s 70,000th birthday,
so we are having a big celebration.
Hope you’ll enjoy yourself, Lord Ziyuan.
By the way,
I wonder who the Qingchi Palace
will send here today.
We deliver
an invitation to the
Qingchi Palace every year.
Since God Gu Jun is traveling
and Lord Fengran seldom
gets out of the Palace,
I guess today they’ll
just send someone else here as usual.
Greetings, Your Highness.
(Qingmu Jingjian)
This…
This one must be the North Sea Lord.
Greetings, Your Highness.
North Sea Lord.
Lord Xianshan, don’t mind the formality.
Your Highness, North Sea Lord,
please come inside.
Princess Jingzhao has also just arrived.
She’s appreciating the flowers
right now in the back yard.
Where’s Lord Donghua?
Master is resting in the back hall.
I’ll go say hi to Lord Donghua.
Jingzhao is in the back yard.
You haven’t seen her for years.
She talks about you all the time.
Would you go and be her company?
Jingjian, a word, please.
Please.
You know
that I don’t talk to strangers.
But you know Jingzhao.
She’s not a stranger.
She’s a girl.
I don’t feel comfortable
when talking to a girl.
In the entire Three Realms,
you are the only one who’d
attach his own Spiritual Strength
to a paperman
so that you can talk to yourself.
What’s wrong with that?
People would think you are a weirdo.
I don’t care what other people think.
Qingmu,
if you always stay alone,
you’ll become withdrawn.
Take my word.
Making more friends
is good for you.
Having one bosom friend
is enough in life.
I have you already.
Don’t forget
that we played chess
for three rounds before we came.
I even let you retract your moves
yet you still lost the game,
and that’s why you finally
agreed to come with me.
Next time I’ll have a
sword competition with you.
I’m sure I won’t lose to you again.
Alright.
Stop talking.
Just go ahead.
Lord Qingmu.
Greetings, Your Highness.
I didn’t expect that you would come
to Lord Donghua’s birthday banquet.
I heard that the Daze Mansion had
the best flower view
in the Immortal Realm.
Since the banquet hasn’t started yet,
how about we take a walk in the yard?
There’s no flower view
in the Heavenly Palace?
Well…
The flower view in
the Heavenly Palace is good,
but no one really appreciates it.
If you don’t wanna walk,
we can just sit here.
That’ll be fine, too.
It’s okay.
Even the talisman bullied me!
So this is the Daze Mansion
where Lord Donghua lives.
It’s such a huge yard.
How am I supposed to get out of here?
I assume that these flowers
are rarely seen in your North Sea area.
The North Sea?
Is it that North Sea Lord Qingmu?
How come this girl looks so familiar?
Have I met her before?
We don’t have flowers
in the North Sea area.
So I’ve never seen flowers like these.
It’s really him!
Nice voice.
But he and Jingzhao
are becoming an item.
Why is he seeing another girl?
I’m being inconsiderate.
The flowers aren’t that
enjoyable after all.
Especially to someone like you
who travels the Three Realms often.
I’m sure you’ve seen
many beautiful views.
A common view like this
must be boring to you.
If it’s possible,
I also want to travel the Three Realms
and enjoy the beautiful views with you.
If Jingzhao finds out that
she’s being cheated on…
I’m used to being alone.
It’s not convenient to take you with me.
Why is this Lord Qingmu
being so cold to her?
Whatever.
It’s none of my business.
I’d better go and keep
looking for Boxuan.
It’ll soon be my Heavenly Mother’s
90,000th birthday.
She’d also love to meet you.
I wonder if you have time
to go to the Heavenly Palace
for her birthday banquet.
So she is Jingzhao!
There’ll be a lot of
guests at the banquet.
I’m sure I won’t be missed.
Moreover,
by that time I should be
having a closed-door training.
I’m afraid I won’t be able to go anyway.
Lord Qingmu, no need to be modest.
Who’s there?
♪Where are you♪
♪Your young face♪
Who are you?
I’m sorry.
I’ve got the wrong way.
Stop!
She’s just an ordinary immortal
who eavesdropped a little.
Don’t worry about that.
It’s not that simple.
Please go to the banquet first.
I’ll be there soon.
Qingmu!
Sorry!
I thought you’d be able to dodge it.
I didn’t know your
Spiritual Power was this weak.
What’s the big deal of being a Lord?
That doesn’t give you the right
to play tricks on others!
I just eavesdropped
a little out of curiosity.
Did you have to insult me like that?
I will pay
for your dress.
Do you think you can afford it?
Then I’ll give you this sword
as compensation.
Is that okay?
This stupid sword made me suffer a lot!
I will let you pay for it!
It’s fine.
My sword is with her.
I can always find her.
Lord Ziyuan,
I heard last month when Prince Jingyang
held the immortal Taoism debate
on Mount Kunlun,
you won the first place again!
You are indeed knowledgeable
and outstanding in the Three Realms!
I’m flattered!
Excuse me,
you need an invitation
to enter the front hall.
Could you please
show me your invitation?
I forgot.
Would this be okay?
You definitely deserved it!
It’s my fault!
I didn’t know you are the Lord
of the Qingchi Palace.
I’m sorry!
You defeated them all!
Let’s drop it.
But the Qingchi…
Fengran!
As a defeated loser,
don’t you feel ashamed to be here?
A defeated loser?
You hurt me badly with a sneak attack
when I fought with
Jingyang back then.
You…
And you were thick-skinned enough
to tell the entire world
that you defeated me!
How dare you!
Back then, you attempted to assassin
the first Prince for a demon!
If Their Majesties hadn’t
spared you on God Gu Jun’s account,
you would’ve been killed
by the thunder strike!
You should’ve stayed at home and
guarded the Palace for God Gu Jun.
What are you doing here?
Lord Donghua sent us
an invitation for his birthday banquet.
Since God Gu Jun is not available,
as the one who’s assigned
to be in charge,
of course, I should come on his behalf.
What?
Lord Donghua hasn’t even said anything,
who do you think you are
to speak for the Daze Mansion?
- Fengran…
- That’s enough.
Your Highness,
I found a few days ago
that one of us Immortals
actually colluded with the Demons!
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪