[antifan_act, hashtag anti-fan, follow]
[Choi Tae-joon]
[Choi Soo-young]
[Hwang Chan-sung]
[Han Ji-an]
[Kim Min-gue]
[So I Married the Anti-Fan]
[Episode 10]
[When I Have Someone Else to Protect]
What if your first love
comes back to find you now?
-No.
-No way.
[Stage of Rejoice]
Well in that case...
I'm sorry.
I'm the type who doesn't think about
things that haven't happened yet.
I didn't expect you would ask me this.
Is this how you're dodging this question?
You're very witty.
Then let's turn back
to the day you debuted.
This is when we should say
a star was born.
Do you remember your debut performance?
Why are you running away?
He's there smiling like everything's fine.
What are you so afraid of?
Do I seem insane to you too?
Should I have raised my hand
and said his first love is here?
Or just say that I'm the person
you wanted to run away from.
Why? Now that Joon seems to be
interested in another woman,
do you want to leave me?
-What?
-If you're done making me suffer,
it's time to let me go.
[Stage of Rejoice]
I get it, so stop looking at me.
Are you talking to me?
Great work today.
Who-joon's talk show was amazing.
Don't you think the question
about his first love will be a big issue?
But who is his first love?
-Aren't you curious?
-No.
Why are people so curious
about someone's past? I don't get it.
It's a type of prejudice.
It feels like Who-joon's first love
would be special.
Geun-young, have you read
"Pride and Prejudice"?
Why? Do you want me
to write a book report?
Come on.
Maybe you have a prejudice against me.
I've read it long ago,
and I recently gave it another look.
You should read it too.
I won't ask for a book report.
Great work today.
Thanks.
[Waiting Room 2]
[Korean Speaking Contest]
Great work today.
[GBC Digital Broadcast Exhibition]
What now?
We need to talk.
Go wait in the waiting room.
Okay. I'll be right out front.
[Studio 1]
That was fun.
You're not an easy guy to crack.
If I was easy,
you wouldn't have cared so much about me.
-What's your relationship with her?
-That's enough.
I already made myself clear.
I meant Geun-young.
What?
We work together on a show. What else?
So you just work together?
Then you won't mind what I do with her.
Why do I always want to take
everything from you?
Bye, then.
Geun-young.
Hey.
I probably shouldn't have said I'd stay.
I made that really awkward.
Anyway,
do you think it's very troubling
to ask someone about their first love?
Do you think so too?
People talk as if
we should forgive everything
Or should we be doing that?
[It's not because you forgive them.]
[It's because they're your first love.]
Everyone is clumsy at first.
-Who-joon!
-Hey!
What's wrong?
Did you leave something behind?
What? No. It's nothing.
Why do I always want to take
everything from you?
My gosh.
Why are you here alone?
Oh, right.
Did you forget to ask him?
See? Adults never keep their promises,
then expect us to trust people.
Figures, I shouldn't have trusted you.
Why would he do anything
that some anti-fan asks?
Hey.
Do I owe him to you or what?
Why does everyone around Who-joon think
I'm a big joke?
I hope someone would leave me
in the lost and found bin
so that no one can find me!
Move!
Geun-young, is something going on?
Why? Now that Joon seems to be
interested in another woman,
do you want to leave me?
What are you looking at?
Jae-joon, there's a new trainee.
It's not that you're great at dancing,
but you have a good sense of rhythm.
You'll catch up quickly.
He's good-looking.
Right?
[I met you first]
[and I liked you first too.]
You were
my first love as well.
It's not like she did anything wrong.
I shouldn't have been angry at her.
[The person you have reached
is not available. Please leave...]
He must be busy.
I should've asked him before.
It's all because of that question
about his first love.
What if your first love
comes back to find you now?
Wait.
So what if his first love returns?
Why didn't he answer...
That's also none of my business.
My gosh, I'm going crazy.
You can't be here.
What are you talking about?
This is my house.
I should've told you before.
One of your fans is here right now.
She knew I was here
and waited or whatever.
So I tried to send her back home,
but she lives in Gimje of all places,
-so I...
-What are you talking about? Hey, breathe.
So what will you do about this situation?
You should wait at home,
and ask Ji-hyang...
My gosh.
Geun-young, you talked to him!
This is a dream.
Yes, it is.
Go back to sleep, it's a dream.
Go on, then. Bye.
What's going on?
So
you watched the TV show
and found this place?
Yes, it's not a big deal.
I should go dig up the ground
or live in a cave.
No, I never told anyone about this place.
And never will.
I'm a huge fan of yours.
A genuine, real, and hard-core fan.
What the heck is
a genuine, real, and hard-core fan?
You asked me to marry you
when I grow up.
What?
I always hated how celebrities make
all these absurd pledges
they can never keep.
What are you saying? I never said that.
You said that to me.
I went to Dongdaemun with my mom
when I was a kid,
and when you finished performing,
you said that as you gave me an autograph.
-I never said that to her.
-Look.
-What is this?
-Goodness.
[Marry me when you get older!]
You asked her to marry you.
You should live up to your promise. Gosh.
I never washed it and kept it that way.
Then I formed a fan club right away
as soon as you made your debut.
I'm your fan club president
of the North Jeolla District.
Oh, the president
Then Ms. President,
you must understand that
this is very troubling for me.
Well, you know.
I'm a huge fan of yours.
I don't spread rumors
that can get you in trouble.
Okay, now. He's very troubled,
so you should go home now.
I'm sure your dad left your name
in the lost and found as a joke.
The lost and found? What is that?
Her dad is the stationmaster
at Gimje Station,
and he registered her name there
because she ran away from home.
You ran away from home?
Why would you tell him that?
You're the president of a district,
so I figured
he should know what your situation is.
If you ran from home, you should go back.
Why would you be here?
Are you sure this will be okay?
She found this place on her own.
She isn't an ordinary kid.
Are you worried about me?
No.
About Ms. President.
An anti-fan like you
might end up rubbing off
on an avid fan like her.
Don't worry.
We're from two different bloodlines.
You just told me not to worry,
so I'll forget how you got pouty.
Whatever. I never pouted.
Why is he here this early?
Hey, get ready. We're going out.
-Yu-ri?
-Yes?
Good morning.
Yes, good morning. Get ready to go out.
Where are we going?
What? Oh, we're all going for a drive.
It's 8 a.m. right now.
Is time more important than me?
No.
Yu-ri, bring your backpack too.
I need that for the drive?
You're a student,
so you'll look great with a backpack.
-Go on and get it.
-Okay.
What are you doing? Get ready.
It's eight right now,
so we'll be there by 11:30 a.m.
Right. You drive.
You saw me behind the wheel.
Exactly. That's why you should drive.
Practice makes perfect.
Wait, are you just tired?
Then do I get to sit in the back with you?
You can do it!
Anyway, are we not going to eat anything?
We haven't had breakfast.
Yu-ri, be quiet. I have to focus.
She was really weird last night,
so I couldn't ask her for dinner either.
Really?
Okay, then. Let's eat something.
I'm hungry.
Let's stop by at a rest area.
I want potatoes, lots of sugar.
I want a corn dog, lots of ketchup.
So they're asking me to get it.
-One corn dog, please.
-Okay.
We have ketchup and mustard over there.
Or you can use sugar.
Ketchup is fine.
[Rest Area]
Who-joon, did you do something bad to her?
Why? Does it look like I did something?
She didn't seem like a real anti-fan.
She didn't seem like
she'd hate someone for no reason.
Why? Did you decide to switch sides
after spending a few days with her?
No way.
How can I put this?
She seemed like someone who's
waiting to be found at the lost and found.
But then yesterday,
-She said that?
-Yes. That makes no sense.
All lost things want to be found.
[Rest Area]
Okay. You can each grab your food.
Hey, forget it. I'll drive. Let's switch.
All of a sudden?
Why?
Wow, they all recognized me
in that short while.
-That could've been bad.
-No one is around.
-Why? Everyone was looking.
-They're all staring.
-Right, Yu-ri? They all looked.
-All the dashcams too.
[Rest Area]
I almost got caught just now.
-My gosh.
-What?
-That could've been bad.
-No one was looking.
She ate so quickly, then fell asleep.
You look after her like she's your sister
after spending a few days together.
What? A sister?
She's an avid fan, I'm an anti-fan.
We're completely different.
[Gimje]
You came out to come here?
Yes.
What? This is...
Who-joon, are you going to my home?
What?
You're right.
You might as well go home, then.
I'm not going home.
Then will you live your life
as a lost article?
I've been abandoned anyway.
You said all lost articles
want to be found.
[Gimje Station]
It may not seem like
your parents care about you,
but it means they trust you.
She's not going to listen.
Exactly. You're great, Who-joon.
Give me your phone.
Why? Are you going to call my parents?
Give it to me now.
Once you go home today,
don't ever run away again.
This is my number.
Come and see me once you go to college.
Don't turn me down when the day comes.
And if you leak my phone number out,
our relationship ends as of today. Okay?
No, I'll never do that.
Thank you for everything, Geun-young.
Bye.
Make sure you see your dad
write "found" on the lost and found sheet.
I'll kill you if you hit on Who-joon.
Hey! That's never going to happen.
Why? What did she say?
Not telling.
[Gimje Station]
Anyway, where's your parent's home?
Why do you ask?
I can already tell
that you weren't born in Seoul.
So where is it?
Are you looking down on people
who were born out of Seoul?
There's this place called Dangjin.
Have you heard of it?
No, I haven't.
You're from the U.S. You wouldn't know.
It's a place called Dangjin.
I'm tired from driving so early.
Wake me up when we get to Seoul.
You didn't even drive for an hour.
Where are your manners?
I think we're in Dangjin now.
I'm so hungry.
Hey, Geun-young, wake up.
Geun-young.
My gosh.
Are we in Seoul already?
Where's your home?
You know where I live.
Just drop me off at the entrance.
No, your home in Dangjin.
Dangjin?
[Dangjin]
Where are we?
Dangjin, what do you think?
Why... Why did you come to Dangjin?
Are we going to my parent's home?
Stop the car here. I'll drive.
Let's go back into the highway.
But we're already here.
I drove for over an hour.
If we turn back now,
it means you're a bad daughter.
I'm sure your mother is worried.
Go show her you're doing well
by making a joke out of a star.
Why would you suddenly come here?
No, if we go there now,
my parents will get furious.
Who's going to deal with that?
Why do you always say no
whenever I try to do something
for you?
Let's go back to Seoul now.
This is disappointing.
Let's see.
Under the moonlight.
Expect guests under the moonlight?
Goodness.
Is someone about to make a visit?
Is this it?
-Why are you so secretive?
-No, wait.
Be quiet.
Who's there?
You. You brat.
-Come here.
-Mom, wait. Mom, I'm sorry.
I can't believe everything you did
to break our hearts.
-Mom, please!
-Whoa, please stop.
Who's this? Why is this man
holding my kid in his arms?
-You little jerk.
-Goodness.
Come on, Mom!
Hello, ma'am. You know me, right?
I'm Who-joon.
What is this?
He's the guy
who put you in trouble, right?
So he's that famous guy?
I'm sorry for making you worried.
Ms. Jang, we came in a hurry,
so this isn't much.
I'll send you something better
once we get to Seoul.
Do I have something on me?
You'll wear his face down
from staring at him.
I can't tell why you're so popular
by the way you look.
She's so straightforward.
Does it hurt a lot?
I guess she really hates me.
Did you see how she beat me in full swing?
I thought she was on a baseball team.
Anyway, she really doesn't know who I am?
Just because you're the national star,
did you really think everyone knows you?
It doesn't make any sense.
I was the most popular
on a survey taken by people in their 50s.
Wow, it's not easy to be like this guy.
You made a lot.
Are you giving him more food out of spite?
No, I just didn't know what he liked.
But no one in this world hates tteokbokki.
When I was younger,
my mother ran a tteokbokki place.
Her business
heroically went under with the review,
"It's tough for tteokbokki
to be this bad."
Is this the famous...
Yes, the famous tteokbokki
in downtown Dangjin.
Right? Everyone loves tteokbokki, right?
Yes, of course.
Oddly, Geun-young is the only girl I know
who doesn't like tteokbokki.
Don't worry. He loves it.
I'm sure he'll finish everything.
I see, I'm glad.
Look. The color already looks appetizing.
I really have no idea
why my tteokbokki place went under.
Try a bite first,
then give me your objective opinion.
Okay.
What? Right.
It's really good.
My gosh, you're more frank than you look.
Geun-young, you should eat up,
then go fetch your dad
before he buys something weird again.
At this rate, he might come home
with stars and the Moon.
He already bought stars and the Moon.
What?
Well, let me put this in a good way.
When you go to the Moon later,
you'll have a piece of land for yourself.
I can't believe this guy.
-Eat up.
-Yes, Ma'am.
This is spicy and sweet. What a meal.
Mom, make him some more.
That's hardly enough.
-Should I really?
-Yes, he loves tteokbokki.
I see.
I can't remember the last time
I had such a nice stroll.
Tell me about it. I always ran around
in a hurry ever since I met you.
That's because you always went around
causing trouble.
I never caused any trouble.
You're the one who gets weird ideas.
Weird ideas? Wait.
If this is about that day,
it's a misunderstanding.
It's okay.
I already forgot all about it too.
What are you doing? Are you going to run?
No, there are no people around,
so I thought we should walk a little.
Have you gone insane?
It'll start a rumor.
That's what it's like in the countryside.
Wait for me. Then can I do this?
Hey, what are you doing?
-Why?
-Come on.
[Jeongsan 3-ri Community Hall]
They won't buy the product
at a reasonable price,
so my year's hard work
almost came to nothing.
-Exactly.
-It's really frustrating. What about you?
It's the same for me.
[Jeongsan 3-ri Community Hall]
You should run
for the village foremanship next year.
-Me? Come on.
-Dad.
Hello, sir.
-Geun-young, you're here.
-Hey.
Wait, is that Geun-young's boyfriend?
-No, he's not.
-Hello.
Wait, he's that jerk on TV
who deserves to be beaten to death.
Yes, that's me. Hello, Mr. Lee.
I'll kill you today and kill myself.
-Wait, Dad! Dad!
-Hey, stop!
-What's with you?
-Dad!
-Stop that!
-Please calm down!
Calm down? My blood pressure
went off the charts because of him.
I can't calm down.
-My gosh, Lee. What's with you?
-Let him go!
What are you two doing?
Get away from each other!
Okay, fine.
Geun-young. Geun-young, one second.
-My gosh.
-You darned jerk.
-Hey, Lee. Stop that.
-Why are you so harsh?
[Jeongsan 3-ri Community Hall]
-Calm down.
-Goodness.
And this young man.
He's that young man who's on TV.
Yes, that's me. Feel free to stare at me.
Yes, it's you.
You're much more good-looking in person.
-Thank you.
-My gosh.
Goodness, how did you
end up coming to our town?
-I just came with her.
-Are you okay?
Okay, fine.
-My gosh.
-Goodness, Lee! Stop!
-Dad!
-Darn you!
-Are you okay?
-Of course. That was a lashing of love.
-Grab a drink.
-Of course, sir.
I heard you're very famous.
-You're a top star or something.
-He's a singer.
Right. Let me pour you a glass, sir.
Sounds great.
Dad, let him pour you one.
When will you get to let a singer
pour you a drink?
If you ever make Geun-young cry,
I'll pluck your eyes out.
Yes, I'll remember that.
Anyway, why does Geun-young
look so bad on TV?
Right.
She's very polite,
and she does a great job
when she runs errands.
She was the most wanted daughter-in-law
in our village up until she turned 25.
Yes, you're right.
Only up until she was 25.
What? Then I'm not most wanted anymore?
No, that's not what I meant.
Geun-young may be suffering
from people's criticism now,
but I know one day,
she'll get the credit she deserves.
We're going to wait.
Geun-young isn't a girl
who lets people down.
I'm feeling much better now that I'm here.
Let me pour you one.
All right, sure.
This is great.
You should take one too.
I can still see lots of stars here.
You know that one of those stars is mine.
You have one too.
Really? Mine too?
Yes, the small, bright star over there.
That's yours.
You're easily persuaded,
but you're also pretty romantic.
But stop buying things.
Mom is getting stressed out.
I know.
She'll get furious
if she finds out that I bought stars.
So this is a secret from her, okay?
Dad, I told her by mistake.
What?
Goodness, should I sell it off again?
-You.
-Yes, sir.
-Carry me on your back.
-Sorry?
Carry me on your back. Come here.
Tell Mom that I got very drunk.
-Go.
-Yes, sir.
A top star's back isn't very different.
Right.
How far can you go with me on your back?
You won't go down
even before you go 100 meters, will you?
No, that won't happen.
I can go very far, Mr. Lee.
Mr. Very Far, why are you trembling?
[Well, it looks a lot like the room
I have in Seoul, right?]
You wanted to come, so don't blame me.
You've had guests here before, right?
I can hear weird wind sounds
from the plumbing.
You have a face mask, right? Put it on.
You're worried about my bronchial tubes?
I'm awfully grateful.
Goodnight. I hope you make it.
Right, I think Mom said
she saw some rats in the drain.
Did she catch them? Or was it a snake?
What? Hey, Geun-young. Geun-young!
Rats?
It must be uncomfortable
trying to sleep on the floor.
Hey, you weren't asleep.
I didn't know we could still see
a night sky like this in Korea.
You're very sentimental.
By any chance, have ever been to Alaska?
I haven't even been to Japan.
Do you actually think I've been there?
Right.
You've heard of the name Benny, right?
Well, you've done
your share of research on me.
My real name is Benny.
I came from Alaska.
Oh, Alaska?
I didn't know that.
People think I'm an international student
who studied in the U.S.,
but after I graduated high school,
I left my single mother alone
and decided to come to Korea.
And now that I see
such a wonderful night sky,
I'm reminded of Alaska.
Do you miss her?
So you should come
and see your parents more often.
They must be lonely by themselves.
You suddenly talk
like you're such an elder.
I'm a year older than you.
What? You're the same age as me.
What? You lied about your age too?
Why do you have so many secrets?
What's true about you?
It's not like I wanted to lie about it.
At times,
I also get confused about who I am.
[These are his memories and love.]
[But why does this make my heart ache?]
[Who do I think I am?]
-My gosh! Goodness.
-My gosh.
What was that? A snake?
Where? Where is it?
Over there.
I knew I'd see a snake here.
This is bad. Come here.
Why are you sitting so close to me?
Is this one of your jokes again?
Am I a guy
who always jokes around with you?
If it's not a joke,
why do you keep doing this to me?
Well, I don't know when it began,
but I like you.
Geun-young, aren't you going to get up?
You must've been tired.
Goodness.
It's so great to sleep at home.
So? Did you get to bed early last night?
Yes, I fell asleep right away.
So where is he?
He's sweeping the yard.
It's a perfect job for him.
What? Sweeping the yard?
Why did you make him sweep the yard?
You're all very odd.
Plato is a perfect read for the morning.
You're finally up.
That's my dad's jacket.
Oh, Ms. Jang let me borrow it
because it got colder.
Anyway, don't you think
she's discriminative?
She makes the guest wake up early,
but left her daughter to sleep in.
I like how consistent she is.
You didn't have to do it.
You never do what you don't want to do.
She said she won't let me eat
if I don't do this.
It's cold. Go back inside.
What is this?
Is today a holiday? Is this a party?
You never make these for me.
A guy should eat this much
and be stronger.
-No one eats this much these days.
-Should I take some off?
No, ma'am. Thank you.
Right.
You should eat first, Father.
Why am I your father?
Then how should I address you?
I thought it'd be impolite
to call you Mr. Lee.
I think he's right.
Father sounds better than Mr. Lee.
-Eat up.
-Don't address me. Just don't.
All right, now. Let's eat.
-Here.
-Thank you.
Let's see.
Eat the green onion.
-The crab shell.
-Right.
Father gave me some green onion.
-Green onion and chicken.
-Goodness.
-He's so witty.
-That's good.
I keep calling In-hyung,
but she won't pick up.
You said she isn't home either.
I'm sorry.
You're her manager,
yet you don't know where she is?
Go look everywhere
and see if you can find her.
Yes, sir.
Darn it.
How did I do?
Great.
[Jae-joon]
They didn't think it was bad.
Then may I listen again?
Sure.
I need to take this call.
[Who-joon's single]
Make sure you eat well.
I packed some sesame oil too,
so don't let it leak.
You didn't have to.
If you want some, take hers.
I packed enough for two.
Wait, aren't people on TV
too picky to eat something like this?
No way, I love it.
Especially your tteokbokki.
I only let you off
because you aren't my kid.
Don't you ever let my daughter
get involved in something unfair.
-All right.
-Okay.
If you be good to her,
I might make something for you again.
If you get my daughter in trouble,
I'll break the antenna off the TV station,
as well as your two legs.
I'll remember that, Father.
Thank you, Father.
I'll come back for more tteokbokki.
-Who says you can?
-Me.
Your mother is such a loving woman.
I still feel full.
It's not that she's loving.
I think she fed you a lot
to avenge me since you were so mean.
No way. You don't give someone
that much fish fillet and meat
for someone you hate.
In the end, she fell for me too.
I'm starting to get jealous of you.
How can you be so confident?
You should have some of that confidence.
You deserve to.
People in your village have
a high level of trust in you.
I was afraid you were an outcast
even at here,
but I was the mean one. I got scared.
It's a whole village of anti-fans.
Why is the car slowing down?
-Are we out of gas?
-No way. One second.
We need to call for help.
Wait, I can't.
Can you move your feet?
I know the button is
somewhere around here.
-Is it over here?
-Should I get off?
No, you can stay.
I think it was somewhere back here.
-That one?
-Is that it?
Can you move your hand?
It was somewhere around here.
Somewhere around here.
Why?
-You did that on purpose.
-I saw the button here somewhere.
-I need to take another look.
-You're really sly.
My gosh.
Yes, I'm on the highway now.
So where exactly are you?
So you were out of gas.
You weren't looking for anything.
Things could've got worse
if something else was wrong.
Wait, isn't this situation
the same as the mistake
Ji-hyang made long ago?
That one?
He told you about that?
That was unnecessary.
Why? After he told me that,
I thought you were
a better person than I thought.
So you went and gave that fan a ride?
You should've told me.
You know, I was being nice to a fan.
Goodness, what a nice celebrity you are.
You came very far.
What is this?
I don't cook at home,
so I'll leave these here.
It's not that I don't like these.
Okay. You should go.
Let's go.
-Get a good rest.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
What are you so curious about?
Where have you really been?
What's with the rice and apples?
Nothing much.
Don't let me catch you
doing something weird, okay?
I never do anything weird.
Anyway, Ji-hyang.
Could you pick up that ring for me?
I want to find my dad again.
Let's contact that alumni group
and do everything we can.
Okay. Let's look for him.
We'll try doing everything we can.
So where have you been?
You've suddenly changed.
Nowhere.
Let's go.
[Did you put
Mother's side dishes in the fridge?]
[Who-joon]
[You don't have to worry. Go to sleep.]
[Geun-young]
"Mother"?
Well, it's a variety show,
but we're technically married,
so she's my mother-in-law?
[I'm still full from everything
your mom gave me.]
[Who-joon]
[Will you cook for me next time?]
Unbelievable. He must be insane.
Why? What?
[It's me. I have something to say.]
[Stranger]
[Can you call me
once you check this message?]
[I'll wait.]
Did you think I didn't know
you two were seeing each other?
If you two keep doing this,
will you get a grip
only after you see how wrecked she gets?
Yes, Ms. No.
Today?
It's just an interview, so don't worry.
Be at the penthouse, okay?
Oh, okay.
We'll get ready for Who-joon's interview.
Please speed it up.
-Look at this.
-What is it?
This is the best part.
-Is this yours?
-This is hilarious. That's insane.
How can this be?
Look at that.
-That's really awesome.
-My gosh.
That's hilarious.
So funny.
Will you check your phone?
That's unbelievable.
[Who-joon]
[What is it? Tell me.]
[Are you all having fun without me?]
Let's begin the interview.
-That's good.
-My gosh.
[Spigen Entertainment, CEO Choi Jae-joon]
Mr. Choi.
What's this?
It got here this morning.
[Notice of Contract Cancellation]
[Saram Law Firm, Client: Oh In-hyung]
Go get the chief manager
who's in charge of Oh In-hyung.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Choi.
It's Who-joon's song
you recently listened to.
["Who-joon's Song Leaked!"]
["Accident or Marketing?
Who is the Mysterious Female Singer?"]
Let's wrap up now. Great work today.
Who-joon's song must've been leaked out.
What?
His first love
and featured by a female singer.
[Who-joon's Song Leaked]
Who-joon and his girls are
all over the news.
What is this?
["Is It the Anti-Fan's Plan?"]
Do these people think
an anti-fan is a criminal?
This is just awful.
-Great work.
-Wait, Geun-young.
Geun-young,
you better stay home quietly for a while.
-Why?
-Well...
Is something going on?
Did something happen?
["Fans Enraged with the Leakage"]
So, are you saying
In-hyung was there or not?
[She just said she wanted to listen.]
Darn it.
["Fans Demand an Investigation!"]
["The Anti-Fan Goes Too Far"]
["Was This Her Plan?"]
-There he is.
-He's here.
-Excuse me!
-One question!
-Please say one word!
-Excuse me!
What's with that face? Was it really you?
I thought you knew.
Have you gone insane?
You leaked the song you sang with him?
Everyone wants to know who the girl is,
do you want me to expose
your relationship too?
Weren't you going to do that anyway?
All you care about now is that woman,
Lee Geun-young.
Were you concerned
that you'll lose your position?
I'm sure you were the one
who got concerned.
Do you think I had no idea
you needed me here
to get Joon to sign with you?
But now it looks like
you won't need me anymore.
Have you
always been this suspicious of me?
Then what about me?
I never got to say anything
all wrapped up under your suspicion!
Do you think
everything is unfair only for you?
You two keep saying
everything is in the past
and act like it's all behind you.
Do you know how disgusting it is
for me to see that?
That's enough!
I used to think everything would be fine
as long as I listen to you.
But
I found out that
there are many replacements
who do everything you want.
Have I
ever been important to you in your life?
It sounds like
you regret everything.
Yes, I do.
I regret this to death. Happy now?
I'm very sorry,
but every single decision
you make from now on
will be wrong.
Especially now.
But still.
At the very least,
you didn't have to say you regret it.
["Did the Anti-Fan Plan the Leak?"]
Stay home until the reporters get quiet.
The agency is trying to stop the articles.
You should go home.
Joon.
Where are you going?
Why are you here instead of home?
Why? Am I not allowed to be
at a friend's place?
Come with me.
To where?
Excuse me.
Don't you regret becoming my anti-fan?
Yes.
A little.
I should've been calm back then.
I should've let it go
even though I knew it was unfair.
Why did I do that?
If I held back,
people wouldn't have hated me so much
whenever something like this
broke out.
I'm sorry.
People took this out on you
all because of me.
I'm sorry to make you stay patient
whenever something unfair happens.
You can cry
when you're with me.
Man, this is so stressful.
They don't even know what they're saying.
Unbelievable.
Hey, you idiots! It wasn't Geun-young!
It wasn't Lee Geun-young!
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
People are going to look at you.
Why? Give it a try.
It makes you feel better.
Say it. Say that you didn't do it.
It wasn't her!
What if people recognize you?
If you don't let it out, it can hurt you.
Do it now.
You idiots!
Do I seem like a joke to you?
Do I seem like a pushover?
You always blame me for everything.
Why do you do that?
It wasn't me!
It wasn't her!
See? Isn't that much better?
Do you sometimes shout out like this
when you get frustrated?
But it's not as good
when you do this alone.
You have to do it with someone.
Well, I guess
you can do this with me from now on.
I'm hungry now that I feel better.
Do you want to eat something?
Okay. I was too concerned about you
that I didn't eat anything today.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Don't cry, you crybaby.
Someone's calling you.
No, I'm not picking up.
Come on, pick it up.
Who's calling at this hour?
[Stranger]
What are you doing? Pick it up.
Okay.
One second.
-What is...
[-Are you Oh In-hyung's guardian?]
[This is the hospital.]