=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 33=
No matter why
Qingmu did so in the Demon Region today,
he
did help the Demons.
If you want me to believe
he’s still loyal,
he must return the Twin Spear
to the Heavenly Palace.
I’ll give you three days.
Fine.
It’s a deal.
No wonder you’ve been merciful
towards Houchi and Qingmu.
Turns out you still want
to reopen the God Realm.
Leave us.
What’s upsetting you, Your Highness?
I never expected that
though we’ve been a couple
for tens of thousands of years,
he joined hands with someone else
even without telling me.
Your Highness,
you want to...?
This has
just begun.
As long as Immortals and the Demons
don’t stop fighting,
when I cultivate myself in my own way,
I’ll sooner or later
tread every other immortal underfoot.
Spare me, Your Highness!
You killed countless immortals.
Why should I spare you?
As long as you spare me,
I will
serve you faithfully!
Serve me?
You’re willing to betray the Demons?
I’ve lived tens of thousands of years,
cultivating myself
in the Abyssal Ridge Swamp.
I don’t care about the fight
between the Immortals and the Demons.
If the Demon God hadn’t appeared,
I wouldn’t have been involved.
It’s wise of you.
God’s... God’s Mark?
It’s my mark.
If you serve me faithfully,
I’ll remove it.
Otherwise, when I want to destroy you,
you’ll be crushed
with nothing left.
I’ll certainly follow your lead
and never betray you, Your Highness!
Thank you, Your Highness.
All right.
Do something for me.
When you make it,
you’ll profit from it.
Yes, Your Highness.
(Qingchi Palace)
Your Grace.
Lady Fengran.
Are Houchi and Qingmu back?
For your information,
Her Grace and Lord Qingmu
haven’t come back yet.
Your Grace,
it took Qingmu lots of effort
to get your permission.
Why don’t you just let him and Houchi
spend some comfortable days?
Anyway, when you’re here,
the Heavenly Palace
can do nothing to us.
We’re in the wrong, after all.
If Qingmu doesn’t return the Twin Spear
in three days,
it won’t end up well.
I’m going to find them, then.
Your spiritual power
seemed to be unstable.
But now,
it’s back to normal?
It’s not only normal,
but also abundant.
Possibly because you have two weapons.
I’m glad you’re fine.
Where Boxuan stays
is the North Sea?
We came here before,
but why didn’t we feel him?
The four seas are linked.
Below the vast North Sea
are countless secret paths.
When I cultivated myself here
in the past thousand years,
I didn’t experience any of the paths.
Maybe it’s the reason.
Don’t get fooled by him.
Boxuan was right in his place,
but he didn’t know?
How is that possible?
Jingyuan?
Why are you here?
In case you’re fooled
by such a liar,
I’m here to protect you.
In the Demon Region,
you even failed
to defeat the Heavenly Empress.
I think you’re the one
who often cheats others.
Let’s go.
Small trick.
What?
They went to the North Sea?
We’re putting pressure on
the Qingchi Palace.
Why did they go to the North Sea,
instead of coming up with a solution?
I don’t know, either.
What should I do now?
Please tell me.
His Majesty has a three-day agreement
with Gu Jun.
In three days,
if the Twin Spear can’t be returned,
their crime of colluding
with the Demon God
and betraying the Immortals
will be confirmed.
No matter how hard
Gu Jun tries to explain then,
he can’t vindicate himself.
Do you know what you should do?
I’m willing to serve you, Your Highness.
But I don’t have
as much spiritual power as before.
There’s a thin spiritual aura
at the bottom of the North Sea
and they can hardly get more power.
But the Demon God is there with them
and Qingmu has just got two weapons.
I don’t think I can defeat them.
This power of God
will last for a couple of hours
in your body,
which can help you get the Twin Spear.
Thank you, Your Highness.
I have some power of God now,
but I’m all alone.
Without some good weapons,
I don’t think I can fight them.
Look at you.
If you hadn’t been so greedy,
you wouldn’t have ended up like this.
This is the Magic Dart
of the Eagle Clan.
It’s the best for a sneak attack.
To make extra certain,
I’m giving it to you.
Remember.
Your aim is to get back the Twin Spear.
Yes.
Don’t let anyone recognize you.
If anything goes wrong...
Don’t worry, Your Highness.
I understand.
Why is Boxuan in such a place?
A secret door is over there.
It’s made of ice?
It’s not ordinary ice.
It’s ancient ice
from the Shanggu Realm.
I don’t think we can break it
with ordinary spells.
Indeed.
Boxuan often used some spells
from the Shanggu Realm.
He must have left a clue
behind the door.
Let’s try to open the door.
Qingmu?
I don’t know why I could open it.
Maybe,
we’ll know
when we find Boxuan.
It’s Boxuan!
Houchi.
What kind of powerful immortal
could seal Boxuan in this place?
And you can’t unseal him
even when you work together.
No immortal could.
But some God or Goddess may.
What do you mean?
Try with your Taicang Spear.
Boxuan!
Qingmu!
No!
It’s going to collapse.
Let’s go!
Go.
Who dared to do this!
Come out immediately!
Octagon God-trapping Formation?
Tianqi, don’t underestimate him.
What did you call me?
Let’s try to get out of here.
There’s power of God in this formation.
Who’s doing this?
I knew it when I first saw
the formation.
But you just realized it?
I never like you.
But if today,
we’re killed by such an unknown nobody,
we’ll be a joke.
Why don’t we defeat him together?
What do you say, Demon God?
You don’t like me?
I don’t like you, either.
You’re just as stubborn as before.
You just need my help,
but you always deny it.
Three-head, how dare you!
It’s not me!
You get the wrong man!
Go!
Who’s breaking in?
Get out of my way.
Stop!
Fengran?
What brings you here?
Your Highness.
Lady Fengran is here for me.
Leave us.
Yes.
Jingjian,
why is there such dense evil force?
There’re always casualties
during every fight
between immortals and demons.
Evil force is generated, then.
I don’t know why,
but this time,
there’s far too much evil force.
Maybe because humans died, too.
I’m garrisoning this place
to release the souls
and purify the evil force.
I understand now.
Getting stuck in evil force
will bring the most harm
to the foundation.
You must be very careful.
You’re worried about me?
In your dream!
You put in a good word for Houchi
in the Heavenly Palace.
I’m caring about you in return.
Don’t worry.
I’ll take good care of myself
and won’t keep you worried.
Keep a safe distance from me,
or they’ll say you collude
with the Qingchi Palace
and the Demons.
Fengran, I’m not scared of that.
Enough.
I’m... I’m here to ask you
if you know where Houchi is.
Houchi?
Isn’t she back to the Qingchi Palace?
When I was patrolling in Dibei Town
of the Human Realm,
I heard that she and Qingmu
had gone back.
They...
They would go to the North Sea before
getting back to the Qingchi Palace.
They should have arrived already.
The North Sea?
That man who just ran away
is the Three-head Fire Dragon?
Why was he ambushing in that place?
What a shameless dragon!
Shortly after he was taken away
by Wu Huan,
he got far stronger power
and came to snatch the Twin Spear.
He must be working
for the Heavenly Palace now.
Jingyuan,
why do you look so pale?
There’s a thin spiritual aura
at the bottom of the sea.
When I was forcibly enhancing my power,
I got my spiritual veins hurt.
I’ll be all right after a rest.
Houchi,
let’s get back to the Qingchi Palace
and tell God Gu Jun that
we found Boxuan
and met the Three-head Fire Dragon.
Then he’ll decide what to do.
Oh, my dear Houchi.
At last, I found you.
Why are you coming?
You have no idea.
The Heavenly Palace
and the Qingchi Palace
have fallen out
because you stopped the fight
between immortals and demons
in the Demon Region.
Why did you come to the North Sea?
Fengran,
we found Boxuan.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
With the Twin Spear,
you can restrain the Qingchi Palace.
You did a good job.
You deserve my thinking highly of you.
I’m flattered, Your Highness.
When Qingmu and Houchi
can’t return the Twin Spear
in three days,
their crime of colluding
with the Demon God will be confirmed.
Gu Jun always shields them.
He’ll certainly defend them.
When they lose the support,
they can hardly regain the old glory.
With such a little trick,
you’ll get rid of the Qingchi Palace!
Multiple benefits.
Enough.
The Dart is yours.
Thank you, Your Highness!
(Purple Moon Spring)
God Zihan,
it’s very serious
that the Heavenly Emperor has sent
more troops to the Demon Region.
I’d like to discuss it with Master.
No need.
Master ordered that
before he summoned you,
you could just command everything.
Has he not returned yet?
Master has been
in the Purple Moon Spring...
I don’t believe that.
Why are you keeping it secret?
Since the battle in the Demon Region,
Master hasn’t returned
to the Third Heaven.
Everything has changed
for the Immortals and the Demons.
Master needs to make a decision
for everything.
Where has he gone?
Sen Jian, how dare you!
How dare you ask about his whereabouts
and be insubordinate!
What?
I was away for only a few days
and you have forgotten
how to be a Demon King?
I’m sorry, Master.
Zihan, come with me.
Master!
- Master!
Your spiritual veins got hurt!
Let me get you in.
(Qingchi Palace)
Your Grace!
Her Grace is back with Lord Boxuan.
Where are they?
In the Huajing Pond.
Houchi really found him?
Your Grace.
Father.
You’re no longer mad at me?
You brought me up.
You’re my only father.
I got you wrong.
I’m sorry for that.
Please forgive me.
I’m glad you’re back.
Houchi,
when you were away in the Human Realm,
God Gu Jun cared
neither for food nor drink
and he kept talking about you.
He said he regretted it so much
and he should have told you the truth.
By the way,
how did you find Boxuan?
You said you found him
because of Qingmu’s dream.
That’s odd.
Your Grace,
please check on Boxuan.
For Master Shanggu,
you indeed suffered the pain
of tearing your Original Being.
Father.
Boxuan was hurt
during the thunder trail.
Now his spiritual sense is closed
and he’s in deep sleep.
When can he wake up?
Don’t worry.
Boxuan has strong power.
After his sense is fixed,
he’ll wake up.
Just take good care of him.
Don’t worry, Father.
I’ll guard him carefully.
Qingmu,
come with me.
No one lived here for years.
It’s quite desolate.
Fengran,
go fetch some ornaments from my study.
Oh,
the eaglewood from the South Sea.
Remember to use it.
Boxuan likes to read with it.
By the way,
get some peach wine heated.
Boxuan likes drinking.
He used to drink some every day.
All right.
I’m on my way.
Did anyone else know
you found Boxuan,
except you two and Fengran?
With the help of the Demon God,
we managed to get him back
from the ice-bound cave
of the North Sea.
So,
he knew it, too.
Your Grace,
is there anything wrong?
The Demon God is cunning.
He even attempted to destroy the world.
He must have helped you
for some personal reason.
Regardless of the peace negotiation,
he started the war in the Demon Region.
We’ll certainly be blamed.
You’d better have less contact with him.
I understand.
Your Grace,
when I saw Boxuan,
I felt something strange.
What was it?
Felt like some Spiritual Strength
flew into my body.
Could he be...?
Your love with Houchi
kind of makes up for their regret.
You mean
True God Bai Jue also had deep love
for True God Shanggu?
The second part of what I told Houchi
is true.
After Boxuan’s sense is fixed,
he will wake up.
But when he wakes up, you’ll...
I don’t care how long I can live.
I’ll always love her until I die.
Don’t worry, God Gu Jun.
I’ll keep working on it.
But...
Will True God Bai Jue be nice to Houchi?
Love is so complicated.
I don’t understand it, either.
No matter what,
I never regret it.
All right.
So much for the personal affairs.
Let’s get to the business.
Give the Twin Spear to me.
I’ll return it to the Heavenly Palace.
Bad.
I knew it!
What happened?
Houchi,
aren’t you curious
what he looks like
behind the mask?
I am.
Then why don’t you open it
and have a look?
Anyway, he’s lying here,
without any ability to stop you.
Boxuan told me that
no one could see his face
unless he removed the mask himself.
He’s got such a brilliant spell?
Fengran,
think about what happened.
Qingmu looked weird, didn’t he?
Was he jealous
because you cared so much about Boxuan?
He can’t be.
In the North Sea,
he called Jingyuan Tianqi.
Tianqi?
Isn’t it the name of the Demon God?
Three-head Fire Dragon?
The Twin Spear was stolen.
The Heavenly Empress could
confirm our crime
of colluding with the Demon God.
Exactly.
In the Demon Region,
immortals saw Houchi fight Jingyang.
You then repulsed Wu Huan
for the Demon God.
If we can’t return the Twin Spear
in three days,
all immortals will go against us.
I’ll go get it back.
It’s too late.
I’m afraid
Wu Huan has it now.
It’s my fault.
If it weren’t for me,
the Heavenly Palace
wouldn’t have pushed you.
Wrong.
It’s not your fault.
Wu Huan is domineering,
but she wouldn’t be my enemy
for such a small problem.
Why on earth
did she do that?
It’s also you who asked them
to collude with the Demon God?
You mean
you want to be an enemy
to the Heavenly Palace
and betray the Immortals?
Houchi absorbed the power
of the Pilgrimage Hall.
Even Muguang has suspected
her real identity.
Why did Wu Huan want to kill her,
instead of noticing who she might be?
Wu Huan,
how much of your loyalty
to Master Shanggu
can be true?
It’s the Demon God.
He killed my master.
Wu Huan witnessed that!
Please accept my condolences.
No one except Wu Huan saw
the Demon God kill Goddess Yuemi.
Even Master Bai Jue believed Wu Huan
and he...
Your Grace.
Your Grace?
What’s the matter?
Nothing.
Don’t worry.
No matter what Wu Huan is planning,
I won’t let her succeed again this time.
Houchi, are you all right?
Why is this happening?
Didn’t Father say
Boxuan’s spiritual sense was damaged
by the thunder strikes?
He looks like he’s lost all his power.
When he’s frozen all over,
I’m afraid he can’t come back to life.
Is there any way to save him?
Yes, but the only way is too hard.
Accumulated spiritual aura
generates treasures.
I hear
we can’t get back someone’s
spiritual power back,
unless we collect
the Ghost Suppressing Tower,
the Spirit Gathering Bead
and the Demon Gathering Streamer
and put his body in them.
Where are the treasures?
Fengran.
God Gu Jun has gone
to the Heavenly Palace.
It’s a serious thing
to collect the three treasures.
Shall we not decide until he comes back?
Did he say when he would come back?
I don’t think
Boxuan can hold that long.
The Spirit Gathering Bead is a treasure
of the Heavenly Palace.
The Demon Gathering Streamer controls
the beasts of the Demon Realm.
The Ghost Suppressing Tower
is suppressing the evil force
and guarding the Human Realm.
Let alone it’ll be a dangerous trip,
even if we get the three treasures,
we’ll immediately be enemies
of the Three Realms.
By then, how can your father
defend Qilian Mountains alone?
Houchi,
Qingmu is right.
When God Gu Jun is back,
let’s ask him for opinions.
Your Highness,
immortals and demons only have
put more soldiers in the Demon Region,
without having any fight.
Why?
If they fight,
the Human Realm will be damaged.
Father is so benevolent
that he doesn’t want
the Human Realm to suffer.
That’s why the demons are safe now.
If I commanded the war,
we would have destroyed
the Xuanjing Palace already.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, mind your words.
Gu Jun?
Why is he here?
I just came back
from inspecting the four seas
and I was told you came.
It’s not the deadline yet.
Did you come here
for some other issue?
Muguang,
do you remember what we promised
when we left the God Realm
sixty thousand years ago?
We promised that one day,
we would reopen the God Realm,
get back all Gods
and regain the old glory.
Over tens of thousands of years,
I’ve never forgotten our promise.
Otherwise,
I wouldn’t have asked you
to get back the weapons.
Did you really ask me to get them back
not for yourself?
Immortals and demons have fought
in the past sixty thousand years.
You didn’t mean to
unify the Three Realms,
but the Three Realms are in chaos
because of you.
Demons helped the Demon God
to destroy the world,
and my master died a miserable death.
I can’t let it go.
But the Demon God is still alive.
Have you thought about it?
Maybe Goddess Yuemi died
for some other reason.
Goddess Yuemi was very close
to the Four True Gods.
If Goddess Yuemi was really killed
by the Demon God,
why would True God Bai Jue
have spared his life back then?
And
was there anybody who witnessed
it was the Demon God
that killed Goddess Yuemi?
Wu Huan witnessed the kill.
As you said,
it was Wu Huan,
not you with your own eyes.
Gu Jun,
what do you mean by that?
You think Wu Huan lied?
In the unrest of the God Realm,
we didn’t have time
to check many details.
Wu Huan has been with you
for 60,000 years.
You should know what kind of person
she is better than I do.
You’ve never doubted even a little bit
about what happened
in the Abyssal Ridge Swamp?
Now, the Demon God and Four Weapons
have appeared one by one.
We’ll reopen the God Realm
sooner or later.
But before that,
I hope you can find out the truth
so that you can console Goddess Yuemi
and other Gods of Stars
who died in the Abyssal Ridge Swamp.
I have to go to the Demon Region
to purify the grievances
generated from the battle.
Think carefully about it.
What?
Gu Jun met your father secretly?
Mother,
it’s true.
I saw Gu Jun come alone.
I asked my men to check on it
and learned that Gu Jun had waited on
the Cloud Platform for the whole night.
Did you figure out
why he came?
The Cloud Platform was quiet.
The Attendant Immortals heard
Gu Jun and Father argue.
They kind of mentioned a name...
called Yuemi.
Don’t worry, Your Highness.
Qingmu can’t return the Twin Spear.
God Gu Jun must have come
to ask for mercy from His Majesty.
Can’t return the Twin Spear?
Did Qingmu
really give it to the Demon God?
If he could return it,
Gu Jun wouldn’t have argued
with your father.
I know
how to deal with the Qingchi Palace.
Just focus on the mission
your father assigned you.
Yes, Mother.
You’re just back from the battlefield.
You must be tried.
Go get a good rest.
I shouldn’t have said that.
I’m sorry, Your Highness.
Go get Three-head to me!
Yes.
Why did Gu Jun suddenly mention Yuemi
in front of Muguang?
Did he find out something?
When I couldn’t find Boxuan,
I thought there was hope
that he wasn’t in danger.
Now I’ve found him.
But he’s like this.
Unexpectedly,
it’s so complicated to save him.
Qingmu.
I don’t want you or Fengran
to be embarrassed.
Nor do I want the Qingchi Palace
to be a target for all.
But I really want to save Boxuan.
Houchi,
could you tell me about him?
How was he to you?
He was very nice to me.
Last time I saw him,
he was leaving the Qingchi Palace
to go through trials.
It’s such a lovely place!
I like it here!
If you like it,
I’ll bring you here again in the future.
10,000 years.
I promise
I will be back in 10,000 years.
And I will find you
no matter where you are.
After Boxuan’s sense is fixed,
he will wake up.
But when he wakes up, you’ll...
Qingmu,
if I insist on getting the treasures,
will you hate me?
Have you made up your mind?
I wouldn’t care if it were someone else.
But it’s Boxuan. I can’t watch him
die like this
and do nothing to save him.
All right.
Now that you’ve made up your mind,
I’ll help you get the three treasures.
But you must promise me something.
On this trip,
I’ll take full responsibility on my own.
All right.
I promise you.
What do you want to do?
I want to protect you
and the Qingchi Palace.
Please allow me
to do it my own way for the last time.
This is my father’s God-binding Spell.
It has his power of God on it.
You can’t remove it.
It’ll be invalid in one day.
Houchi,
you can’t go alone.
What shall I do if you’re in danger?
Remove it from me!
After I get the treasures,
I’ll come back immediately.
I’m wrong this time.
Take care.
Houchi!
Three-head,
did anything special happen
in the North Sea that day?
Please spare me, Your Highness.
The Demon God had such strong power.
I’m afraid he recognized me.
What?
How dared you not tell me!
You evil woman!
I won’t bear with you anymore!
I knew you were crafty.
You’re dead meat!
Your Highness! Your Highness!
I’ve got something else.
Please don’t kill me.
When I trapped them,
I heard Lord Qingmu
mention Boxuan to Houchi.
I didn’t know who Boxuan was,
but Qingmu asked Houchi
to take Boxuan and leave.
Boxuan?
Did they go to the North Sea
for this man Boxuan?
If this time,
you dare to fool me again...
I don’t dare to fool you, Your Highness!
I never dare!
Never.
Leave us.
Thank you, Your Highness!
Boxuan?
Does he have something to do
with the portrait at the bottom
of the Huajing Pond?
No.
I must have someone
keep an eye on the Qingchi Palace.
Or I’ll always be in a passive position.
As recorded in books,
the Ghost Suppressing Tower
came from the Shanggu Realm
and it can suppress all evil force.
(Imperial Mausoleum)
It’s in the Underground Palace.
It’s indeed the Ghost Suppressing Tower!
No one is allowed to get close
to the Ghost Suppressing Tower.
Who are you?
How dare you come to steal it!
Are you Lord Bi Xi guarding the Tower?
Now that you know me,
how dare you come to steal it!
You get me wrong.
I just want to borrow it
to save a friend.
I’ll return it after that.
All greedy men say the same thing.
The Ghost Suppressing Tower
can help with cultivation.
How will you return it
after you borrow it?
Now that you managed to break in,
you must have strong power.
For the sake that you’ve cultivated
yourself for thousands of years
and you have pure spiritual power,
I won’t kill you.
Leave immediately.
I must get the Tower today!
Sir, if you refuse to lend it to me,
don’t blame me for offending you.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪