=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 34=
Sir, if you refuse to lend it to me,
don’t blame me for offending you!
Where did you learn how to
break the Bagua Liusheng Formation?
I read about this formation
from Boxuan’s ancient books
when I was only 300 years old.
Who sent you here
to steal the treasure?
I’m just a nobody.
Turns out you’ve integrated
yourself with this tower.
So, you’ll never separate from it.
I don’t care if you find out.
Many people have seen my true body
over the past 60,000 years.
But no one has been able to get past me
and take away
the Ghost Suppressing Tower!
There’s always a way to break either
the Five Elements and Bagua,
or the coexistence of Yin and Yang.
How dare you!
This is…
This is the bone-piercing evil force
that only exists here.
It’ll kill you as soon as
it reaches your bones.
The people who tried to steal
the treasure over the years
all died
when exposed to this force.
So will you!
Hurry!
Remove the God-freezing Spell for me!
And I’ll change you back! Come on!
If Houchi is in danger,
I won’t let you off!
Hurry!
I’m impressed that you’ve reached
a high cultivation base
at such a young age.
But you are ill-intentioned
and greedy for the treasure.
So, don’t blame me for ending your life!
If you tell me who sent you here
to steal the Ghost Suppressing Tower,
I may give you a quick
and painless death.
What good deeds have you done?
Why are there so many mortal prayers
protecting you from the evil force?
Dibei Town?
You are Houchi, the young Goddess
of the Qingchi Palace.
You are the one who defended Dibei Town.
No, I have nothing to do
with the Qingchi Palace.
It doesn’t matter if you don’t admit it.
You said that you wanted
to borrow the tower to save someone.
Is that true?
Your Lordship,
I want to borrow the tower
to save an old friend
whose life is in danger.
He needs the tower
to gather his spiritual sense.
That’s why I had to break
into the Underground Palace.
Hope you can grant me this favor!
Thank you, Lord Bi Xi!
Goddess, do you know
why I’m willing to help you?
I’ve guarded this tower for
tens of thousands of years.
I was formed from the spirit
of the Ghost Suppressing Tower.
True God Bai Jue guided me
and asked me to purify the evil force
and protect the human world.
A few days ago,
the Immortal and the Demons had a fight
in the Demon Region
and put the human world in danger.
You are the one who
stopped the battle in time.
Otherwise, it could’ve been a tragedy
for the people in Dibei Town.
You saved their lives,
so I’m helping you
for the good deed you did.
Houchi from the Qingchi Palace
will keep your kindness in mind.
If you need my help in the future,
just send a message
to the Qingchi Palace.
I’ll do everything I can
to repay your favor!
All right.
Since you need to save someone’s life,
you should hurry back.
But keep in mind
that you must bring the tower back
as soon as possible.
My spiritual power
can only suppress the evil force
for a short period of time.
Any later than that the evil force
will fill the human world
and harm human beings.
I’ll keep that in mind.
As soon as my friend wakes up,
I’ll bring the tower
back to you in person.
Your Ladyship,
what brings you here?
The Three Realms are in disorder.
The Qingchi Palace
might be affected one day.
I hope you can give me
some herbs for protection.
The life-saving kind.
Life-saving?
I remember that last time when I
prepared the spiritual herbs for you,
you showed little interest
and said they weren’t even
good enough for bathing.
Did I say that?
You did.
Your Ladyship,
you are not asking
for the herbs for yourself, are you?
Will you give me or not?
I won’t!
Chang Que!
Okay! I will!
Tell me,
what kind of herb do you want?
The herb that can fend off
the evil force.
What a coincidence!
I happened to spend 100 years
refining an elixir called
Hundred Spirits Pill,
which can not only purify
all kinds of evil forces,
but also help the patient
to gather spiritual power
and strengthen the cultivation base.
This pill
is perfect for Prince Jingjian!
Fengran.
Qingmu?
Come with me.
The Demon Gathering Streamer
is in the Demon Realm.
I should go find Jingyuan first.
The Spirit Gathering Bead is owned
by the Heavenly Empress.
It’ll be the hardest thing to get.
I’ll figure out a way after getting
the Demon Gathering Streamer.
Where’s Houchi?
She went to the Imperial Mausoleum
to get the Ghost Suppressing Tower.
And now,
I need to go to the Heavenly Palace
and the Demon Realm
to get the Spirit Gathering Bead
and the Demon Gathering Streamer.
I want you
to stay here and wait for
God Gu Jun to get back,
to see if there’s some other way
to save Boxuan.
Hold on.
You mean you’ll help her to
steal the three treasures?
At this point,
if she commits felonies in
the Three Realms all by herself,
no one can save her.
But if she only takes the tower,
the Heavenly Emperor will just
punish her lightly
on God Gu Jun’s account.
Then what about you?
Once the three treasures are collected,
close the mountains immediately.
I will admit my guilt
to the Heavenly Emperor
and tell him it was my idea
to steal the three treasures.
You’ll get yourself killed!
When Houchi awakens Boxuan,
even if the Heavenly Palace forgives me,
I’m afraid I’ll still…
The Heavenly Palace is quite far away
from the Demon Realm.
If you want to get the bead
and the streamer before Houchi does,
you won’t be able to make it
all by yourself.
I’m familiar with the Xuanjing Palace.
Let me go and get the streamer.
No.
It’s a serious matter.
I can’t get you involved.
Just because it concerns Houchi,
I can’t sit back and watch.
Let’s go.
Be careful.
Thank you, Master!
I won’t fail you.
Don’t worry.
Although I’m not a True God,
I still have the good stuff for you.
I will train you into
a God as quickly as I can.
Goddess Yuemi was very close
to the Four True Gods.
If Goddess Yuemi was really killed
by the Demon God,
why would True God Bai Jue
have spared his life back then?
And was there anybody
who witnessed it was the Demon God
that killed Goddess Yuemi?
Wu Huan witnessed the kill.
As you said,
it was Wu Huan,
not you with your own eyes.
Gu Jun,
what do you mean by that?
Wu Huan has been with you
for 60,000 years.
You should know what kind of person
she is better than I do.
You’ve never doubted even a little bit
about what happened
- in the Abyssal Ridge Swamp?
- Wu Huan!
How come you were in there?
Master,
it was the Demon God!
He pushed Goddess Yuemi
into the formation core.
I witnessed the God power
of Goddess Yuemi
being shattered and destroyed!
Huan was the only one
who witnessed Master’s death.
Could it be really like
what Gu Jun said?
No!
No way!
It’s impossible that
Huan would’ve framed the Demon God,
not to mention killed Goddess Yuemi!
Your Majesty.
What brings you here?
The Feng Clan just presented us
with some lucid Ganoderma.
I decocted some herb soup with it
and I’m here to bring it to you.
It can alleviate fatigue
and nurture spiritual power.
Thank you.
You are thinking of Goddess Yuemi again?
My master gave
this magic weapon to me
when I became her disciple.
She was very kind to me.
She guided me along my cultivation
and helped us Gold Dragons
of Mount Tianci
establish our power in the Three Realms.
I told her that I would repay her,
but now I can never do that.
I just don’t understand.
Back then the Demon God and my master
had been together for long
and so close to each other.
And there was no resentment held
between them before the Destruction.
Why would he kill her?
Do you remember any details?
Why are you mentioning it again?
I’m just wondering
if the Demon God
had some unspeakable reasons.
Goddess Yuemi was sent by Her Grace
to talk to the Demon God.
And then they had an argument.
I witnessed
that the Demon God pushed her
into the formation core.
The Destruction Formation absorbed
all her God power.
At last,
she died of exhaustion of God power.
Goddess Yuemi also helped me before.
Though tens of thousands
of years have passed,
I still can’t get over the pain
when thinking about her death.
It’s my bad.
I shouldn’t have mentioned it.
Your Majesty,
whatever the reason was, it was
the Demon God who started
the Destruction Formation
and thus became the enemy
of the Three Realms.
That is the fact.
He didn’t deserve to be a True God.
Master Zhiyang entrusted
the Three Realms to us.
We should fulfill our duties
so that we won’t let him down.
I got a headache.
Please go back.
Let me give you a massage.
I said,
go back.
Qin.
Why don’t you stay
and spend a night
in the Xuanjing Palace?
Get out of my way.
Qin!
The immortals are crafty.
And the Demon Region is guarded
by Jingjian and Jingyang.
It’s quite dangerous.
I’ve got Father’s permission.
I’ll go with you tomorrow.
I returned to the Third Heaven
for the future of the Demons.
Please watch your behavior.
Qin!
I know you are still mad at me.
I don’t expect your forgiveness.
But could you not
shut me out?
Yes, I made a mistake.
But I don’t want us
to miss each other again.
Okay?
Good sister, don’t be soft-hearted!
Sen Yu,
sometimes it’s just not meant to be.
Since we’ve missed each other,
then it’s Heaven’s will.
You and me, it’s not gonna happen.
Qin!
So easy?
What are you doing here?
I was just about to ask you
the same question.
Lady,
think about it.
If it weren’t for my master’s approval,
how could you
be able to break the barrier
of this secret chamber?
So the Demon God helped me in.
No wonder it was so easy.
Is the Qingchi Palace in trouble?
I need the Demon Gathering Streamer
to save Boxuan’s life.
It’s just as my master thought.
Then hurry back.
Be more careful in the future.
Don’t be so careless.
Then I’ll thank the Demon God
on behalf of the Qingchi Palace.
If Sen Jian and Sen Yu
find out that Master lent
the streamer to the Qingchi Palace,
I wonder how they’d think of him.
Houchi.
Fengran, what are you doing here?
You don’t need to go
to the Demon Realm now.
I’ve got the Demon Gathering
Streamer for you.
Did they hurt you?
Thanks to the Demon God,
I didn’t even have to fight.
Instead, I heard some gossip.
How did Jingyuan know
that I needed the streamer?
I’ll tell you after we get back
to the Qingchi Palace.
So, you went to the Demon Realm.
Then what about Qingmu?
He went to the Heavenly Palace to
get the Spirit Gathering Bead for you.
The Heavenly Empress has the bead.
If he confronts her head-on-head,
she won’t let him off easily.
But after the battle
in the Demon Region,
the immortals in the Heavenly Palace
all point fingers at you.
It’d be too dangerous
for you to go there.
I’m the one who wants
to get the three treasures.
I can’t put him in danger alone.
I’ll go to the Heavenly Palace
right now.
And I’ll bring him back as soon
as I see him.
I won’t let the Heavenly Emperor
and the Heavenly Empress find out.
I’ll go with you.
It’ll be riskier if we go together.
Makes sense.
The immortals aren’t fond of me either.
Then you’ve got to be careful.
Jingjian’s place is not far from here.
Maybe he’ll have a better idea.
This is an important place
of the Heavenly Palace.
Uninvited visitors are not allowed in.
I’m Qingmu, the North Sea Lord.
I’m Prince Jingjian’s close friend.
He asked me to bring this
to the Heavenly Palace
and put it in the treasure house.
What’s in it?
I’m not sure either.
Without Prince Jingjian’s permission,
I don’t dare to open it.
Since it’s Prince Jingjian’s stuff,
we’ll take care of it.
Thank you.
I’ll take my leave.
Sorry!
Your Highness,
Qingmu is here in the palace.
He actually broke into
the Heavenly Palace.
Could he be here for the Twin Spear?
Luckily, I’ve prepared for this.
What brought Fengnyu here?
Your Majesty,
it’s already been three days.
Has the Qingchi Palace
brought back the Twin Spear?
Your Majesty,
please go outside with me.
Fengnyu just told me
that someone is here
to steal our treasure.
Don’t know where the Heavenly Empress
keeps the Spirit Gathering Bead.
Oh, I got it!
The Spirit Gathering Bead is also
a weapon from the Shanggu Realm.
The Taicang Spear may be able
to sense its whereabouts.
Who’s there?
North Sea Lord?
It’s you?
Your Majesty,
I told you
that Qingmu was not a decent man.
He even dared come to the Heavenly
Palace to steal our treasure!
Now that you’ve caught him red-handed,
please punish him as he deserves!
North Sea Lord,
will you admit your crime?
I wonder
if she has found Qingmu and Houchi.
What are you hiding?
Nothing.
You didn’t see anything.
Open your hand and show me.
Is it from someone you love?
It’s really nothing.
Please just leave it, okay?
As a white phoenix,
how come you have a red feather?
Wait, this feather is mine!
How did you get it?
Fengran,
actually,
I wanted to tell you in
the Abyssal Ridge Swamp that…
Did I just hurt you?
No, it’s the evil force
I was exposed to.
I’ll be better after two hours
of meditation.
Let me transfer some
spiritual power to you.
Here,
it’s the Hundred Spirits Pill
that Chang Que refined.
It can help you gather
the spiritual power
and fend off the evil force of
the Demon Region.
Thank you.
What brought you to the Demon Region?
We have some trouble.
I just came back from
the Xuanjing Palace.
What kind of trouble
that made you go to the Xuanjing Palace?
I borrowed the Demon Gathering Streamer.
Demon Gathering Streamer?
We found Boxuan in the North Sea area.
You’ve really found that Lord Boxuan?
But he was badly injured
from the tribulation.
He’s lost all his spiritual sense.
Only by using the three
treasures together
can his life be saved.
Therefore, Houchi, Qingmu
and I respectively went
to the Human Realm, the Heavenly Palace
and the Third Heaven
to get the three treasures.
So far, we’ve got the
Ghost Suppressing Tower
and the Demon Gathering Streamer,
but we still need the Spirit Gathering Bead
from your Heavenly Palace.
The bead is not that important
to the Heavenly Palace.
I don’t think my father
would give them a hard time.
Where is everybody?
Something happened already?
Goddess Houchi,
we’ve been waiting for you.
The Heavenly Palace
is indeed hospitable!
You really went all out to welcome me.
The Heavenly Empress knew that
you’d come to the Heavenly Palace,
so she asked me to wait for you here.
Goddess, please go to the Fuyao Hall
and take a seat first.
Her Highness will see you
after she finishes the business at hand.
What did you do to Qingmu?
So, you know that North Sea Lord
broke into the palace
and stole the treasure.
Can I assume that you were the one
who sent him to commit
such a bold crime?
I don’t have time to play
word games with you!
This is the Heavenly Palace.
The Heavenly Emperor and Empress
aren’t expecting you at all.
So what can you do? Force your way in?
Your Majesty,
I came here to borrow
the Spirit Gather Bead.
It was an emergency,
so I took a shortcut to get it.
You could’ve asked
His Majesty for the bead.
Why did you have to adopt
such a dirty method?
I can’t help thinking
that you are here up to something.
In my opinion,
you could be working for the Demons.
Your Majesty,
I deserve to be punished
for stealing the bead,
but I did that
for saving someone’s life.
It has nothing to do with the Demons.
Your Highness,
I don’t understand
why you always assume
that the Qingchi Palace and I are
on the Demons’ side.
Do you really wish
that the Qingchi Palace
colludes with the Demons
instead of being of help for
the Heavenly Palace?
You betrayed the Heavenly Palace
and turned to the Qingchi Palace.
How dare you accuse me of wronging you?
Fine.
Then let me ask you.
It’s already been three days.
Where is the Twin Spear?
The others may not know,
but you do, don’t you?
Houchi.
Houchi,
don’t beat around the bush.
If you have anything to say,
just say it.
Not only will I say it,
I’ll also let all the immortals know
what kind of person you really are
as the Heavenly Empress!
Under the North Sea,
the Three-head Fire Dragon
struck a sneak attack
and took away the Twin Spear.
You asked him to do that, didn’t you?
I don’t know what you are talking about!
During the battle in the Demon Region,
the immortals and the demons all saw
that you abducted the Dragon.
How will you explain that?
I did abduct the Three-head Fire Dragon,
because I thought
it’d be easier for the Immortals
to beat the Demons
if the Demons lost one general.
I did nothing wrong!
How dare you mention the battle?
The battle in the Demon Region
killed so many innocent people,
who had nothing to do with it.
As the Heavenly Empress,
you repeatedly caused trouble,
framed the Qingchi Palace,
and sowed discord between
the Immortals and the Demons.
Wu Huan, what are you really up to?
Houchi!
Who do you think you are to lecture me?
How dare you be so rude
in the Heavenly Palace!
Don’t you have any respect
for His Majesty?
So what?
Even if the True Gods
and the Chief God are here,
as long as there’s injustice,
I have nothing to fear to voice.
This is the Heavenly Realm.
In the future, there’ll
be a Human Realm.
All human beings will worship the Gods.
But only the human heart
will last forever.
If the people are righteous,
the whole world will be ruled
by justice.
If the people are selfish,
even if the Ancestral God is here,
you should still wipe out everything.
The Three Realms
will eventually be yours.
The Twin Spear?
You do cherish your life.
I’m afraid you wouldn’t
have used the Twin Spear
if you had another choice.
Now that the truth is revealed,
we’ll leave the Twin Spear
in the Heavenly Palace.
You are the Heavenly Emperor.
How will you deal with this matter?
Houchi,
I will make things right
for the Qingchi Palace.
Your Majesty,
that’s not what happened!
Please let me explain!
Pass my decree.
What the Heavenly Empress did
is against Heaven’s will.
And it’s uncalled for that
she set innocent people up.
As punishment,
she’ll be banished to
the Nether World for 100 years.
Your Majesty!
Go and say goodbye to the children.
And then leave for the
Nether World for self-reflection.
Your Majesty,
how can you just abandon
what we have and…
Say no more.
Father, I have something to report.
I’m tired.
I’ll hear it another day.
Your Majesty,
even though the Qingchi Palace
isn’t working with the Demons,
before Houchi came
to the Heavenly Palace,
she already committed
an appalling crime!
I sent Jingyang to investigate.
Don’t you want to know the fact,
Your Majesty?
Was there a problem when you
got the Ghost Suppressing Tower?
Lord Bi Xi voluntarily
gave me the tower.
There couldn’t be a problem.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Bi Xi,
what happened exactly?
Your Majesty,
someone broke into
the Imperial Mausoleum,
hurt me
and took away the Ghost
Suppressing Tower.
Who did that?
Father,
it was Houchi who hurt Lord Bi Xi
and took away the tower.
Bi Xi,
is Jingyang telling the truth?
His Majesty is here.
Just be honest.
His Majesty will stand up
for you and punish the ones
who make trouble in the Three Realms.
Your Highness,
about the human world thing
I talked about…
Rest assured.
As long as you keep your word,
my mother will surely keep her promise
and protect the human world from
disasters and wars for 1,000 years.
Your Majesty,
Prince Jingyang is telling the truth.
Goddess Houchi of the
Qingchi Palace hurt me
and took away the tower.
Since the tower was taken,
the evil force has burst
out of the Underground Palace
and spread to the human world.
Please help me take back the tower
for the sake of the people’s lives!
Lord Bi Xi,
that day you told me
that you’d use your own spiritual power
to temporarily suppress the evil force
and keep it from the human world.
Yes.
Even though I suppressed it temporarily,
some evil force still spread
to the human world.
That’s enough!
Houchi,
did you really take away the tower?
Yes.
Ridiculous!
The tower is used to protect
the human world.
How could you do
such a ridiculous thing?
Your Majesty,
don’t fall for
Bi Xi’s one side of the story.
I was the one who asked Houchi
to take away the tower.
Qingmu,
it was my idea and I should
take full responsibility.
Don’t try to cover for me.
Goddess Houchi,
you were just brazenly lecturing me.
How ironic!
Houchi,
I don’t care why
you took away the tower.
You must give it back to Bi Xi right now
so that he can put it back
to protect the human world.
Your Majesty,
I know
that I made a serious mistake
taking away the tower,
and I’m willing to take full
responsibility for it.
But please forgive me
that I can’t just return it yet.
Do you even know
what you are talking about?
I do.
Your Majesty,
the tower is not the only thing
that can suppress the evil force.
I’m willing to use my own
spiritual power
to strengthen the evil force seal
in the Underground Palace.
I’ll take 100 years
to purify the evil force that’s
already spread to the human world.
But today I still have
something urgent to take care of.
May I take my leave, please?
When I finish my business,
I will bring back the tower
and accept your punishment.
What a nice speech!
Since you dared take away the tower,
how could you even care
about the safety of the human world?
If His Majesty lets you go,
you’ll be back to the Qingchi Palace
and under the protection of Gu Jun,
then we can do nothing
about you anymore!
Your Majesty,
I’m willing to take a God’s Mark.
If Houchi breaks her word,
I’ll be punished by the Mark
and burnt to ashes!
Qingmu!
Houchi, tell me
why you refuse to return the tower.
What will you use it for?
Your Majesty, I have an old friend,
who failed the tribulation and is dying.
Only the tower can save him.
I know what I’m doing is unforgivable,
but I can’t just watch
my friend die and vanish.
Please grant me this favor!
Houchi,
since you are willing to purify
the evil force in the human world
for 100 years at the cost
of your own cultivation base,
I’ll let you do it.
After you have strengthened
the evil force seal,
you’ll be condemned to punishment.
Thank you, Your Majesty!
Your Majesty!
Please allow me
to purify the evil force
together with Houchi.
Once the crisis is over,
I’ll go back to the North Sea
for self-reflection.
Mother.
Father totally
trivialized Houchi’s crime,
yet he’ll banish you
to the Nether World.
That’s so unfair.
I don’t understand why.
Your father wants
to reopen the God Realm
with the help of Houchi’s status.
Ridiculous!
What wishful thinking!
Mother,
what do you mean
by “Houchi’s status”?
Never mind.
You don’t need to know the details.
Jingyang,
I want you to go
to the human world again.
I need you to release the evil force
from the Underground Palace
before Houchi has a chance
to suppress it.
Mother,
if the evil force is released,
the human world will become a mess!
Houchi must be heavily punished
so that the Qingchi Palace can
finally become the target of criticism.
Would you rather see your
father and I be alienated
and bullied by the Qingchi Palace?
The Qingchi Palace’s existence
is a threat to the Heavenly Palace.
Between the future
of the Heavenly Palace
and the lives of the mortals
in a small town,
which one
is more important?
Understood, Mother.
Houchi,
we’ve collected the three treasures.
You can go back to the Qingchi Palace.
I’ll go to the Underground Palace
to strengthen the seal.
I can’t let the human world
suffer again.
I’ll go with you.
Okay.
You just asked me to go back
to the Qingchi Palace.
What?
Are you jealous of Boxuan?
Yes.
I admit I am.
You are silly.
Houchi,
I really cherish the time
I spend with you.
Me, too.
Qin…
I’ve said
that I’m in a bad mood
and I don’t want to be disturbed!
It’s me!
Father!
Greetings, Father!
How long have you been drinking here?
I’ve been sitting here
since Chang Qin left.
I’m not sure how long it’s been.
It’s been four hours already!
But I feel hurt!
I don’t feel like doing anything
except drinking.
Father,
I can’t live without Chang Qin!
Idiot!
Do you know that the Ghost
Gathering Streamer is missing?
What… What did you say?
Who?
Who dared steal the treasure
of the Demons?
You are in charge of taking care of it!
You’re asking me?!
I failed my duty!
I’m willing to be punished.
According to my informant
in the Demon Region,
Fengran was seen carrying the steamer.
Fengran?
When…
When did she come here?
As a prince of the Demons,
how can you be bothered by love
and use liquor to numb yourself?
No wonder Chang Qin doesn’t love you!
Father,
I’ll assemble the troops in
the Demon Region right now
and get the streamer back!
It’s a draw!
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪