♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 25=
You look so calm and relaxed that
you don’t seem to be worried at all.
Of course! Chenyue is valiant
and skilled.
There won’t be any problem.
But it’s already this time.
They should be back from the raid.
Don’t worry.
Listen! There are footsteps!
-Emissary Lu!
-It must be them!
-Finally you’re back!
Listen to me.
General Feng accidentally
fell into the cliff.
What?!
When we were retreating,
we were surrounded and intercepted
before we got out of the territory
of the Nanzhao army and had an accident.
I intercepted several attacks
but we failed to beat them.
Now give me the order
to take a troop to search and rescue!
No, wait.
What about Long Yan? Didn’t he
protect her?
Long Yan followed her
and jumped off the cliff.
That’s great.
Long Yan is there. Chenyue will be fine.
General Zhao, lead the counterattack
immediately!
We must save Chenyue!
Yes, sir!
Where is this place?
I remember my arm got hurt.
Why is it cured now?
Long Yan?
Why are you…?
Why are we here?
Like you, General, I was forced
by the enemy to jump off the cliff.
But, fortunately, I was lucky to be
hung by a protruding branch.
Are you hungry now?
Have some fruit.
(Luofeng Pavilion)
Lord Qianxun, do you know
why Dragon King hasn’t been back
to his Dragon Pool lately?
He is in the human world.
He went to see Liuying again?
Dragon King loves her.
He would be happy as long as he
can see her one more time.
You used to distain
love affairs.
But now you seem to understand
the Dragon King’s mind.
How are you getting along with
your little Blue Bird?
It’s my business. You don’t need to
worry about it.
Dragon King is carried away by love.
You’d better not follow his steps.
I’m afraid it’s difficult for that
lazy little Blue Bird
to get into immortality.
So you shouldn’t take her too seriously.
Why not?
So what if Qingqing fails
to become immortal?
You think only human and demon
are different?
Immortal and demon can’t have
a good end either.
You and I are immortals
with eternal lives.
But bird demon can only live for
500 or 600 years.
How can you be together forever?
To avoid the pain of separation
in the future,
I advise you to
not take it seriously.
Not take it seriously?
You have written so many fates.
The love stories you wrote were all
not serious?
I’m just being nice and reminding you.
Forget what I said.
See you.
It’s more important to help her through
the tribulation and become immortal
in the future.
The Meteor Mark is no big deal.
I don’t think it’s ugly.
Still can’t use it.
General.
Just sit.
Yes.
The commander is missing during the
war between two armies.
It will affect the morale of the army.
I wonder if Uncle Zhao and Zheng…
General, don’t worry.
Although we have fallen off the cliff,
our previous sneak attack plan
has been successful.
The enemy’s provisions have been
destroyed
and the plants have been poisoned.
I believe our soldiers will
be able to drive the Nanzhao Army
away from the border.
Uncle Zhao is experienced.
I was overthinking it.
General,
the one who forced you off the cliff
with sword was one of our soldiers.
Did someone plot to kill you?
I have thought about it.
But what’s the motive
of the person behind?
At the beginning, Mr. Guo
paid assassins to come to my place
to cause trouble,
then someone stole the Fengs’
Commanding Badge to frame me,
and then the soldier on the cliff.
I think there is some kind of
connection between these things.
And on the day we set off,
what on earth did Jin want to tell me?
I think that is also related
to this thing.
But now
it’s not my biggest concern.
What I’m most worried about
is how we should
climb up this high cliff.
Chenyue!
I clearly remember that
you were far away from the cliff.
Did you jump off to save me?
It’s my duty to protect General.
Sorry.
I was lost in thought
and took you for my sister.
So,
you have a sister?
Yes.
She is at the same age as you.
It’s so good to have a brother like you.
I used to have a brother
who always protected me as well.
I’m Qingqing’s brother.
So, of course I’m also your brother.
Then,
I can see you anytime?
I used to have a brother
who always protected me as well.
I’m always by your side.
We’ll live and die together.
OK!
We’ll definitely win!
What?!
Why is this mark still here?
Are the pains I suffered
in vain?
I can do peach blossom makeup
for you every day,
alright?
Calm down!
It’s not the first time he fools you!
Last time, when he saw the mark,
he turned around and left right away.
Actually,
this Meteor Mark
is pretty special.
Special?
That also means it’s ugly!
You have pretty face. You don’t
understand my trouble.
But, you really look so pretty.
Listen,
do not only know to play.
Remember to practice everyday
to become immortal soon, you know?
I never said I wanted to
become immortal.
If you don’t,
how would you be with me forever?
Take this.
(Heavenly Secret Guidebook)
You’re not enlightened.
This is the Secret Guidebook
for your practice.
You must practice diligently
according to it.
Don’t be lazy.
There are so many words!
I’ll check on your practice next time
I come.
If you slack off,
I will punish you.
Why do you just leave again?
Stay with you?
If I became an immortal,
why should I still be your maid?
What’s the point of it?
I won’t!
(Heavenly Secret Guidebook)
Xiyun!
Haven’t you come to Wind City long ago?
Why did you come to see me only now?
Do you not love me anymore?
How could I not?
You may leave first.
Let me tell you a piece of good news.
Feng Chenyue fell off the cliff
and disappeared.
Is she dead?
I hope so.
Can you do me a favor?
I want you to go to convince the King
to send people to investigate the
disappearance of Feng Chenyue.
Why?
Why?!
Don’t you really know why?
Xiyun, it hurts!
How did your brother’s eye get blind?
Don’t you want to revenge me?
If you don’t,
my love for you is in vain.
But…
But what?
No more talks.
Not only do I want her dead,
I also want her to
be charged with treason.
That would be even better if I could
bury her with my own hands.
Chenyue,
where are you?
Let’s split up
and see if there’s a way up.
We’ll meet back at the cave at noon.
General, be careful.
There are no trees on this cliff
except weeds.
Like you, General, I was forced
by the enemy to jump off the cliff.
But, fortunately, I was lucky to be
hung by a protruding branch.
When we sneaked up on Dongluo Army,
how come none of the arrows
flying towards me hit me?
The Dragon King in my dream
must be you, right?
Why don’t you admit it?
Look!
Are you making fun of me?
What are these? Why armors?
They are so heavy!
You go fight a war and let me
pretend to be General and ride
a horse there?
Do you want to tire me out?
Well, Qingqing…
It’s fine.
Qingqing, we need to thank you
this time.
We can’t let the enemy
know Chenyue’s disappearance.
Yes.
If they knew General
was in their territory,
it would be dangerous.
Don’t worry.
Chenyue will be fine.
I hope so.
So,
we have to recapture this place
as soon as possible.
Now Nanzhao has lost all its provisions,
the morale is destroyed.
I heard that
they have been hunting for food
in the mountains for days.
The beasts are all eaten up.
Now there are only some fish and
shrimps left.
They can’t hang in there for long.
Lay a fish net in the upper stream.
I want them
not even able to have fish and shrimps.
Give my order.
All get ready to attack at any time.
Yes, sir.
General! Go now!
Gao Yang!
49 days have finally passed.
General.
You are still up so late.
I dreamed of my soldiers.
Are you alright?
It’s so dark here.
So many fireflies!
As long as you fly a firefly,
it will come to me
and lead me to you.
Then,
I can see you anytime?
So beautiful!
General, do you know how long can
they live?
Seems to be only seven days.
Although their lives are short,
they still live so bright and shiny
in this short period of time.
It’s a meaningful life.
Just like our fallen brothers.
They also shined bright
in their own lives.
They had no regret
even if they died.
♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if the moon shone for you♪
♪Bright or dim♪
♪Fate is like a rain of flowers♪
♪Withering in the sentimental world♪
You know what?
♪In a flash I picked your teardrop♪
I think I experienced
this scene once before.
♪Does my heart ripple with memories♪
♪Only to remember you♪
Maybe in your dream.
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
Then why
so many fireflies suddenly came?
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
I don’t know why.
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
Emissary Lu! Emissary Lu!
Emissary Lu,
His Majesty sent an envoy here!
It’s Mr. Guo!
I’m afraid Mr. Guo is coming
with a bad intention.
-Mr. Guo.
Gentlemen, please excuse me.
Mr. Guo, please.
Please have some tea.
Where is General Feng?
I’m here on His Majesty’s order.
I need to see General Feng.
General Feng fell off a cliff
in enemy’s territory.
She is now missing.
We’re doing our best to find her.
Missing?
It’s just like the rumors.
How could she, the General Feng,
disappear?
Could it be that she ran away
from the battlefield?
-How could our general run away?
-You…
When the enemy comes,
our general will never run
even if all your family have fled away!
You’ve got a lot of nerve!
How dare you!
Mr. Guo, please tell His Majesty for us
that General will never run away.
You know what?
I need to
see her if she is alive
or her body if she dies.
Now I can’t see neither her
nor her body.
If she didn’t surrender,
then she must have escaped!
I’ll go back to report to His Majesty
right away!
Mr. Guo!
Our general is not that kind of person!
You… How dare you…!
I dare!
Mr. Guo has come a long way here.
He needs enough rest.
We need to do our best to find
General Feng first.
Before that,
if Mr. Guo wakes up again,
serve him again in Qingqing’s way.
Emissary Lu,
this is not good.
That will leave a proof.
It will bring us troubles.
Then, what to do?
He will always wake up.
Wait.
This is my ancestral
Seven Days Forgetting Medicine.
He won’t remember anything
after he wakes up.
This is a good idea!
Now his problem is settled.
And Nanzhao
is also cornered by us.
Now my only worry is…
It’s that
it’s not sure
if Chenyue is alive or not.
That’s it.
Give my order to attack immediately
and find back General Feng!
Yes, sir!
I just found two old vine strips here,
which we can use to climb up.
I also checked around here.
Why didn’t I find them?
This place is not easy to find.
Maybe you missed them.
I think so.
You must be him.
-Chenyue!
-General!
Great! It’s really you!
Are you alright?
Don’t worry.
I can’t be better.
I told you.
Our General is blessed by the God
of Heaven,
and can always turn ill luck into good.
Thanks to Long Yan this time.
You escaped from death in this war
and won a great victory.
I will never let you be in
danger again.
I will petition His Majesty
to summon you back to Wind City
right away.
Nanzhao has retreated?
Yes!
We burnt their provisions.
Then they have no other choices
but only to retreat!
We owe it to you!
Thanks!
Long Yan.
Long Yan?
He is there.
Come on!
Let’s make a toast to General together!
Congratulations, General! May the
good luck always be with you!
Nanzhao’s envoy has come
to make peace.
Let’s drink as much as we want
at tonight’s celebration!
Feng Chenyue defeated Nanzhao Army.
How am I going to frame her?
I won’t even believe it myself
if I do that.
Mr. Guo.
This is so weird.
How did I fall into a coma last night?
Such a thing never happened before.
Mr. Guo, you don’t know it.
The heavy dampness in the South
is easy to make people drowsy and tired.
But drinking can help you
relieve fatigue.
Mr. Guo, please drink up.
Cheers.
-Come on.
-Come on. Cheers.
-General.
Did you see Long Yan?
-No.
I will remember you.
Wherever you are,
I can always find you.
Yuchi, don’t leave me.
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪