♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 26=
Yuchi, don’t leave me.
After the three tribulations,
I won’t give you to anyone.
How is your practice going?
What practice?
Last time I gave you the
Heavenly Secret Guidebook
for practicing to become immortal.
Oh, I remember…
You didn’t even take it seriously!
Why so angry?
Has anyone ever taught you
how to smile?
Just like me.
Curl up the corners of your mouth
like a gold ingot.
That’s the best smile.
You should practice diligently.
Don’t play with these jewelries
all day long.
They can cover my Meteor Mark.
I don’t want you to see it and
dislike me because of it.
You think it’s ugly because you think
I mind it?
You…
So what?
It’s not on your forehead.
Of course you don’t mind it.
And,
you don’t care about if I mind that
you mind it.
You know how to help me get rid
of the Meteor Mark.
I just want a string of
your Fleeting Pipa
to remove the mark on my face…
No, no. Remove the Meteor Mark
on my soul.
It will not
scare you away again.
Maybe
after you get rid of the mark,
you will study the Guidebook seriously
and try to become immortal.
Lord,
I’m really studying the book today.
But I just can’t understand it.
There are so many
drawings on this book.
What do they mean?
You scolded me.
But look at you. The sun is in
the middle of the sky,
but you’re still sleeping.
Xue Qianxun! Get up!
Lord?
Lord! Lord!
He really pulled out the string?
Yes. But he failed.
That’s great.
Great?!
Explain it to me now.
Pulling out the string is equivalent to
pulling out his tendons!
If the string is drawn out completely,
it will break all his meridians.
He won’t die since he failed to do it.
He will recover after recuperation.
Die?
How could it be like this?
It’s all my fault!
I shouldn’t have told him about it!
Immortal of Fate,
please! Please help me!
How can I make him feel better?
Or, is there any medicine that
can make him less painful?
There is.
But…
What?
You know the rules here.
I can open the door for you
if you want to borrow books to read.
But if you want to take medicine
and treasures away of my place,
you need to pay a price. You…
I have my feather.
Your feather?
Blue Bird’s feather
is beautiful and gorgeous
like Dragon Scales.
And it’s hard to regenerate.
It is quite rare.
But I heard that
you have to endure a sharp pain
when pulling out the feather.
It’s just like pulling out the tendons.
Look at your thin body.
I think you’d better give up.
Immortal.
Your wound…
The precious feather of the Blue Bird
really lives up to its fame.
I didn’t expect you to
really do this for him.
You did pull it out yourself.
This is Three Pearl Leaf Tea
made by God Gou Mang
with leaves like pearls.
It can revive everything
and has a miraculous effect on
meridian injuries.
Remember to let him drink it regularly.
But,
don’t tell anyone
it’s exchanged with me,
or they will all come to me.
I don’t have that much of it.
I got it.
My Lord, have some tea.
Do you feel better?
My Lord,
you suddenly fell into a coma yesterday.
Immortal Taiyi said it might be injury
on your soul.
We must find out the cause,
otherwise…
I’m fine now.
You may leave.
Yes, My Lord.
Why are you pulling a long face?
Sorry, My Lord.
It’s all my fault for talking nonsense
and causing you to pull out the string.
I didn’t know it would hurt your soul
and let you suffer from the pain.
You can punish me or scold me.
Or I can be your maid again.
I can also stop eating and singing.
Don’t cry.
I did it of my own will.
How could I punish you?
Why are you so nice to me?
Now you still ask me why?
It can’t
have no reason…
Because…
Because I like you.
You really like me?
You’re not making fun of me?
It’s always the real one.
I never made fun of you.
Why are you crying again?
I’m angry with myself.
I’m so stupid and dumb.
You’re always so nice to me,
but I keep doubting you
and ignoring you.
A worthless bird like me is only worthy
of someone like you in my dreams.
No.
What’s wrong?
I… I…
My eyes are swollen from crying.
They don’t look good.
Besides, I didn’t say I like you.
(General’s Mansion)
General, as the old saying goes,
if he doesn’t take the initiative,
you can take it first.
What old saying is it?
Qingqing?
Qingqing!
General, Qingqing is not here.
Then you come to help me.
Bring me the towel on the table.
Yes.
My hands have just applied cream.
It’s not convenient to do it.
Since she is not here, sorry for
bothering you to help me.
Yes, General.
♪Pure white sunshine♪
♪Clouds hide the moss♪
♪There comes the deer’s call♪
♪Run slowly with soft footsteps♪
♪Wind blows the skirt’s hemline♪
♪You’re in the shadow of the tree♪
♪If I don’t come along♪
Qingqing said I was not like a girl
because I only use swords.
So she tries hard to keep my feet
in good condition.
Look at my feet.
Do they look like a girl’s feet?
♪The heart beats fast and deafening♪
♪Wait until the red sunset♪
The feet are a girl’s privacy.
I shouldn’t touch your feet.
But you have already touched them.
Only you and Qingqing
have ever touched my feet in this world.
Keep on drying them.
♪Like a thick wine flows into the sea♪
Yes, General.
♪And into your heart♪
♪The leaves rustling not too loud♪
♪The heart beats fast and deafening♪
♪Wait until the red sunset♪
♪Embraces the delicate breeze♪
♪Thousands kinds of beautiful flowers♪
♪Are not as good as your grace♪
It’s alright now.
After our victory,
many soldiers took leave to return
to their hometown to get married.
Don’t you want to go back to
your hometown?
I only want to protect General.
♪And into your heart♪
Don’t marry either?
I just want to protect General.
Good.
♪Your heart♪
Star Halo! It’s a good sign!
Sit here. Let’s watch it together.
Why don’t you admit that you’re the
Dragon King?
Could it be that
you have something to hide?
This Star Halo
is just the same as the one
we watched together before.
I’ve never seen Star Halo before.
General, you must have misremembered.
Why do I remember it was you?
It’s cold.
I’ll go get you a coat.
Wait!
Why do you always change the topic
when I mention the past?
What do you mean?
I don’t mean anything.
My duty
is to protect General.
General!
Come here.
I got information of what
happened in Tiger’s Howl Valley seven
years ago you asked me to investigate.
(Seven years ago
in Tiger’s Howl Valley…)
There is really something wrong.
Seven years ago,
who on earth killed Jin’s father?
Feng Army never sent anyone
to Tiger’s Howl Valley.
The smell of the pills
given by His Highness
is exactly the same as the smell
I smelled
when I first met him and fainted.
What’s this smell?
It smells good.
I feel dizzy…
Mandrake?
You’re not sick.
You’re poisoned by Mandrake.
Don’t take it again.
It can only temporarily
relieve your pain,
but later it will make you suffer more.
All you see it hatred.
(Feng)
Father!
You must remember the hatred.
(Dongluo Hall)
Say it again.
Feng Chenyue
came back unharmed.
You may leave now.
(Dongluo Hall)
Came back unharmed.
Feng Chenyue…
Good…
She came back unharmed.
Feng Chenyue.
How come you just can’t die?
Your Highness.
What’s the matter?
I heard Your Highness is leaving
Wind City.
I wonder if I can get more…
Life-saving Pills?
Yes.
You know it’s hard to make this pill.
Only one can be made in a month.
It’s impossible for me to bring a lot.
If you’re loyal to me,
I will send people to deliver it to you
when the moon is full.
Leave now.
I’ll never dare to betray you.
Wait!
Feng Chenyue.
Feng Chenyue didn’t die,
but now she must be weak.
Yes.
Now you lead other guards
to go assassinate her.
Maybe there’s still a chance.
But, Your Highness,
more people will only attract
more Feng Army soldiers.
Please let me go alone.
You can do it alone?
Your Highness, don’t you remember?
Now I’m Feng Chenyue’s friend.
Attack from a friend
is the hardest to avoid.
Yes.
Don’t waste any time. Go now.
But, I still have one request.
Say it.
I don’t know if I can
come back after this assassination.
I hope I can have a drink
with Your Highness
to thank you for your kindness
these years.
Sure.
Go now.
Excuse me for my leave.
Go.
Feng Chenyue.
I knew you’d came.
Let’s do it.
Han Xiyun sent you to kill me, right?
When did you become his assassin?
Seven years ago,
I became his secret guard.
Han Xiyun is known for his cruelty
in the battlefield,
killing people, even babies.
But you’ve been under his command
for even years.
Why?!
Stop asking questions.
Just kill me.
You came to me
just to let me kill you?
Yes.
No more talks.
Just do it.
Why are you seeking death?
I’ve worked for Han Xiyun for years
and carried countless guilts.
I would like to die
by your hand.
Alright.
Then I’ll kill you now.
It’s too dark and I missed the point.
Do you want me to kill you again?
Jin? Jin!
Can you help her?
I can try.
But no one should be by my side.
Alright.
I’m afraid you’re too silly
to figure it out.
You’re the silly one!
General.
I heard the sound of fighting.
Where is the assassin?
Jin got poisoned.
Long Yan is helping her.
Let me have a check.
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪