[English subtitles are available]
Stop touching it.
My mouth is numbed and I
think my voice has changed, too.
I can't even speak properly.
It's not too serious.
It won't stay like this, right?
Of course not. The braces
will make your teeth look good.
I'll make you some
porridge when we get home.
Aren't you returning to Henggang?
What's the hurry?
I'll stay until you put on your braces.
I've already had my two teeth extracted.
So don't worry about me.
Just go home.
I'm heading back to the cafe.
My part-time worker is on leave today.
So the shop is short of staff.
That little cafe of yours
isn't making money.
Why don't you just close it down?
Mother, you always tend to
talk about money.
That's my dream,
okay?
I see.
You're a university graduate.
And all you want is to be
a librarian or cafe owner.
Just look at your classmates.
They're either bankers or
working at Fortune 500 companies.
And you?
I have a secure job.
What?
The young won't care about that.
You're the odd one out.
You have no ambition and are
still unattached until now.
Can't you just give me a break?
Just go home.
I really have to go now, see you.
-I'm in a rush.
-You haven't eaten yet.
Just go home.
Don't skip your meal.
[Sweet Teeth]
[Episode 2]
-Hello.
[-Zeng Li.]
[Where are you?]
I'm at my shop.
[Thank god, I need
a favour from you.]
-What's wrong?
[-I woke up late.]
[I'm late for my lecture.]
[Can you help me mark my attendance?]
But we don't look alike.
[No worries.]
[Professor Wang doesn't recognise me.]
You'll be in trouble
if I'm exposed.
[No one can help me except you.]
[Please.]
[I'll really be in trouble]
[if I'm absent again.]
It's been a long time since I graduated.
Excuse me, you need
to focus on the lecture.
Okay.
Work hard.
And keep it up.
[The students now have changed.]
[No one is reading a magazine.]
What?
It's him?
[Why it's Au Jing Chu?]
[I'm in trouble.]
Silence.
Professor Wang is admitted to
the hospital due to heart disease.
I'll replace him for now
until your final term exam.
[Don't tell me Professor Wang
is actually Mr. Wang.]
We're going to have a roll call.
-Wang Rui Kai.
-Here.
-Zhang De Quan.
-What's wrong with you?
This is Mr. Ai's lecture, okay?
-Chen Rui Xin.
-I bet you've never attended his lecture.
How I wish I could attend his lectures.
And I really hate this.
You're so lucky.
His lecture is really tough.
Last term, half of the students
failed the prosthodontics exam.
-That's scary.
-Indeed.
-Keep your voice down, okay?
-Just look at her.
She was reading a magazine earlier.
Now she doesn't even dare utter a word.
[-I'm finished.]
-Lei Xin Lin.
[-Ai Jing Chu knows Dou Dou.]
-Here.
[What should I do?]
-Hao Ru.
-Here.
Dou Dou.
Help me.
Here!
Please stand on your feet.
Remove your hood.
Don't you know the rules?
Do it now.
And your cap.
I think I've come to the wrong place.
I'm so sorry.
Just carry on.
Dou Dou.
[-What did he just call me?]
-You can't seem to speak properly.
You've just extracted your teeth?
[He's having face blindness again.]
Really?
I'm sure my dentist
-isn't good enough.
-[Really?]
[Say it again.]
Maybe.
So you should focus in class
and be a good dentist in the future.
[What does he want?]
[He knows I'm not Dou Dou.]
[I know you're not her.]
Return to your seat.
[There's no escape now.]
[You think you can just leave?]
Are you just going to stand here?
Let's continue the roll call.
When the maxillofacial is damaged,
[Zhengxin Building]
there will be changes
in the oral cavity.
-When the resonant cavity is damaged,
[-The time]
[seems to last forever.]
the voice will become unclear
and even incomprehensible.
[The effects of maxillofacial defects]
The patient will suffer
tremendously mentally.
[You're making me feel the same.]
Excuse me, I want to go out.
For patients with minor cleft lip,
we'll usually use segmented or secondary,
or even alginate impression.
This is specially for those
having problem opening their mouth.
Dou Dou.
Are you leaving now?
Nature's call.
No one can leave my class now
no matter what.
Return to your seat.
[Ai Jing Chu.]
[Are you a devil?]
Dou Dou.
Please take your notes.
I'll check on you after class.
Let's continue.
-The preparation of the mould
[-How do I take notes]
[-with just a magazine?]
-and choosing the mould.
The upper jaw impression tray should be
about 3 mm wider than
the upper alveolar ridge.
[-You two are so kind to me.]
-The height of the surrounding edge
should have a distance
of about 2 mm from
the mucosal fold.
[Upper jaw?]
[Alveolar ridge?]
[Mucosal fold? What are all these?]
[I'm almost 30,]
[why should I have to suffer this?]
Bye.
You have to take down the notes, hurry up.
I'll be done in no time.
Just leave without me.
I'm done.
You may leave.
You knew I'm not Dou Dou.
Why did you ask me to stay back?
You're not her.
Why are you here?
You should know this.
Isn't it a norm to help others
mark their attendance?
I've never done this when I was a student.
You think you're helping her
but it's the opposite.
It's not as serious as you said, right?
A bad doctor
is a bane to the patients.
Fine.
It was my fault.
Give her the notes for self-study.
She's be tested next time.
Sure but you'll have to
tell that to her personally.
-Why?
[-You knowingly asked me that.]
Don't you think that's your duty?
Have you taken your medicine?
What?
You're mocking me!
Take one metronidazole tablet
after a dental extraction
then one erythromycin
ethylsuccinate tablet after a meal.
Thrice per day and take
them both after a meal.
Talk less and eat something light.
I...
[Alarm clock]
[The History of Chinese Stomatology]
[Library Card, Donghu University]
[Category: Oral cavity; Borrower: Zeng Li]
Zeng Li?
The patient who marked
attendance for Dou Dou?
Why did she read a book about oral cavity?
[Library Card, Donghu University]
[Category: Literature; Borrower: Zeng Li]
She even read this before?
[A Brief History of
Home Video Game Consoles]
[Zeng Li]
And this, too.
Did she just borrow them for fun?
[This is truly a friendly reception.]
[L1 Agricultural Science]
[L2 Industrial Technology]
[L3 Transportation; L4 Aerospace]
You read the group chat?
The team building will be held
at the hot spring in Tongshan.
This is third time
within this year, right?
I think you got it wrongly.
I remember we only had it twice.
The last time
was on the 12th of December.
Does it matter?
It was just a difference of one day.
I still think we had it thrice.
Zeng Li.
Look.
He's just dashing whatever he wears.
He's just ordinary to me
after seeing him often.
You're a lucky girl.
I only met him 2-3 times.
-Give me your phone.
-Why?
Your Leica camera is
good in taking pictures.
I'll post it online later.
Bad idea.
I don't want a stranger's
picture in my phone.
Come on.
Just look at his nose.
It's beautiful.
His mouth is so sexy.
And his hands.
[What am I staring at him?]
So pretty.
-Just like the characters in comics.
-Idiot.
-He's tall and handsome.
-Give it back to me.
Stop bothering me.
He's so handsome.
Xiao Wu, you have a parcel.
She gave me a scare.
Are you done?
Don't delete them, I'll be right back.
[Don't come near me.]
[Please, no.]
Excuse me.
[Please don't ask me anything.]
Stop looking at me.
Zeng Li?
I'm not her.
Do you have any books about
the Alexander Discipline?
I think we have.
You can search for it via our app.
I've checked and it's available.
However, it doesn't have a shelf number.
Let me help you search for it.
It's weird.
I didn't do this. It was my colleague.
Let me explain.
She took your pictures with my phone
because it has a Leica camera.
Anyway, it wasn't me.
It's okay.
You'll have dental pain
if you talk too much.
Aren't you helping me find the book?
[The Alexander Discipline]
I've found it.
You can find it on A03.
Thanks.
These are the snacks recommended
by an Internet celebrity.
Spicy beef.
And glutinous rice cakes.
I would have eaten it now
if it wasn't for my dental extraction.
No, you don't.
Why?
This, this and this.
They're too spicy for you.
You two know each other?
Not that, too.
It's too hard for you.
So what can I eat, Mr. Ai?
This one.
Don't you think you're making a big fuss?
-Who was that?
-What's going on?
-Does it hurt?
-We're sorry.
It hurts!
You have inflamed gums.
If you don't choose
what you eat carefully,
you can forget about
putting on your braces.
You might as well do a gum surgery.
I can eat.
Take your medicine promptly.
Only plain food.
If it hurts too much,
apply ice to it.
Let me buy you an ice pack.
Hold on.
Save the hassle, I can take it.
[The Alexander Discipline]
Looks like you haven't
borrowed this before.
[Library Card, Donghu University]
What do you mean?
He smiled at you.
Wu Wan Xia.
Please.
Delete the pictures
after you've posted them.
Your phone is really good, love and peace.
I've bought you bubble tea, Mr. Ai.
Sorry, I don't usually drink this.
I bought it specially
for you. Just take it.
Hope you enjoy it.
You can have it
so long as you remember
to brush your teeth.
Here's for you.
For me?
You can use it as an ice pack.
Can I drink it?
Sure.
But you can't use it as
an ice pack after that.
Your choice.
Wait.
I would have to go into
a long queue to get this.
Would he do that for me?
He must have picked it up
from somewhere else.
Did you say something?
This is picked up from somewhere else. Oh!
Sorry.
It hurts!
This sunscreen
is refreshing and not sticky.
[Ma Yi Yi]
It's good for sun protection.
Its SPF comes with PA+++.
It's SPF 50.
It lets you enjoy the beach
without worries.
I can't travel without it.
Let's check out the bullet screen.
Why are you promoting the
sunscreen yet you're tanned?
Because I would be even tanner
without this.
My link is at the
bottom left of the screen.
Go get it.
You were great, Ms. Yi Yi.
Here your phone.
-Thanks.
-You're welcome.
[Jike Gaming]
Hurry up!
You're too slow!
What a coincidence, Ma Yi Yi.
Where's Zhang Teng?
Well...
Yi Yi?
Aren't you going on a business trip?
Hang on.
Why are you here?
We bought this wristband together.
I want an explanation.
Wait.
No excuse.
Why did you lie to me?
Are you seeing someone else?
No.
Then why are you hiding from me?
It's just your imagination.
Give me your phone.
Wait.
This isn't nice.
I want my privacy.
The boyfriend of a girl from my cafe
hits the bull's-eye.
There are secrets in a phone.
Fine.
So you've been hanging out with your pals
for over a week?
Why have you been avoiding me?
I just feel exhausted.
I need a break.
But we just get together not too long ago.
Yes.
I think you've changed
since we get together.
-What do you mean?
-You used to be cool towards me.
You merely replied me with an
emoji when I texted you on WeChat.
[Zhang Teng: Had your meal?]
[Zhang Teng: What's up, dear.]
[Zhang Teng: Finished your work?]
Even worse, you could totally ignore me.
[Zhang Teng: Why are
you ignoring me? Busy?]
How I wished to get
a better response from you.
So I was on fire.
Then what?
Then we finally get together.
And you've changed.
Now whenever I text you,
you tend to give me multiple replies.
[Ma Yi Yi: Why are you ignoring me?]
You'll even send me several types of emoji
[Ma Yi Yi: What's up.]
[Ma Yi Yi: How about
having dinner together?]
just to check up on me.
[Ma Yi Yi: Why are you silent?]
And you do it in various fanciful ways.
So you mean
I'm too clingy.
You're tired with me.
You can say that.
Fine.
I'll change.
I'll give you more space.
Are you happy now?
It's actually my problem, Yi Yi.
I shouldn't have
got together so soon.
What do you want then?
I don't understand.
Don't you think it's best
to be ambiguous in a relationship?
In fact, I really
enjoyed the time when I was
smitten with you.
Hello, dear. What are you reading?
-It's a story between two lovers.
-Next order.
It's so romantic.
She likes your novel.
The male character is simply my dream guy.
How I wish you were half as good as him.
The story isn't true.
They always dream of
falling in love with men.
-You should read this.
-Come on.
Have you done this before?
Enjoy your meal.
-Thanks.
Let's begin.
How's your drink?
Your debut novel is a success.
You should let your mother know
lest she thinks you're unambitious.
Just forget it. I've wrote it for fun.
I think I'll forever
do nothing more than this.
If she knows about this,
she'll want me
to be a famous writer.
Then I'll have sleepless nights.
-Are you okay?
-It was just a breakup.
It's been hours already.
Get over it, okay?
I'm just stunned.
-What actually happened?
-He said...
It was my fault, not yours!
I just wanted to take a break
from a relationship.
It's not wrong to be clingy.
I just lost my feelings for you.
Don't cry.
Hello...
The girls are a handful.
I could neither be
truthful nor avoid them.
Deng Hao Ran.
Do you also think
that the best part of a relationship
is when you're smitten with someone?
Brilliant.
Whose wise words are those?
I couldn’t think of such words.
I was right about Deng Hao Ran
and Zhang Teng being alike.
-I'll help you teach him a lesson.
-He deserves it.
-Take that!
-I'm your older brother.
Mind your manners.
But my mother has divorced your dad.
Hang on.
What if I treat you to a meal?
My dear brother.
Good girl.
Let's go.
Let's celebrate Ma Yi Yi's
breakup with Zhang Teng.
What do you prefer?
Hot pot or Thai food?
Sorry.
I'm trying to lose weight.
Really?
You have your chance.
I'll go with my buddies then.
-Go for it.
-Excuse me.
I'm trying to lose weight
but not on a diet.
Let's check it out.
Let's try this new vegan restaurant.
It's got two Michelin stars.
I can't wait to go.
Come on.
You all are just good for nothing.
Mr. Deng.
Your mobile app is making a good profit.
How could you not treat us to a meal?
You're so stingy.
Tissue paper.
You're not asking me
to treat you to a meal.
You've been actually
asking me to do so weekly.
Enough said, let's go.
-Let's go!
-Thanks!
Thanks, boss.
Let's go get changed.
-Hurry up!
-Dou Dou!
We're going for a meal.
Just take it from here.
[Convenience Store]
[Hot Pot]
I wonder why the guys we've met are alike.
We have Deng Hao Ran, Zhang Teng
-and...
-And Ai Jing Chu.
Don't cry, you'll be fine.
Can I drink this?
Sure.
But you can't use it as
an ice pack after that.
Zeng Li.
What's with you?
I don't think Ai Jing Chu is a bad guy.
He really cares for
his students and patients.
I think he's a responsible person.
Many guys like this are
successful in their career.
How do we make ourselves look good
without money?
Thanks.
You haven't seen him for two days.
You miss him already?
Beware lest you end up
following Dou Dou's footsteps.
You should really explore the
career as a writer, Zeng Li.
Why are some of us
lost in our life?
We tend to meet men
who are either playboys or two-timers.
Are you girls criticising the
men while I was away just now?
Where's my soup?
Why's there nothing left?
I should ask you to leave.
Then I'll go have my meal
at a cheap BBQ restaurant.
We have good intentions. Don't you get it?
A playful and selfish man like you
should opt for vegan food instead of meat.
It'll detox your body.
-I could do a good deed, too.
-Thanks.
You're welcome.
I want you to explain to
me with your experiences.
Why when a woman gets older,
she tends to meet disloyal men?
Really?
You tend to meet such men, right?
What are you doing?
I'm so sorry.
I wanted to kick him.
I got the wrong person.
I'm so sorry.
It should be you.
Take that!
Serve you right.
Aren't there many young
interns at your hospital?
Find me and Zeng Li
a good man.
Of course, you should keep one
for yourself if you find any.
You two can have them all.
It's a hassle to get into a relationship.
I might as well focus on
my job or write a thesis.
-Don't you think so?
-No.
I agree.
Wu Ying is right.
You either face the reality
and not get into a relationship
or stop complaining and enjoy it.
I'm not in for a ever-lasting love
but just to experience it.
Nice.
I organised a gathering a while ago.
A guy fancied about a girl
and he went all out for her.
However, she rejected him.
He complained to me
that many girls play hard to get nowadays.
So,
we don't always get what we wish.
And we tend to blame
the other person for that.
Oh my.
I think he's got a point.
I feel the same, too.
-But I don't agree.
-So be it.
Now we have three votes against one.
What you said isn't valid.
Let's drink to it.
Fine, as you said so.
-Here.
-Serve you right.
You deserve it.
-Bless you.
What has it got to me with me?
Bless you, Deng Hao Ran.
-Deng Hao Ran.
-Hey...
-It's refilled.
-You're crazy, too.
-Let's begin.
-Deng Hao Ran.
He's so funny.
In repentance,
there is salvation.
It's so fun.
-We're cleansing your soul.
-This is Songkran.
It's raining!
Get some more water!
[Outpatient]
Mr. Ai.
Where's Zhou Wen?
She has taken a leave to attend
to personal matters.
So you're working alone today?
Yes. What's wrong with that?
Zhou Wen told me that it's
a hassle to install braces.
The glue tends to dry quickly.
It requires two persons to do it.
I can manage by myself.
We'll begin now.
Open your mouth.
You may get the glue on your mouth
if you remain like this.
Try to relax.
I can't see your
teeth if you do this.
How about a song to
make yourself relax?
Any preference?
I like Karen Mok's song.
I don't have it.
How about Jay Chou?
No.
Don't you use NetEase Music?
What's that?
Just forget it.
Any song will do.
Sure.
Mr. Ai.
What song is that?
It's the theme song of an anime.
How about this.
I'll tell you the story about this anime
while I install the braces.
Open your mouth.
The story is set in the year 2046.
In order to defend
against malevolent aliens,
the Space Defence Force
is recruiting everywhere.
Mikako, the heroine is enlisted.
A training through the universe begins.
Xiao Sheng, the hero who's
been having a crush on her,
always receives her greetings.
As they get further apart from each other,
it takes a longer time
to send messages.
Sometimes, it even takes up to two years.
Eight years later,
Xiao Sheng, who has
undying love for Mikako,
has finally joined the
Space Defence Force, too.
He suddenly gets the news
that eight years ago,
the fleet she belongs to
is annihilated.
Now Xiao Sheng suddenly
receives a message.
It was sent by Mikako eight years ago.
And she said.
Hello, Xiao Sheng. I know you're 24.
I'm Mikako and I'm 15.
In fact,
I've always had feelings for you.
It's done.
Let's take a break.
It was fast.
Is the story boring?
No.
It's quite a beautiful story.
It's raining.
Do you have an umbrella?
No.
Mr. Ai.
Are you going to lend me an umbrella?
I don't have it with me.
Let me drive you home.
It's okay.
Isn't it out of your way?
Are you really going to send me home?
It's okay.
You think too much.
It's just out of my way.
By the way, what's NetEase Music?
Give me your phone.
Let me install it for you.
It's done.
[Outpatient Exit]
Thanks.
Bye, Mr. Ai.
Hey...
[Touch the star]
[Xiao Sheng hears a message tone.]
[It's a message Mikako sent years ago.]
[And she said.]
[Hello, Xiao Sheng. I know you're 24.]
[I'm Mikako and I'm 15.]
[In fact,]
[I've always had feelings for you.]
[Try only going for soft food.]
[Avoid having hot and
cold stuff concurrently.]
[Brush your teeth properly.]
[Your braces will cause soreness]
[for a couple of days.]
[It may]
[affect your speech.]
[There will be increase of saliva.]
[All these are normal.]
[Contact me if there's a serious
scratch on the oral mucosa.]
[Do also contact me if your braces]
[aren't secure, have
fallen off or are loosen.]
[Zhou Wen usually
sends the doctor's orders]
[so I overlooked it earlier.]
[By the way,]
[I'm Ai Jing Chu.]