fTiming and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ You're by my side, illuminating a beam of light for me ♫
♫ Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet ♫
♫ Your breath brushes up against my cheek ♫
♫ With you warming up the stage,
happiness never comes to a close ♫
♫ Boring jokes add some sweetness to the dinner ♫
♫ Daily life is even more like a comic than comics themselves ♫
♫ Happiness and sadness ♫
♫ Make up the moments of life ♫
♫ Rainy days become very special because of you ♫
♫ Picked up a pitiful youngster off the street ♫
♫ No matter when and where, you always appear ♫
♫ Holding me tightly and spinning in circles ♫
♫ Rainy days make me so nostalgic because of you ♫
♫ Becoming some part of the memories ♫
♫ Walking down a street with lights lighting up
one after another ♫
♫ Warming up the whole world ♫
[Please Feel at Ease Mr. Ling]
[Episode 14]
Brother Yue, your tie is crooked.
Ling Yue!
Anxin, why are you here?
If I hadn't come, I would definitely have been cheated on.
Right, Xin'er?
It's not what you think.
Then what?
Anxin, don't wrongly blame him.
I'm not talking to you.
If you want someone to blame, blame me.
Enough.
Ai Li, escort Miss Gu out.
Miss Gu, please.
Wait.
This is yours, right?
You like it? If you like it I'll give it to you.
You can give away a phone, but you can't give a boyfriend away.
You understand that, right?
Of course.
Take it back. My phone is perfectly fine.
We should each mind our own things. Do you understand?
Then I'll take my leave. Goodbye.
It really was a misunderstanding. It's not what you think.  Oh, really?
Oh, really?
She was about to leave, but tripped which is what you just saw.
Then this Miss Gu can really fall.
You know that I-
Ew, don't put my hand on that lipstick print.
It's burning.
What are you doing?
I'm changing my clothes so you won't be upset.
Are you absolutely silly?
You're taking off your clothes in the office. If anyone sees, they'll think-
Then I'll change later.
This is nice.
It must've been hard lately, right?
I'm sorry.
I don't have any way to help you.
Please feel at ease, Mr. Ling.
Brother, why haven't you left yet?
I'm not so much at ease after what happened so I came to pick you up.
Don't worry, I've talked to the security.
They will be making more rounds.
Don't worry, it's really not a big deal.
Why wouldn't it be a big deal?
Do you remember you had a bad dream when you were younger?
Even though you were scared to death,
you still refused to make any noise so you wouldn't bother anyone.
Do you remember?
Brother, don't worry.
I'm not a kid anymore. And that was when I was eight.
I can protect myself.
Did you go on a date with You You?
Did you forget? You forgot?!
Why don't you go already? She'll kill me!
- Hurry, go.
- Then you go up.
I'm sorry, I'm late.
Ansheng, no problem! Since you're so handsome, whatever you do is right.
Let me tell you, something big happened!
It says that Gu Xin'er and New Way's President are engaged!
Really?
That Ling Yue...
I'm sorry, You You. I can't watch the movie with you.
- I have to find Ling Yue and ask for an explanation.
- I will go with you!
That bastard.
Ling Yue, you...
Come out!
You two leave first.
Okay, President Ling.
Ling Yue, what's with you and Xin'er?
Right.
-You're making a fuss over nothing.
-Am I making a fuss over nothing, or are you trying to hide something?
There's no walls that wind can't pass.
(T/N: Secrets are bound to be discovered one day)
Besides if there's truly nothing, what about the news?
Where's the news?
Actually it's not news, it's gossip.
Now is when you need us Gu family the most.
How could you use Anxin
and then use Xin'er?
Gu Ansheng, I'm very curious.
Why do you keep targeting me?
Why I keep targeting you?
You, President Ling, act decisively and there's nothing you can't do.
I'm afraid everyone in this business is aware of that.
You're right.
I am certainly decisive, but I am not willing to use any method possible.
If we're talking about using any means to get his way,
your old man Gu is more fitting.
I don't need to rely on other people.
And I don't need your worry.
Ansheng, after hearing what he said are we misunderstanding him?
Listen up.
Your relationship with Xin'er will always be ambiguous in the eyes of an outsider.
That's why any move will cause something like this to happen.
To you, it may be nothing.
But think about Anxin. It will hurt her.
If you don't protect her,
I will.
Gu Ansheng,
you are just her brother.
What right do you have to protect my girlfriend in my place?
If you hurt her again,
I will take her back.
Then try and see if you can.
What are you two doing?
You're all family, whatever it is just talk it out.
Ansheng, he's explained already. Let's go.
Ansheng.
What is it?
Earlier when you said there was someone you like,
did you confess?
Not yet.
Do I know the person you like?
Why are you asking this?
Is the person you like Anxin?
I...
No matter who you like,
the person I like is you.
You You
I'm sorry, I always thought
Why are you apologizing?
If you like it, then you do. And if you don't, you don't.
After saying it, I feel much more light-hearted.
Then, why don't you get in the car?
- I'll drive you back.
- No, I can get back on my own.
It's not safe to go back on your own. I'll drive you.
No, if you're so nice to a single girl, I'll misunderstand.
Hurry and go back.
I don't know how Anxin will react after she sees the news.
You should go keep her company.
Then I'll go back first.
Let me know when you get home.
So embarrassing! So embarrassing!
My entire reputation is ruined!
[Zhao Lei]
I hung up! Why do you keep calling?!
What?
You're phone's out of battery-
What does your phone running out of battery have to do with me? I'm upset!
What?
What meeting?
Where's my idol?
Where's my charger?
You have quite the setup.
Of course, I'm a professional.
Thanks! Bye
Everyone has been waiting a long time, right?
Then let's give a warm welcome to Asia's prince of music,
Mike!
Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike!
Hello!
I love you guys.
I love you too!
Ok, our meet & greet officially starts now! Please take a seat, Mike!
We will be ending the fanmeeting here.
Let us bid farewell to Mike.
Are you okay?
Why are you-
I thought you'd be too busy fangirling and wouldn't have a chance to eat.
So I got you some food.
Have you been waiting for me?
Right, and this.
I'll carry it for you first.
Is there something on my face?
Yes
What?
A bit of cuteness.
Am I being flirted with?
Are you still busy? Remember to eat.
Why are you here?
I can't come?
Is there something wrong?
Nothing, I just wanted to see.
What power does this place have?
To make Brother Yue return repeatedly?
Looks like I thought too much.
Aside from reeking of poverty,
there's nothing special here.
Maybe he thinks that all of this is fresh momentarily.
Your words are so disgusting, are you still that well mannered Miss Gu?
But you've always been a jealous and helpless person.
Jealous?
What would I be jealous of?
Should I be jealous that you have a lowly identity?
Please get out.
What right do you have to tell me to go?
What right?
The right that I am the owner of this house so I can tell you to leave.
Owner? Who the owner is is still up to debate.
I remember that this house is rented to you by Ling Yue.
But that's right,
You really like turning the tables that much?
I'm telling you,
this is owned by Ling Yue.
But I pay rent every month so this is mine.
I have the right to tell you to leave.
How could such a model citizen
be expelled from school for purposefully hurting others?
It has nothing to do with you.
You're so savage. Does Brother Yue know?
Your Brother Yue
likes someone as savage as me.
Unlike you, two-faced,
you're pretty hypocritical.
So what if he likes you?
What worth are you feelings to him?
Now that he's in trouble, can you help him with your feelings?
Your feelings to him,
are a burden.
Ling Group's CEO position is also because of you
that he lost it.
-What do you mean?
-Ling Group's CEO position belonged to Brother Yue.
How come after his accident, he suddenly isn't?
Haven't you thought about the reason?
What exactly do you want to say?
You still don't know?
Did you think he stayed with you in this lovely haven
without any sort of sacrifice?
It's because he was tripped up over your trivial problems
and angered Uncle Ling.
That's how he lost everything that should've belonged to him.
The rumors on the Internet about me and Ling Yue,
you've seen it, right?
That's fake.
I believe in him.
Whether it's true or false,
is it that important?
What's important is
I am the only person who can help Ling Yue.
This point, you know it very well in your heart, isn't it?
You're right!
He only has you in his heart.
That's why he always refused my help.
But did you know?
Ling Yue shed lots of blood and sweat to build the New Way you see now.
The more strong New Way is,
the more Ling Yue's position is high.
If he ever falls down, everyone will mock at him.
He will fall from his peak into a pit.
Everyone will say he is an adopted son that only relies on his father!
Are you capable of watching someone as proud as him
give up on everything for you?
Even if I leave him,
would Ling Yue choose you?
It's not important whether he chooses me or not.
-What's important is for you to leave.
-Xin'er.
Xin'er.
Stop talking.
What's wrong, brother?
You want to meddle in this again?
If there's any problems, let's talk once we get home.
Go home?
Do you still know which one is your home?
Stop arguing.
Brother.
I am your biological sister.
The dessert shop that Anxin likes to go,
I also like that place. Did you know?
But Brother, you've never thought
of buying a portion for me too.
In your heart,
there's only this adopted sister.
Xin'er, you and Anxin are both equally important.
Same thing as from other, I don't want it.
Anxin.
Are you still okay?
I'm okay, Brother. You can go back.
You're obviously sad. Since when did you have to stay strong in front of me?
Leave him.
I won't allow you to suffer alone.
Why do you always want me to leave the person I love?
I...
can't give you happiness?
I'm just worried about you.
I'm fine, Brother. You don't need to worry.
The news on the Internet is fake. I won't believe these things.
Go home and go to rest early.
I'm getting tired, good night.
Good night.
Even if you don't need me,
I will always be here for you.
I'll eat it later. I'll come see you after I'm done.
Be good, wait for me.
[Xin'er]
Hello, I need a designated driver.
The address is the entrance of Soho Bar.
Xin'er.
Why you know I am here?
Sorry for being late.
Yes, you come too late.
However, I have already called for a designated driver.
Fast Bird Designated Driver?
How did you know?
I just called to pay the designated driver.
Xin'er, can I get in the car?
Get in.
Why do you seem troubled?
When did you start to care of me?
Forget it if you don't want to tell me.
Xin'er,
are you really preparing to enter into a marriage alliance with my second brother?
Since you know, why are you still here?
So it is true, isn't it?
There's indeed a preparation.
You are not even willing to lie to me.
But I declined it.
I planned to use this
to make my father spare New Way for the time being
But, no matter what, Older Brother Ling Yue refused.
It's very embarrassing to keep being declined by him.
Xiao Sheng.
Sorry. I just feel it's not worth for you to do this.
Doesn't matter.
Enough. Let's not think of this kind of problems.
You owe me a date. Make it up to me now.
I always think.
I have always wondered when the day would come
when I can be with the one I love,
to watch an on-air movie.
I don't know if I have this honor.
to be the one you wished for.
I am sorry.
Why need to say sorry of this.
Xin'er, whenever you look back,
I will always be behind.
Dad, why is someone standing at the entrance?
Why are you so free and staying home today?
I'm fine.
Dad, did you read the news on your cellphone recently?
I don't do that.
It's bad for the eyesight to read too much news on the cellphone. Cut down on this too.
Dad,  I will stop doing this.
Dad, read it if you have the time
and understand how to solve the situation.
No need. Be direct if you have anything to say.
Dad, Second Brother's company is in trouble.
It's regarding this?
You already know? I thought you don't go online.
I don't. Can't I read the newspaper?
Dad, you are not bothered about him?
Why should I? He's doing well with his company.
Why should I be bothered?
You are not aware. Second Brother has been badly battered.
His resources have been cut off.
Your information is rather up-to-date.
In any case...
let's not talk about him.
Why are you tearing my head off again?
You keep talking about your second brother.
Do you want to see him in trouble
or are you really concerned about him?
How can I be concerned about...
I'm concerned about Ling Group.
Think about this.
Although we granted autonomy rights to New Way
but we are, after all, Ling Group.
We have mutual interests. Right?
Besides, no matter what, Ling Yue is our family too.
He's your son.
If they beat him, they are slapping your face too. Isn't that so?
Why are you laughing?
I'm laughing at you.
You have finally grown up.
You know how to stand on Ling Group's perspective and think about the problems.
I'm just looking ahead.
In my memories of you as an adult,
this is the first time I heard you
being so concerned about your younger brother.
I'm not concerned about him.
I'm concerned about Ling Group.
Fine. Regardless of who you are concerned about,
I will pay attention to your younger brother.
[New Way]
President Ling, we didn't receive any positive feedback from the public after we issued the our statement.
What about France?
They probably heard about this sign of trouble.
They are not willing to collaborate with us for the time being.
Gu Yuanchao is willing to go all out for this.
President Ling, Gu Yuanchao knew about our bargaining chip.
That's how he could discuss terms with the other party.
However, our collaboration party signed the confidential clause.
Moreover, we didn't publicly announce these brands.
How did he get the information?
I'm worried about this too.
Are you saying that we have a spy in our company?
Does anyone wants go eat steamed rice with dried duck?
You are here.
- I kept a portion for you too.
- Thank you.
I'm leaving.
I personally cooked this.
It took a long time.
You only succeeded 20 percent of mine.
Don't eat it then.
I have been too tired lately.
I don't have energy to eat.
I will feed you.
Okay then.
Fine.
I will feed you.
Open your mouth bigger.
What a fool.
I suspect you did it on purpose.
You wanted to choke me to death and inherit my Huabei account.
Do you want some? This is your favorite flavor.
Later.
I actually have something to tell you.
There will be a lot of nonsense online recently
- regarding me and—
- I know.
Don't worry.
I have been on the discussion forum for a long time.
Why could I not be sharp and see through the rumors?
These kind of discussion traffic, trivial nonsensical explosive news.
How could it trick me?
I was afraid that you'll feel wronged.
I won't feel wronged when I spend every moment I'm with you.
On the other hand, you're
so tired recently and keep overworking.
How can it not be tiring working without proper rest?
Do you want to ditch work
and let's go out to relax?
Go where?
You'll know once we go.
♫ Meeting unexpectedly, those lost memories ♫
♫  What a beautiful encounter ♫
♫  and accidentally found love  ♫
♫  When I first met you, I never believed ♫
♫  that we would be so intimate someday ♫
♫  You were so cold, making me unable to get closer ♫
♫   Always prepared a plan b  ♫
♫   Follow me right now to fill in this gap  ♫
♫   And travel among the sea of people ♫
♫   I accidentally encountered love ♫
♫   Waited at the intersection  ♫
♫   What a beautiful encounter  ♫
♫  What I accidentally found  ♫
♫   was love ♫
♫   Getting closer to you, bit by bit, seems like some sort of magic  ♫
♫   Just like its fated ♫
♫   Your gentle facial expressions were well hidden ♫
♫  Pampering me and giving me courage ♫
♫   Follow me right now to fill in this gap  ♫
♫   And travel among the sea of people ♫
♫   I accidentally encountered love ♫
♫   Waited at the intersection  ♫
♫   What a beautiful encounter  ♫
♫  What I accidentally found  ♫
♫  was love  ♫
♫   Waited at the intersection  ♫
♫   What a beautiful encounter  ♫
♫  What I accidentally found  ♫
♫  was love  ♫
♫  was love ♫
When you were down there, you said you weren't afraid of heights.
That's right. I'm not afraid of heights.
It's good that you're not afraid of heights then.
It's not a big deal to ride 20 minutes on a ferris wheel.
20 minutes?
You hit your head. Does it hurt?
If you're afraid then hold onto me.
Look into my eyes.
Do you feel a bit more at ease?
♫ Walking with you through a long street on a dark night ♫
What will you do if I wasn't by your side?
♫  Watching the street lights going on and off ♫
♫ You can see how far the future is ♫
♫ once you turn around ♫
♫ I haven't differentiated it yet I already start to yearn ♫
Ling Yue, I heard other say that when you reach the highest point on the ferris wheel
wishes will definitely come true. Let's make a wish.
They're tricking kids.
Dummy. You should listen to your girlfriend at this time.
Okay then.
♫ No matter how much it is, ♫
♫ it will never be enough ♫
♫ However eternal, the money is never enough ♫
♫ Let me love you ♫
♫ Let me use my sincere heart ♫
♫ Learning to be warm to cover ♫
♫ those cold memories from the past ♫
♫ The scenery along the way, we walked and stopped again ♫
♫  ♫
Go up.
Someone will see later.
The entire building is mines. How would they dare to.
Childish.
I'm leaving then.
I'm leaving.
Ling Yue!
What's wrong? Are you reluctant?
I forgot something.
What?
Send me your Alipay account number.
Isn't it good to keep owing me?
Just send me it. I'll pay it back, bit by bit.
Okay. It's my phone number.
I'm leaving then.
♫ Hold me  ♫
♫ gently ♫
♫ Give me the last of yourself ♫
♫ Memories are like heavy rain. Having never walked through it, ♫
♫ how would you understand? ♫
What's wrong?
♫ Gaze at me, don't avoid me ♫
♫ Give me the last of yourself ♫
Nothing.
I just miss you a bit today.
I keep feeling that something is off.
Nothing is off.
In Korean dramas, the leads
take a long time to go to the toilet.
This is just a small thing.
In the future, we can act more of this kind of plots.
♫ We rely on each other ♫
♫ Like a fortress sheltering the soul ♫
Go up.
I'm leaving.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Soaking the memory wet ♫
♫ Fate works bizarrely ♫
♫ The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly beats out of normal ♫
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Obviously, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness,
for it has always been you ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Yet the reminiscing has never been able to stop ♫
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Using all of my most beautiful adjectives ♫
♫ Is still not enough to describe your name ♫
♫ Our story is exclusively ours ♫
♫ Our palms hold onto the key to the future ♫
♫ Using love to slowly open up ♫
♫  a lifetime  ♫