Sub by iQiyi & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
My Dear Guardian
Episode 6
Sure.
Thank you.
How is it?
Zhuo Ran
I cooked seafood porridge.
I'll turn off the heat
if you don't want to eat.
It's to save electricity.
Bring me some.
Such a brat!
"Bring me some."
Isn't that my book?
This is my house.
Did you prepare steamed bun?
No.
I've homemade whole grain pancakes though.
Do you want to try?
Bring it here.
It smells wonderful. I want to try it too!
It's quite delicious.
Of course.
It would go well with pickles.
Liang Mu Ze.
Have of you heard of a story before?
Long, long time ago, a man
kept bossing his housemate
who was a doctor around.
Finally, one day,
his housemate poisoned him to death
without anyone knowing.
Haven't you heard that story before?
I've heard about a story.
It's about a Special Forces soldier
who was poisoned to death.
Three seconds
before the poison came into effect,
he punched the person
who poisoned him to death.
Have you heard of the story?
What a coward.
Thank you.
The book is nice, isn't it?
Can you guess who the murderer is?
It's not Umeda Hachiro for sure.
It's not him for sure.
The story is like this.
Let me tell you.
In the end,
Mitarai was the one
who resolved
the Tokyo Zodiac Murders.
Isn't it interesting?
I have many detective novels on the shelf.
I can tell you the ending one by one.
Do you know what is
the most miserable thing in life?
Not having any canned food.
Misery is when you're reading the climax
of a detective novel,
someone breaks the ending to you
without warning.
Is detective novel
tastier than canned food?
I bet Liang Mu Ze
is as upset as
having constipation for five days.
He deserves it.
He was lazying in the sofa
like a braised egg
and bossing me around
as if I was his babysitter.
Let me tell you.
This is just a warning.
If he does that to me again,
You better shut up now.
I'll...
Have you finished taking a shower?
Hug me, handsome.
Do you want some tea?
Yes.
Sure.
Here you go.
Please try it.
What's that smell?
What's wrong?
Take it away.
Did you just bring my toilet bowl here?
Are you scared of durian?
I'm not scared of it. I don't like it.
So you're scared of it.
Take it away!
Sure. Don't be scared.
Here.
Drink some tea to calm down.
I'll finish all of it.
Are you done?
Liang Mu Ze, you're so sensitive.
Don't go.
I'm just joking.
Take it away!
It's not easy to brew the tea.
At least take a sip. Don't waste it.
It's either I leave or you take it away.
I'll take it away.
I'll get lost.
Is it nice?
Is this Pre-Qingming Longjing?
Suitable for kids.
You know about tea too?
So what?
I swear I'm not secretly thinking that
you're old-fashioned.
My grandma loves drinking tea.
When I was young,
I always had Longjing, Pu'er
with her.
I see.
When you go back to
your hometown next time,
I'll prepare some tea leaves for you
so that you can bring it back
for your grandma.
No need.
Don't be shy.
Before I left, I had stolen
quite a bit of tea leaves
from my dad's tea cabinet.
My home is near to Hangzhou.
I have quite many opportunities
to taste Longjing every year.
No matter how expensive tea is,
it is meant to be tasted by people.
Its value will only be reflected
when more people try it.
Don't feel sorry for me.
No need.
Don't be shy.
My grandma passed away long time ago.
My grandma passed away long time ago too.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know that.
My bed is not covered with bed sheets.
If you feel sorry for me,
lend me a bed sheet
and make the bed for me.
Sure, I'll do it.
Something is not right.
Why should I feel sorry for him?
He mentioned his grandma first.
I didn't know that.
Why should I contribute my bed sheet?
Why should I make his bed?
Who does he think he is?
He is your landlord.
It's either you put up with him
or you leave.
Make the bed for him, huh?
Sad story, huh?
Fine, let's make his wish come true.
I've a bad hunch.
And in the name of the Moon,
I will punish you!
Liang Mu Ze.
Poop-picker, wake up! You're getting late.
I'm going to be late.
Will you stop staring at me?
I'm sorry. I came to the wrong place.
I'm doomed.
I'm leaving.
Finish it before you leave.
Thank you.
Did you go out to get milk
early in the morning?
I didn't buy it.
You left it in the fridge.
You got it from the fridge?
I didn't keep milk in the fridge.
It's here.
Why did you give it to me?
It's not expired. I've checked.
It's whipping cream.
Do you know
how many calories it contains?
I have no idea.
Why did you give it to me then?
You kind of enjoyed it.
-Liang Mu Ze!
-You're going to be late.
What did you say?
Forget it. I'll get another driver.
It's okay.
Are you having motion sickness?
It's gut fermentation syndrome.
I feel like vomiting.
It's okay.
Just put up with it.
It's not a serious problem.
Don't be dramatic.
You need to be strong.
Liang Mu Ze, you said that on purpose.
You're thinking too much.
I'm just an old hog.
I can't tell
whipping cream and milk apart.
They're the same to me.
You're talking nonsense!
You're angry at me
as I made your bed
with a printed Sailor Moon bedding set.
You're seeking revenge.
Listen.
You're a special forces soldier
and yet you're so petty.
For a man like you,
let alone insomnia,
you may drop dead one day soon.
Who is the petty one?
It's you.
We're here.
Good morning, Xia Chu.
Good morning.
He's my comrade.
Will you get down now?
Why are you here?
I'm here for something.
Have you eaten breakfast?
Yes, I've eaten.
Keep it for lunch.
What's wrong?
Take it away.
I can't look at it the same way anymore.
This is my comrade.
Find out someone for me.
It's one week after the patient,
Luo Xiao Jun underwent the surgery.
It's time for the review
of heart ultrasonography.
There's no blood clot on septal occluder.
The reading of blood cell count
and coagulation index are normal.
No active bleeding is found.
The drainage tube was removed last night.
That's great.
Dr Zhang
has completed yet another challenge.
The coagulation during the intervention
and the bleeding management
during thoracotomy
were managed well.
I don't deserve all the credit.
Thanks to Xia Chu.
All right. Xia Chu should
come out with a case report.
She's pregnant!
I'm not pregnant.
You're pregnant.
You almost puked.
So what?
That's the sign of pregnancy.
Xiao Jun, don't talk nonsense.
It's always shown on TV.
Stop talking.
Why are you laughing?
Yang Mu Ze is such a jerk!
If it ever happens again,
I'll poison you to death!
The military medical doctor
needs to attend to something urgent.
They need our help.
Get ready.
Why is it me?
As Mr Zhang said,
we need to send a houseman there.
You're not in.
All of us
unanimously recommended you
as the representative.
Are you really pregnant?
If you admit that you studied eight years
in medical school for nothing,
I'll admit that I'm pregnant.
Are you pregnant
and he refuses to be responsible?
Isn't that the storyline?
Who refuses to be responsible?
What nonsense are you talking about?
That military officer.
If not so,
why would you poison him to death?
That's between him and me.
All right. I got it.
Go now.
The success of the surgery
has further strengthened our determination
to develop and produce
3D technology.
I hope we can start from
the department of cardiothoracic surgery.
We shall work together
to set up a special fund
for 3D Printing and hologram technology
which is non-profit making.
It's to expedite
the development of 3D technology.
From my personal view,
clinical technology innovation
is definitely a good movement.
We welcome such exploration.
However, as for the hospital,
we need further discussion on it.
We can do it.
However, as for the mode of operation
of the special fund,
we need further clarification.
Don't worry. I'll draft a
Strategic Cooperation Framework Agreement
as soon as possible
and explain to all of you in detail.
That's great.
We'll wait for the good news, Mr Zhuo.
Dr Zhang.
Thank you for making the contact.
Sorry to have troubled you.
Don't worry.
Not to mention you're Xia Chu's friend.
Personalized medicine
is the trend.
3D printing technology
is an important element.
If the special fund
can go through smoothly,
I think
it's beneficial to everyone
be it your company,
our hospital and department
or our potential patients.
It's a win-win situation.
It's worth doing.
Do you have time for lunch?
I would like to treat you
and Xia Chu a meal.
I need to conduct a surgery
in the afternoon.
Furthermore, Xia Chu hasn't come back yet.
Where did she go?
She's gone to the military camp
for health security tasks.
Are you looking for her?
It's such a hot day
yet you guys have to work under hot sun.
Thank you for the hard work.
It's our duty.
It's mainly because
casualties have increased lately.
Not only do I have to manage equipment
and medicine supply alone,
I also have to take care of the patients.
I'm really up to my neck.
What are they doing?
Have you heard about
The Heavenly Maid Scatters Blossoms?
It's time for you to see new things.
Liang Mu Ze, can you do it?
He's Liang Mu Ze
of Special Forces Brigade.
His marksmanship
was made known in the division
during the training.
Some people call him
the God of Guns.
God?
He's just mental.
Get ready to shoot.
Sub by iQiyi & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
I injured my arm. I need treatment.
Treatment Room
The wound is not too bad.
No stitches are needed.
Stop moving!
It's too big.
What?
The plaster is too big.
It's not nice looking.
Everyone looks ugly when they're injured.
Don't bolster yourself
if you want to look good.
Why did you fool around for no reason?
Do you really think that
I was fooling around?
Weren't you?
You shot down cans of beer in a row.
No doubt it's interesting to watch
but what can the tricks do
when it comes to actual battle?
A few years back,
there was a kidnapping case.
The Special Forces
had to assist the SWAT
in rescuing the hostages.
However, the kidnappers
threw a gas tank right off the roof.
Fortunately, an officer found out about it
and shot the gas tank with a gun.
The gas tank exploded in the air.
Not only did he save himself,
he also saved the hostages.
He also saved the onlooking crowd.
You're right.
It's not practical in war.
However, in a battlefield,
one will encounter more violent situations
with blood and gore.
Those situations can only be handled by
these unusual training.
It's done.
Where is the sink?
It's next door.
Thank you.
By the way,
take care of the wound hygiene.
Rest well.
-Keep the wound dry.
-Sure.
The kidnapping case that you mentioned
sounded dangerous.
Did you experience it on your own
or did you hear it from someone?
I made up the incident.
I just wanted to make a point.
That's smart.
Xiao Bai, I'm leaving.
Okay, bye.
Bai, I've reserved a table.
Pack up.
Sure, bye.
Is Mr Zhuo back yet?
He's not coming back today.
What?
How is it going?
Do you like her?
I'm just looking around.
She's coming over to our office
for recording.
If you like her...
Really?
I'm obsessed with her.
Will you bring me to your office
to see her?
No problem.
This is my name card.
When Mr Zhuo is back,
inform me at the first instance.
No problem.
That's great!
Do you want some fish?
These snakeheads reached only today.
They're fresh.
Listen.
The snakehead is best for soup making.
It's good for muscles
and it helps in wound healing.
What do you think?
Will you buy a snakehead?
I'll get one.
Sure.
It's just a machine.
Can it print a weapon?
If we work on the materials,
any object
can be produced with data.
3D printing will rule the world soon.
We, on the other hand,
is changing the rules of the game
in the present world.
Are you trying to print weapons
because of the owner of that car plate?
What have you found?
It's not confirmed yet.
It's time for dinner.
Is this a new bowl?
Do you need so many bowls?
No, I don't need it.
Why did you buy it then?
You don't have to use all the tableware.
You can appreciate the beauty.
Can you see that?
I plan to buy more
beautiful tableware
and hang them on the wall.
It'd look nice in the photos.
You're just fooling around.
Life is all about
fooling around endlessly.
♫ I had a quick glance at your eyes ♫
♫ It could be the destiny
but it is not practical ♫
♫ Your expression popped out on my mind ♫
♫ I learn to face the music
instead of evading it ♫
Here.
The steamed dumplings are ready.
Have you taken a shower?
Didn't I tell you
you must keep the wound dry?
I didn't wet it.
Listen, take care of the wound.
Don't take it lightly.
If the wound is infected,
you'll ruin my reputation.
What reputation do you have?
The reputation of a houseman?
What's wrong with being a houseman?
A houseman can be passionate
and ambitious too. Okay?
Think about it.
All the experts
used to be a houseman
who had ascended with time.
If everyone treats us differently
just like you,
how do doctors become better?
How does medicine field develop?
The fish soup is bland.
What are you doing?
Don't add salt!
If you consume too much of salt at night,
it'll cause more burden to kidneys.
You will be at a risk of losing caesium.
Furthermore, it may trigger
tens of diseases including stomach cancer.
It's not good for wound healing too.
More importantly...
More importantly,
you're having an early menopause.
Premature menopause.
My mum used to have the same symptoms.
Liang Mu Ze!
Give me back the fish soup!
Give it back to me!
Give me back the snakehead fish soup!
Oh no.
He is mental!
He insisted to add
so much of salt in the soup.
He ruined the soup.
Just let him be. It's not for you anyway.
Why are you so upset with him?
I bought the snakehead. I cooked the soup.
I even treated his wound.
I need to be responsible to my cooking
and my patient.
You're nothing but stubborn.
He just added some salt in the soup.
How is that a big deal?
Do you know?
Liang Mu Ze
did so many strange things.
He doesn't sleep at night.
He's always posing
in the living room for no reason.
I saw that many times by chance.
What's going on?
He would just
stare
straight into your eyes.
It's really scary.
You make a man
sleep on a bed covered
with Sailor Moon printed bedding set.
It'd be strange if he can fall asleep.
Also,
he insists to
close the curtain during day time.
The whole house is lifeless.
Liang Mu Ze, what are you doing?
I'm trying to avoid the light.
This is my curtain!
This is my house.
Is he a cactus monster or what?
He's full of thorns!
Being vigilant at all times
could be a conditioned reflex
as he's a military officer.
Please let me know at first instance
when he's back
It's nothing do to with being vigilant.
He's too bossy.
He wants to take control of everything.
He wouldn't even allow me to sing.
♫ Missing you so much ♫
♫ Protecting me at all times ♫
Xia Chu.
-What's wrong?
-Will you stop singing?
Will you stop singing?
What's wrong?
My singing is not too bad.
Are you sure?
You must have misunderstood
the meaning of "not too bad".
I think it's all right.
You're asking too much.
♫ Thoughts of you are like a river ♫
♫ Protecting me at all times ♫
Xia Chu.
What's wrong?
Are you awake now?
-Liang Mu Ze!
-What?
That's too much, isn't it?
He's inhumane.
However, Dr Xia,
why don't you consider
some other hobbies?
After all, your singing
is truly annoying.
Who is annoyed?
I'm the annoyed one, okay?
Listen.
What drives me up the wall is
he caused harm to Er Miao!
Did you feed it raw meat?
Yes.
It doesn't eat raw meat.
That's why it's yearning it. Am I right?
Of course.
I love meat. Especially ones like you.
Spend the rest of your life with him.
Spend the rest of your life with me.
Okay?
Sure.
You're a pervert cat!
Spend the rest of your life with me.
I'm dying.
You brought a female cat home.
If it's a male cat,
it would be following you around.
I'm so irritated.
How could you still laughing at me?
What is so irritating?
You didn't sell yourself to him.
If you can't put up with him,
just move out.
It's easy to say.
Moving out
means looking for a house
and redecorating the place.
I don't have the time.
Ladies, do you like the bed?
Thank you.
By the way, is your landlord
really so annoying?
Doesn't he have some plus points?
He's not really annoying.
He's just strange.
Speaking about plus points,
the training camp that he's in
is quite near to the hospital.
There were a few occasions
where he stayed at home
and he let me hitch a ride
to the hospital the next day.
Compared to most guys,
he's quite tidy and neat.
He is hygienic.
He always makes his bed.
It's as if no one has slept on it.
Furthermore...
What?
Come in.
Liang Mu Ze.
What's wrong?
Well...
I heard noises
coming from the living hall.
Can't you hear that?
No.
I think I must have heard it wrongly.
Well...
There are thunders and lightnings.
It's quite loud.
Are you scared?
I'm not scared.
I'm a little scared.
Forget it.
I'm going back to my room.
Let's go to the living room.
I can't sleep anyway.
Liang Mu Ze.
Are you having insomnia again?
If you can't fall asleep,
you can try meditation.
Firstly,
close your eyes.
Relax your body.
Then, starting counting.
One, two, three, four, five.
Inhale.
Count to five.
Exhale.
Inhale.
No matter what,
ever since we share a house,
my mum doesn't have to worry
about my safety anymore.
In that case,
he's not completely useless.
Then why are you picking on him?
Please know your position.
He's your landlord.
He's not your husband.
As long as
he doesn't install a hidden camera
to peek on you
or doesn't sell his house away,
all the other things
are not important.
Of course.
If you plan to move in with him,
then we shall adjust the standards.
I don't plan to move in with him.
Do you know?
Everything that you just complained
sounded as if both of you
are a little couple
trying to get along with each other.
What nonsense are you talking about?
It's quite good actually.
At least you have someone
to pick fight with at home.
You guys can take care of each other too.
It's better than living alone like me.
Mr Zhuo is back in the office.
He wants to have dinner
with you tonight.
I have to go.
Why are you in a rush?
Slow down.
Sub by iQiyi & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔