Sub by iQiyi & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
My Dear Guardian
Episode 4
Why
did such a dramatic matter happen to me?
I'm sorry, Mi Gu.
I've just found out
that I left you behind.
You had already left
when I went back for you.
Where are you now?
Did you return home?
Please don't be mad at me.
Too many troubles happened tonight,
my mind went blank.
Forgive me, Mi Gu.
Silly girl, I've reached home.
Rest assured.
Get some rest too.
Everything
will be better tomorrow.
This is my name card.
Remember to call me if Xia Chu
goes to this kind of place again.
Miss Mi Gu?
Do you know me?
You took the wrong luggage.
That's yours.
We've never met before.
Never.
Halt!
Turn to the left!
Face forward!
The destination is TSC base.
Run and go!
One, two, one...
-Xiao Teng!
-Yes!
Lead the team!
Captain!
Welcome back!
How's the water temperature?
It's too cold.
That's why I lead the team back.
What's wrong?
Do you want to try?
Yes, I do.
Report!
Captain, the Brigade Headquarters want you
in the Brigade Commander's office
at eleven o'clock.
Okay, noted.
Yes!
Is Xiao Jun hospitalised?
Yes.
His operation is tomorrow, I wish
to take leave.
No.
Someone from the higher unit
is coming tomorrow.
Thunderbolt Commando
was picked to take
the comprehensive assessment.
As usual,
every participant's result
will be recorded.
The team will fail
if any one of you gives up.
So
think thoroughly
whether to put Tian Yong on.
I don't have to think.
Just let him decide.
It's a matter of the honour
of the Special Forces Brigade
and your future.
Liang Mu Ze,
don't let me down.
Yes!
Luo Xiao Jun's condition is complicated.
A simple interventional surgery
can only cure ASD,
but it's useless
to the left inferior pulmonary artery.
It's the same to thoracotomy,
the wound is large
and it damages the patient's
cardiopulmonary function.
So I think
the most secure way is
to have a hybrid operation by combining
medical and surgical treatment.
You, cardiologists perform
the blocking of ASD.
We, cardiac surgeons operate
on the pulmonary artery.
The operation duration
can be shortened in this way.
And extracorporeal circulation
is not needed either.
The post-operative survival rate
will be improved.
If the interventional surgery fails,
we can still perform
surgical repair of ASD.
In this way,
we can avoid a second surgery situation.
This will put forward higher requirements
for our performance.
I hope that everyone
can work together.
Okay, you're dismissed.
This case
can be written in the SCI case.
Guess whom Zhang will take
to enter the operating room.
May I have your attention?
Xiao Xiao.
Yes.
From now on,
you're in charge of Luo Xiao Jun.
Tomorrow,
you're going into the operating room.
Thank you, Dr Zhang.
I'll work hard
and get the job done.
Hand over the information to her.
If anyone wishes to observe my surgery,
I hope that you guys
can impress me with your performance.
Teacher,
I'd like to talk to you.
What's the matter?
I was the one discovering
Luo Xiao Jun's condition
and
I'm in charge of communicating
with his mother.
So what?
That's why you thought
you could daze and desert at will
during today's preoperative
discussion meeting?
You can do whatever you want
because he is your loot, right?
No.
Let me tell you this.
There are only two results
of saving lives.
Either
a promise success,
or zero failure.
There's no other choice.
Do you know how complicated
Luo Xiao Jun's surgery is?
Do you know how risky his surgery is,
how high the risk is?
If you have never
thought about what I said,
I'll never allow
an unprepared resident
to enter my operating room.
I'm sorry, Teacher.
I'm extremely disappointed
with what you did today.
Miss Lan
Miss Lan.
Girl,
why didn't you answer my video call?
Are you working overtime?
No, no overtime today.
My internet is down.
I don't want to waste my internet data.
Have you eaten?
Yes.
What did you eat?
I ate
my homemade sweet and sour ribs.
I cooked vegetables too.
And a bowl of millet congee
with half a steamed bun.
Not bad.
You have made yourself a hearty meal.
Of course.
A healthy body leads to a healthy life.
That goes without saying.
Right.
You need to take care of yourself.
You're out there.
I don't request anything,
but you need to eat well
and take good care of yourself,
do you hear me?
Girl,
how is
Liang Mu Ze's house?
Do you still want to move out?
I do.
When are you going to move out?
How's your house-hunting?
I can come over to help you
if you're not free.
Never mind.
The house...
I've already found one.
It's very near to our hospital
and the environment is good.
I like the renovation as well.
The point is
the landlord is not in the country.
He is unfamiliar with the domestic market.
The fee is over
one-third below the market rates.
It's cost-effective.
I see.
That's great.
Then I'll tell Mu Min.
No, don't...
Mum.
Son, what are you doing?
I'm going to sleep.
Sleep?
Are you sleeping alone
or sleeping with someone?
Mum, I'm in the unit.
I know that.
How is it?
What progress are you two making?
It's good.
How good is it?
When we're at home,
she cooks,
I wash the dishes.
And then,
we go for a ride.
Both of us
know each other's job.
What a relief!
We talk every chance we have.
Move out
from my house in one week.
It's very good.
Really, very good.
Is it?
Yes, we're good.
Then why did her mother tell me
that she found a rental
and that she's ready
to move out to live alone?
Really?
What do you mean?
Stop playing dumb!
She didn't tell me that.
What's going on?
Did you tell her
that you have a son?
Did you?
Liang Mu Ze,
I think you're crazy.
I'm not... I...
I... My reception... I...
Hello, Mum,
I've got bad reception here. Hello?
Liang Mu Ze, I tell you this.
If you dare to kick her out,
I'll find you a new tenant right away.
Too much noise, I can't hear you.
I can't hear you.
You wait and see!
The reception is bad.
I'm sure
I can still deal with you.
I can't hear you.
Mum...
Liang Mu Ze!
This brat!
Old lady
You had trouble sleeping too?
What do you mean?
You can't sleep,
but I'm just waiting to sleep.
How's your preparation
for the assessment?
I'm a bit cringed but
I don't want to give up.
Then just go on.
But I'm afraid that
I'll affect the result of the team.
"Why did you say there's nothing to wear?
I'll take my own cloak for you to share".
Is this how they said?
The recruits line up,
the Special Forces Brigade
Hunter Military School, Isaia,
we are brothers.
I leave my life to you,
the result means nothing.
What's after that?
What do you mean?
How does the poem continue?
Captain Liang,
I wish you could hear yourself.
Why did you say there's nothing to wear?
I'll take my own cloak for you to share.
Our Sire sends the troops, let’s make
our armour suit and spear shine.
We move forward, your hand in mine.
Why did you say there's nothing to wear?
I'll take my own cloak for you to share.
Our Sire sends the troops, let’s make
our armour suit and spear shine.
We move forward, your hand in mine.
Why did you say there's nothing to wear?
I'll take my own cloak for you to share.
Our Sire sends the troops,
let’s make our armour suit
and spear shine.
We move forward, your hand in mine.
The age of death of the deceased is
in the range between 40 to 45 years old.
The cause of death
is haemorrhagic shock
due to the gunshot wound on the chest.
From the deceased's skin wound
and the residue,
the deceased was
bitten by a large dog after he died.
But this is not the most crucial point.
The most crucial point is that
from the pathological anatomy,
I found
the deceased had suffered
from a very severe kidney disease.
He even needed a kidney transplant.
Transplant?
Yes.
Moreover,
the deceased and the data
sent by the Interpol
of the seriously wounded person
who was almost kidnapped
in Isaia Joint Medical outpost,
are highly matched,
no matter if it's their
ABO RBC blood group
or MHC antigen.
Rao Zhi,
there's been a murder
in Jiaotong University's district.
Okay, noted.
I'm going to the scene.
We'll talk about it later.
Okay.
Let's go.
Take a look in there. Yes.
Rao Zhi,
how is it?
It's in there.
Rao Zhi.
Rao Zhi, over here.
In the operation
The blood vessel of the kid is fine,
it might be difficult.
Okay, noted.
Go a little further.
How is it? Are you okay?
Gearing up, I can't wait.
Are you guys done?
Yes!
Depart!
Sub by iQiyi & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♫ Standing upright and neatly lined up
under the scorching sun ♫
♫ Lift up the head and do the same
in the strong wind ♫
♫ We are dauntless and unbeatable ♫
♫ Relying on each other ♫
♫ Diving into the ocean like swordfish ♫
♫ Taking the aircraft as if
an eagle is soaring across the sky ♫
♫ Cross the forest and the mountain
in the wind and rain ♫
♫ Fearless blood burns the thorns ♫
♫ Concentrate firepower
while facing the powerful enemy ♫
♫ Strike bravely, we are together ♫
♫ We're fearless
while facing the disaster ♫
Action!
♫ Strike bravely, we wish to be together ♫
♫ Sweating in the summer ♫
♫ Heaven and Earth are
our clothes during winter ♫
♫ The safety of the world ♫
Reload!
Hurry up!
♫ Depends on me and you ♫
Okay!
Bazooka!
Last round!
Cross the obstacles!
Get on the car!
The leg is injured!
The last mile!
Gopher!
What's wrong?
I'm cramping up!
Unload!
Come!
Let's go!
How is Xiao Jun?
I just received the news.
The operation didn't work.
Bradycardia!
Stop!
Withdraw the anaesthesia!
0.5mg atropine, quick!
Yes!
Let me do it.
I think we should repair the ASD.
No.
The heart rate and blood pressure
of the patient are unstable.
He can't undergo cardiac surgery.
Why did it fail?
How could it fail?
There shouldn't have been no problem
about the surgical plan.
What's the problem?
I don't know.
It would be great if I knew it.
Xia Chu,
do you know that?
The responsibility of a doctor
is to relieve often,
to comfort always,
to cure sometimes.
It means that
medicine
has boundaries that we can't reach.
Doctor is not God.
I've tried my best.
Really.
Perhaps the God of Fortune
is not on our side this time.
Then...
Then what should we do next?
When he has recovered,
we'll repair the atrial septal defect
and the surgery of the pulmonary artery.
But
his cardiopulmonary function
was seriously damaged.
Can he really withstand the trauma?
I hope so.
How's your wound?
It's fully recovered.
Then why did you act like
you were dying during the assessment?
Why would your strength
be reinforced otherwise?
Xiao Jun's condition is not good.
Have you asked the doctor?
No.
What about giving a call?
I'm scared.
13944822375
It's Dr Xia's number.
I have Zhang Yi Chi's number,
why would I ask her?
Dr Xia is prettier.
You're shallow.
I can get over it.
You can do it too,
sooner or later.
Mu Ze.
What would you do
if you knew Xiao Jun's operation
didn't work?
Call the doctor
to ask about the reason why it didn't work
and the next arrangement of the operation
to start an early preparation.
Right, it should be like this.
And you'll comfort
Xiao Jun and your sister-in-law.
You'll tell them
that you'll protect them,
even if the sky falls.
You've always been like this, right?
What are you holding back for?
I'm not sure.
I'll be scared
if it's a very bad result.
Will you?
I will.
Then what should I do?
I dare to stand in front of you
because I know
you're right behind me.
You too.
Go find your comrade
and fight with them.
It's me.
I'm looking for the house.
It's not about the house.
It's about Xiao Jun.
So you know.
The reason of the failure
is not known yet.
I have no idea
why it became like this.
Perhaps that's what
clinical practice is like.
Even if
we're well-prepared,
there might still
be a probability to fail.
We are making the second surgical plan.
It needs some time.
No matter if you believe it or not,
I still want to say
actually,
we, the doctors, are the ones who wish
more than anyone else
that the patient could be safe
every time we send them
to the operating room.
We...
I'm sorry.
Anything else?
If you have nothing to ask, I'll...
800-meter road with obstacles.
When I reached two-thirds of it,
I thought I couldn't do it.
8000-meter mazy run.
When I reached the final mile,
Tian Yong was hurt.
I carried him.
I knew he was hurt.
And he knew I was exhausted.
But the reason I carried him
and ran to the finish line
was only because he wished
to be on the field.
What are you trying to say,
Liang Mu Ze?
Xiao Jun is only eight years old.
I know the hospital is not my battlefield.
Now I also know that
doctors
are irreplaceable.
So I ask you
not to give up
on Xiao Jun
no matter what,
okay?
I got it.
I'll pass your message to Dr Zhang.
Thank you.
Dr Zhang.
I just finished an operation
and came here to see Xiao Jun.
You've worked hard.
What did you buy?
A customer ordered a bracelet from me.
She was eager to get it so I went out
to buy some accessories.
I heard it from Mu Ze
that you've opened a book store.
Opening a book store is my hobby.
I sell some clothes
designed by me
and some freelance designers
in the store.
And I sell some
cultural and creative products too.
Dreaming is important,
but it's important to earn a living too.
Don't you think, Dr Zhang?
Dr Zhang,
does Xiao Jun still have a chance?
Will you be willing to try
if we arrange a cardiac surgery
for Xiao Jun?
For his current situation,
it might be hard
to proceed with an interventional surgery.
I think
we're more confident
on performing a surgery.
I follow your decision.
I feel bad for him
as he has to suffer a lot
at this young age,
but you are a doctor.
I believe in your choice
as long as Xiao Jun can be cured.
I trust you, Dr Zhang.
I understand.
Who is it?
It's early.
Coming!
Why have you come here?
I want to sleep on my half Tatami.
Have you had breakfast?
Yes.
Don't mind me, carry on.
There are food and beverages
in the fridge, help yourself.
Okay.
Didn't you tell me that
you're really busy
preparing for the surgery?
The surgery didn't work.
Why?
I don't know.
Perhaps it's often the case.
The patient whom the doctors
pay a lot of attention to
might not have a positive outcome.
I increasingly find that
what we can do is very limited.
I think
something's wrong
with the Feng Shui of your house.
Did you get someone
to read the geomancy?
Why don't
you move out?
I wish too.
But the other houses are more terrifying.
Come to our district.
There's a unit in our district,
it has the same layout as mine.
It's right above us.
Does it have
a floor-to-ceiling window too?
It does.
That...
He gave me this at that day
after you left.
To get your news.
I was thinking
to throw it away,
but then I thought
he might not mean any harm.
It's been years after all.
I'll just throw it away.
Sub by iQiyi & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔