Sub by iQiyi & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
My Dear Guardian
Episode 8
Xiao Jun.
Do you still like
Xuan Xuan from your school?
What do you like about her?
I like everything about her.
Why?
Is she the prettiest girl
in your school?
I don't think so.
Then why do you like her?
Why did you suddenly ask me this?
Luo Xiao Jun.
How do you feel?
What say you?
I think you're doing really well.
Xia Chu.
Change his dressing.
Yes.
What are you doing?
We're discussing about the next step.
You're really in the mood.
All right. Let's go to Room 3.
Is it so difficult to see a doctor?
Let's go.
Let's go. It's time
to see the psychiatrist.
Don't mess with me.
I'm not messing with you.
-It's your turn.
-It's my turn.
Liang Mu Ze.
The  white blood cell count
of patient no. 18 is still low.
Pay attention to him.
If your family like it,
just let me know.
I can bring more for you.
Don't be shy.
What are you doing?
Dr Zhang.
Don't sell it too hard.
You're going to make our nurses
go bankrupt soon.
That's impossible.
These handmade reusable bag
are designed by me.
-It's a present for the nurses.
-Is it?
It's to thank them
for taking care of my son.
Thank you so much.
We're getting back to work.
Thank you for the present.
You should get back to work. By the way,
-it's for everyone.
-Thank you, Ms Meng Zhen.
The patterns and designs
are my ideas.
You won't find it anywhere else.
I hope you like it.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I don't get one?
It's rare to see men buying reusable bag.
Hence, I didn't make one for you.
However,
I know that doctors are hygienic.
Therefore,
I made you a soap.
I hope you like it.
You made a soap for me?
Look,
my surname is carved on the soap.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
It's personally customised
and it's the only and only in the world.
I'll keep it well.
Sure.
By the way, we just checked on Xiao Jun.
He's recovering well.
We changed his dressing today.
If everything goes well,
he can be discharged on Monday.
Really?
Thank you so much!
Okay, got it.
I'll come now.
There's a patient in the emergency ward.
A metal pierced through his chest.
I'm going down to have a look.
Take care of your respective patients.
-Call me if anything.
-Yes.
Okay, you go ahead.
Ms Meng Zhen, we're getting back to work.
Okay, go now.
Have you fallen in love with someone?
No.
Say it.
It's a secret between us.
I won't tell Ms Zhen.
I'm not you. I'm not scared of your mum.
Who are you scared of?
I'm scared of you the most.
Xiao Jun.
It's time to change dressing.
Here.
Pull your shirt up.
Let me help you.
Go away!
Don't touch me. Get out now!
I'll leave after changing the dressing.
Here, be good.
I don't want you to do it.
Get out!
Xiao Jun.
Xiao Jun, what's wrong?
Dr Xia, what's going on?
Nothing.
Dr Xia, you need to learn
how to respect your patient.
What if the patient is wrong?
If he stays stubborn,
he will bear greater pain in the end.
Dr Xia, it's just changing the dressing.
Why would he suffer from greater pain?
Nothing.
I'll come again later.
Sure.
Why hasn't medical order
for patient no. 17 here yet?
You're the slowest. Speed up.
No...
My desktop went dead just now.
I just got it repaired.
Explain to the patient!
Can you please change dressing
for Luo Xiao Jun on behalf of me?
No, I'm occupied.
I'll prepare the medical order for you.
You can leave all the medical orders
that has to be done within this week
to me.
Two weeks worth of medical orders.
It's a deal.
It's done.
-Thank you, Dr Xiao.
-No problem.
Thank you.
By the way, Xiao Jun,
tell me the truth.
Why won't you let Dr Xia
to change your dressing?
It's none of your business.
It's none of your business too.
Luo Xiao Jun!
What's wrong with you?
You're being rude.
Liang Mu Ze.
Will you take care of Ms Zhen forever?
It's none of your business.
Xiao Jun.
You haven't told me
what you want for lunch.
Will you, Liang Mu Ze?
Of course. Do you have to ask?
I want braised pork ribs.
Two portions please.
Ms Zhen, go with Liang Mu Ze.
Why are you so happy?
Liang Mu Ze promised
to take care of Ms Zhen forever.
What does that mean?
That means I took note of it.
I know why you hate me.
It's because of Liang Mu Ze, right?
Listen.
Ever since we met each other
for the first time,
I've always been your doctor.
Now, I'm still your doctor.
I'll be responsible of your health
until you're discharged.
Please don't hate me.
It's nothing to do with Liang Mu Ze.
It's for your own good.
If
you hold grudges against me for nothing,
you may hurt yourself in the end.
Please buy me a bouquet of flowers.
What?
In the name of Liang Mu Ze.
Send a bouquet of flowers to my mum.
That way, I'll believe in you.
Will you behave and receive treatment?
Yes.
That's a deal.
-Are you going back to the camp later?
-Yes.
Xiao Jun becomes more sensitive
after falling sick.
Don't take what he said just now
to heart.
Meng Zhen.
Xiao Jun is a kid but I'm not.
I'll honour my words.
You don't have to do that, Mu Ze.
It's been eight years.
It's more than enough.
I can take care of myself.
Xiao Jun has grown up.
I can take care of him by myself.
As for you,
you should move on.
You should go on with dating,
getting married
and have your own children.
You should find your own life purpose.
Taking care of you is my life purpose.
Do you plan to live like this
for the rest of your life?
Both of us know that
it shouldn't be like this.
Sometimes,
inappropriate promises
could be a form of disturbance
to a kid.
Mum.
Xiao Jun.
Xiao Jun, why are you here?
Didn't I tell you to wait in the ward?
It's for you.
Where did you get the flowers?
Liang Mu Ze got it in secret.
He wants to give you a surprise. Look.
It's a card with his name on it.
Hurry up, Liang Mu Ze.
Aren't you going to propose?
The flowers are so beautiful.
I like it.
I like it no matter who the sender is.
However...
We can't get married.
Why?
You promised
you will take care of her forever.
I'll take care of both of you forever.
However,
it's different from getting married.
Why?
Is it because you don't like my mum?
Here, come here.
Listen.
Come here.
Sit down.
Let me tell you.
Marriage is something important.
It's not as simple as you imagine.
It's not just about liking someone or not.
There are more elements to it.
Therefore,
I can't marry Liang Mu Ze.
It's not going to happen.
Can you understand?
He promised to take care of you forever.
He said that out of kindness.
However, taking care of us
is not his responsibility.
It's a success!
Stop crying, Xiao Jun.
Stop crying.
Xiao Jun.
What's wrong?
Was it you?
Yes.
Are you crazy?
Ridiculous.
Yes.
I'm crazy.
Dr Xia.
You should apologise to her.
Dr Xia, sorry to have taken up
so much of your time.
It's okay. I'm going to meet a friend
at the emergency department.
Be careful!
Dr Xia, are you okay?
Put up with it.
Your bone is fine
but the ligament is injured.
If it's not fixed,
it won't recover.
You're a doctor.
You should know the consequences.
How long will it take to recover?
It will take about a week.
Don't walk too much and rest well.
Can I go to work tomorrow?
Go to work?
Do you plan to give up
on conducting surgery?
We'll talk about it
when your leg has fully recovered.
You may get back to work.
I can handle it.
I'm going back to the unit at 6 o'clock.
You should come back with me.
Why?
You'll be staying there for a few days.
Why? He's worried about you.
No.
I promised Zhang Yi Chi
to take good care of you.
It's done.
Go get a wheelchair.
It's not needed.
Liang Mu Ze!
Military officers have great stamina.
Liang Mu Ze, let me down!
Put me down!
Stop moving.
I won't be responsible if you fall.
Put me down!
We're in the hospital.
You're creating a scene.
Stop looking around.
-Look at them.
-You...
Let me down!
Stop moving.
I...
Let go of me! I want to get down!
You're abducting me.
I'm going to scream for help.
If you don't mind embarrassing yourself,
you may do so.
I don't mind.
Should we follow them?
Go back to the office.
Mi Gu?
Mi Gu!
I'll be there in half an hour.
Roll down the car window.
Mi Gu!
He's gone?
Yes.
He requested to be discharged.
Didn't you know?
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
One, two, three, four!
I think I just saw Captain Liang's car.
Stand still!
Tian Yong.
Captain.
Dr Xia?
Yes.
Good day, Mrs. Liang.
Good day, Mrs Liang.
Good day, Mrs Liang!
What are you doing?
Who is Mrs Liang?
Brigade Commander.
Good day, Brigade Commander!
I told you to come back at 6 o'clock.
You're late 20 minutes.
What happened?
Reporting.
Chief.
He was late because
he kept me company at the hospital.
Who are you?
Reporting to Brigade Commander.
She is a cardiac surgeon
from 109 Hospital.
Reporting.
Dr Xia was my saviour.
She saved me
when we were in Isaia.
It's you, Dr Xia.
Hello.
I have been wanting
to thank you face to face.
I didn't expect to see you today.
Chief, don't mention it.
You may call me Xia Chu.
Sure, Xia Chu.
What happened?
I accidentally fell down.
Captain Liang ran into me
in the hospital and hence,
he took me in.
Took you...
Look at me.
I got it now.
Xia Chu.
You're going to stay here
for a while, right?
-Yes.
-No.
She'll stay.
Chief.
The military camp
is full of confidential information.
I'm an outsider.
You're not an outsider.
Xia Chu.
You're Tian Yong's saviour, right?
That means you're the saviour
of Special Forces Brigade too.
Am I right?
Yes!
-Liang Mu Ze.
-Yes!
-Take care of Xia Chu.
Chief.
I need to get back to the hospital.
I didn't apply for leave.
You don't have to worry about that.
Just stay here, relax
and nurse your wound.
I'll talk to your boss later.
-Liang Mu Ze!
-Yes!
Send Xia Chu to the guest house.
Yes!
-I'll send her there now.
-Go.
-Thank you, Chief.
-Goodbye, Xia Chu.
I'm leaving, Brigade Commander.
-Tian Yong.
-Yes!
I've a meeting
at the Brigade Headquarters.
So, please send dinner
and daily necessities
to Dr Xia.
Get her a few pair of clothes too.
Will do, sir.
-Tian Yong!
-Yes!
Sing the cadence while marching.
Yes!
Turn to the rear and march!
♫ Unity is strength ♫
Ready, sing!
Liang Mu Ze, I don't want to stay here!
You're not going to stay here.
I want to go home.
You'd better not do that.
Why?
Because I took you in.
I was giving you face.
I said that because he's your boss.
In fact, I'm kidnapped by you.
Don't act innocent.
Fine, no matter what,
you can only leave after you've recovered.
Liang Mu Ze.
Are you worried
it'd be difficult to explain
to Mr Zhang Yi Chi?
It's okay.
You don't have to take it to heart.
I can explain for you.
Just let me go, okay?
Let me survive on my own, okay?
What does that mean?
Just how much do you loathe
military camp and Special Forces soldiers?
No matter how much you loathe us,
you have to put up with us.
It's nothing to do with military camp
and the Special Forces!
I just want to stay alone!
I just want to go home!
I don't want to stand in your way
and being called crazy.
Can't you just let me go?
No.
Why?
That's my house.
I have the final say on
whether you can go back.
Attention! At ease.
Xia Chu.
Stop crying.
Is the medicine not working?
Yes, she's been crying.
Where are you?
I'll check on her.
We're in the military camp.
Are you sure that her bone is fine?
Don't worry.
The diagnosis by Orthopaedic Department
is surely accurate.
Furthermore, even if she injured
her bone,
a minor outpatient treatment
wouldn't make her cry.
Be honest.
Did you bully her?
How is Xiao Jun doing?
I've just done with my work.
I'm going to check on him.
All right, give me a call if anything.
You should take care of yourself.
Since you brought her back,
you should take care of her.
When you're dealing with a lady,
you have to be gentle, okay?
She's injured
but her parents are not around.
She must be fragile at the moment.
She can't take your cold treatment.
All right, I've to go.
He brought her back.
Sub by iQiyi & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Outpatient Department
Have some food.
Is it sweet?
Did I scare Liang Mu Ze away?
He's not made of paper.
He's gone back to the military camp.
No.
I almost died
from the illness.
I had two surgeries.
My heart is problematic.
You're all right.
You've recovered, okay?
Nothing will happen to you.
No one can predict the future.
If one day
I leave this world just like dad,
I hope
someone can keep you company
and take care of you.
Otherwise, you'll be lonely.
You'll be sad for sure.
That's why I lied to you
and claimed that the flower
was from Liang Mu Ze.
I like him.
I thought you liked him too.
I didn't lie on purpose.
I know.
You will be fine.
You'll always be by my side.
Don't think too much, okay?
I know.
You will be fine.
Are you doing laundry?
Dr Zhang.
Done with work?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
The laundry detergent
accidentally got into my eyes.
That's a little far-fetched.
Did you cry?
Xiao Jun bought me a bouquet of flower
in the afternoon.
He told Liang Mu Ze to propose to me.
Propose to you?
Were you touched?
It's never crossed my mind that
my son would be the match-maker for me.
He said,
he's worried that if he left the world,
I would be lonely.
Actually that's a good idea.
Liang Mu Ze is a nice man.
I think you should consider him.
What? Liang Mu Ze?
Yes.
How is that possible?
Listen.
I embroidered a piece of table cloth
a few years back.
It's a blue bird.
I really liked it.
However, one day,
I accidentally spilled juice on it.
It's tainted.
I couldn't get rid of the stain
no matter how hard I tried.
I thought
I could produce another one
but I couldn't do it.
When the patterns are similar,
I can't help but keep comparing the both.
Even if the new one is more delicate,
I would always miss the old one.
Mu Ze seems so familiar to me.
When he stood before me
in the army uniform
that I'm especially familiar with,
it's as if I could see the shadow
of Xiao Jun's dad.
Therefore,
I trust him.
I even relied heavily on him once.
However, I know that
I can't bring my feelings forward.
He won't do that.
I won't do that either.
There are many patterns I can do.
However, there is only one blue bird.
I get it.
I can totally understand that.
Stop thinking so much.
Xiao Jun will slowly grow up.
He won't let you live a lonely life.
Thank you, Dr Zhang.
See you.
Goodbye.
Xia Chu.
Have some water.
Listen.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have had scolded you.
However, bringing you back to the camp
is for your own good.
Am I right?
Someone will take care of your meals.
You'll recover faster.
Just stay here with ease.
I'll always be in the camp.
You can reach me anytime
for anything.
Okay?
Xia Chu.
I'm hungry.
No problem.
Reporting!
Come in.
Captain Liang.
Why do you look troubled?
Look at the operational requirement
suggested by the sixth team.
How can I not be troubled?
I'm not talking about
operational requirement.
I'm talking about Dr Xia.
She's a lady after all.
She's staying at the guest house alone.
Do you think it's appropriate?
Dr Xia is a doctor.
She knows how to take care of herself.
Why are you doing this to her?
You're used to staying with her.
-Lieutenant Tian.
-Yes!
I think our platoon
is lacking vigour lately.
Is it?
I was receiving training elsewhere.
As the vice captain,
aren't you supposed to lead by example
and make sure everyone in the platoon
including yourself
to be disciplined in physical training?
Look at your
physical fitness test results.
What happened to you?
However, the overall performance
of our platoon has improved.
Xiao Teng won the second runner-up
in 800m obstacle race.
-Is that good enough?
-No.
-No!
From tomorrow onward,
train yourself to death.
Make sure you get number one
in the next assessment.
-Do you hear me?
-Yes!
Leave.
Yes.
♫ Standing upright and neatly lined up
under the scorching sun ♫
♫ Heads up in the strong wind
and act boldly as usual ♫
♫ Unafraid of the challenges and dangers.
Our generation is invincible ♫
♫ We trust each other ♫
♫ Dive into danger like a swordfish
diving into the deep ocean♫
♫ Flying a fighter jet like
a bold eagle soaring high in the sky ♫
♫ Trekking through forests
and over mountains ♫
♫ Our passion burns the thorns down ♫
♫ We've always been naughty brats ♫
♫ We know we have great responsibilities
even though we haven't grown up ♫
♫ Endless, dull repetitions ♫
♫ It's to make sure we don't hesitate
when danger strikes ♫
♫ Throbbing disappears
in a blink of an eye ♫
♫ Know that there's no second chance
on the battlefield ♫
♫ Relentlessly looking
at each other again and again ♫
♫ It's to make sure we don't surrender
to fate ♫
♫ Concentrate the firepower
in the face of a strong enemy ♫
♫ You and I fight fiercely ♫
♫ We are fearless even when
we are confronted with calamity ♫
♫ You and I fight fiercely ♫
♫ The stability and peace
of all places in the world ♫
♫ Can be achieved by you and me ♫
He's showing off.
So?
Have you gotten any the idea
for the coming shoot?
Let me know if you have any ideas.
Boss, why don't we film
about internet entrepreneurship?
How about acting agencies?
Why don't we go for food column?
Mi Gu!
Are you okay?
What do you think?
I didn't mean it.
Something went wrong with your guest.
Not only did you not solve the issue,
you dozed off during the meeting.
Do you still want the job?
Boss.
I've completed the new proposal.
Please take a look.
Filming a doctor's daily life?
Filming a doctor's daily life
to present the doctor-patient relationship
which is a public concern.
We can also make the show stands out
by including all kinds
of eye catching rare diseases.
At the same time, we can instil
the correct values on health and death
in the public.
Not only is it evergreen,
it's also interesting to watch.
More importantly,
I have a good subject to feature.
What do you think?
Do you think it's doable?
Yes.
Lad.
Your mum is exhausted
from taking care of you.
Now that you're discharged,
you must listen to your mum.
Got it?
Yes.
All right, Dr Zhang.
You don't have to send us off.
Send me a message
after you've reached home.
Sure.
Xiao Jun, say goodbye to Dr Zhang.
Goodbye.
Let's go.
Dr Zhang, you're indeed
not picky at all.
My patient is discharged today.
Am I not allowed to send him off?
Why didn't you come that weekend?
You went there?
Of course.
I waited for you for the whole night.
No way.
I'm serious. Why would I lie?
I know you well.
Li Juan.
You...
You're anything but stubborn.
Even if you waited at the pub
for the whole night,
you're not just waiting for me, right?
We had a date.
Who else would I wait for
if it weren't for you?
Are you crazy?
Are you free tonight? Let's go together.
I'm sorry.
I already have a date.
Sure, can't wait to eat it.
See you tonight.
See?
I have everything in the world.
I took care of the surveillance system.
I'm ready.
Do you really want to do that?
"The Tokyo Zodiac Murders"
by Soji Shimada
Listen.
I have a bad hunch.
You'd better be fast.
Are you done?
Can you hear me?
Will you answer me?
Can you hear me, Zhuo Ran?
Can you hear me?
Are you Xia Chu's pet?
What is your name?
Don't touch me.
I didn't know that you had a cat.
Can you hear me? Yang Mu Ze is back.
Zhuo Ran, can you hear me?
Liang Mu Ze...
Liang Mu Ze is back!
Can you hear me? Liang Mu Ze is back!
What's wrong?
Help!
A bad guy wanted to hurt me.
A bad guy is after me!
Are you missing your owner?
She'll be back soon.
That's enough. Go watch the door.
I don't care if she's coming back soon.
I want you to take me away from here.
Can we rewind to the earlier time?
Usually it works that way.
However, something is wrong
with the surveillance system.
There is no video signal.
No signal?
Yes.
We just got it repaired.
Hence,
the earlier recording is not available.
Sorry about that.
Sub by iQiyi & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔