♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
=The Eternal Love S3=
=Episode 03=
Enter.
Greetings, Eldest Princess.
Girls from all over the place
are trying to imitate Your Highness's style.
To be like you, they'd...
Peasant girls?
The girls born into noble families
have all drawn their eyebrows in
your Floating Cloud eyebrow style.
The crimson yarn robes you particularly adore
are in extremely high demand.
From now on, draw my eyebrows
in the Sparrow Soaring style,
and throw all of my crimson yarn robes away.
Yes, Your Highness.
Not only are the women in the country trying
to imitate Your Highness' fashion style,
every gentleman in the city,
no matter how discourteous it may be,
all wait for Your Highness on your way
to the Imperial Palace,
just to catch a glimpse of Your Highness.
Even if it's to see me,
they must still abide by the moral codes for men.
Tell them to leave,
since there is only one man in this world
that I take a liking to.
Yes, Your Highness.
Are there any other rumours about me?
They say that Your Highness
is beautiful and attractive.
They speak of how stunningly gorgeous
Your Highness is,
how unmatched the eloquence of
Your Highness's prose is,
and that Your Highness is the talent of
the century in Dongyue.
No slanderous rumours?
Slanderous rumours?
A... Absolutely none.
Speak!
There were two women gossiping
that you have a great figure and a round face.
Round?
No, no, no!
It's rosy! That's right, rosy, Your Highness.
Drag him out!
Come and take him away!
Your Highness!
Your Highness! Please forgive me, Your Highness!
It wasn't me who said that!
Your Highness! Your Highness!
I beg you, please forgive me!
Your Highness!
Why is life so hard?
I've finally climbed to the top of
the social status pyramid,
yet my man is nowhere to be found.
If Cheng Cheng is in the same situation that
I once was,
then he would switch personalities
whenever he lies.
I've got to test it out.
Jing Xin.
Your Highness.
No slacking off during work.
Slacking off?
Get a ride ready,
I'm going to visit Mo Residence.
Your Highness, you're still going to
the Mo Residence?
Is there anything wrong with that?
Nothing.
Cheng Cheng,
you've got to do it this time.
No matter what,
you need to come out and see me.
Please.
(Mo Residence)
Your Highness, my elder brother is not here
at the moment.
I've come here for you.
I want to tell you that
I forgive you for yesterday's incident.
I thank Your Highness for her mercy.
I shall take my leave now.
I just... have a favour to ask of you.
As long as that favour causes no harm to others,
especially to my elder brother,
then I will do everything I can to fulfill
the request of Your Highness.
I wouldn't do anything that harms others.
I want you to tell me a small lie.
You're asking me to lie?
I don't know how.
You're too humble, Mo Lian Cheng.
If you don't know how,
then who was the one who fooled me
with the divorce paper,
and who was the one who lied to me,
saying that he was still unsatisfied?
Wait... then he lied already, isn't it?!
Has he switched yet?
Don't worry. Do you think I can do anything
in broad daylight?
You can't in broad daylight,
but that doesn't mean you can
in the dead of night.
I still want an explanation regarding
Your Highness' harassment towards me
yesterday.
Who harassed you?
That was...
Eldest Brother, you misunderstood.
But just now, I clearly heard...
It wasn't harassment.
I'm just afraid that people
would belittle me for it.
Well, that was an outstanding lie.
What a pro.
The incident that happened during
the Harem Selection was not all your fault.
Her Highness has helped clear your name.
You must also try to cope with it.
Yes.
Then... I will stop bothering you guys.
You...
He still hasn't switched.
My eighth brother still needs some time.
I will do all I can to persuade him.
I can't believe lying doesn't work on
Mo Lian Cheng.
That's against science.
Don't tell me he'd have to sleep and then...
No no no.
The first two times he switched,
he didn't sleep either.
A smash to the head!
That's the only way left now.
It's my last resort.
Jing Xin.
Your Highness.
Pass along my message to the Mo Residence.
Tell them to let Eighth Young Master accompany me
on my trip tomorrow.
Just say that...
it's to pray for the prosperity of Dongyue.
The Eighth Young Master?
Not the Eldest Young Master?
Mo. Lian. Cheng.
Understood.
Oh dear, this is going to be such a mess.
Princess, Eighth Young Master is here.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Tan Er.
Is there anyone else in there?
Having fun playing hard to get?
You're really going to keep playing hard to get
so you can keep having fun, huh?
Now that all eyes on us,
let's see if you can harass me now.
I see you brought your love rival here.
Well, we shall see if you will regret
that decision!
Gentlemen, please come on in.
Today,
we will play a game of escape room
in this inn that's in the middle of nowhere.
Now I will explain to everyone
how to play escape room.
Suppose there are a lot of carnivorous ghosts
in the room we are in right now.
We must use our own eyes
and hands
to find some...
to find some clues.
Then escape this room.
Clues, clues.
Eighth Young Master, I can't reach it.
Would you please help me?
Tan Er!
Your Highness! Are you alright?
Who would be so malicious
so as to hurt us passersby?
That's what that man deserves.
Sooner or later,
the misfortune would return to the one
who did it.
You!
This place is cursed.
Let's hurry up and leave.
It must have taken a lot of time and effort
for Your Highness to set up such traps.
Who set up traps?
This was supposed to be a game of escape room,
who knows what else lies are in store?
Qu Tan Er! What is this now?!
Your Highness!
Eighth Brother!
Eighth Young Master!
Have they... gone outside?
Come! Let's go search outside.
You set up all these traps
and keep harassing me.
What is the meaning of this?
I swear I didn't know about this trap!
Stop babbling!
Hurry up and figure a way out!
Stop pretending!
How about let's be honest with each other?
What is the purpose of all this?
I have nothing to say to you!
You're not my Cheng Cheng.
You!
You jerk! You heartless man!
I won't allow you to forget about me!
Stop trying to hide from me!
Forget? Does this have to do with my lost memory?
I did forget about some things
that happened between us.
Right?
I knew it!
I knew that it wasn't anything complicated.
You just lost your memory.
Now we need to find a way to return to
where we once were.
You're no Eighth Young Master.
You're my one and only Cheng Cheng!
Do you still remember... the time
when you were trying to win me over?
You were so assertive yet gentle towards me.
Tan Er, stay within three feet of me.
If my consort were to be gone,
what joy there remains in life,
what relief death would bring me, as a prince?
Prince?
Your Highness, do you mean...
that I once was knighted?
You used to be the Eighth Prince of Dongyue
who then became the Emperor!
- Princess.
- You...
I know that we're not in the royal palace,
but you still must be cautious with what you say.
I mean it's because you said you don't remember,
that I started talking about all this.
That day our son was being naughty...
Our son?!
Your Highness, this story is very interesting,
but I'm afraid I can't listen to it anymore.
Who was telling you a story?
I swear,
if there is even half a lie in what I said,
then I'll die the moment I leave my room!
There's light coming from there!
Let's get out first.
Tan Er, stay within three feet of me.
If my consort were to be gone,
what joy there remains in life,
what relief death would bring me?
I will protect you.
Those who hurt you will be my enemies.
Tan Er!
Cheng Cheng...
Tan Er! It's me!
I'm your Cheng Cheng.
Cheng Cheng,
is that really you?
It's me.
Promise me you won't leave me again.
I promise.
I now know
why you hit me in the head.
You must not be further than three feet
away from me.
I won't be more than three inches away from you,
let alone three feet.
♪For you, I'm willing to let go of
all my glory and splendour♪
♪To wander the world with your hand in mine♪
♪Your most beautiful years
are etched into my heart♪
Your Highness, what happened just now?
Eighth Young Master, be careful,
in case there are more assassins.
Your Highness!
Tan Er!
Eighth Brother!
Tan Er, please wake up!
Tan Er!
Perhaps it was Qu Tan Er who protected me
from the assassins?
It's all my fault.
I shouldn't have left your side.
Eighth Brother, are you alright?
I'm fine.
Who would've thought that there would be
assassins hiding here.
It's too dangerous here.
Thank god Her Highness and Jing Xin are here.
We must hurry back and report this to the officials.
It's a bad idea to make this incident known.
Someone must've taken their time to plan this,
so as to get Her Highness and Eighth Brother
to fall into the trap
and lead them to the exit where the assassins
were hiding.
Let's wait for Her Highness to wake up
to make any decisions.
You're right, Eldest Brother.
Our top priority now is to return home.
Let's go.
(Mo Residence)
Father, you were looking for me?
You left the residence without telling anyone,
even caused Second Princess
to almost be assassinated.
Do you understand the consequences of this?
I left for the trip
on Second Princess's invitation.
The assassination attempt was a coincidence.
What wrong did I do?
Then do you know
that being close to Second Princess would
cause rumours to spread?
What I have done
is what you have wanted, Father.
Then why don't you hurry up
and let the Empress take a liking to you?
That is the shortcut!
Father is not someone who is impatient
and rushes for success.
So you should know that
allying with the Empress is not the best idea.
Her Majesty is hard to control,
but Second Princess is different.
Lian Cheng.
Second Princess has your eldest brother.
They are childhood friends,
which makes it much easier!
I think that
Eldest Brother is very devoted
to Second Princess.
Father, can you really be sure that
between Second Princess and Father,
he will take your side?
So that's why you are trying to befriend
Second Princess?
Beware of your plan backfiring.
Your Highness, you're awake.
Where am I?
This is the Mo Residence.
After you lost consciousness,
you were brought here to rest.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Don't worry.
What about Mo Lian Cheng? How is he?
And the others?
Are they alright?
The three young masters
of the Mo family are all fine.
Please rest assured, Your Highness.
What's going on?
Do I have to get hurt in order for him to switch?
Something's off.
Why did he switch back all of a sudden?
We have yet to report the assassination.
Please guide us, Your Highness.
Who else is there that wants me dead
other than that person?
Unfortunately, I don't have any evidence right now.
There's no firm evidence that points to her.
Your Highness, are you really alright?
I really am fine.
Just look at my strong body.
Well, since I've been severely hurt...
What do you say if I rest for a little longer?
Your Highness, do you mean that you'll be
staying at the Mo Residence for some time?
But I heard that
Mo Feng Yang, General Mo,
will be returning today.
Mo Feng Yang?
What kind of new character did I unlock now?
Why are you surprised, Your Highness?
General Mo has always been an important figure
to Dongyue.
It's the sister Shi Si mentioned.
[*"Shi Si" means Fourteen]
I haven't figured out Mo Lian Cheng yet,
and now a general appears.
Forget about that general,
Mo Lian Cheng, I am onto you!
Jing Xin.
Yes, Your Highness.
Go to find the Eighth Young Master.
Understood.
Eighth Young Master.
I changed into some clean clothes,
so I took a little longer.
Are you alright?
Sorry to have dragged you
into this and frightened you.
Since Your Highness is still hurt,
I shall take a leave.
Since when did Your Highness have
pulmonary problems?
Headache, fatigue, weariness.
Young Master Mo,
can you bring me my medicine?
It's right there.
So painful.
I'm so exhausted.
I can't even lift my hand.
How about you feed me?
Then I'll go call Jing Xin over.
Don't.
Jing Xin is a guard and she's clumsy.
How about you do it?
Come closer.
I can't reach it.
Tan Er, why did you get up?
Feeling better?
Here.
I shouldn't bother you to do this, Eighth Brother.
Tan Er,
if you don't get any better,
that'd be a problem.
Here, drink this.
I've had two bowls of this medicine already!
Yet I don't feel it working.
That's what I said! You can't just take medicine!
I'll find an imperial physician for you.
Sure!
Let Jing Xin go with you.
Alright, get some rest.
I'll return in just a moment.
Jing Xin!
(Mo Residence)
Feng Yang.
Sister!
There.
Father, I have conquered Fort Gu Feng
and returned victoriously.
You are the hero of Dongyue,
the pride of the Mo Family,
and my outstanding daughter.
Feng Yang!
Eldest Brother.
It's good to see you back.
It must've been hard for you all these years,
being away from home and fighting battles.
Jing Xin and I are going to find
an imperial physician for Tan Er.
Let's talk more when we come back.
Feng Yang.
Sister! You're truly the heroine of our Dongyue.
Shi Si, you've grown up a lot.
Feng Yang,
Second Princess and Lian Cheng
went out for a trip,
but unfortunately came face-to-face
with assassins.
Her Highness is resting at our mansion for now.
Lian Cheng is looking after her,
so he's a bit late.
Let's go in, shall we?
On my way back, I heard rumours
about Eighth Brother.
Seeing that he is personally taking care of
Her Highness now,
it appears that I've missed out on
a lot of things.
Feng Yang should go to the guest's room first
to pay my respects to Her Highness.
Feng Yang.
I've been sick for so long.
Why don't you carry me and take me for a walk?
It has only been a while,
and you're going for a walk again?
I'm just so fatigued.
I'm so exhausted.
You two!
Greetings, Your Highness.
Looks like the assassins did not spare you guys.
They even broke Your Highness's leg.
Don't worry.
I've just been lying down for too long,
and am feeling a little sore.
My four limbs are all intact.
Then Your Highness should be careful during
your future outings,
bring some more guards to ensure your safety.
Eighth Brother, don't bother Her Highness anymore.
You must report to Father before
you leave the mansion.
Now that we've greeted Your Highness,
Eighth Brother and I will take our leave
so that Your Highness can rest peacefully.
Farewell.
You!
We're not in the army,
shouldn't you tone down
your commanding general demeanor a little?
It has only been a year and you've become
much more unyielding.
Who gave you the courage?
The empress? Or is it the second princess?
It has only been a year,
yet where is all this resentment coming from?
Being touchy-feely in the same room,
getting all affectionate when
it's only afternoon,
feeding her medicine and food,
and being with her every day.
Do you realize that you've become
the laughing stock of the folks?
What use is there if I earn all this honour
for our family
only to have you squander it!
What you've said is not what I intend.
You've directed your anger at the wrong person.
She ignores Eldest Brother and has a fickle mind.
But look at you!
If it weren't for you seducing her,
how would she have noticed you?
You're confusing right and wrong.
What a joke!
I may be low in seniority,
but I am the only daughter of the Mo household.
I must protect the Mo Family's reputation
for Mother.
Mo Feng Yang!
I ordered Mo Lian Cheng's every action.
On the surface, you're scolding him,
but who you actually want to scold is me, right?
I would never dare to.
It's my elder brother who should
stop being careless.
Being an important figure to Dongyue,
why are you so conservative, so narrow-minded,
so gullible, and so arrogant?
Careless? Against the moral codes for men?
I think you're just too hung up on matriarchy!
You won't stop talking about rules and precepts.
Those are nothing but prejudices.
You...
Qu Tan Er spoke up for me.
Why do her thoughts
coincide with mine?
Cheng Cheng!
Your Highness, who are you calling for?
Calling for my dear, my husband.
My Cheng Cheng!
You watched me fall again.
It's like this every time.
What's going on?
You don't know me? Again?
Since Your Highness
has helped restore my reputation,
her Majesty will certainly take pity on me.
Your Highness needn't worry.
What do you mean?
You're still thinking of being into
the harem?
If she was just using those words to deceive me,
that'd be too awkward of a lie.
Furthermore,
how could I frequently overstep boundaries
and not recognize my actions?
Did she mistake me for someone else
or was I really involved with her in the past?
You jerk! You heartless man!
I won't allow you to forget about me!
Stop trying to hide from me!
You used to be the Eighth Prince of Dongyue
who then became the Emperor!
I swear,
if there is even half a lie in what I said,
then I'll die the moment I leave my room!
Careless? Against the moral codes for men?
I think you're just too hung up on matriarchy!
You won't stop talking about rules and precepts.
Those are nothing but prejudices.
Her state of mind impresses me
and coincides with mine,
even more than Father's.
To seek her help
would be way more efficient than
marrying the Empress.
Since she has taken a liking to me,
it'd be a win-win.
Don't these men
feel embarrassed for writing
such cheesy greeting cards?
These noble childes admire Your Highness
so much that they're impossible to turn away.
A word from the Empress.
Your Highness, please manage
your subordinates well.
If it were to happen again,
the consequences will be severe.
Your Majesty, the assassination incident has been
taken care of.
From what I can see,
Second Princess has become more bold
than before.
Exactly right, Your Majesty.
According to our scouts,
Her Highness indeed seems odd.
After she had awoken from falling
into the water,
her temperament has become a lot more lively.
She even dared to
say that men and women are equal,
and even criticized matriarchy.
How has the Mo Residence been recently?
Mo Yuan Long has been living in seclusion.
No signs of treason.
The Eighth Young Master of the Mo family has been
punished quite frequently, seems quite down.
In the end, the young master of the Mo family
is not him.
If the wind shifts,
there's no need to keep him.
Yes, your Majesty.
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪A flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part,
no matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part,
no matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪♪We leave our steps behind
in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪