♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
=The Eternal Love S3=
=Episode 05=
What's up?
Starting to have an attitude to the wife
after becoming a concubine?
In the main hall,
I said that you'll only be able to follow through
if you follow your heart.
Why do you not understand me?
You're always putting on different acts.
How would I know if you're being serious?
Do you think I'd joke around with
my true feelings?
I told you, no matter when
and who we have become,
I'll find you
and fall in love with you.
I'll marry you a thousand times.
We'll never be apart.
Cheng Cheng.
♪Wisps and strands are hard to put aside♪
♪The day we become lovers of two lifetimes♪
♪We can never return to our very first encounter♪
♪Everyone knows love has always been
difficult to fulfill♪
♪Yet I still bet on it with a lifetime♪
I'm like this again.
Will you blame me again for
disobeying the Three Orders and Three Rules?
You did this while aware of the rules.
You won't believe me if I say you were the one
who initiated this.
Well,
I'm not going to waste my energy on crazy people.
Wait.
In the main hall,
did Her Majesty approve our plans?
Yes.
You'll be my concubine.
Mo Yan Chen will be my wife.
I can't tell if it's a good thing
that I've fulfilled my wish while not having
my memories.
Eighth Brother,
how can you blame it on Tan Er
when the Empress granted the marriage?
Tan Er,
I know it's not the best decision for you,
but please don't blame it on Lian Cheng.
He has his reasons.
I thought he was going to blame me
for marrying Mo Lian Cheng.
Why is he comforting me?
I'll take him home.
For what he did to you,
I'll make it up to you on his behalf.
Let's go.
You must do something to make it up to me.
Screw him.
They can finally get married.
I'm jealous.
It'll be your turn very soon.
Greetings, Father.
Congratulations, brothers.
The imperial order has arrived.
Second Princess has thought it through.
Only this way, Eighth Brother and I
can be lucky enough to serve the same wife.
Since your wish has been fulfilled,
do not let Her Highness down.
I understand.
I won't let Father down.
Eighth Brother,
it's normal to not be together with your loved one.
The past is the past.
It's better to face it
than to dwindle in sadness.
Eldest Brother,
there's nothing going on between
Second Princess and me.
I will not be a threat to you.
I understand, there's nothing to explain.
You love Her Highness so much,
but she seems to be a free spirit.
It would probably…
Eighth Brother,
it's not a husband's place to discuss his wife.
I understand the personality of Her Highness.
I know all about
the powerlessness of Her Highness
throughout this whole thing.
You don't have to say anything more.
But...
There are no buts.
Both of us will be serving the same wife,
we'll need to support each other,
as not to leave any opportunities
for others to gossip.
The marriage has been set and
the virginity inspection is coming up.
Eighth Brother, are you worried?
The virginity inspection?
Eldest Brother, are you worried?
Me?
I certainly am not worried.
However,
didn't the Empress order you to the palace
late at night?
But nothing was done, right?
It's not a minor thing.
Are you still... or not?
No need to ask more about it.
Eighth Brother,
even though the Empress is the one
granting the marriage.
If you go back on your word,
I'll find a way to make
Second Princess only marry Eldest Brother.
I haven't settled on an answer,
but you seem to have an answer.
I just want to remind you that
if you know something's going to happen for sure,
it'd be better to plan ahead.
Are you worrying about me
or our family's reputation?
If you've made up your mind,
be ready to face the consequences.
Feng Yang.
I'm a princess of a kingdom.
It still takes so much to get married.
It's almost like the Single's Day sale.
[*Single's Day is a shopping holiday in China]
You put in the deposits in a split second
but spend the rest of your life paying the bills.
I'm doing so much.
These men aren't doing anything.
That's not fair.
They can't just do you like this.
They have to go through the virginity inspection.
Virginity inspection?
To check whether they're still virgins.
Men can be inspected as well?
I heard that
it's a skill that has been passed down
for generations.
No one knows exactly how except
for those virginity inspectors.
These secret skills
are usually fake.
I can't say for sure about other things,
but the virginity inspection
is definitely precise.
There was once a nobleman
who was selected by the Empress
to join the harem.
He was punished by law
because he didn't pass the inspection.
How was he punished?
He's no longer with us.
Oh no.
Cheng Cheng's body should
belong to the Eighth Young Master of this world.
If something had really happened between him
and the Empress,
wouldn't he be in big trouble?
That doesn't make sense.
If so,
why was the Empress so sure about
granting this marriage?
Unless…
Jing Xin,
hand this to Mo Lian Cheng.
Keep it a secret.
Go.
On it.
I've never asked for anything in this life
besides money.
Please keep Cheng Cheng safe.
(Don't worry,)
(Jing Xin and I will be right outside during
tomorrow's virginity inspection.)
(We'll rescue you)
(if anything starts to go wrong.)
(You'll always be my Cheng Cheng)
(regardless of your virginity status.)
She might be a player,
but she is indeed responsible.
(I've heard someone say that)
(the most important moments of your life)
(will stick)
(even if you have forgotten about everything.)
(It's just like that Sakura tree.)
(The fragrance and the petals are always there.)
(No matter how many lives have passed,)
(we'll always meet again under the Sakura tree.)
(Cheng Cheng, no matter if you know about it)
(or not,)
(you'll be able to remember the times)
(that we were with each other once again.)
(Because those memories)
(can defy the flowing time.)
Why do her words
make my heartache?
The fragrance of Sakura
resides deep
in my heart.
Could it be...?
(Tan Er)
(If you see this letter when you return, please
wait for me to find you. Please. Tan Er)
Tan Er.
(Virginity Inspection Bureau)
Jing Xin.
Are you sure about waiting over here?
Yes.
Why don't we see anyone?
I need to go and check.
I was worried that something
would happen to you.
Your handwriting is still terrible.
What?
We've been together for such a long time.
Asshole.
Why didn't you tell me that you're back?
It's fun tricking me, right?
Your Highness.
Open the door, Your Highness.
If you keep it closed for longer,
rumors against the Eighth Brother may spread.
Whatever the rumors may be,
I'll handle them for him.
If Your Highness doesn't open the door,
I'll have to open it myself.
Since Your Highness didn't find anything,
I'll be taking Eighth Brother back home.
No one can leave without my permission.
Your Highness should know,
if there is no reason to decline the marriage,
you shouldn't be seeing the groom
before the wedding.
Otherwise, you'd make a huge mistake
and must plead guilty to the Empress.
Even if you can handle it,
the Mo Family can't.
(Mo Residence)
I'll have to find a way to get out of here.
If I can't see Tan Er before losing my memory
again,
I don't know when we'll meet again.
Father, I've been waiting for so long.
I'm finally able to be with you face-to-face.
Father, how have you been?
If you truly care about my well-being,
then you shouldn't be causing any trouble
before the wedding.
Feng Yang told me about what happened
at the Virginity Inspection Bureau.
I apologize for not being caring.
The plan has yet to be carried out,
how could you speak as if you were a prince?
My mistake.
Father, have you thought that
seeking power too eagerly
will cause you to be eaten alive by the power?
Such a stupid opinion.
Only those who aren't at the top
will be harmed by these.
What you should really be concerned about
is how to win the Second Princess's heart.
Are you getting married just
to waste your virginity?
Stay here
and think thoroughly about your mistakes.
Come.
My Lord.
Lock the door.
Yes, My Lord.
Father is still trapped by his ambition
Even in another universe.
Tragedy may occur again
if I don't
stop him.
(Mo Residence)
I'll have to go find Tan Er.
How can I do that
without being noticed?
It's pretty exciting
to secretly visit a guy's room
late at night.
Cheng Cheng.
Tan Er.
You've evolved.
You stayed for a much longer time this time.
You're even better.
You know how to pick locks.
Young Master,
you look so gorgeous and tasty.
How dare you.
Refusing me?
Are you trying to flirt with me?
What you took from me at
the Virginity Inspection Bureau
should be returned to me now.
Return what?
You are mine.
If I return it to you, wouldn't it still be mine?
♪She longs eagerly day and night♪
♪Each stitch sends love from afar♪
♪Only, how could she let you know of her misery♪
♪All is well in her letters♪
Can you stop switching back
during critical moments?
Again?!
Whenever I see her, I can't control my actions.
Did she play some voodoo trick?
It was just a kiss.
We already have a child.
Kissing is nothing.
A child?
You don't believe me?
Isn't there a mole on your left inner thigh?
You!
You must have paid
the Virginity Inspection Bureau
to spy on me.
You can't do anything you want even if
you're a princess.
You...
So it's all my fault now?
What a slacker.
Don't switch.
Confront me just with this face.
How dare you change?
How dare you?
I'm beating you up.
Tan,
you're mad at the Eighth Young Master again?
If I don't let my anger out,
I'll have a serious breakdown.
Since you love face-changing so much,
how about I call you 72 metamorphoses?
[*Magic Power of Sun Wu Kong in Pilgrimage to the West]
Isn't it normal for a man to be fickle?
You never know what a man thinks.
Can't deny that.
Oh right, the Secretariat
wants to ask Your Highness
about Prince Consort's living arrangements.
Snow Court.
Snow Court?
Snow Court is the backyard.
Change its name to Snow Court.
My design skills
are superior.
But I only got to
assist my customers in designing theirs.
It's finally my turn
to show people my skills.
Jing Xin, bring me some pen and paper.
Alright.
Here,
plant a Sakura tree.
Install a pavilion
here.
Zhuo, Qi,
you're doing it wrong.
The longer ones should face that way.
Yes, Your Highness.
The fabric is also wrong, Jing Xin.
It should be softer than this.
We've already changed it five to six times.
You're describing it in such detail that
it almost sounds like you've seen it before.
So smart.
How is the bed doing?
The design I gave you.
We're making it according to your design.
But if you keep doing this,
aren't you worried about getting into trouble?
I don't mind getting into trouble
if I can live here happily
with Cheng Cheng.
♪From a full moon to a new moon,
who longs for loneliness♪
♪Lonely music-playing looks to the waning lights♪
♪In the end, it is but a vague period
in the years gone by♪
(I'm the most handsome guy of Dongyue)
♪Still keeping this face in mind for
a thousand years♪
(Jing Xin's cutie)(I want a kiss)
I don't know if Cheng Cheng will ever be okay.
If I knew better,
I wouldn't have fought with him in Dongyue.
I didn't know he put in such effort
to win me back again.
♪From breaking down the barriers
to falling helplessly in love♪
♪We share a night of happiness,
till deaths do us part♪
What?
I heard that Princess named your place
the Snow Court.
Think about it.
This means she's playing it cool with you.
Snow Court.
She could've given it any other name.
Why Snow Court?
It sounds so sad.
It's like you're thrown into the cold palace.
(Snow Court)
Why does the name sound so familiar?
Why is my heart aching?
Young Master, your crown and formal robe
should be much better than those
of Eighth Young Master.
But look at this…
You are losing boundaries.
Eighth Brother and I are serving the same wife.
Competing with one another is taboo.
You should be even more careful
after you follow me into Second Princess's
residence.
Don't cause any trouble.
Yes.
You and Her Highness are deeply in love.
Her Highness will like it
no matter how the robe looks.
There's no freedom of marriage
for those of the royal family.
Since I'm marrying the one I love,
I have no other wishes.
Eldest Princess is here.
Greetings, Your Highness.
I've already told you,
you don't have to be this formal with me.
Your Highness is Tan Er's eldest sister.
After the wedding,
Your Highness will be my eldest sister as well.
I must be respectful.
Mi Xue.
Your Highness.
Leave us.
Threads made of gold and silver.
Hundreds of embroidery workers spent three years
to finish this one piece.
That one is too average. It doesn't fit you.
Tan Er knows my taste.
I quite like the wedding robe she gave me.
You have big ambitions.
Why do you suffer in silence?
You avoided me as much as possible.
But compared to Qu Tan Er,
I know you better.
But I have already found my happiness.
This robe
will find a better owner.
This robe belongs to you.
You'll take it one day even if
you don't take it today.
You'll wear it one day even if
you don't wear it today.
Your Highness,
you can pick any man you want in this world.
Why are you spending so much effort on me?
There are thousands of phoenix trees
in this world,
but I only long for one.
Yan Chen,
do you remember the time at Jingyi Pavilion?
Eldest Brother,
you aren't in charge today, but why are you...
Second Princess finished her articles
very quickly.
She just left.
You're late.
Fourteenth Young Master.
Coming.
Eldest Brother, I'm leaving.
Jing Xuan.
(Phoenix rests on the phoenix tree)
(Pearl and jade piece together as one)
Pearl and jade piece together as one.
Please forgive me, Your Highness.
I overstepped.
♪Those are simply two fans, love doesn't lie♪
♪This wound burnt deeply,
now we have forgotten one another♪
♪How come my eyes turned red all of a sudden♪
♪This wound has made my heart strong♪
♪It is just confusion in the mortal world♪
"Tons of wine won't make you drunk,
great articles won't be forgotten after centuries."
I've heard this poem somewhere.
(I won't let you escape this time.)
(Asshole, in the name of the moon, I'll punish you!)
Why does all this look so familiar?
Did something
really happen between me and her?
Cheng Cheng.
I'm coming.
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪A flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪the love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part,
no matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part,
no matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind
in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪