Our Secret
EP20
Thank you.
The end-of-the-world fireworks
gave me a reason to apply for Hua Qing University again.
Tomorrow
is the opening exhibition of the robotics competition.
Would you like to come?
Don't push your luck here.
We had a deal today.
Hanging out together was an accident.
Well then,
you are gonna have to hang on a little longer,
cause I'm not giving up.
Xianxian.
Su.
What are you doing here?
I tried to find you in your room.
Your roommate said you were out.
It was raining outside.
Hope you didn't get caught in the rain.
With me around,
she won't.
Am I interrupting something?
No.
A little bit.
Well, how about you give us a minute, then?
Sorry.
There's something about work
to discuss with Xianxian.
She's getting a little tired.
What about another day.
Su, it's okay.
What do you need me for?
Let's find a quiet place,
that we can sit down to talk.
Okay.
Let's go.
Xianxian, look over this.
This is...
You're everywhere!
Good point.
What's wrong with me being a customer here?
Xianxian,
There was this comic book company in the Huai city,
who asked us to design an app.
It's almost done
and is about to be launched.
The Director Zhang of the comic book company,
asked me if I could recommend an artist.
And I thought of you.
Tech companies make comic book apps, too?
Your company really does everything.
Yeah, because we are a startup company.
The boss wants to try various services.
He's got foresight.
Thank you.
If he doesn't,
he wouldn't send me here to cooperate with Xianxian.
You're right about that.
That could be the only common point
that we share.
But,
I have no experience in
working on comic book apps like this.
Don't worry about this.
This app is currently the first one in China.
and the only professional platform exclusively for comics.
I think it's quite good.
I wonder if you're interested.
So what do I need to do?
It happens that we are currently in the Huai City,
if you're interested,
come with me to see director Zhang tomorrow.
Tomorrow? Tomorrow is probably not okay.
Are you...
Are you going to see him?
No.
The show-stand for our comic club need to be prepared tomorrow.
I'm afraid I can't make time.
Then...
I'll make arrangement when you are free.
That's great. Thank you, Su.
So I'll take my leave now.
I have to work on my sketch tonight.
Let me walk you to your place.
Don't we all stay in the same hotel here?
See you then. You don't have to walk me there.
Wait a minute.
I need to talk to you.
Could you please give us some privacy?
Su,
how about you go first?
Okay.
Remember to rest early.
If there's anything,
call me at any time.
Okay, Su, bye.
Bye.
Good night.
Go ahead.
To be honest,
I don't like this guy very much.
But,
what he just said,
sounds like a good opportunity.
It worth you consideration.
You chose to do what you love,
I'll definitely stand behind you.
Then I'll go back to my room.
Don't forget to come to the robot exhibition opening tomorrow.
I'll be waiting for you.
Did you two make up?
We were never together.
There can't be "make up".
Forget about that.
You betrayed me!
You've been in the amusement park all day,
and earned a course from Professor Ye.
Couldn't ask for more.
Xianxian's not here yet?
How could it be？ It's late already.
Hurry up.
Lou Feng.
You put this here first,
then go upstairs to get tomorrow's schedule.
And you need to check out tomorrow's costumes in the dressing room.
I have to go to the dressing room?
I'll go to the dressing room.
My work is done here anyway.
You're not going to the robot contest opening?
No time for chat. Just move.
Okay, see you then!
Xianxian, I love you!
Get the schedule, hurry up.
Sir, this truck is ready to go!
Are you guys ready?
In a minute,
everyone's going to the central exhibition hall to give speeches.
Could you wait for some minutes?
We need few more minutes.
How many plans are you gonna show?
Let's go with one first.
Are you doing this or not?
You can start the show now.
Don't wait for me.
I'm sorry.
Without Xianxian,
you can still give the show of your robot.
Without her here,
there is no point in doing the show anymore.
Why don't you just go inside? It's fine.
So, one two three four five six...
Why is it locked?
I'll go to the dressing room. My work is done here anyway.
Anyone out there?
Someone's in here!
Good work. See you guys.
Bye! Bye!
Xing Lufei, I got the schedule.
Good.
Then we're done here today.
Good work.
So...
Where's Ding Xian?
Ding Xian is...
She went to check out the dressing room,
and then I think there's something urgent, and she just left.
Then I'll see you.
Bye.
Something urgent?
Boss,
The opening ceremony is over.
I don't think Xianxian will come.
Why don't we just go?
It's okay. You can go.
You don't have to wait for me.
Okay, don't be too late.
No worries.
Sir, why do you have Ding Xian's cell phone?
Oh, I'll fetch it right away.
Wasn't she with you?
Don't tell me she is...
still at the Comic-Con Center.
Ding Xian!
Zhou Siyue!
Zhou Siyue, I'm here!
Ding Xian!
I'm here. Can you hear me?
Ding Xian, are you in there?
I'm locked inside!
You step back a little!
Step back, okay?
Are you all right?
I'm okay.
Come.
Getting in here like this,
are you sure we won't get caught?
It's an emergency after all.
Just give me a second.
How did you get locked up in there?
I have no idea.
You have to be more careful from now on.
If I'm not around someday,
what should you then?
Well...
I'm sure I'll get out the next day.
I could just wait for someone to open the door for me.
That's enough tough talk.
Oh,
how was your opening ceremony?
I didn't do it.
Why?
Aren't you here,
just for the robot contest?
That's not entirely true.
I'm also here for you.
My little Lord Zhou,
when did you become so unambitious?
That's because,
I am sure enough that
I can get the first place in the contest,
and I will get you too.
I'm leaving.
Why do you hate being with me so much?
Zhou Siyue,
when did you become such a scoundrel?
Maybe you should get to know me better.
Come here.
Stay here and don't move.
Fellows, I'm leaving.
I want to go away and look around.
Will you come back?
I'll be back. Bye!
Goodbye!
We'll wait for you to come back!
I'll miss you guys.
Don't you forget to miss me!
Help, help!
He's awake! Yes!
That's great!
I thought
that you never check Weibo.
"Little Monster Dairies"
Catchy name.
Ding Xian,
you once asked me
what is true love.
Now I know the answer.
Her look seems ordinary,
yet I finding her beautiful day by day.
It's like...
she is so stubborn that almost makes in rage
and yet making me feel,
she is the cutest in the world.
It's like knowing that she's lying,
and yet,
I just couldn't spoil her poor acting.
It's like...
always crying like a mess,
and yet she is still attractive.
You're a mess.
Who is that
you are talking about?
Ding Xian,
I love you.
Would you be my girlfriend?
What are you doing here?
Who let you in?
How did you get in here?
Now you people don't even give a shit
about us security guards anymore?
Put down your information!
We're sorry.
I brought her there.
So, it has nothing to do with her.
You young lovers nowadays...
Must you have to seek thrills?
Write. What are you looking at?
Just write, everything!
We're not lovers.
Look at your good-looking face,
how come you can't even get a girl?
I was working on it.
And then you cut me off.
Y'all wait here for a sec.
I'll go for a check.
You can't leave until everything's clear.
You haven't given me an answer yet.
Zhou Siyue,
I'm sorry.
I'm not planning on a relationship.
Gee, you,
you sure can hold a grudge.
Fine,
I'll be waiting for you.
I'll wait for your answer.
Xianxian.
why are you here?
Su.
Mr. Su, what brings you here?
You know them?
They're my friends.
Here.
Thank you.
That's it. You can leave now.
Don't do that again.
Mr. Su, see you then.
Good work.
Why are you here?
The contest starts tomorrow.
I'm here to check the procedures with the organizer.
Are you going back to the hotel?
I can give you a ride.
Sure.
Thank you.
Xianxian,
your mom called me the other day.
She asked me to take good care of you,
since we are both in the Huai City now.
I'm a little busy these days,
when I'm done, I'll take you out for fun.
Mr. Su, you're so busy,
maybe we should forget about these social courtesies.
That's where you're wrong.
For me, Xianxian was never a courtesy.
She always sees me as a brother, too.
Does she?
Then how come I have never heard her mention
you, her big brother?
Maybe it's because you two
were never that close?
It's no wonder that you didn't know.
Of course Xianxian wouldn't tell you.
She wouldn't tell anything to a stranger.
Even if she doesn't tell me anything,
I know what she likes,
and what she dislikes.
Xianxian,
I want to talk to you,
about the comic book app.
What is it?
Do you mind giving us a minute?
It's not a secret.
Can't you talk in front of me?
It's okay, Su. Go ahead.
Director Zhang of the comic book company
saw your works on your Weibo, and liked them very much.
He's having a dinner tomorrow,
and wants to sign the contract with you in person.
That's great. Thank you so much, Su.
I didn't do much.
I just introduced you.
I'll take you shopping for some clothes tomorrow.
It's better to dress formally.
What's wrong with her clothes?
It's okay, Su.
I have clothes.
Don't worry.
Okay then, I'll go with you tomorrow.
Don't be nervous.
Ding Xian won't be nervous.
You don't know her very well.
I'll see you then.
Zhou Siyue,
I have told you,
stay away from Xianxian.
I have told you too,
I won't let go.
So that's all for today's discussion,
I hope that in the contest,
we'll all have a good performance.
Thank you all.
Awake now?
You took notes?
Good for you.
Career, love,
acing in both.
Look at him,
what a social butterfly.
Talking to everyone.
Come on, it's none of your business.
Let's go.
Where are you going?
Comic-Con.
Maybe you shouldn't go.
Why?
Because Xianxian is not there.
How do you know that she's not there?
I asked Lou Feng and she told me.
Then where is she?
She's...
she's taken back to the hotel by Su Bocong.
Xianxian, how was your show today?
It went well.
And there were a lot of people.
I finished just now.
So you haven't eaten all day?
- I'm used to it. I'm not hungry. - Ding Xian!
Why didn't you answer my call?
My cell phone is dead.
Weren't you at the academic conference?
Why are you back so soon?
It's over.
Don't you have a speech to prepare?
I pulled an all-nighter and finished it last night.
Then you should go back to your room and catch some sleep.
What are you doing here?
I wanna see you.
Mr. Zhou, you are really everywhere.
Can't seem to lose you.
Right back at you.
Mr. Su.
You're probably not in a position to laugh at me.
Anyone wants some juice?
- I'll get it. - I'll get it.
No, no, no, I'll go.
- Stay here. - Stay here.
Waiter, a glass of juice please.
What kind of juice would you like?
- Blueberry. - Blueberry.
Hot or cold?
- Cold. - Cold.
And sweetness?
- Full sweetness. - Full sweetness.
One cup?
One cup each.
I'll pay for mine, and he pay by himself.
Okay.
Thank you.
This is too much. I can't drink this much.
Xianxian, you must be hungry.
What about have a dinner together before we go back?
Okay.
Mr. Su, you treated me last time.
I feel quite embarrassed.
I'll pay this time.
I haven't said yes yet.
Sure.
Why don't we call up everyone?
We haven't had dinner together yet in the Huai City, anyway.
I know a place that is quite good.
However,
Mr. Zhou, I'm afraid it's gonna cost you.
Don't worry about me.
You should worry about
whether you stand a chance anymore.
Too sour.
See you around.
You're back.
What is this?
Blueberry juice.
No, thanks. It's too sour.
Rumors had it, two cute guys
went for you at the same time today.
Tell me tell me,
are you super happy today?
How is that possible?
They are two big babies!
I am so annoyed.
Anyway,
I'm still rooting the CP of you and Zhou Siyue.
You liked him for so many years.
If you can't be together,
it'd be such a huge shame.
Actually,
he asked me If I would be his girlfriend.
I almost said yes.
You refused?
I liked him for so many years.
And he's only been after me for a few days.
If I just say yes so easily,
I'll be completely controlled by him
in the future.
You have a point.
But,
I always feel that something is missing
between the two of us.
What is missing?
I don't know.
I can't figure it out.
Is she going?
It's his treat this the evening.
Are you going?
Forget it. I'm not.
Come now!
I'll go out for a while.
Bocong,
why didn't you go inside?
I want to tell you something.
What is it?
Here's the thing.
I know that you like Ding Xian.
I can help you.
Why are you helping me?
For Zhou Siyue?
Well, they're not together yet.
I still have a chance. So do you.
Lou Feng,
did you forget something again?
You're so...
Why are you here?
To take you to dinner.
I'm not hungry.
You don't want to see me?
Don't flatter yourself.
I'm buying dinner for everyone because of you.
I can't believe you're not even coming.
I didn't ask for that.
Anyway, I'll starve myself here if you won't go.
I'm not leaving.
Fine, I'll go.
I'll go eat.
Welcome!
Xianxian.
Here.
Xianxian, this way, I saved you a seat.
Okay.
Zhou Siyue, sit here.
Boss, here.
I'm telling you,
we've been here for so many days,
and didn't get the chance to get together, right?
Today, my boss pays the bill.
Just order anything you want, cheers!
Okay, thank you, Prince Charming.
You're welcome.
Just enjoy yourself.
Here, order the food.
Thank you.
I want this.
Thank you, handsome.
Nice that we're together here today.
Let's not just eat.
How about playing a game?
Which game? Just the one we used to play.
The King game.
I brought the cards. Here.
You are all prepared.
Of course.
Do you know how to play?
I don't know.
Here, I'll deal.
It's okay. I'll teach you.
Pass it on.
First hand, who's the king?
I am the king.
My order is simple.
Give me a toast, and call me gorgeous.
That'll do.
Who do you want? Right. What's the number?
What's the number? What's the number?
Number two.
Number two. Who's number two? Who's number two?
Who is number two?
Gorgeous, to you.
What? I can't hear you.
What?
Ban Jiayu, sorry.
You gorgeous, here to you!
Drink it up! Up, up.
Drink up. You're good.
Well done.
Nice.
Go on, go on.
Who is the king? Who?
I am
the king.
Number three should ask number six a question.
Fine, number three, number six.
I'm number six.
Who's number three? Number three.
Number three.
Go ahead and ask.
A question.
Have you done anything bad lately?
What kind of question is that?
You should get punished. Come on.
Are you serious, Zhou Siyue?
You're still holding the grudge about me stealing your chocolate?
That's mean!
That doesn't count. Change the question.
That's fine. I have asked already.
I'll have one myself.
You drink up.
Drink up.
I'm in poor health, don't mess with me.
No problem.
Come on.
So this time, you deal.
Okay.
What kind of question was that?
I'm missing one here.
I suspect that the other day,
it's her who locked you in the dressing room.
No way
I am the king.
Since you are all so uptight,
I'll be the bad guy.
So, number five and number four.
Kiss each other.
Number four, number five.
Okay, okay,
Who?
Who is it?
Who? I'm number five. I'll punish myself.
Wait.
Let's drink together.
Drink up, drink up.
You can hold liquor just fine.
Boring, no kiss.
Boring.
One more round, one more round.
Boss, I...
Zhou Siyue, see you.
See you.
Bye!
Thank you, Prince Charming.
Take care of Yuanfang.
Why should I take care of Yuan Fang?
Zhou Siyue,
You should be clear that
she'll live a better life if she is with me.
The point is if she wants or not.
I don't think so.
Give me some time.
I'll make her understand.
That's some wishful thinking of yours.
That's the truth.
So long as she's willing to,
sooner or later, we'll belong with each other.
What about you?
whether you're studying abroad, or finding a job,
you don't really think that your little high school romance,
is enough to get you through all that, do you?
Think it over.
Here's your change, sir.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Now I declare the robot contest
a successful complete.
In this contest,
we've seen
outstanding students from major universities across the country.
Nanjing University, Heilongjiang University of Science and Technology...
How much longer is this gonna take?
Any minute now.
So now, we're going to announce
the top three of this year's robot contest.
First of all, the champion of this contest,
goes to Zhou Siyue from Hua Qing University.
Let's have Zhou Siyue up the stage for the award.
Thank you.
Hello, everyone.
I am from Hua Qing University.
I'm Zhou Siyue from the research team.
Hello?
Siyue, use this one.
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
Liu Xiaofeng.
It's been a while.
Yes, indeed.
You're here representing the University of Science and Technology?
Yeah.
Why did you go to the University of Science and Technology?
I remember you said you wanted to study economics
You remember that?
Actually, I am majoring in computer because of you.
Uh-wait, no, I didn't mean...
Don't get me wrong.
I'm just really grateful to you.
I'm not sure if you remember,
when the college entrance exam was close,
I was very nervous.
The pressure of that last year of high school was too much.
In fact, I am also very confused.
Whether I get in the university or not,
I am not sure what I should do in the future.
What kind of person I want to be.
In this world,
There are many, many hard-working people.
But not everyone
can get what he wants.
But,
if you can't get what you want through hard work,
then what's the point for working hard anyway?
We work hard so we won't regret.
If it wasn't you,
I would have no confidence to go to the college.
That's gross, man.
No, I mean it.
At that time,
I always thought that you were so out of touch.
But ever since you hang around with Ding Xian,
you've got a little more human touch.
Am I this cold-blooded before?
No.
How do I put it? It like...
Maybe I think that's who you really are.
How are you two now?
Are you together?
Not yet.
I'm still waiting for her.
Why wait?
She's been waiting for me all these years.
I...
should give her enough patience too.
But have you ever thought about this,
for a girl as good as her,
she's never short of admirers.
You're right.
Then see you!
Wait.
What are you gonna do?
Go find her.
Hello, hello.
Excuse me, where's Zhou Siyue?
He has some business to attend to and left.
If you have something important,
I can tell him.
Here's the thing.
I want to work with him on a project.
Here is my name card.
Please do give it to him.
Okay, thank you.
- Xianxian. - Su.
Wait a minute.
What's the matter? It's the first time I wear high heels.
Not very used to it.
It's hurting my feet.
You look...
beautiful today.
Really? Yes.
Thank you!
This is for you.
Su.
You've helped me a lot.
I can't take any more gift from you.
And this is too expensive.
Not really.
Just for good luck.
So you could successfully seal the contract tonight.
You're wearing such a beautiful dress,
it should go with a nice necklace.
I can do it myself.
It looks great on you.
Thank you.
If I can seal the contract,
I will buy you a big meal.
I really wish you don't be too polite with me.
Let's go.
Here.
Thank you.
Let's go in.
Director Zhang.
Okay, you can go.
Su, you're here.
This is...
This is the one I told you about before,
the author of the Little Monster Dairies,
Ding Xian.
She's so young!
How do you do, Director Zhang.
First of all, thank you very much for enjoying my comic.
I hope we can have a pleasant collaboration.
About the content of comics,
here's what I think.
I have some new ideas,
and I hope to give you a briefing.
Sure, please.
Here's my idea.
What about making your little monster,
personified.
Then we give the little monster a romance,
and let him fight against evil monsters to level up.
Meanwhile, we lengthen the content.
The audience nowadays,
like that kind of stuff.
By the way, if the contract with this little lady
has no problem,
let's sign it today.
Excuse me, Director Zhang,
I need to go to the bathroom.
Director Zhang, will you excuse me for a moment.
Okay.
Xianxian,
are you all right?
Yeah.
I just find...
this is different than what I thought.
Xianxian,
people in this line of work
only care about maximizing profits,
which might make you a little uncomfortable.
But,
he doesn't even care about my idea about the work,
or the ideas I want to convey.
The two are inherently different.
The comic series that you started out at first was for yourself.
You don't need to care about other people's feelings.
But when it comes to commercial use,
you have to consider whether the public likes it or not.
That's just the way it is.