♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 35=
Why did I dream of a dragon?
Why did Yuchi get hurt in my dream?
Why am I so worried?
You cast Seven Deadly Spell on him?
Where is he?
He is gone.
It’s alright if he is dead.
Now,
no one can stop me
from taking the Yin Soul.
If it was not your birthday today,
Master wouldn’t let you go.
You should have still been
at Introspection Wall
and not be able to get so many gifts!
Qingyan? Qingyan?
Did you hear me?
You…
What’s on your mind?
You’re over happy now.
You’ve been eating this peach cake
for an hour.
You made it so delicious.
So smooth-tongued.
Qingyan,
after your birthday today,
you will be an adult.
You’re the most valued
apprentice of Master
and you are gifted and smart.
You’ll be the
best candidate for the head of our sect.
You must work hard.
Why hasn’t Yuchi
come to see me?
When it’s my 18th birthday,
can you come to tell me
the stories of the past long ago?
Sure.
Is Yuchi in some trouble?
Qingyan!
Where are you going at this hour?
Yuchi!
Anyone here?
Hello?
Anybody here?
Don’t come in!
Yuchi!
I told you not to come close!
Yuchi,
is it you?
Yuchi, you got hurt?
Mortal,
why are you here
in my place?
Yuchi,
what are you talking about?
Look carefully.
I’m Qingyan!
Qingyan?
I miss you so much.
Yuchi.
You have mistaken me for someone else.
I will never mistake you.
You are Yuchi.
Why don’t you recognize me
after just a few days?
Is it because
you got hurt?
Your body is so hot.
Let me get you some water.
Don’t bother.
You should leave now.
I need to heal your wounds!
Yuchi,
why are you pretending
you don’t know me?
You are a human.
I’m a demon.
We are different.
You should go now.
You really don’t know me anymore?
I never keep those
unimportant things in my mind.
It’s getting dark.
You should go now.
Unimportant things?
Go now!
It’s raining outside.
Can I wait for a moment?
It has already stopped.
But it’s still thundering.
It’s just thunder.
Then…
I’m going.
My mind had been settled as still water
through the previous thousand years.
The only thing that made my heart ripple
was meeting you.
You’re the shimmer in the dark night,
letting me see a glimmer of light.
Wait.
It’s dark outside.
Let me walk you back.
But, your wound…
It’s just Seven Deadly Spell.
I once said to myself that
I would never let anyone else
take care of you.
But this time
I have to break my promise.
I dare not to recognize you
not because I don’t want to,
but I don’t want you to suffer
the pain of loss like me.
I can only
walk you here.
Yuchi.
It’s too dark here.
I’m afraid.
Can you stay with me a little longer?
A man and a woman
walk together alone in the dart night.
It’s not proper.
Yuchi,
you haven’t told me
the stories of the past,
but
I always feel that
we have known each other
for a long time.
♪When dream is over I want more♪
You’re overthinking.
♪Memories make me miss you♪
I’m just a passerby in your life.
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
Passerby?
♪There’s regret when we part♪
If you’re afraid of the dark,
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
I can help you light up
this dark valley.
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
But, from now on,
you have to learn to walk bravely
on your own.
Yuchi,
I feel upset
to hear you say that.
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
Parting is a problem that
needs to be faced eventually.
♪To complete our destiny♪
Take it lightly
and you won’t feel so sad.
You don’t need me anymore.
Just go now.
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
I’ve thought of so many things
to say to you
during such a long reincarnation.
I want to tell you how much
I miss you and suffer.
I want to tell you
my love
has never elapsed with the time.
But, until the moment that you’re
leaving in front of me,
I suddenly don’t know
what to say.
♪For the exchange of my wish♪
Maybe looking at you quietly like this
is already my greatest satisfaction.
Yuchi,
Master taught me Mind-clearing Song.
It’s very effective
in treating internal injuries.
Let me play it for you.
Please, just let me do it.
The Seven Deadly Spell
has hurt me deeply.
I can’t hold on much longer.
Maybe…
I can’t protect you anymore.
Although it’s a torture to wait
and protect you for hundreds of years,
I’m glad to do it.
You gave me the Dragon Pendant.
I give you a sky full of fireflies.
I have got such a beautiful thing
to look forward to
in such a long time.
I have seen your youth,
your wedding,
your happiness
and sadness.
I was insisting on accompanying you
to go the long way,
to watch many fireworks,
but now
we can only stop here.
There are so many things
you can’t deny in this world.
Even though I enjoy the last time
with you so much,
I can only
keep you in my heart now.
Where else could she be
if not in the Kunlun Sect?
With Dragon King.
Where is Dragon King?
With Qingyan.
How dare you!
About the weird things Yuchi said…
Seven Deadly Spell…
It can’t be a normal wound.
I remember reading about it in a book.
The Seven Deadly Spell is based
on the sorrow, bitterness, loneliness,
separation, resentment,
hatred and anger, and unstoppable
(Seven Deadly Spell)
with the seven blades of Yin Wind.
The one injured by it
will have all the organs damaged,
the seven apertures blocked
and be slowly suffocated and dead.
So, Yuchi will die?!
(Mind-clearing Spell)
Yuchi.
I must be dizzy now.
It looks like
you’re standing in front of me
and smiling at me again.
You didn’t see it wrong.
I’m back.
Didn’t I tell you to leave
and not come back?
I won’t leave.
You told me
parting needed to be faced with.
But, I want to ask you,
if you don’t have much time left,
what do you want to do?
If it were me,
I’d want to stay with my beloved one.
Why bother letting your beloved one
suffer the pain of parting?
Parting is painful.
But if you can’t even share the pain
with your beloved one,
isn’t it another kind of pain?
I’m afraid the time left is too short
to say anything before
we say goodbye.
Even if only for a moment.
But this moment
is precious to me.
I think it’s worth it.
Sometimes,
a lifetime feels like a moment.
But sometimes,
a moment is eternal.
♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
Sometimes, a lifetime
feels like a moment.
But sometimes, a moment
♪Bright or dim♪
is eternal.
♪Fate is like a rain of flowers♪
♪Withering in the sentimental world♪
I’ll keep this precious moment
eternally in my heart.
No matter how short our time
together will be,
I want to be by your side.
I’m not afraid of the pain of parting.
I’m only afraid that
I can’t be with your
in the last time you have left.
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
I want to be with you.
Just let me stay by your side.
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
Thank you.
♪I wanna stay with you in this life♪
I don’t know why.
I feel so familiar with this place.
It’s like I’ve been here before.
What’s on your mind?
I don’t have much wealth.
I only have this Dragon Pool
and my thousand-year power.
I hope you don’t mind.
I don’t care about that.
I only care about you.
Now you have known that I’m a demon.
I saw your Dragon Horn that day.
Then, will you be responsible for me?
Responsible?
Don’t you know that?
The play says that
if a man looks at a woman’s body,
the woman loses her chastity.
Then the man has to be responsible
for the woman
and will definitely marry her.
Now you have seen my horn.
I’ve lost my chastity.
I just saw your horn.
It’s not so bad like
you lost your chastity.
About my chastity,
if you want it,
I’m happy to give it to you.
I don’t really want it.
I have so many things I want to do,
but I don’t know which one to do first.
Then, do the one
you want me to do the most.
Where are we going now?
To see the beautiful place
in your dream.
Don’t be afraid.
I’m here with you.
(Luofeng Pavilion)
Finally! You’re awake.
Where is Xue Qianxun?
Lord left with Immortal of Fate.
Where did they go?
I didn’t ask.
But, Lord looked weird.
I thought something was wrong.
Can you find him?
Xue Qianxun! Xue Qianxun! Xue Qianxun!
Even the Three-call Spell can’t work.
He must be in a trouble.
My feather!
What are you doing?
I’m activating my inner core
to take my feather back to my body.
Then I can have the strength
to go find Xue Qianxun.
But, you can only get a temporary
effect by absorbing the power so fast,
and it will affect your longevity!
Xue Qianxun didn’t answer
my Three-call Spell.
He must be in a trouble!
Do me a favor, please!
It’s so beautiful!
How I wish
time can stop at
this moment.
Although this moment is beautiful,
I wish
you can have more beautiful moments.
I have had.
This feeling is so familiar,
as if I’ve dreamed
of it before.
It’s not a dream.
In fact, I’ve been with you
for a long time.
We did
fall in love with each other here.
But back then, we could only
be each other’s passerby.
And now,
we can finally have each other.
How come I don’t know any
of what you’re talking about?
There are things
that just need to be known by me alone.
I don’t like this.
I hope I can bear all the things
together with you in the future.
I promise.
How did you
fall in love with me at the beginning?
Because you are my destiny.
I want to be with you forever.
Just like this.
What’s wrong?
I don’t know.
Feels like some kind of power
is tearing me.
Someone is putting his hand
to your soul.
Show up.
Surprise!
Just because of the Yin Soul,
when I asked you
for the Book of Fate of Liuying,
you said you didn’t have it.
You’ve been coveting it
since then, right?
I just didn’t want you to have
too many entanglements
with that mortal girl at that time.
You used me to help her
become a princess,
nourishing her soul with the noble power
of the royal family.
Then you let her be born
in the general’s family
to strengthen her essence.
And in the end you arranged her
to cultivate immortality,
nourishing her soul
with the spirit power
of the Kunlun Sect.
The purer her soul is,
the more power you will gain.
That’s right.
With the nourishment of noble power,
the power of strong essence
and the protection of spirit power,
the Yin Soul can be mature enough.
If it can be used by the people
with cultivation like me,
it can become a heaven defying thing.
By then,
I’ll be no longer the Immortal of Fate,
but the master of the whole world!
During all these years,
aren’t you afraid that someone else
will take her away?
You’re here with her.
You’re such an infatuated one.
You’re so scheming.
I’m scheming?
How was I treating you
before you met Liuying?
We’ve been friends for years.
Don’t force me.
You’re hurt by Seven Deadly Spell.
What else can you do?
Darn it!
So, he was just trying
to cast blindfold spell
by having such a long talk with me.
I’d like to see where else you can hide!
Immortal of Fate wants
to take Qingyan’s soul away.
I thought about it.
This is the safest place.
You dragon demon!
How dare you talk nonsense!
Immortal of Fate is an immortal!
Not a demon!
Why would he want Qingyan’s soul?
I warn you…
Priest Xuanyang,
please help me take good care
of her in the future.
Qingyan is my apprentice.
I will take care of her.
Qingyun, bring me
the greatest treasure of our sect.
Gather all the disciples.
I will set up a barrier
with everyone’s power.
No immortal or demon
will be allowed to step in.
Yes.
Before that,
I’ll help you hold them back.
You?
You’re hurt badly.
No big deal.
Alright, I’ll lead you out.
Qingfeng, be on guard.
Yes.
Yuchi Longyan,
we’ve been friends for a thousand years.
Once I get the soul,
you can join me to rule
the three worlds!
If you dare to hurt Qingyan,
I will make you disappear!
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪