=Miss The Dragon=
Princess Liuying! Don’t run!
Go wait for me in the carriage.
I’ll be there in a moment.
Yes.
Little firefly, where is your master?
What took you so long to come?
♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if the moon shone for you♪
♪Bright or dim♪
♪Fate is like a rain of flowers♪
♪Withering in the sentimental world♪
♪In a flash I picked your teardrop♪
♪Does my heart ripple with memories♪
♪Only to remember you♪
Let go of me!
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
That Dragon King protects his love.
I protect you.
Yes.
Are you afraid now?
I’m…
I’m not so afraid.
I’ll protect you forever.
Trust me,
will you?
Yes.
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
I see.
To return a favor is to marry you.
Now that I pledged to be yours,
I won’t ever change.
You’re always my Liuying.
Your name Liuying means fireflies,
so, I’ll give you a firefly rain.
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
Liuying,
I love you.
Since we have feelings for each other,
and promise each other a lifetime,
we can get married.
I’m flying in the sky now!
You’re taking me fly in the clouds!
This is just like what I imagined!
You imagined this?
Yes, I did!
Hold on tight!
Yes!
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like a sky of fireflies♪
♪Settling in the sentimental world♪
♪Like stars♪
♪Shining for the travelers♪
It’s so beautiful.
Now you’re a general,
but you still like these things.
I like the fallen flowers,
the fireflies,
and the fireworks.
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
Liuying.
Ayu.
Chenyue.
So,
you’re always with me.
No matter who you are,
I’ll always be with you.
Where are we going now?
To see the beautiful place
in your dream.
Don’t be afraid.
I’m here with you.
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I wanna stay with you in this life♪