♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 36=
Immortal of Fate wants to take
Qingyan’s soul away.
I thought about it.
This is the safest place.
You dragon demon!
How dare you talk nonsense!
Immortal of Fate is an immortal!
Not a demon!
Why would he want Qingyan’s soul?
I warn you…
Priest Xuanyang,
please help me to take good care
of her in the future.
Qingyan is my apprentice.
I will take care of her.
Qingyun, bring me the
greatest treasure of our sect.
Gather all the disciples.
I will set up a barrier with
everyone’s power.
No immortal or demon
will be allowed to step in.
Yes.
Before that,
I’ll help you to hold them back.
Yuchi Longyan,
we’ve been friends for a thousand years.
Once I get the soul,
you can join me to rule
the three worlds!
If you dare to hurt Qingyan,
I will make you disappear!
What a waste of our friendship.
Up to you now.
Wake up!
He won’t wake up.
Even if he wakes up,
he won’t forgive you.
After all, he becomes like this
because of you.
Why am I here?
Master,
where is the man who took my back?
You shouldn’t get anxious.
Calm down.
Master, just tell me.
I will go find him if you don’t tell me.
Master! Let go of me!
Qingyan,
the one who took you back
is not a human!
He is a dragon demon!
Master,
you know he is a dragon demon?
Did you hurt him?
He approaches you
just for your soul!
Fortunately, I found it in time
and didn’t get you hurt.
Master, it’s impossible!
He has been protecting me
for hundreds of years.
He will never hurt me.
Don’t you remember what I told you?
Human and demon are different.
Master, our love for each other
is true and sincere!
He got hurt by Seven Deadly Spell.
I have to help him!
You’re bewitched by him.
I forbid you to go to him again.
Just play the Mind-clearing Song
here alone to calm down.
Master!
Master! Let me out!
You’re hurt by Seven Deadly Spell.
If you use your power at this time,
you will be killing yourself.
It’s going to be a tough battle,
but I can delay it
as much as I can.
Put it into the barrier.
You will die soon
without your inner core!
This may be the last time
I do my best to protect her.
What should I tell her if she asks
about you after she wakes up?
Tell her to forget about me.
Tell her that
I approached her
just for her soul.
Aren’t you afraid that
she will misunderstand you?
As long as I can make her forget me.
I don’t want her to live in pain.
I’m ashamed
of my prejudice in the past.
Master! Let me out!
Master!
You can’t leave Yuchi
there alone!
Master!
Master! Let me go out!
Master…
You integrated your inner core
into the barrier?
You really want to die!
Since
you don’t want to live anymore,
I don’t have to show mercy on you.
Master said you couldn’t leave!
No one can stop me today!
Step aside!
No! You can’t leave here!
The entire Kunlun Mountain
is protected by a barrier.
Master.
Senior, I’m sorry.
Yuchi,
I hate you!
Not because of your ridiculous excuse
of approaching me on purpose
for my soul,
but because you want to
hide it from me again.
You are
facing something alone again.
Didn’t we agree to share it together?
Don’t try to leave me alone again!
You’re looking for death!
Qingyan!
We promised
to face it together.
It’s too late.
Once Immortal-trapping Net
is started,
nothing can stop it.
You disappointed me a lot.
You should be happy for me.
I’m about to be the supreme King
of the three worlds!
You said you would marry me.
But, I can’t wait till that day now.
(Yan Yue)
Thank you, Liuying.
I see.
To return a favor is to marry you.
♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
No matter who you are,
I’ll always be with you.
That Dragon King
protects his love.
I protect you.
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
Now that I pledged to be yours,
I won’t ever change.
You’re always my Liuying.
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
Yuchi!
♪I keep my love for you♪
No!
Come back!
She,
her soul,
even a single hair of her is mine.
What does it have to do with you?
The person I have always cherished
so much in the long time
is now killed by you
so easily like this.
I have guarded her
so carefully through three lives,
but you just destroyed
it all in one moment.
She has given her soul to me.
Give it back to me!
Now that I can’t die,
the pain will torment me forever!
And I will always remember that
it was your ambition
that caused all of this!
I will make you pay back
for all these!
Xue Qianxun! Stop!
Dragon King!
Are you going to kill him?
Xue Qianxun! Xue Qianxun!
No! No!
I won’t let you get yourself killed!
Xue Qianxun!
Wake up!
Emperor!
Help me!
Yuchi Longyan has absorbed the Yin Soul
and is going to rebel!
Emperor!
I don’t want to die! I…
You took her away from my world!
I will now return
all this pain to you
a hundred times,
a thousand times!
Xue Qianxun!
Xue Qianxun! You…
Wake up…
Qingqing,
it’s so good to see you.
You can’t die.
Hang in there.
I’m the Lord of Luofeng Pavilion.
I won’t die.
Don’t leave me here alone.
Don’t cry.
I remember you said
I look good when I smile.
Xue Qianxun!
Deep love will be broken.
Fate can’t be decided by himself.
The Star against the Heaven
will be lonely with a cursed kiss.
But if you’re willing to die for each other,
this curse
can be reversed.
A bloody kiss can reverse the curse.
The Lonely Star can be
against the Heaven.
Your fate is in your own hand.
The deep love is a sure thing.
Qing.
I first met you a hundred years ago.
The bride was not you
when I was the groom,
and the groom was not me
when you were the bride.
I had prepared the most beautiful
wedding for you,
but now
I can’t wear the red dress for you,
but I can only wear the
mourning clothes for you.
What’s the point of living
with only me left?
If I can’t remember you in my next life,
you must remind me early
of our promise.
I will.
I’ll seize you tightly.
Hope you’ll be well prepared.
I’m now by your side,
reminding you every moment,
but you don’t remember our promise.
Bold Yuchi Longyan!
How dare you absorb the Yin Soul!
The rebellious act against the heaven
will get yourself destroyed!
That is…
Supreme Thunder.
It can crush all things
and all souls.
Nothing can withstand it.
We could have been together.
But the heaven broke us up.
Since the heaven broke us up,
I will get justice from it!
The heaven
has deceived my for three lifetimes!
I will make you pay back
what I have lost doubly!
All the demons and ghosts!
Gather and work for me!
He is summoning the resentment
of the demons and ghosts!
Under the Supreme Thunder,
everything will become ashes.
Their souls
are destroyed.
Actually…
Isn’t Dragon King stupid?
How could he fight against the heaven?
If he pled with the Emperor,
there might be some chance
of reviving Liuying.
Immortals have the most
magic treasures, right?
But…
I know.
Don’t comfort me.
It’s not his style to
talk nicely and beg someone humbly.
But, I think,
that’s all?
He had waited for hundreds of years.
But, this is how it ends?
It’s not like that…
No.
Don’t tell me that
they once had each other at least.
They should be together
for at least one lifetime.
I agree.
So,
look.
What’s this?
I just used the Immortal-trapping Net
to take in their souls.
Why didn’t you tell me earlier?
Tell you earlier?
You didn’t allow me to.
Great! They can finally
be together!
And I don’t need to fix the Sky Net.
I’ll leave the job to the two of them.
Yes.
(End)
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪