LORRAINE: I had a vision in Amityville.
I had a premonition of your death.
(SCREAMS)
We have both seen
the same inhuman spirit.
Mom, who's that?
LORRAINE: The demon
in your painting is real.
- (WIND HOWLING)
- (CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(METAL CREAKING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Are you certain
we're making the right decision?
We have no other choice.
(SISTER VICTORIA
BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SISTER JESSICA SIGHS)
(DOOR CREAKING)
Will the relic truly save us?
Have faith, Sister.
(CRYING) Our Father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name,
thy kingdom come,
thy will be done,
on Earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread.
And forgive us our trespasses
as we forgive
those who trespass against us.
- (CHAINS RATTLING)
- (SISTER JESSICA SCREAMS)
(WHIMPERING LOUDLY)
(CONTINUES WHIMPERING)
SISTER JESSICA: (PANTING) Take it!
This evil needs a vessel to escape.
It will come after you next.
Don't let it have you.
- You know what you must do.
- I can't.
Then not even God can save...
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(ROARING)
(SISTER VICTORIA YELPING)
(PANTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SISTER VICTORIA CRYING)
- (DOOR OPENING)
- (GASPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CONTINUES BREATHING HEAVILY)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Forgive me, Father,
for the sin I'm about to commit.
(CRYING)
(GASPS)
(CONTINUES CRYING)
Forgive me, Lord.
(CHAIN RATTLING)
(CREAKING)
(MAN SINGING IN FRENCH)
(GRUNTING)
(CONTINUES SINGING IN FRENCH)
- (CROWS CAWING)
- (PANTING)
(CAWING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(IN ENGLISH) Oh, God.
(CROWS CAWING)
- (DOOR OPENS)
- (FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
BISHOP PASQUALE: Father Burke?
Bishop.
BISHOP PASQUALE: So, the last time
you were here was what night?
Six, seven years ago?
FATHER BURKE: After my time
as a chaplain ended in the war, yes.
Well, we appreciate you coming again
under such short notice.
(DOOR OPENS, CLOSES)
Father Burke.
Sit.
We have received news
that a nun has taken her own life
at an abbey in the mountains of Romania.
Suicide is a terrible, terrible sin.
But it doesn't strike me
as strong enough reason for a reunion.
But the news of it would not bolster
our argument to keep
with the faith and the Church.
- You're not telling me something.
- Why do you say that?
Because we're in the Vatican.
Let me put it this way, Father.
In this, albeit, rare instance,
we do not believe
we're the ones with the secret.
BISHOP PASQUALE: Those are your
travel documents and contact information
on the man who discovered the nun.
He lives near the Abbey
in a small village called Biertan.
You will want to talk to him first.
Also in the file is the name
of a postulant who can help
assist you in your inquiries
since it is a cloistered convent
and your access will be limited.
She's also familiar with the territory.
SISTER IRENE: I have survived
many terrifying encounters.
But nothing could have ever
prepared me for this.
My only hope now was that
the beast could not smell me.
But then, the wind changed and...
- (ROARS)
- (STUDENTS GASP)
- (SCREAMS)
- (STUDENTS LAUGHING)
Run for your lives!
Mother Superior says that
dinosaurs were never really alive.
God just put their bones here
to test our faith.
That seems like a pretty dirty trick,
don't you think?
GIRL: But they're not in the Bible.
SISTER IRENE: Well, do you believe
in penguins and koala bears?
- ALL: Yes.
- They aren't in the Bible either.
The Bible is God's love letter to us,
but it doesn't mean that
He doesn't want us to ask questions
about the wonders of His creation.
- But Mother Superior says...
- (GASPS)
Wait a minute. You've got
a little something on your nose.
- There.
- (STUDENTS LAUGH)
Ahem.
(STUDENTS GASP)
STUDENTS: Ooh!
- SISTER IRENE: The Vatican?
- I'm as surprised as you.
- I haven't even taken my vows yet.
- Oh, he's aware of that.
He's waiting for you in the garden.
And change into your habit.
This is an official visit.
FATHER BURKE: It shouldn't take
more than a few days, at most.
You were recommended for the journey
because of your familiarity
with the territory.
"The territory"?
Yes. Romania.
I'd never been
in that part of the world.
- Really?
- There must've been some mistake.
I apologize if you coming here
was a waste of your time.
No, no. No apology necessary.
Every decision the Vatican makes
is with purpose.
I'm sure they had
their reasons for selecting you.
(GASPING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
What is it?
Mr. Theriault?
Hi.
Jealous husband or angry father?
I'm sorry, what?
Well, usually it's one of the two
when an older man
and a young, beautiful,
not-so-innocent girl show up on
my doorstep at this hour of the morning.
I beg your pardon, Mr. Theriault,
but you and I have never met.
Oh.
Oh. Then perhaps it's time we did.
Call me Frenchie.
Everyone does.
Mr. Theriault, we are here because of
the nun you found at the Abbey.
How'd you...
Are you a priest?
And she is a nun.
Oh. (CHUCKLING)
Forgive me
for my impure thoughts, Sister.
I had no idea.
Never seen a nun out of her vestments.
Not that I'm opposed to it.
Excuse me.
Monsieur Theriault...
The Abbey.
Is it far?
In matter of distance, no,
but it takes time to get to.
If I may ask, why were you there?
I was delivering the quarterly supplies.
Apparently, the Abbey has had
some kind of arrangement
with the village for centuries.
FATHER BURKE: Do you think you could
take us there sometime soon?
FRENCHIE: I don't think so, Father.
Is there someone else
in the village, then?
Everyone in this village
pretend like the Abbey doesn't exist.
Even talking about it
might get you in trouble.
It's settled, then. You will take us.
- With all due respect, Father, I...
- Please, Frenchie.
(BOTH SPEAKING ROMANIAN)
You took a plane from Rome,
a bus from Bucharest.
Now, my friends,
you're in the Dark Ages.
- In the backwoods of Romania.
- (ENGINE STALLS)
(ENGINE STARTS)
Now, you travel by horse.
- Where are your things?
- (LAUGHING)
(WHISTLES)
(CONTINUES LAUGHING)
FATHER BURKE: "The postman's charge."
Ten letters with an "L."
Deliveries.
You have a knack for this, Sister.
SISTER IRENE: What brings a Frenchman
to the countryside of Romania?
Actually, I'm French-Canadian,
but don't tell anyone.
Doesn't sound as romantic.
I came here looking for gold
but when I met the people here,
I just knew this was the place
I was meant to be.
Wanted to help them. Any way I could.
That's very noble of you.
I know.
Tell me, Sister,
how long have you been a nun?
I'm not a nun yet.
I'm still just a novitiate.
You still haven't taken
your temporary vows?
"Temporary"?
I didn't think there was anything
temporary about being a nun.
Temporary vows would help prepare me
for a life of total consecration.
"Would," Sister? Or "will"?
(HORSE GRUNTING)
Whoa.
What happened?
- Everything all right?
- (HORSE WHINNIES)
FRENCHIE: We walk the rest of the way.
The horse won't go any further.
(SISTER IRENE GRUNTS)
Maybe you should get a new horse.
Well, it's not the horse, Father.
It's what lies ahead. He's scared.
The locals say it's a cursed place
and the horse agrees.
If I may ask, Father, why is it
the Church sends you on such tasks?
The Church reaches out to me
when it needs an investigation
into unusual phenomenon
associated with Catholicism.
Unofficially, they call it
"miracle hunting."
I thought we were here
because of a suicide.
We are, but it's only part
of our investigation.
I also have orders
from the Vatican to determine
if the grounds are still holy.
FRENCHIE: Well, I can give you
my opinion on that now, Father.
A result of the war?
Bombing raids, yes.
I've heard stories of how
the ground shook for days after them.
I've tried to find more information
on the castle itself,
but there's no record of it
in the village.
And the locals only spit
when it's mentioned.
- "Spit"?
- Yeah, to ward off evil.
It's an old and silly superstition.
And if you ask me,
these crosses that surround the Abbey,
they keep the evil in, not out.
Did you try to contact someone inside
when you found the nun?
FRENCHIE: I did. No one responded.
But then again, in the two years
I've been delivering supplies,
she was the first nun I'd seen.
FATHER BURKE: Frenchie, when you found
the nun, what did you do?
FRENCHIE: I moved it to protect the body
from the elements.
FATHER BURKE:
Where did you move it to, son?
In the icehouse.
It's where I leave my deliveries.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
When I found the sister,
I thought maybe moving her in here
would help preserve her.
Uh...
(MUMBLES)
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
(DOOR CLOSES)
I should tell you
one more thing, Father.
What?
That's not how I left her.
What do you mean?
She was laying down
when I left her here.
Not like that, sitting up.
There have been cases
of bodies twitching or sitting up,
not long after death.
Yeah, but, Father, who knows how long
she was dead when I found her?
You're not helping.
Sorry.
SISTER IRENE: Father, what is it?
It seems to be a key of some kind.
(DOOR RATTLING)
That's the door the nuns would
enter from to retrieve the supplies.
So they wouldn't have to
leave the castle.
We should give her a proper burial.
(PRAYING IN LATIN)
(BELL RINGING)
(IN ENGLISH) It was common practice
during the plague.
When people feared to be buried alive.
If you were unfortunate enough
for it to happen,
you could ring the bell
to let those above ground know
they have made a mistake.
I think being here is a mistake.
(RINGING)
FRENCHIE: That's where I found her.
How is that possible? It's been weeks.
I told you. This place is...
What's the opposite
of a miracle, Father?
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SISTER IRENE GASPS)
(SHUDDERING)
Hello?
Please excuse us
for our unannounced arrival.
Hello?
THE ABBESS: What is it you want?
I'm Father Anthony Burke.
This is Sister Irene.
Are you the Reverend Mother?
THE ABBESS: I am.
You haven't taken your vows yet.
Uh...
(STAMMERS) No.
- Please...
- Why are you here, Father?
We come on behalf of Rome,
to inquire about the recent death
in your convent.
THE ABBESS: "Recent death"?
One of your nuns.
I found her outside.
Hanged from the neck.
(THE ABBESS SPEAKING FRENCH)
(IN ENGLISH) Would you allow us
a moment, please?
THE ABBESS: You should leave with him.
Are you saying you weren't aware
of the recent passing of the nun?
Rome is concerned about the safety
and well-being of your cloister.
I'd like to speak with the sisters
so I can offer my assurances
to the Church.
THE ABBESS: I can offer
the assurance you seek.
I'm afraid that won't suffice.
They will just send more, and perhaps
less diplomatic, church officials.
THE ABBESS: Yes, Father.
However, the gate
will be closing shortly
as we are about to take our vespers.
Followed by the Great Silence
which ends midmorning.
Come back tomorrow
and you will find the answers you seek.
There is lodging in the convent.
You may stay there.
Thank you.
FRENCHIE: Why could you not
talk to the sisters now?
Why must it wait till morning?
The sisters take a vow of silence
from sunset to sunrise
that must be respected.
You should begin heading back yourself.
I imagine you don't want to be caught
on those roads when night falls.
Better the roads than here, Father.
We'll be fine, son.
Come back in a few days.
That should give us enough time
to get what we need.
Yes, Father.
(GASPS)
Hello?
(LEAVES RUSTLING)
Hey.
Hey!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
- (DISTANT ANIMAL SOUNDS)
- (CONTINUES BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTING)
- (GRUNTS)
- (SNARLS)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(YELPING)
I'll take (GRUNTS) that.
(PANTING)
Okay.
All right.
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
- SISTER IRENE: Father?
- Hmm?
You mentioned "miracle hunting" before.
Is that...
Is that a role you sought out?
No.
God, no.
(CHUCKLES) I'm a part of a small
select few the Church relies on to
look into their more
unusual matters.
So, you know Bishop Forne?
How do you...
Because he helped me when I was younger.
I had a series of visions
when I was a girl.
My father believed
I was mentally unstable.
Or worse, a liar.
But word of my visions
reached the Church.
Cardinal Conroy, specifically.
And he sent Bishop Forne
to meet with me.
What were your visions?
(SIGHS) There were many.
Never the same one repeated.
But after each one ended,
the same thought
would be stuck in my head.
Which was what?
"Mary points the way."
(FATHER BURKE SIGHS)
What is it, Father?
I was thinking of a similar incident
I encountered in France. During the war.
I was stationed there. Near Lyon.
I was told to investigate
a boy with visions.
(DANIEL BREATHING HEAVILY)
But, unlike your case,
after what I believe
was careful evaluation,
(SNIFFS)
I made the judgment he was possessed,
and proceeded to act accordingly
within the laws of the Church.
My God. Daniel...
What have they done to you?
(DANIEL SNARLING)
Was it a success?
The Church thought so.
They believed the evil was cast out.
But not you.
(SNARLING CONTINUES)
Most Glorious Prince
of the Heavenly Armies,
St. Michael, the archangel...
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
(CRYING) Help me, Father!
Come to the assistance of Daniel,
whom God has made in His likeness!
(SCREAMS)
- Behold the Cross of the Lord!
- Why won't you help me?
Ye hostile forces!
(SCREAMING)
Daniel sustained severe injuries
during the exorcism.
Ones from which he could not recover.
Daniel, I'm so sorry.
He died days later.
I often wonder if I was too eager
with my determination.
That is a puzzle.
(STATIC CRACKLES)
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC STOPS)
- (FOOTSTEPS RUNNING)
- (OBJECTS CLATTERING)
(FOOTSTEPS RUNNING)
DANIEL: (WHISPERS) Father.
(THUNDER CRASHING)
(RUSTLING)
(TWIG SNAPS)
DANIEL: (WHISPERS) Father.
Daniel?
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(DANIEL GAGGING)
(SNAKE HISSING)
(GRUNTS)
- Wait! No! Help!
- (POUNDING ON DOOR)
Help! No!
(BELL RINGING)
(WIND HOWLING)
(CHURCH BELL TOLLING)
Help!
Somebody.
(EERIE CHANTING)
(EERIE CHANTING CONTINUES)
(GASPS)
(SHUDDERS)
(GROWLING)
(YELPS)
- (BREATHING HEAVILY)
- (CROSS CREAKING)
(GASPING)
- (GRUNTING)
- (POUNDING ON DOOR)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(RINGING)
Help! Sister Irene! Help!
(BELL CONTINUES RINGING)
Father! Father?
Father?
(PANTING)
(CONTINUES RINGING)
(GASPS)
(BELLS RINGING)
(RINGING INTENSIFIES)
Help!
Help me!
(GASPS)
(SINGLE BELL RINGING)
- Father?
- (MUFFLED) Sister?
Sister Irene!
Father, I can hear you!
- (POUNDING ON DOOR)
- I'm right here!
(PANTING) Oh, thank God. Thank you.
(GRUNTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(MUFFLED RINGING)
(SCRATCHING)
(SISTER IRENE GRUNTING)
(SCRATCHING CONTINUES)
(GRUNTING)
(THUDS)
(SHOVEL THUDDING)
(SIGHS)
(GRUNTING)
Hurry!
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
- (GRUNTS LOUDLY)
- Wait! Wait!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(FATHER BURKE GRUNTING)
(GASPING)
- (PANTING)
- (COUGHING)
Thank you. Thank you, Sister.
(GRUNTING)
How did you get in there?
The ground was covered.
There is a powerful evil presence
in this place.
Maybe those books will help
shine a light on our answer.
SISTER IRENE: There's more of it.
How is that possible?
- Another puzzle.
- (CHURCH BELL TOLLING)
Abbess?
As requested,
we are here to speak with the nuns.
It seems like that's as much
as an invitation as we'll get.
I'll go find the Abbess.
Take this.
See what you can find out about it.
It was obviously important
to the deceased.
Sister. Be careful, please.
I will, Father.
- (CHURCH BELL TOLLING)
- (THUNDER RUMBLING)
Hello?
Wait!
(SISTER RUTH PRAYING IN LATIN)
(WINGS FLAPPING)
Sister?
(CONTINUES IN LATIN)
SISTER OANA: (IN ENGLISH) Sister!
We mustn't stop praying,
even for a second.
This convent has had
perpetual adoration for centuries.
The sisters pray in shifts
to maintain a constant vigil.
I am so sorry to have disturbed her.
Sister Ruth has withstood more than
just someone sneaking up behind her.
I'm Sister Oana.
We were told you were coming.
Please, follow me.
(CONTINUES IN LATIN)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
What?
Another round.
I told Luca it was on the house.
- FRENCHIE: Why did she cover the mirror?
- It's tradition here when someone dies.
You cover the mirror, so the deceased
doesn't see their reflection
and become a ghost.
Someone died?
You didn't hear?
Luca's daughter committed suicide.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
I can't believe it. She was just a kid.
Twelve years old.
Hanged herself in his barn.
Hanged herself? Why?
Why did Addi Constantine's crop
turn to dust?
Why was little Stefan struck blind?
It is that place. The Abbey.
Whatever evil is up there,
it's leaking out, poisoning us.
(SPITS)
And that couple you took
up there yesterday.
- Who were they?
- Priest and a nun.
Are they still up there?
Yeah. Pick them up tomorrow.
You recently discovered a body
up there, didn't you?
Yeah, Grigore, yeah.
Well, I believe you're about
to discover two more.
FATHER BURKE: "And out of the ground
formed every beast of the field
"and every bird of the sky.
"And whatever the man called
the demon creature, that was its name."
"Valak.
"The Defiler.
"The Profane.
"The Marquis of Snakes."
(LOUD RATTLING)
Sister!
Sister Irene!
Sister Victoria's death
was a terrible tragedy for the convent,
but we still feel her presence.
She was the most devoted
out of any of us.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Excuse me, Sister.
- Sister...
- (DOOR LOCK CLANKS)
(DOOR CREAKING)
Forgive us, we're highly protective
of our privacy.
Some of the sisters would prefer
I not speak to you at all.
We appreciate your willingness to do so.
Sister Oana, can you tell me about
the history of this Abbey?
It was built by a duke in the Dark Ages.
The Duke of St. Carta.
He wrote countless texts
on witchcraft and rituals,
in which to call upon
the forces of hell.
Hell used him to open a gateway
so that an unspeakable evil
would walk amongst us.
(RUMBLING)
But the Church stormed the castle.
They sealed the gateway
using an ancient relic
containing the blood of Jesus Christ.
The Church claimed the castle
for their own
and our perpetual praying began
to secure the Abbey
and contain the evil.
For centuries it worked
and evil was kept at bay
until the bombs of war shook the Abbey
and evil found another way
to open the gateway.
Sister Oana, last night in the chapel,
I saw a nun.
She was... She felt anything but holy.
Do you see her, too?
I've seen her stalking
the hallways at night.
We all have.
She looks like us,
but she's not one of us.
It's something unholy.
It takes on different forms to
deceive us and prey on our weaknesses.
It appears as a nun
so it can hide among our cloister
until it can corrupt us all.
I fear her presence
means the portal has opened again.
It made Sister Victoria
commit the ultimate sin.
SISTER ABIGAIL: Sister Oana.
Sister Ruth is nearly finished
with her prayers.
- It's time you attend to yours.
- Yes, Sister.
You haven't taken your vows yet?
- No.
- Then this is not a place for you.
- You need to leave now.
- SISTER OANA: She can't.
The gates have closed.
You must stay until they open again.
When do they open?
SISTER OANA: Sunrise.
You must stay the night.
Sister Irene.
(WIND WHISTLING)
Good night, Sister.
Sister, wait.
Yes?
Sister Victoria had this
in her possession when she died.
Do you happen to know what it's for?
No.
(VOICE WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY)
Now, please, I must go pray.
(LOCK CLICKS)
(FOOTSTEPS RETREATING)
Where are you?
THE ABBESS: You won't find
another way in, Father.
Abbess?
THE ABBESS:
What is it that concerns you?
I'm afraid there's something
very wrong with this place, Abbess.
Like many places in this world,
the Abbey has a long history.
Not all good but we repent.
That nun, I found her
clutching the key in her hands.
What does it open, Abbess?
THE ABBESS: It's too late, Father.
Sister Irene is lost.
(BONES CRACK)
Abbess?
- (FATHER BURKE YELPING)
- (CANDLE CLATTERS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(THUNDER CRASHING)
FATHER BURKE: Sister Irene.
SISTER IRENE: Mary points the way.
(ECHOING) Mary points the way.
Mary points the way.
(SCREAMS)
(GASPS)
(SHUDDERING)
(RUSTLING)
(VOICE PRAYING IN LATIN)
- Who are you?
- (BONES CRACKING)
(PRAYER BEADS CLINKING)
(SHIVERING)
- God save you.
- (GASPS)
- (KNOCK ON DOOR)
(DOOR UNLOCKS)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(SISTER IRENE
BREATHING HEAVILY)
SISTER VICTORIA:
Sister, please come.
Sister Oana?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WATER DRIPPING)
(SISTER IRENE BREATHING HEAVILY)
(DOOR UNLOCKS)
(GASPS)
Oh, God.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WIND HOWLING)
(GRUNTING)
(CHAINS RATTLING)
(CONTINUES GRUNTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SCREAMING)
- (PANTING)
- (ROARING)
(SCREAMING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(MUFFLED WHIMPERING)
(WHISPERS) Quiet.
The evil grows stronger.
Get your things and meet me
in the chapel, Sister.
Only prayer will get us through
the night.
Go. Leave.
Now.
(VOICES WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY)
(SISTER ABIGAIL PRAYING IN LATIN)
SISTER IRENE: Hello?
(SISTER ABIGAIL
CONTINUES PRAYING IN LATIN)
SISTER IRENE: Sister Oana?
(SISTER ABIGAIL CONTINUES
PRAYING IN LATIN)
DANIEL: How long
have I been dead, Father?
How long?
Daniel?
I'm sorry.
(SHOUTS) Why won't you help me?
(RUMBLING)
(GASPS)
- (GRUNTING)
- (SNARLING)
(SISTER ABIGAIL PRAYING IN LATIN)
SISTER RUTH: We need to pray, now.
And whatever happens,
whatever you may see or hear,
keep your eyes forward
and don't stop praying.
(ALL PRAYING IN LATIN)
(GASPING)
(PRAYING IN LATIN)
- (ALL CONTINUE PRAYING)
- (SISTER IRENE PANTING)
(SISTER IRENE PRAYING IN LATIN)
(SCREAMS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CONTINUES PRAYING)
- (THUNDER RUMBLING)
- (RAIN PATTERING)
FRENCHIE: That's the door the nuns would
enter from to retrieve the supplies.
So they wouldn't have to
leave the castle.
(BELL RINGS)
(BELL RINGING)
(GROWLING)
No, no. (GRUNTING)
- (OBJECTS CLATTER)
- (SNARLING)
Holy mother of God.
(PANTING)
Frenchie!
Thought you could use some help.
Thank you.
But please, by all means,
next time, do use the shotgun.
Well, I'm saving that
for emergencies, Father.
(PRAYING IN LATIN)
(SNIFFLES)
(NUNS GROANING)
(GASPS)
(GROANING)
(GROANS)
- (POUNDING ON DOOR)
- (NUNS CONTINUE PRAYING)
FATHER BURKE: Sister!
Sister Irene!
(POUNDING CONTINUES)
SISTER IRENE: Father Burke.
(GROANS)
It's Father Burke. He will help us.
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
FATHER BURKE: Sister!
(LOUD POUNDING ON DOOR)
Sister Irene!
(SISTER IRENE GRUNTING)
SISTER IRENE: Oh, thank God, Father.
- Are you all right, Sister?
- (EXHALES SHARPLY)
Frenchie?
What happened?
We've been praying, all of us together.
Perpetual adoration, it's the only thing
that's been holding back the evil.
Who's been praying?
All of us. The other nuns.
They were here.
They were praying when we were attacked.
The nuns tried to warn me.
Visions.
They felt so real.
There's no one left.
We have our answer, Father.
As if there was any doubt before,
this place is no longer holy.
(FATHER BURKE SIGHS)
- Oh, Father.
- (SNARLS)
(ALL GRUNTING)
FRENCHIE: Father, what do we do?
(SNARLING)
Get my bag, Sister! Hand me the cross!
Put some holy water on it. Here, hurry!
Please, Father, hurry!
- (CHANTS IN LATIN)
- (SNARLS)
Hold it down! Cover its face!
(FRENCHIE GRUNTING)
(FATHER BURKE CHANTS IN LATIN)
(IN ENGLISH)
I cast out the demon in you,
in the name of God the Father Almighty!
And the power of the holy spirit,
I ask this in the name
of our Father, Jesus Christ,
who is coming to judge
both the living and the dead,
and the world of fire!
(GROANS LOUDLY)
(GASPING)
(SCREECHING)
(GRUNTS)
(ALL PANTING)
That felt like an emergency.
We're too late.
The evil is free.
No.
For the demon to enter our world,
it must possess a human soul.
Sister Victoria must have been
the last nun in this cloister.
SISTER JESSICA:
You know what you must do.
I can't.
- Then not even God can save...
- (SCREAMING)
It wasn't suicide.
It was a sacrifice,
so the evil wouldn't take her soul.
I did not understand
a word you just said, but, uh...
Sounds like
your investigation's complete.
So, let's get outta here.
We can't just leave.
Oh, come on. Why the hell not?
We have to seal the gateway,
to contain the evil.
SISTER IRENE:
The gateway is in the catacombs.
(FATHER BURKE GRUNTS)
But we can't close it without the relic.
The blood of Christ.
"Christ." Jesus Christ?
Did the sisters tell you where it is?
The Abbess was found dead
in the tunnel to the catacombs.
(SIGHS)
I think I know where that tunnel is.
Good. Then, that's where we look first.
But, Father, before we do,
I'd like to take my vows.
Are you certain?
My visions.
I now know they are a miracle of God.
And I am ready to commit my life to Him.
FRENCHIE: Now, that, Sister,
is a noble act.
It's a shame, but...
FATHER BURKE:
By the authority entrusted to me,
and in the name of the Church,
I receive the vows you have taken.
I earnestly commend you to God.
That your gift of self is made one
with the sacrifice of the Eucharist.
And might be brought to perfection.
May the love of God
unite you forever and ever.
(PRAYS IN LATIN)
(WATER DRIPPING)
FRENCHIE: Well, there's nothing here.
SISTER IRENE: There has to be.
They told me
this key unlocks a door to the relic.
That could be anywhere in the castle.
It is here. Don't you see it, Sister?
What?
Mary points the way.
(CLICKING)
(GASPS)
FATHER BURKE: The blood of Christ.
Holy shit.
The holiest.
Only a true bride of Christ
can wield something so sacred.
Wait.
What is it?
Shouldn't we say
a prayer or something, first?
There's a time for prayer,
and a time for action, son.
Now is the time for action.
Also still feels
like a time for prayer as well, Father.
"Finit hic, Deo." God ends here.
(DOOR OPENS)
SISTER IRENE: We need to search
everywhere to find the gateway.
(METAL CLANGING)
(FRENCHIE BREATHING HEAVILY)
(DOOR CREAKS)
- (SNARLING)
- (GASPS)
(FOOTSTEPS RUNNING)
VOICE: (WHISPERING)
Sister Irene, this way.
(SISTER IRENE GASPS)
Hello? (GRUNTS)
- (SCREAMING)
- (NUN SNARLING)
Sister Irene!
Sister!
(PANTING)
(SCREAMS)
(GASPS, SCREAMS)
(GASPS)
Irene!
(GRUNTS)
(VOICES WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY)
(NUNS CHANTING)
- (BONES CRACKING)
- (CHANTING STOPS)
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
Lord Jesus, in your Holy Name,
I bind all evil spirits to this fire!
Protect us from evil
with your holy light!
(LANTERN GLASS SHATTERS)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(GASPS)
(PANTING)
SISTER IRENE: Frenchie. Help me.
Of course.
(PANTING)
- (BONES CRACK)
- (GASPS)
(BONES CRACK)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(FRENCHIE PRAYING IN FRENCH)
- (SCREECHING)
- (FRENCHIE SCREAMING)
(IN ENGLISH) No!
(IN DEMONIC VOICE) You failed.
Just as you have failed
everyone in your life.
(FRENCHIE GRUNTING)
Tomorrow, a village will be missing
its idiot.
You should've kept running
when you had the chance, Frenchman.
I am French-Canadian.
(FRENCHIE GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
Run!
- (SISTER IRENE GRUNTS)
- (FRENCHIE GROANING)
SISTER IRENE: Frenchie!
(FRENCHIE SCREAMING)
(SCREAMS) No!
(HISSING)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
- (CHOKING)
- (SNARLING)
(GASPING)
FATHER BURKE: Sister!
Sister Irene!
- (SNARLING)
- (FATHER BURKE GRUNTING)
(SNAKE HISSING)
(CHOKING)
(HISSING)
(GROANING)
(GASPING)
(GRUNTING)
(CONTINUES GASPING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SHUDDERING)
(SCREAMING)
(SNARLING)
FATHER BURKE: In the name of the Father,
the Son, and the Holy Spirit.
(CHANTING IN LATIN)
- (SNARLS)
- (SCREAMING)
(SNARLING)
(GASPS)
(SPITS)
(SCREECHING)
(CONTINUES SCREECHING)
(SCREAMING)
(FRENCHIE GRUNTING)
No, no, no!
(PANTING)
(SOFTLY) Come on.
(COUGHING)
Okay.
(GROANS)
I hope you don't mind.
It's called "the kiss of life."
It's just called that way.
(STAMMERS) It's just, it's not really...
Frenchie, what's your real name?
Maurice.
Thank you for saving my life, Maurice.
You're welcome. (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
We should get going.
Into your hands, Oh, Lord,
we humbly deliver your servants.
The nuns of St. Carta.
They served you in this life
with strength and faith.
Deliver them now from every evil.
And let them live with you
in perfect grace, forever.
Amen.
Thought this ground wasn't holy anymore.
It is now.
Will you stay on in Biertan?
FRENCHIE: Oh, I think I've had
my fill of Romania.
(GRUNTS) My father was a tomato farmer.
Maybe I'll try that for a while.
Sounds a little boring
for a world traveler like you.
(CHUCKLES) Certainly hope so.
ED: An exorcism can be very dangerous.
Not only for the victim,
but for anyone in the room.
Take Maurice Theriault,
his friends called him Frenchie.
He was a French-Canadian farmer.
Nothing more than
a third-grade education.
Yet, after he was possessed...
- (SNARLS)
- (CHOKING)
...spoke some of
the best Latin I'd ever heard.
And like that, an upside-down cross
started to appear from within his body.
ED: Which brings me to the three stages
of demonic activity.
Infestation, oppression, and possession.
- (SNARLS)
- (LORRAINE SCREAMING)
English - SDH