♪Memories of the past are always vivid♪
♪They accompanied me to take every step♪
♪On the road♪
♪Going through heat and cold♪
♪The bumpy journey
has rendered my longing♪
♪Rock solid♪
♪The same moonlight
shines on our shoulders♪
♪Even if we are far away separated♪
♪We are close in our hearts♪
♪The wind blew away the past♪
♪I look for your distant location
on the starry night♪
♪In the ocean of faces♪
♪For you, my heart burns and races♪
♪Despite its turns and twists,
fate is in my hands♪
♪May waiting convert regrets
into a happy ending♪
♪May solitary figures
find right companions♪
♪And become a pair♪
=Time Flies and You Are Here=
=Episode 15=
(Life is unexpected and
what I wanted is not what I get)
Speak.
Well,
my childhood friends,
Cheng and Ying are getting married.
My family
wants to return to Yuyangli Village.
My mother...
My mother thinks that
since we're already married,
the relatives back at
Yuyangli Village
would like to meet you.
That's why she would like you
to return with me.
I'm not going.
Why not?
Why should I?
Well,
I heard you haven't been
in a good mood lately.
Why not you just treat it as a getaway?
A getaway?
Your village is filthy and squalid.
Do you intend to comfort me
with this trip
or show me off
as a trophy back at your village?
Zhao Xiaoqian.
What's wrong?
Fine.
I understand.
You don't have to go.
I'm going home to inform my mother.
Is that good enough?
What's going on between
the both of you?
What do you mean?
I just embarrassed my family.
I'm just throwing a tantrum.
Why did you say that?
What exactly happened?
Did you know
what was written
on the lantern she brought home?
To cut all ties.
Is that what Xiaoman feels?
What else
could it mean?
She invited me to return to
Yuyangli Village with them
to attend a wedding ceremony.
This family
doesn't treat me with respect.
Have you asked her about it?
Could there be any
misunderstanding in between?
Xiaoman doesn't seem like...
It doesn't matter.
She intends to cut all ties with me.
I should quit bothering her.
If it's truly a misunderstanding,
you should stop it before it's too late.
I'm playing chess.
It's just a wedding ceremony.
He wouldn't attend despite
how much I begged him.
He insulted weddings of our village...
Maoya.
Look.
It's a huge rooster.
This is tonic meant for
Commandery Prince.
(Commandery Prince's Mansion)
Trim the flowers well.
Hongsu,
is everything ready?
Yes.
Why is there a rooster in the mansion?
Lady Xie.
How atrocious.
Duke of Yongguo's death
anniversary is coming up.
The whole of the mansion
is solemnly prepping for the ceremony.
All you've done is fooling around.
How dare you bring in
such filthy creature?
The death anniversary
of Duke of Yongguo?
Hurry up.
Hurry up and throw
this filthy creature out.
Your Highness.
What's going on?
Can't you see I'm reading?
Zhu Momo is picking on Lady Xie again
because she brought a rooster home.
A rooster?
Zhu Momo is in charge of
the household affairs.
There's nothing wrong
in disciplining Lady Xie.
You shouldn't hurt her
because of a misunderstanding again.
I don't like your tone of voice.
I'm hurt as well.
Am I that heartless?
You did not clarify the situation.
Lady Xie violated the rules
and brought filthy creatures
into the mansion.
According to the rules,
she should be punished severely.
Zhu Momo!
Your Highness,
Lady Xie brought such a vile creature
into the front yard.
I'm afraid such an act will collide
with the spirit of late Duke of Yongguo.
My mother acquired this rooster
from the Temple of Confucius.
I was told to boil soup
from it for you and Xingzhou
as replenishment.
Besides,
a rooster is believed to bring luck.
All right.
I understand.
I'll punish her on your behalf.
I shall cook you up.
Wait a minute.
I need to ask you something.
What's it that you wanted to ask?
What's it called?
Who?
The rooster.
Why would you name a rooster?
What are you trying to ask?
Is this about its name?
(Lotus Garden)
Forget it.
It shall be named
Zhao Shengwu.
We had a horse named
Shengwu in the past.
It was a horse.
This is a rooster.
Why would you grant the rooster a name?
What's wrong?
Can't roosters have names, too?
Besides, this rooster
belongs to Xingzhou.
Xingzhou is my learning partner.
The rooster would be my partner, too.
It has to bear my last name.
What in the world is wrong with you?
That lantern...
What do you mean?
Does your mother really
want me to head to Yiyangli Village?
You're acting really strange recently.
You're really fickle.
I'm terrified.
Is it because
of Duke of Yongguo?
If you're upset,
you don't have to go.
I told my mother...
You sure are noisy.
(Lotus Garden)
Forget it.
I'll go.
I'll ask you after the trip.
Watch the rooster.
Do not look at me.
Zhao Shengwu, come here.
Mr. Liangji.
Besides serving His Highness,
I have to serve the horse.
Now, I'll have to serve
a rooster as well.
Life is hard.
What a pity.
Look at how plump the rooster is.
Bite it.
Bite its side.
Go on. Bite on it.
Bite it.
Awesome!
Fetch the money.
Here, Overlord Yan.
Apparently, Xu Shu from
the academy next door
organised a cricket competition.
All nobilities of the academy
received an invitation.
A cricket competition?
Didn't you receive it?
That can't be.
You're a son of a bureaucrat.
I'm not surprised.
A son of bureaucrat
has been following Commandery Prince
around like a lapdog.
Do you know what it means?
He was given great opportunities,
but he'd rather behave like a lapdog.
Eventually,
he'd be belittled and berated.
You're spewing nonsense.
I shall attend the event
with Zhao Xiaoqian tomorrow.
I'll show you
what true brotherhood means.
Prepare the cash.
I'd empty your pockets then.
Let's go, Overlord Yan.
Mother.
Why are you bringing
along roosters and ducks?
There are plenty at Yuyangli Village.
It's fine.
I can handle it.
They are here.
Madam Xie.
They are here, Madam Xie.
We are here.
Madam Liu.
Madam Xie.
Greetings, chief.
Greetings.
You're finally here.
How are you doing?
We're doing great.
That's good.
What do you think?
What a perfect pair.
We're at the presence
of the great Commandery Prince.
Pardon our failure to welcome
Your Highness appropriately.
Please rise, chief.
I'm here
at Yuyangli Village as a son-in-law.
Spare the formalities.
Yes, Your Highness.
Maoya did marry a man of prominence.
You're right.
Men from the city
are different indeed.
Chief.
The banquet is starting.
Let's enter the courtyard.
Sure.
The banquet begins.
Your Highness.
This way, please.
Let's go.
Please, Your Highness.
It looks comfortable.
You're all grown up.
Your Highness,
have some food.
Thank you.
Enjoy yourselves.
Here.
Thank you.
There's no good food
here in the village.
Your Highness.
These are fowls of the village.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
Here's a toast to you.
Cheng, is it time for a toast?
His Highness
is greatly concerned about Xiaoman.
Finishing this cup of wine
should be fine, right?
Quit standing around.
Hurry up and offer a toast.
May you be blessed with sons.
They are nobilities of the city.
They aren't used to our crude wine.
Isn't that right?
It's fine. Cheers.
Here's a toast to you.
May you be blessed with a son.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Your Highness,
please enjoy.
Feel free
to eat to your heart's content.
Go ahead.
Cheng.
Fellow guests.
Cheng,
can you request His Highness
to act as the host
to receive the bride?
Father,
what are you thinking?
He's the Commandery Prince.
His Highness can't possibly
act as our wedding host.
How would you know that
if you never tried?
On behalf of Maoya,
His Highness came all the way here.
Hurry up.
Father, you...
Listen to me.
Well...
You...
Your Highness,
my father would like Your Highness
to act as the host of our wedding.
That way, the harvest
will increase by the year.
That's right.
Is Your Highness willing to
receive my bride from the residence?
Sure.
I'm eternally grateful.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Your Highness,
please come with me.
Go on.
Enjoy yourselves.
Go along.
All right.
Look at my son-in-law.
He sure is great.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Let's drink up.
Cheers.
Drink up.
Chief, let's drink.
Here.
All right.
Cheers.
Xiaoman,
we haven't seen each
other in a long time.
Isn't that right?
If it wasn't for sister's marriage,
we wouldn't be able to meet you.
That's right.
Well, here I am.
Just now,
I sneaked a peek at Commandery Prince.
His Highness is
charming and attractive.
He's hundred times better than Cheng.
I can't wait for the harvest
during spring next year.
Cheng should get a change of face, too.
Don't say that.
I envy you on the contrary.
You may get married to Cheng
openly.
Although the village
isn't as wealthy as Wujiang Prefecture,
I know that Cheng
will only love you for
the rest of his life.
I genuinely desire to be with him.
He doesn't have the guts to mistreat me.
Look at you.
Xiaoman,
you're great at hairdressing.
I want you
to dress my hair for me today.
All right.
Let's see.
Your Highness,
please give me a moment.
I'll call for Your Highness
once it's ready.
Cheng.
Xiaoman,
are you and His Highness
in love?
Don't be ridiculous.
I...
I don't know.
Actually,
we signed a contract of two years.
We agreed
to part ways after two years.
In the end,
we aren't a real couple.
I beg of you
not to make fun of me.
That's enough. Forget it.
You asked me to host
the wedding previously.
Now that
the Commandery Prince is here,
you're fawning over His Highness.
Cheng,
well done.
Come on.
Don't say that.
It's my big day today.
Don't ruin the mood.
Was I wrong?
Maoya doesn't even
have feelings for His Highness.
She must be coveting
after his power and wealth.
I overheard Xiaoman telling Qiao that
the both of them
live separated lives.
I bet you didn't know.
Previously,
Maoya was caught in a
frivolous scandal.
Nobody would be able to
accept a woman like that.
Like I said,
a woman will turn foul
once she enters the city.
Who could have thought
that Xie Xiaoman
who grew up prude in the village
would end up behaving
promiscuously at the city?
Besides,
he only holds a mere title.
According to the tutor,
by the hands of the late Emperor,
his brother was...
Your Highness.
Right now, we are
considered...
What's it?
Our feelings could be considered
mutual.
His Highness is beating someone up.
Let's go check it out.
Let's go.
Stay right there!
Your Highness, please stop!
Please stop!
He...
Please stop hitting him!
- Please...
- Get over here.
Come here!
Stop hitting him!
What are you doing?
Zhao Xiaoqian!
Your Highness!
Zhao Xiaoqian, are you out of your mind?
Ask him what he said!
Repeat your words if you dare!
What are you going to do about it?
Xie Xiaoman,
what's wrong with your husband?
I did not say anything.
He came up and hit me right away.
I'm being accused.
How dare you?
Zhao Xiaoqian, what are you doing?
Why did you hit him?
I went easy on you.
It's someone else's wedding.
This wedding is
once in a life time for Ying.
How could you mess it up?
What did he say? Tell me!
Why did you hit him?
The wedding means nothing.
You still do not admit
we're husband and wife anyway.
You still insisted on
cutting ties with me!
Zhao Xiaoqian,
let's talk it out.
Do not touch me!
My brother's death anniversary
is coming up.
I'm in a bad mood.
I've caused a commotion.
My apologies.
Zhao Xiaoqian.
Xiaoman.
Son-in-law.
Why did the fight break out?
When I was fixing the garland
on His Highness,
I noticed he was clothed
in white garments.
I suppose
he's mourning as the death
anniversary of his family
is coming up.
His Highness came
to the village to attend my wedding.
I'm more than grateful.
I do not want this incident
to affect your relationship.
Mourning?
Did you say something
about Duke of Yongguo?
Yes, what's wrong with that?
Shut your pile hole.
How dare you?
Maoya!
What do you think you're doing?
I told you to squat by the walls!
It hurts!
You ran your mouth!
You're a man yet
you can barely keep your mouth shut!
You deserve to squat by the wall
for the rest of your life
for gossiping!
Chief,
give him a good beating later.
I am
conveying this message on behalf
of the Commandery Prince's Mansion.
The Commandery Prince's Mansion
will pay for the damages.
Well...
You may go on.
Excuse me.
I'm going after him.
Xiaoman,
wait for your mother
and take the carriage.
After passing by Xiongjie Camp,
there's a passage on your left.
Xiongjie Camp?
Xiongjie Camp under
the command of Xu Zi?
My mother will remain at the banquet.
She should take the carriage.
I would like to drop by Xiongjie Camp.
Do you have a cart?
Yes.
Your Highness.
The carriage was left behind
for Lady Xie and her family.
It's a long journey.
Is Your Highness planning
to return by foot?
I'll walk.
Anyway,
Master Yan's servant, Douzi,
delivered a letter.
He would like you to join him
in the cricket fight
at the brothel tonight.
He insists that you attend.
All right.
I'll meet him at the brothel tonight.
By the way,
how far is the next relay station?
It's up ahead.
Is this the Xiongjie Camp?
Hold it right there.
Who are you?
I...
I'm the concubine of
Commandery Prince of Julu.
I would like to meet
Grand Commandant Xu Zi.
One!
Two!
Three!
Is there any reconnaissance
on the route
to the city in the last couple of days?
One!
General,
the bandits are cunning and ruthless.
They robbed multiple households.
However,
among the soldiers we dispatched,
none of them was able
to track them down.
Two days ago, I made the soldiers
disguised as students.
They managed to figure it out.
They did not expose themselves at all.
One!
General,
a visitor seeks an audience.
Three!
I'm Xie Xiaoman.
I'm the concubine of
Commandery Prince of Julu.
Greetings, general.
One!
Concubine?
A concubine has the guts to question me?
The Commandery Prince's Mansion
sure is lenient.
I'm here for a reason.
Punish me as you see fit, general.
All I want to find out
is what happened between
Duke of Yongguo and
Commandery Prince of Julu.
Why would His Highness...
Silence.
How dare you question about
the matters of Duke of Yongguo?
You're a mere lady,
but you sure are bold.
You intruded an army camp on your own
and came directly to question me.
Are you aware
that if I keep you imprisoned here,
Zhao Xiaoqian would not
be able to get you out?
I'm well aware.
You're His Highness' master.
He'd never rebel against your will.
However, I came
for this purpose.
If I do not obtain an answer,
I'm not going anywhere.
Fine.
I would like to find out
on what rights do you
have to question me.
General, you intend
to capture the bandits
along this area.
I'm willing to offer myself as bait
to aid the capture.
(Commandery Prince's Mansion)
Douzi came by and said
Master Yan
is already waiting for
Your Highness at the brothel.
Fetch me my cricket.
I shall depart now.
Has Lady Xie returned to the city?
Yes.
The coachman said that
Lady Xie came back,
but she went to
Xiongjie Camp.
Xiongjie Camp?
What is she doing there?
Your Highness.
It's ready.
Bandits?
It's impossible for Wujiang Prefecture
to be infiltrated by bandits.
General Xu is guarding the city.
What are you talking about?
Your Highness.
(Notice)
This was issued by the magistrate.
It requests
Your Highness to minimise travelling
out of the city.
Prepare my horse!
Prepare the horse!
Hurry up!
(Brothel)
Why isn't Zhao Xiaoqian here yet?
Master,
you brought the cricket
to the academy
and had your share of fun.
Should we
return home right now?
I...
Old Master Yan will be
enraged if he finds out.
You're such a coward.
Xu Shu
is clearly underestimating me.
Regardless, today is the day
I must stand up for myself.
What...
What if we lost?
Do not jinx it.
Cut the crap.
Zhao Xiaoqian
would be bringing Zhao Jinguo over.
It's impossible to lose.
Give it to me.
I'm going to place my bets.
Master.
Hurry up.
All right.
Implore him to hurry up.
Go on.
Seriously.
Attack!
- Attack.
- Yours is weak.
Look at it.
Get out of the way.
Let me.
Another round.
Come on.
What is it called?
What a cricket.
It's strong.
My cricket is called Jin Pipa.
That rascal
really showed up.
Come on.
I'm going to show you
who calls the shot around
Wujiang Prefecture.
Attack.
No one can mess with me.
Attack its side.
Attack.
What are you doing?
It wasn't over.
The table is reserved.
Move aside.
Isn't this Yan Boyang?
Why are you here instead of keeping
Commandery Prince company tonight?
I was wondering who reserved the table.
It was you.
What's the matter?
You haven't gotten your
back kicked enough?
That's another matter on its own.
Yan Boyang,
should we
play a special round?
I'll add on 50 strings of 1000 cash.
If I lost, I'd call you my grandfather.
What do you think? Are you up for it?
Place your bets.
Agree to his offer.
What are you afraid of?
You're a man.
Hurry up and make your decision.
Hurry up.
Are you afraid of him?
Yan Boyang is used to acting as
Commandery Prince's lapdog.
He doesn't even have the guts
to bet on a cricket fight.
Forget it.
Get out of here.
What are you talking about?
Watch your mouth.
I'll join you.
Come on.
Place your bets.
Lady,
you're beautiful.
Take her!
Yes!
Who's there?
Show yourselves!
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Who are you?
Why are you sticking
your nose in my affairs?
Hanchen of the Zhao Family.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Fine.
Charge!
Watch out.
Apprehend them all.
Do not move!
Move it.
Get up.
Master.
Capture them all.
Do you know how dangerous this is?
How long will you remain hiding
in Wujiang Prefecture?
Master, what you did
brought me shame.
I did not force her into this.
She volunteered herself.
Do you know
her reason for doing so?
She came to Xiongjie Camp alone today
just to ask me a question.
You suffered from the death
of Duke of Yongguo.
You're tormented by
the trauma day and night.
She asked me
what she can do for you.
Forget it.
Mere bandits
can't hurt the young lady.
Go home.
Sorry for the trouble.
Let's go.
Nobody knows what life holds.
A futile attempt to oppose fate
will only leave one in dismay.
Are you hungry?
Let's get some noodles.
Noodles are served.
Please enjoy.
Thank you.
Here.
When I was young,
I remember being hungry at night.
My brother was able to get me food
anywhere.
One particular night,
he got me a bowl of
noodles just like this one.
It was really delicious
just like this one.
Can you tell me
the stories of your childhood?
After this,
I'll take you somewhere.
Attack.
Bite it.
Bite its side.
Attack.
Bite it.
I'm telling you.
My cricket, Jin Pipa,
will win no matter what it takes.
Mingguan.
Bite it.
Attack.
Attack its side.
Bite it.
Come on.
Jin Pipa?
I had high expectations.
That's right.
Yan Boyang,
it's your unlucky day today.
Pay up.
It's too early to get excited.
Zhao Xiaoqian will be here soon.
He shall defeat everyone
with his cricket, Zhao Jinguo.
You're bluffing.
Yan Boyang,
you should focus on paying the bet.
In my opinion,
to Commandery Prince,
you're but a mere dog.
Let's see if he'd show up tonight.
To His Highness, you're probably
less than a dog.
Jerk!
I'll kill you!
How could you hit him?
Stay put.
Let me go.
You wanted to hit me, didn't you?
Fetch the pledge.
You...
I'm warning you.
I'm giving you three days.
If you do not pay me,
I'll submit this pledge
to the magistrate.
You should know that
His Majesty is eliminating
corrupted officials now.
Your entire household
will be implicated then.
Get out of here!
Get lost!
Move it.
Leave.
Get lost.
Quit embarrassing yourself.
Get out of here.
Get lost.
When I was young,
whenever Shengwu was upset,
he would hide himself.
The attendants of the mansion
would panic.
They can't find him anywhere.
Shengwu's brother is the only
one that could find him.
He'd bring Shengwu to the rooftop.
He said,
whenever you're upset,
look up to the stars.
Afterward, both of them
entered the palace.
His father was no longer his father.
His father is now his royal uncle.
He could no longer climb up the rooftop
due to his distinguished identity.
There are many things
he can no longer do.
Back then, before they left,
their parents bid them farewell
and told them solemnly.
"From now on,
you and your brother are now
the sons of the Emperor.
In public,
do not ever bring up
the prince's mansion.
You're forbidden to
even think about it."
Back then, he was a young child.
He was reluctant to
part with his parents.
He had so much to say to them.
However, he was not allowed to.
He's forbidden from even bringing it up.
He can only write his words
down on the kite.
What happened after
they entered the palace?
After that,
the Empress suffered a miscarriage.
Brother fell ill for a long time.
That year, it was constantly
snowing at the capital.
It was really cold.
The Empress wanted to
perform a ritual for the late prince.
Her Highness employed budget
cuts through the palace.
We don't even have charcoal to
run the heater at our dwelling.
I sneaked into the Emperor's palace
and stole some charcoal
to warm brother up.
A small amount of fire
didn't make a difference.
Winter is agonising in the capital.
I vividly remember that day,
the entire palace was bustling.
Nobody cared about us.
I was the only one
who stayed by my brother's side.
I stayed by his side
all day and night.
I could never forget that day
at Wude Palace.
I would never forget
when my brother died,
he was barely 20 years old.
Your brother wouldn't
want to see you this way.
He wants you to live on
and move forward.
Stop dwelling in the past.
All right?
What about you?
Why did you go to Xiongjie Camp?
Was it for my sake?
I noticed how gloomy you were recently.
You're easily irritable, too.
I supposed it was because of
Duke of Yongguo's death anniversary.
I wanted to find out
what happened.
I wanted to help you.
Help me?
What can you help me with?
I'll help you to move on.
What's so funny?
You said you had
something to ask me then.
You said you were going to ask after
we return from Yuyangli Village.
What's that all about?
Well,
what do you mean by the lantern?
The lantern?
Congwen promised to return my lantern.
Congwen?
Yes.
Back then, Congwen was
bidding Courtesan Zhu farewell.
I couldn't stop
Courtesan Zhu as her
carriage rode away.
I handed the lantern to Congwen
so he could give it to Courtesan Zhu.
It was really urgent then.
I didn't give it out on purpose.
Do you believe me?
Believe me.
I was worried of upsetting you,
so I bought another one.
Are you mad?
Where did you buy it from?
At a stall by the streets.
There weren't many left.
I recall the store owner asking me
if I was certain about my purchase.
Did you check your purchase?
What are you laughing at?
I'm laughing at how silly you are.
What do you mean?
You're silly all over.
Zhao Xiaoqian.
Hanchen.
You're still as mischievous as
you were back when we were kids.
Lingniang?
She just arrived tonight.
She insisted on meeting you
before leaving with us.
(Lotus Garden)
Lingniang
is the daughter of the officer
back at the capital.
What was his name?
His name is...
Shen Zunfu.
Yes, Shen Zunfu.
His daughter, Shen Zhaowen,
is Lingniang we speak of.
According to Mr. Liangji,
she grew up with His Highness.
Back at the palace...
Make yourself clear.
She's the goddaughter of the Empress.
She's granted the title of
Commandery Princess Rong'an.
She grew up with His Highness.
Previously, they even...
What did they do?
Mr. Liangji didn't continue.
Go on.
Get back to work.
What could that possibly mean?
They must have been
in love with each other then.
That can't happen.
You just got to sustain
your position at the mansion.
Commandery Princess Rong'an
appeared out of nowhere.
Why do you think
a lady would
travel all the way here?
Zhao Xiaoqian must be the reason.
I can't allow this.
I must think of something
for you to secure your position.
Lady Xie.
The garments for the Dance of Nuo
are prepared for you.
My hands are all red.
What's that?
Don't you know that?
Before the civil examinations,
the academy
has a tradition.
The Dance of Nuo will be
performed to invite blessings.
Then, we shall head to
Mount Kunyan Temple
to pray for the success
of the fellow candidates.
We're supposed to dance?
That's right.
Apparently, we are to
perform for the deceased
principal graduates.
My mom told me
the Dance of Nuo is a sacred ritual.
We shall wear a mask
and hold a sword,
and perform the dance as
a form of worship to the sages.
The prayers of the goddesses
are meant for the dead souls.
Can the dead souls hear us?
I'm not sure about that.
However, I believe in such.
Look. Besides prayers, rites
are meant to commemorate
our family members
and converse with
the dead.
The dance isn't something
we should focus on.
Take it seriously.
If we dwindle on like this,
Zhao Xiaoqian
might be charmed by Lingniang.
I don't care about that.
I have matters to attend to.
Where are you going?
Were you waiting for me?
I need to talk to you.
What's it?
Minggu told me the academy is
hosting the ritual, Dance of Nuo.
I'm wondering...
♪Ask the moon whether it has seen♪
♪The other end of the earth♪
♪Your feelings fluctuate
like the moon's wane and wax♪
♪Have they ever been the same?♪
♪Carried by misty clouds,
the moon came into your eyes♪
♪As a substitute for me, it appeared♪
♪Cast our eyes over the bustling street♪
♪Don't shed tears when we part♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪