[wind chimes tinkling]
[woman singing Spanish lullaby]
Subtitles by kisskh.me
[woman speaking Spanish]
[laughter echoing]
[wind blowing]
[Diego] Mama?
Bartolo?
Mama?
- [water sloshing]
- [gasping]
[Bartolo grunting]
[gasping]
[screaming]
Mama, no!
[Anna] Sam, come on.
We're late.
Guys, the bus is almost here.
Chris, in case I'm late
for any reason,
there's dinner in the fridge.
[Chris] Meatloaf. Got it.
Misty!
Sorry, sweetie.
[Chris] Mom, where's my jacket?
[Anna] It's in the closet
upstairs.
Quick, quick, quick.
Lunchbox.
All right. Okay.
I got my keys.
And... No.
No, no, honey,
I already packed it.
Here you go.
Take your backpack. Let's go.
Chris? Let's go.
- Come on, guys.
- Oh, I see it.
[Anna] What? Honey, no,
you can't wear these.
- Okay.
- We're gonna miss the bus.
[Anna] Let's go, let's go,
let's go. Come on.
Shit!
Language, Mom.
[man] Department
of Social Services.
[Mr. Hankins] Oh, Donna,
what's the latest
from the Alvarez case?
[Donna] I called several times.
She's not answering the phone.
I'm taking patrol over there.
Something's up at that house.
Patricia Alvarez?
Why? What's going on?
We got a call from the school.
Alvarez boys
aren't going to class again.
Okay, well,
why is Donna going over there?
I transferred
some of your cases.
Now, Donna has more energy.
- More energy?
- And more time.
She doesn't have the outside
responsibilities you have.
- She has no kids.
- She has support at home.
'Cause her husband isn't dead.
She was on time
every day this week.
All right? But believe me,
we all understand.
Do you?
Doesn't really feel like it.
Less time here,
more time at home
might not be such a bad thing.
Patricia Alvarez isn't gonna
talk to someone like Donna.
"Someone like Donna"?
I just mean that she knows me.
I've been with that family
for four years.
I've seen those kids grow up.
Patricia trusts me.
She knows that I'm a mom, too.
The job is to do
what's best for the kids.
Okay, okay, look.
Just keep the case.
Once you get done here,
check in with patrol.
- I don't need patrol.
- Take an officer.
That's not a request.
[officer] I'm sorry.
[Anna] You know what, I can
handle this myself, okay?
I'm sure you can.
[baby crying in other house]
[sighs]
Hi, Patricia.
How are you?
Are the boys home?
- Ma'am, open the door.
- No, that's okay.
Just give us a second.
Patricia, where are the boys?
They're somewhere safe, Anna.
[Anna] Oh.
Look, I don't know
what's going on,
but I might be your best bet
at clearing things up.
So why don't you let me in
and you can show me that
they're safe, like you said?
No, he doesn't even
have to come inside.
Okay? Why don't you
just let me in?
[door chain unfastens]
Uh-uh. Promised her
that I'd go in alone.
Yeah, out of respect
for Officer Garcia.
Your husband
was a police officer.
You think he'd let you
go in there alone?
Yeah, I do.
[sighs] I'll be right here.
Thank you.
- [door chain fastens]
- [sighs]
Patricia,
what happened in here?
Where are the boys?
If you're drinking again or
if you're having some kinda...
[shushing]
[breath trembling]
[softly] Listen.
What?
What do you hear?
Her crying.
[mutters in Spanish]
[door opens and closes]
[gasps softly]
[faint thud]
Carlos?
Tomas?
[gasps]
Get away from that door, Anna.
- Patricia...
- Get out, Anna.
What do you have inside here?
- [speaks Spanish]
- Patricia, please. I just...
[in English] Get out!
Please, just tell me
what's in here.
- Get out!
- [Anna gasps]
- [grunts]
- Stay away from that door!
- [officer] Anna! Anna! Anna!
- I told you! Get out!
- [Anna screams]
- [officer] Jesus Christ!
Get off of her!
Now! [grunting]
[Patricia] Don't open the door!
- Calm down! Stop!
- Just one more night, Anna!
[officer] I said calm down!
[Patricia] Just one more night!
- Let go of me!
- [panting]
You don't understand!
[door creaking]
[gasps]
Oh, my God!
[whispers]
Close the door, please.
[whispers] She'll hurt us.
No, she won't.
I promise.
[siren wailing in distance]
Guys,
everything's all settled.
You're gonna have warm beds,
and hot food,
and a shower.
Okay?
My gosh!
How did that happen?
She did it.
Your mother did that to you?
[Tomas] No.
It wasn't her.
Your mother loves you.
You know that, right?
Whatever's happening,
we're gonna
take care of it, okay?
But for tonight,
you guys are safe.
I promise you.
We're not safe anywhere.
[cackling]
[whimpering]
Hi!
Sorry I'm late.
How was school?
[Samantha] Same old, same old.
Hey, Sam.
Hey.
There was meatloaf
in the fridge.
Did Chris warm it up for you?
I don't know.
[singsong] Hello?
Yeah, he heated it up.
Okay. Where is he?
He's playing in Dad's office.
[Anna] Not too much TV, okay?
[Chris] We've got
a 10-15 in Midtown.
Suspect is on the run.
I'm pursuing on foot.
I think I see something.
There he is.
I'm on his tail.
I see the suspect.
I need backup.
Bam, bam!
I'm taking fire!
Freeze!
Bam, bam, bam!
I got him.
I got the suspect.
Call it in, Coop.
We got him.
Mom, I'm all done!
[sobs]
I'm coming! [sniffles]
Right. Let's see.
Okay.
Rinsing.
[gasps loudly]
[door thuds in distance]
[door creaks]
- [footsteps approaching]
- [keys jangling]
[door opens and shuts]
[gasps]
[woman crying nearby]
[whispering] Tomas. Tomas.
[electricity buzzing]
[yelling] Tomas.
Tomas.
[electricity continues
buzzing]
[whispering]
Tomas, what are you doing?
Tomas, come back.
[Tomas gasps]
[La Llorona] Carlos.
[screaming]
[phone ringing]
[gasps]
Hello?
Anna, it's Coop.
We just pulled the
Alvarez boys out of the river.
I'm gonna need you to meet me
at Fourth and Mission.
Okay, I'll be right there.
[police siren wailing]
Stay in the car. Okay?
And please
don't wake up your sister.
I'll be back in a few minutes.
[faint police radio chatter]
[officer] I'll keep
checking on this one.
This way, ma'am.
[officer] All right.
[indistinct chatter]
[Anna gasps]
Oh, my God!
I don't understand.
What happened?
We found them in the river.
They were drowned.
When you saw them,
how were they?
They were fine.
They were scared,
but they were fine, Coop!
I promised them
that they would be safe, Coop.
- I promised them.
- Anna, don't blame yourself.
[Patricia screaming]
Mis hijos! Mis hijos!
[officer] Hey! Hold her.
[shouting in Spanish]
[in English] It's your fault!
I tried to stop her!
[speaking Spanish]
Who?
Who did you try to stop?
La Llorona.
[siren wailing]
[camera flash pops]
[camera flash popping]
[camera whirring]
[woman sobbing]
[continues sobbing]
[gasps]
[softly] Nino...
Mijito...
Mijo...
[Chris shuddering]
[La Llorona speaking Spanish]
- [sizzling]
- [screaming]
[La Llorona] Nino!
Sam! Sam, let me in!
- Open the door! Hurry!
- Chris? What are you...
Open!
[panting heavily]
[door alarm beeping]
[screaming]
[gasping]
What's going on?
Didn't you see her?
Who?
[panting]
[squeaking]
[Chris gasps]
[Chris grunting]
[Samantha]
Chris, what's going on?
[gasping]
Chris?
[winder squeaks]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[straining]
[panting]
[breathing deeply]
[gasping]
Hey, sorry, guys.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
[sighs]
I'm fine.
You okay, honey?
Yeah. I was just
imagining things.
Okay.
Night.
Love you.
[inaudible]
[Father Perez]
He's a curandero.
The ritual is called smudging.
It's supposed to rid the body
of any negativity
that may have
attached itself to it
during times of great stress.
Do you believe it works?
[chuckles softly]
What does it matter
what I believe?
It's what they believe.
And if they believe in that,
then surely
they believe in this.
Did you know the boys?
Yeah. I was their case worker.
Can I ask you
a question, Father?
Yes.
Do you know anything
about La Llorona?
[gasps softly]
I haven't heard that name
since I was a child.
The Weeping Woman.
She was known for her beauty.
The most beautiful woman
in that part of Mexico.
Then one day,
a rich and handsome ranchero
rode into her village.
[chuckles]
She set her sights on him.
The marriage was splendid.
They had two beautiful
children whom they treasured.
But then, after a time,
she discovered him in the arms
of a younger woman.
What'd she do?
She took from him
what was most priceless.
She murdered their children.
In a fit of jealous rage,
she drowned them in the river.
After she realized
what she had done,
- she was consumed by guilt.
- [sobbing]
She threw herself
into those same waters.
Then is cursed
to roam the earth,
searching for children
to take their place.
Children are told to behave,
listen to their elders,
or La Llorona will come
and steal them away.
So it's a folktale?
To some.
Here.
It has seen me through
many dark nights.
May it do the same for you.
Oh, thank you but my husband
was the religious one, not me.
You don't
have to be religious
to have faith.
[thunder rumbles]
[thunder rumbling]
[sobbing in distance]
[sobbing continues]
[sobbing stops]
[thunder rumbling]
[breathing heavily]
- [wind blows]
- [gasps]
- [wind gusting]
[thunder rumbling]
- [screaming]
- [sizzles]
[gasping]
Chris?
Chris!
Sam?
[footsteps running]
[Samantha whimpering]
Sam?
What's going on, honey?
Honey, what happened
to your arm?
I fell.
That's quite a fall.
Hey.
I know things are a little bit
hard right now.
And I know that the world
sometimes seems scary.
But I was thinking,
remember what
Daddy used to say?
About if you were scared
and he wasn't there?
He'd tell you
to hold onto to Misty
and you squeeze her
really tight.
Does it feel any better?
That feels
a little bit better, right?
What are you looking at?
[knock on door]
Coop's here.
Come on.
Come on, sweetie.
[thunder rumbling]
Rough day, guys?
Can we go watch TV?
Sure.
[sighs heavily]
[TV playing]
Um...
Cheers?
It's been that kinda day, huh?
- Week.
- Month?
- Year.
- [chuckles]
I don't know.
They're hanging in.
I think we need...
Time.
Yeah.
And the occasional takeout,
so thank you.
You're welcome.
Well, if you're not
in the mood
to talk personal problems,
how about professional ones?
Oh, no. What?
It's about Patricia Alvarez.
We know that she had
some involvement
in her sons' deaths,
but she has a solid alibi.
Several parishioners
at her church say
they saw her at the time
that her kids were taken.
Really?
You know her story.
Just take a look at the file.
Maybe you'll see
something I missed.
I would love to help you
but she does not
want to see me.
Well, that's just it.
She's angry at you.
And one of the first things
your husband
ever taught me is that...
Angry people love to talk.
[sighs]
[Carlos] She did it.
[squeaking]
[door thuds]
[wind blowing]
[door slams open]
[hinges creaking]
- [door opens]
- [gasps]
[door closes]
[door continues opening
and closing]
[breathing shakily]
[wind blowing]
[sighs in relief]
Chris.
What are you doing?
Hey.
You okay, honey?
Chris?
Honey?
You all right?
You okay, honey?
- Chris?
- [gasps]
[Chris panting rapidly]
[Anna gasps]
[groans]
Chris?
Honey. Hey.
Come on.
Hey, wake up.
What happened?
You were sleepwalking, baby.
Oh, sweetie.
You were just sleepwalking.
It's okay.
Come on. Come on, baby.
Let's get you upstairs.
Let's go to sleep.
Come on.
You're okay.
[rustling]
[switch clicks]
Is there someone in here?
Because my husband is a cop
and he's gonna be home
any minute now.
[door opens, creaking]
[screaming]
Sam! Chris!
Kids, wake up!
Open the door!
[panting]
[screams]
What are you doing
in my house?
[gasping]
What are you doing
in my house?
Get out of my house!
- [screams]
- Mom?
[Samantha] What happened?
[continues gasping]
Nothing. Nothing.
Nothing, honey. Nothing.
I'm sorry.
Come on in, honey.
Go on, go on.
Why don't you sleep
in Mommy's bed tonight, okay?
[breath trembling]
- [alarm beeping]
- [gasps]
[Samantha moaning]
[Samantha] Chris,
get your foot off of me.
What?
[door buzzes]
Patricia?
I'm very sorry
about your loss.
I can't even imagine
how you must feel.
How I feel?
[scoffs]
I feel nothing.
Because I have felt the worst.
I am done.
I don't care
what they do to me.
You should be sitting here
instead of me.
You killed my boys, not me.
[speaks Spanish]
Patricia,
you had them locked up.
I had them hidden.
[speaks Spanish]
[in English]
And now she has them!
She has them!
[whispers] Mis hijos.
What happened to your arm?
What happened to you,
Patricia?
La Llorona.
Your children,
have they heard her crying?
Have they felt
the sting of her tears?
They will. Soon.
And she will come for them.
You know why?
Because I told her to.
No, Patricia...
You know, when my boys died,
I didn't pray to God
for their salvation.
Instead, I prayed to her.
[chuckles]
I prayed,
and I prayed,
and I prayed to her
to give my children
back to me
and take yours instead.
[inhales sharply]
[muffled thud]
[breathing shakily]
[faint thud]
[grunts]
[Samantha sobbing]
Sam?
[Samantha continues sobbing]
- [wind gusting]
- [grunts]
[gasping]
[screaming]
[panting]
[wind blowing]
[screaming]
Chris!
What?
[Chris groaning]
[gasps] Chris!
Chris!
- [Chris inhaling sharply]
- [indistinct PA announcement]
- [doctor] Ah.
- [Chris exhales]
Sprained this pretty bad,
champ.
[knocking on door]
[Anna] Cooper, hi.
What?
The hospital called?
Yeah.
Welfare check.
[Donna] Samantha,
how did you get those burns?
How about you, Chris?
I told you, I fell.
Is that true?
Where was your mom?
Anna, you know
you can't be here.
Oh, come on, Donna.
I wouldn't...
They're trying to protect you.
They're telling you the truth.
I would never hurt my kids.
She's right.
You can't be here.
[Donna sighs]
You may not believe this,
but I hate having to be here.
I promised your dad
I'd watch out for you guys.
So if you ever need anything,
just call me. Got it?
We had to release
Patricia Alvarez.
Didn't have enough
to charge her.
Maybe she didn't do it.
What do you mean?
I don't know. Never mind.
Anna,
whatever's going on here,
fix it.
Dad, for the first time
in my life, I'm in love.
That's very serious.
[Anna] Hey.
And she loves me, Dad.
Chris...
Can we talk?
Honey, I need to know
what really happened.
[water splashing]
[Chris] I saw a woman.
In the house?
In Samantha's room.
I thought it was Sam but...
A woman in a white dress.
She was crying.
She wants us.
She wants us to be hers.
Ow. Mom, that hurts.
Rinsing.
You believe me?
Yes.
I do.
[grunting]
[gasping heavily]
[muffled screaming]
[faint thudding]
Sam?
Sam! Sam!
Sam! Open the door! Sam!
Sam!
[grunts]
[Samantha coughing]
[gasping deeply]
What happened?
What happened to you?
Honey.
You okay?
What happened?
Sam?
[whimpering]
[Chris] Mom.
[stammers] Mom. Mom!
Mom!
- [screeching]
- [screaming]
- [sizzling]
[groans] Go!
[Samantha continues screaming]
Go! Run!
Go!
Run!
[whimpers]
- [rumbling]
- [yelling]
[door rattling]
Run!
Go!
- [whimpers]
- [rumbling stops]
[Anna] I know it sounds
hard to believe.
[Father Perez]
A few years ago,
I placed little stock
in legends, myths,
things that go
bump in the night.
But then
there was an incident
with a doll.
It opened my mind
to possibilities
out of the ordinary.
Can you help us?
The Church works with people
who specialize
in situations like this.
Okay.
But to get to them, we'd have
to go through the archdiocese.
How long does that take?
At its best, several weeks
for a case to be approved.
[Anna] No.
There may be another way.
It's unorthodox,
but he's local.
However,
if you choose this route,
I must obey
the laws of the Church,
and remove myself
from this process.
As I said,
his methods are unorthodox.
And the Church, well,
the Church has their ways,
and he has his.
It's why he abandoned
the collar years ago.
He used to be a priest.
Yes.
But now, he's a faith healer.
A shaman who operates
on the fringes
of religion and science.
A curandero.
- [music playing on radio]
- [door bells jingling]
Don't touch anything, okay?
Hola. Excuse me.
- Um...
- I've seen you before.
The Alvarez memorial.
Yes?
Yes. I was her case worker.
Well, if you've come just to
gawk at my shop,
I have more
important things to do.
You know what,
I don't think that
we're in the right spot.
I'm sorry.
Come on, guys.
Have you seen this before?
Yes.
What is it?
The Church can help you.
No, no, no, please. The Church
sent us here, to you.
This is Church business.
Please.
[Rafael] These are the marks
of La Llorona.
You have seen her then?
[Anna] You ever seen her?
No.
Not directly.
But I have seen what she does.
What do we do?
We are facing an evil
that has no bounds.
But she's not human. Right?
No. But she was,
until her murderous vanity
consumed her.
She's just a dark spirit.
Unholy. Forsaken by God.
Okay, that's it. I'm gonna
take them to a motel.
Why?
She's attached herself to
your family, not your house.
If you move,
she will follow you.
What are we supposed
to do then?
I don't think
that's gonna help.
No. Not just this.
At the memorial,
I saw you speaking
with Father Perez.
He said that
you used to be a priest.
My journey
began in the Church.
Yes.
That was a long time ago.
Take me to your home.
We must begin immediately.
We're done.
I'm sorry, are you just gonna
rub eggs all over everything?
You think it's silly,
don't you?
Pretty much.
Come with me.
This ritual, la limpia,
is used to detect
the presence of evil.
The bloodier the content,
the greater the evil.
[chanting in Spanish]
Oh, that's a trick.
I saw it on Johnny Carson.
Mom.
[all gasp]
Ta-da.
Did you see that on Carson?
No.
[praying in Spanish]
Amen.
[Rafael in English]
We all need to work together.
La Llorona
thrives in darkness.
Let's prepare.
[muttering prayer]
That cross was carved
from a tree in Mexico.
It blooms with red blossoms
that make it look like
it's on fire.
[speaks Spanish]
The fire tree.
[in English] They say
the fire trees wept
as La Llorona
drowned her children.
As the only witness
to her sins,
they hold a special power
over her.
[blowing]
In nomine Patris, et Filii,
et Spiritus Sancti.
Amen.
What is that?
[Rafael]
The tears of La Llorona.
I've sanctified them.
Why?
Antivenom.
[thunder rumbling]
Is that another ritual?
Yes. Breakfast for dinner.
That was David's thing.
Breakfast for dinner.
I used to always tease him
it was 'cause cereal
was the only thing
he knew how to make.
Tonight, la comida
is for comfort,
after everything
that you've been through,
and what's to come.
You don't seem very confident.
I'm confident in God.
Father Perez said you turned
your back on the Church.
The Church? Yes.
God? Never.
- [electricity crackles]
- [Anna gasps]
Get the kids.
[rattling]
Watch the flames.
A steady flame tells us
that our protective charms
are working.
Is she coming?
She's already here.
[loud thud]
[floorboard creaks]
[thudding]
[all shuddering]
- [thudding continues]
- [floorboard creaking]
What is she doing?
She's searching.
For what?
Us.
[La Llorona screeching]
[all shuddering]
[water dripping]
[breathing shakily]
[faint whisper]
[sizzling]
[Anna gasps]
[screaming]
[children screaming]
Mom!
[Samantha] Mommy?
[gasping]
[muttering]
[rattling]
[Samantha] Rafael,
help us.
[both gasping]
[thud]
[wood creaking]
[whispers] Mis hijos.
[Chris and Samantha screaming]
[Chris] Mom!
Mom, she's got me!
[screaming]
Mom!
[Samantha] Chris!
[Chris] Mom!
Sam, help me!
[Samantha] Chris! Grab my hand!
[screaming]
No!
[screeching]
- [sizzles]
- [screaming]
[continues screaming]
[screaming stops]
[roars, wails]
[sighs]
You told us we'd be safe!
You said
the light would protect us!
Not true.
Mommy, Misty's gone!
I can't find her!
[Anna] Honey, not now.
You let her get me.
What are you talking about?
You used my son as bait?
No. Of course not.
I used all of you as bait.
Are you crazy?
What if you didn't
get to him in time?
But I did.
And now La Llorona
is out of your house.
What are those?
Remember the fire tree?
Those are its seeds.
As long as this line
remains unbroken,
she cannot enter.
Do not touch them.
La Llorona will do
whatever she can
to get back inside this house.
[banging]
- [door slams open]
- [Anna gasps]
- [Chris] The back door!
- [Anna] Chris!
[wind howling]
Quick!
Grab a hammer and nails!
[Chris] She's gonna get in!
[grunting]
Don't let her in! Don't!
[Rafael] Away, spirit!
You have no power here!
Away from this family!
Anna, hurry!
[wind chimes tinkling]
[Rafael] Hold it steady!
Hold it!
Just a few more nails!
[grunts]
[sighs]
[wind chimes tinkling]
[Anna] Sam!
Get away from that door!
Mommy, I got Misty
and I didn't break the beans.
[screaming]
[screams]
[grunting]
Sam!
Sam! Sam!
She's gonna drown her.
Oh, God! The pool!
Sam!
[gasping]
[flashlight buzzing]
[screeching]
Mom!
[chanting in Spanish]
- [Anna screaming]
- [screeching]
Amen.
[screaming stops]
[both gasp and cough]
[Anna] Take her!
- Is she okay?
- She's okay!
She's breathing.
She's okay.
[Anna panting]
What did you do?
Your pool is now filled
with holy water.
La Llorona had no choice
but to leave.
Thank you, honey.
Sweetie?
Are you okay, honey?
Sam. Sam.
Sam?
What's she doing?
Sam.
What's wrong with her?
Rafael?
La Llorona had your daughter
in her grasp.
Now, when she calls to her
she will go.
When we banish the spirit,
her trance will be broken.
Until then,
we have to keep them close.
[Anna shivering]
[Anna] What?
What are you thinking?
What?
What do we do?
Do we have to?
[Rafael] Yes.
Just until sunrise.
Okay.
Okay, you gotta sit down. Sam.
Sweetie.
You are so brave.
Your daddy would be
so proud of you.
The way you look after
Sam and me.
I need you to know
that it's okay to be scared.
Everybody is, sometimes.
I am.
Daddy was.
Rafael?
No.
He's lying.
I love you, Mom.
I love you too, baby.
I love you both so much.
It's okay, Mom. Do it.
[wind whistling]
Where did you get that?
It's hers.
[Rafael] Hers?
[Anna] It was around her neck.
[Rafael] Keep it close.
We might be able to
use it against her.
[door creaking]
[Chris] Mom! Mom!
Chris!
- Chris!
- Mom!
Mom!
[gun clicks]
[shrieks]
[Anna] Patricia.
Patricia.
Patricia, please.
You took my babies from me!
- Don't do this.
- She'll give them back to me.
[Anna] Patricia,
please don't do this!
Patricia, please.
Please put the gun down.
Okay? We can talk about this.
You and I can
just talk about this.
Okay? Patricia, please.
[groans]
Please...
Please bring them back to me.
No.
Give me back my boys!
[thunder rumbles]
No!
[screaming]
Mom!
Run! [chokes]
[grunting]
[thunder cracking]
[Samantha yelps]
[Chris] Come on.
- It's locked.
- Mine too.
Let me check this one.
Chris, they're all locked.
What do we do?
[groans]
[Samantha] Hurry, Chris!
Please. Oh, God.
Come on! She's coming!
- She's coming. She's coming!
- I know!
- Faster!
- I got it!
Pull it!
[Chris] Go, go, go!
Come on. Hurry.
Grab the rope.
[both grunting]
She's coming.
[thunder rumbling]
Help!
[Chris] Grab the light.
[Samantha] Here it is.
- [screaming]
- [Chris yells]
[both gasping]
[rope creaking]
- No.
- This way.
- [Christmas carol playing]
- [screams]
- Follow me.
- Okay, I'm coming.
[Chris] No!
[toy squeaks]
[song continues playing]
- [flashlight crackling]
- Oh, no.
- [song slows down]
- No.
[song stops]
[thunder cracking]
[breathing heavily]
Get behind me.
Help!
They're not your kids!
No!
Let them go!
[muffled scraping]
- [loud thud]
- [gasps]
Go.
[Anna] Chris! Sam!
[gasps, groans]
[pounding on door]
- [screeching]
- [children screaming]
Kids!
Behold the cross of the Lord
and begone, wicked spirit!
[yells]
[Chris] Mom!
[Samantha] Mom.
[thunder cracking]
Mis hijos!
[Rafael] Anna!
[screeching]
[gasps]
[screams]
[La Llorona screeching]
[sizzles]
[groans]
[all gasping]
[Anna sobs]
Ta-da!
[Anna chuckles, cries]
Come here.
It's okay.
You're okay now.
Thank you.
I don't know
how I could ever repay you.
[chuckles softly]
You two were very brave.
Even I was scared for a while.
Really?
No.
Not really.
[engine starts]
Race you inside.
[Chris and Samantha laughing]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
[woman sobbing]