You see?
I think it's right here.
(In the base of e-sports…)
Well, let's go.
(Anything unimaginable could happen.)
Can I get any rewards from you, captain?
A little red flower from the captain.
Silly pig Lu Sicheng,
the ugly flowers won't come off.
You don't like the little red flower?
I can draw you a tortoise next time.
So they went to do
this kind of stealthy things.
Do you have the guts to say that again?
Let's go to dinner together.
My treat!
Okay, it's your treat.
(However,)
(peace and love)
(do not belong here.)
Dad.
Mom.
Who's that Chessman?
Who on earth is that Chessman
you always talk about?
Does he have a crush on you?
By the way, Mr. and Mrs. Tong.
I forgot to tell you something just now.
I also have a name called Chessman.
Good, good.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
=Falling into Your Smile=
=Episode 5=
I slept very well last night.
That's right.
You should go to bed earlier from now on.
All right.
That's our gaming area.
It's a nice environment.
Interesting. The restaurant is here.
Come on.
Good morning, Mr. and Mrs. Tong.
- Good morning.
- We have prepared a good breakfast.
I don't know which flavor you prefer.
So I bought a little bit of every kind.
We have congee, doughnuts, soy milk,
coffee and Panini.
You can choose whatever you like.
That's too much.
Let's all eat together.
We've already ate earlier.
Enjoy your meal, Mr. and Mrs. Tong.
Okay. Thank you.
Good morning, Mr. and Mrs. Tong.
Hi.
My name is Han Meimei.
Good morning.
How do you do?
Good morning, Mr. and Mrs. Tong.
Good morning.
We have to review the game from yesterday.
You set the time.
Good morning, Mr. and Mrs. Tong.
Good morning.
Okay, let's find some time this afternoon
and review the game with them.
Okay.
Mom, Dad.
Wait for a while.
I've called you a special taxi on Didi.
It should be here soon.
What special taxi?
We can just hail a car
on the side of the road.
It'll be fine.
That's right.
You just got here.
It must have cost you a fortune.
Save your money.
It's okay, Mom.
You can hardly hail a taxi here.
It's convenient to use Didi.
It just takes a few moves of the fingers.
Yao.
I'm telling you.
This is a quite a remote place.
I didn't see anyone
when I came here last night.
If you go out at night,
you must find someone to go with you.
Don't go out alone.
Mom.
I'm not a kid anymore.
I can take care of myself.
Besides, we're all teammates.
We're all about the same age.
It's not sure who will accompany whom.
If you really need to go out,
you can ask Chessman
to accompany you.
Cheng?
Forget it.
His name is
Lu Sicheng?
What does his family do?
I think they run a business.
He seems
to have been born in a well-off family.
He's polite too.
Did he  study abroad?
- Is this the one?
- Yes.
That's it.
Hello.
Driver of Special car on Didi,
Lee at your service.
Are you the passenger whose
tail phone number is 0305?
Yes, to the high-speed railway station.
All right, let me take it for you.
No, I'll do it myself.
I'll do it.
Okay, you can take a break.
Thank you.
Where did he go to study?
I don't know.
Mom.
Why do you ask?
Do you want me
to bring his household register too
to show you?
You even have his household register?
Let's get in the car.
All right, time to go.
Come on, please get in.
Come on, be careful.
Please fasten your seat belts.
Mom, Dad, have a safe trip.
Text me when you get home.
Okay, I got it.
Don't worry.
Yao.
Good for you.
Go for it.
Eat on time.
- Bye-bye
- Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
Let's go. It's time for our regular meeting.
Today we're going to talk about
the four-preserving-one system.
According to the traditional definition
of the four-preserving-one lineup…
Excuse me.
Wait for me. I've got a delivery.
Okay.
Let's wait for him.
Ming.
Take a look at this.
Is there a problem here?
Tong Yao.
These are all from your fans.
Your fans are so nice to you.
These are all your favorites.
This gift box looks so fancy.
The packaging is exquisite.
Tong Yao.
Your fans have good taste.
What's this?
Tong Yao, you even have male fans.
Dear Yao.
I wonder how you're doing these days.
- How are you doing?
- Give it to me.
Are you happy? You…
In twenty-four hours a day,
- do you even think of me…
- Cat.
for one minute?
Who is "The Place Where the Sun Blooms"
here?
Sunflower, Jian Yang.
From now on, all deliveries from him
should be rejected.
Don't do that.
It's delicious.
(Tripe (spicy flavor)
Meat Gathering gift pack snacks)
(Jian Yang,
CK Base in Luohu District, Shenzhen)
Guys, attention.
I think
we kept a good atmosphere this morning.
The club happens to
have just officially approved
the team's schedule I newly submitted.
Let's get started.
That means from tomorrow,
no sleeping in.
What time do we start training then?
Nine o'clock.
Nine o'clock?
Set your alarm for 8 o'clock.
Even Shorty can
go to bed early and get up early.
What are you two complaining about?
That's right.
I need to get my beauty sleep.
Come on, let's get on with it.
Their tactics versus our tactics.
If their topsolo
chooses a shikigami dominating
in leading lines,
then it'll be crucial
to choose our shooter and midsolo.
It will determine the winner of the game.
Adjust your routine.
Get some early rest today.
Get up.
Get up and train.
Let me sleep for five more minutes.
If you don't get up,
your salary will be deducted.
Rui, that's inhuman.
Get up.
The sun is shining,
the weather is beautiful.
A new day has begun.
Let's cut to the chase
and get back to business.
Today's first day of training. Take it easy.
Cat is more experienced
with physical training.
Let him lead the training today.
All right.
Since today is the first day,
we must activate the joints.
Wait until we sweat a little bit.
Come on.
Move your joints.
Wrists.
Ankles.
Almost there.
Are you ready?
- We're ready.
- Let's start with a jog.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Let's do it.
Come on.
No.
Run.
I thought it was a jog.
Don't just look. Go on.
Come on, come on.
I'm hungry. Where's Cat?
I may get a sunburn.
You are too short to be burnt by the sun.
Lu Sicheng.
I'm so tired.
Poor thing.
Captain.
Can you talk to Rui?
This is not physical training.
It's clearly physical abuse.
(Who's begging Cheng
not to abuse her physically?)
(It's a girl's voice.)
(Is it Smiling?)
Cheng.
Captain.
I'm on the air.
The whole world can see you.
(I made a screenshot.)
What are you doing?
Peek-a-boo?
I'm on the air.
Let me see.
I'm begging for Smiling to be on the air.
The kind with a camera on it.
Sooner or later, you'll be seen.
There is nothing to hide.
That's a good point.
Tong Yao?
No way.
Haven't you already signed
a live streaming contract?
Besides, you will be seen sooner or later.
What's the point of hiding?
This camera doesn't suit me very well.
Didn't you buy a beauty camera?
Screw you.
Remember your live streaming target.
You can make up for
forty-five hours in a day or two
at the end of the month.
Unless you find someone
to kidnap Rui by then,
otherwise, he will still make a merciless
deduction of your monthly performance.
(Bought a beauty camera.)
(Which kind-hearted ghost just)
(hunted our Cheng?)
(Why is Cheng so thoughtful?)
(Tong Yao, hurry up
and start the live broadcast.)
(I'll shut down the live broadcast
if you keep yelling.)
Take a look at people's outcry.
Tong Yao.
It seems that you have to
open the live broadcast today.
Okay.
But you have to give me some time.
I need to get ready.
What do you need to prepare?
It's just a live broadcast.
And you're going to get all dressed up
like going to the Queen's dinner party?
Rui, please leave me alone.
All right, all right.
(Amao's Mom)
Fan's leader.
Let's get to work.
Hi, I'm looking for...
Hi, I'm looking for Tong Yao.
Hi, beauty.
Help me. Emergency.
Excuse me, friend.
Please close the door.
Okay.
Why are you hiding?
Why do I feel that
you are poking me in the eye?
Look at yourself, my friend.
Your dark circles are coming out.
Without the concealer,
how can you pass the test
of a high-definition camera?
Sis.
Your skin is all dry
from staying up all night training.
I can't come over every time
to put on makeup for you.
Save yourself before
the next live broadcast.
Remember.
Take a mask every day
to get more water replenishing.
Yes. I'll follow the advice of my friend.
That's my girl.
I just saw Cheng downstairs.
He's really handsome.
I didn't expect you guys
to become a CP so soon.
What do you mean?
Don't talk nonsense.
How is it that I'm talking nonsense?
I witnessed the whole
"E-sports White Snake Legend"
as soon as I came back from abroad.
Don't talk about the past.
What, is Jian Yang still haunting you?
"The Place Where the Sun Blooms"
is back in the world.
Don't laugh.
Did you and Ai Jia make up?
Why should I make up with him?
I wouldn't have come
if I hadn't come to do your make-up.
If you want to settle with Ai Jia abroad,
you should just tell him.
How do you know he doesn't want to?
Does he have time to listen to me?
All he does every day is gaming.
I dare say
he must not want to give up his club.
Even if his salary is now a little higher,
can he still play forever?
And he hides in his room every day
like a vampire.
Who are you calling a vampire?
Even if you are,
you're still a cute vampire.
Is that okay?
Yes.
But what are you going to do now?
Since I've turned down a job offer abroad,
I'll try to find a job at home first.
I remember
didn't you have a part-time job
as a gaming host
when you were in college?
I was doing it for Ai Jia, all right?
I don't want to mess with this now.
But
I did get asked to fill in recently
to host
a national league draw.
National league?
Isn't that the league
I'm going to play in next?
You said yes?
I'm still thinking about it.
Close your eyes. I'll draw your eyeliner.
Close your eyes.
Here is your Smiling.
Why are you hiding?
Head up, chest up.
I made this face
not for you to look on the floor.
That's right, Tong Yao.
Why do you keep your head down
with such a pretty face?
You have a nice lipstick color.
What brand is it?
Lipstick?
Is she wearing lipstick?
How can I not tell it?
Carrot color.
It sets off her skin color.
Go conquer the world beautifully.
My work is done.
Miss, I'll see you off.
I'll open the door for you.
Tong Yao.
You look good.
Don't look so sad. Come on.
(I miss you. I really know I'm wrong)
Go up, go up, I've slipped away.
(Honey, forgive me, okay?)
Kill the snake. Kill the snake now.
Okay, okay. Good.
Good, good.
Get him.
Catch him.
Honey.
What is it? What is it?
Honey! Honey!
Honey.
Honey, I'm here.
Chubby.
Do I look okay like this?
Will I look too pale?
Tong Yao.
You've already adjusted it 800 times.
The official Microblog has been posted
for 10 minutes.
Do it.
(Camera not turned on)
(Watch on Mobile, Share, Follow)
There are so many people.
One, ten, one hundred, one thousand,
ten thousand, one hundred thousand.
300,000?
That's a lot of people.
Should I quit?
That's okay.
The number of live broadcast platforms
is illusively high.
There are probably
only 20,000 to 30,000 people.
Block anyone who calls me ugly later.
I depend on you to maintain my reputation.
Okay.
Can he block them all?
Cheng.
I advise you to be kind.
(Loading at full speed)
(- Three with two.
- I can't take it.)
(North Wind. I hu-ed. Big Four Winds.)
(Four twos. Jokers.)
(The most mysterious person in history
is about to reveal herself.)
(How should I pretend not to loathe her)
(ugly looks?)
(- I'm waiting online.)
- Go back.
(My wife, my God.)
(She is as good-looking as I thought.)
(You're really a woman.
My view of the world crumbles.)
Hello, everyone.
I'm Smiling.
Right.
I'm the chosen anchor who was little known
but is a professional now.
From now on, I'll see you all every month
in the studio.
Remember to subscribe to me.
I'm going to start playing the game.
Thank you.
(War on)
I won't be able to see the pop-ups
while playing the game.
What is invisible doesn't exist.
I'm such a little smartass.
I can't believe they got
a schoolgirl to play the game.
Team ZGDX employs a child laborer.
I'll report it.
You don't look more than 1.6 meters tall.
It's so funny
to watch a schoolgirl playing
as a professional.
Lu Sicheng.
What are you doing?
Read the pop-ups.
I'm in the live broadcast.
Be polite.
Don't swear, kid.
I didn't say that.
Besides, Chubby swears every day.
He is hopeless.
You can chat.
Why did you mention me all of a sudden?
Don't read the pop-ups.
I will get distracted.
I'll die.
No.
Who is reading the bullet-screen comments?
It's Cheng.
Yeah, it's me!
My wife is not Oitsukigami anymore.
It's Smiling.
You probably need to see
an ophthalmologist.
If the brain department is less crowded.
I recommend you can also go.
What is he doing?
Smiling.
You look so good, so good, so good.
So cute, so cute.
So many.
Or go to the toilet
to eat something to calm down.
You think it's interesting to read
the bullet screen comments like that, right?
Yes.
Tong Yao obviously looks so cute.
Why do you play the game so fiercely?
In me, the tiger sniffs the rose.
How long are you going to read for?
Until I'm tired.
Can you adjust the height of the seat?
Sitting like this, you look so short.
The camera cannot
take a full picture of your face.
Only the forehead shot?
You don't know how to use
the e-sports chair, do you?
You…
Congratulations!
What a loss!
Rui,
you bought a black and white monitor
for Tong Yao?
How do I not know that?
Tong Yao in anger looks so cute.
Of course!
The puffer fish is also very cute
when it is angry.
Lost in the first round.
Tong Yao, you used to be
a substitute fighter, didn't you?
A substitute fighter would be so poor.
Do you believe that?
What is your relationship with my husband?
Who is your husband?
Tell him to come over and let him talk to me.
You need Cheng to read the bullet
screen comments while playing the game.
Shame on you.
Did I ask him to read me
the bullet screen comments?
Who can buy a packet of dummy pills
and feeds it to him?
I donate one yuan.
See my record here?
It's the result of reading
the bullet screen comments.
Shame on you!
Room administrator, time for work!
Ban this guy's account!
That's it for today.
The anchor is not too happy.
And needs to have some yogurt
to calm down.
Shorty,
send your
beauty camera brand
to Chubby later.
I…
Lu Sicheng,
were you a mute in your last life?
Really bought the beauty camera.
Tong Yao values her looks so much.
Lu Sicheng!
Tong Yao is really fierce.
(ZGDX's new midsolo
shows her face during live broadcast.)
(No.1 Tamamo-no-Mae on the Chinese server
is actually a cute girl)
(1 ZGDX new midsolo Smiling
is a cute girl)
(ZGDX's new midsolo
shows her face during live broadcast.)
(No.1 Tamamo-no-Mae on the Chinese server
is actually a cute girl)
(The most potential professional e-sports player
1. Smiling)
Cheng.
(Invitation: The Friendship Tournament)
Your former boss TAT is inviting us
to a training match.
Not now.
I see that Tong Yao is now quite positive.
She's doing well in training sessions lately.
- Maybe we can…
- No.
Tong Yao needs more training for a while.
Talk about it later.
Good.
You are the captain to obey.
Cheng.
From the pocket,
take out the candy.
It's Xylitol candy.
That won't work either.
And…
Mrs. Lu has instructed
no candy is allowed.
Congratulations, Tai.
Once again, you led the TAT
to win the game again.
Can you reveal your next plans?
This year's World Finals, of course.
Previously, in last season's
Spring Finals,
you defeated the strong opponent Ox
in one fell swoop.
So in today's Onmyoji tournament,
do you have any other players worth noting?
Our team gave the opponent's region,
many seniors before, right?
Although they are very powerful seniors,
there are always newcomers
in the South Korean arena.
So we are not very afraid.
I noticed that…
I heard that they recently
recruited a female player.
I am quite interested.
They just don't give me a chance.
I heard that the customs of
the Chinese arena
are not quite the same.
What they may focus on
may not be just things
like competition results.
Maybe the female players are there to
increase the popularity of the team.
She is not that powerful.
Of course they not dare to ask her to fight.
You mean the ZGDX
declined your invitation to a training match?
Doesn't that mean they are afraid?
Really?
What's the Chinese saying?
"A turtle retracting its head into its shell."
*Coward
(Tai expresses his opinion on
ZGDX's new midsolo, Smiling is challenged)
(Tai is not easy to deal with.)
(I guess Smiling also knows)
(her own capability, right?)
(It turns out)
(the whole team is given)
(the label of "Coward".)
(Immediately arrange
a training match with TAT.)
(What are you waiting for,
when the public opinion is like this?)
(Mr. Li…)
(But Cheng said…)
(It's decided.)
(Make a reply by
the official Microblog this afternoon.)
(Got it.)
(ZGDX e-sports club has accepted
TAT's invitation to training tournament)
- ZGDX is so tough.
- Looking forward to Smiling's performance.
(Tong Yao will participate in this training match)
Tai is so arrogant.
Hurry to frustrate him.
As I said,
it is not the time to make
a training match with TAT.
But they have openly provoked us.
And we have been training for so long.
Tong Yao…
should have already adapted.
Why did they provoke?
They must have heard some rumors.
Now the club PR says to the world that
our new midsolo is unbeatable
in the training match.
To prove our strength to South Korea,
just call their operator team.
Why must we respond to TAT?
This is the decision of
the club's general manager.
I can't argue with that.
Now the public opinion out there
believes that
ZGDX members are cowards.
We can't really be one, can we?
Just one lost game.
Before the start of the new season,
strong teams in the two regions
can know something about each other.
That's good!
Sooner or later, we will have to face TAT.
Tai is different.
It's not as simple as just losing a game.
The club has made a schedule.
It is designated that Tong Yao
must attend this match.
Well, whatever you want.
Anyway, in case of a problem,
don't ask me to clean up your mess.
You're too protective of her, aren't you?
You protect her every time.
As for the previous
E-sports White Snake Legend,
just speak directly on the internet.
The club came to me.
I dealt with it.
But now you even don't allow
the training games.
It's really inexplicable.
You know very well that
the improvement learnt
in a training game against
a powerful South Korean team
before the season
will surely prevail over that
which we can get
from a game against domestic teams,
those inferior to us, right?
And what's wrong with losing a game?
It will not destroy our confidence, right?
I really don't understand you.
Lu Sicheng,
you really like Tong Yao, don't you?
Unexpectedly,
you even like preying on those nearby.
I won't answer such a question.
Think about
whether what you just said is funny.
So the reason you are so protective of her
is that she's a little girl.
You think it's difficult for her
to achieve nowadays achievements.
You're afraid that she will be eliminated
from the club if she loses the game.
Rui.
If Shorty hears you say that,
probably she will jump up
and hit you on the head.
When will you stop talking about "Shorty"?
I don't see her as a little girl,
so there is no sympathy,
and no mercy.
Let alone thinking that
it was difficult for her
to achieve current achievements.
I took her for
the newcomers that
the team can use in the future.
It was hard to let her know
the importance of professional athletics.
She just integrated into the team.
This circle is complicated and
full of all kinds of people.
Like her, who only wants to play the game
and achieve good performance,
it's really hard to find.
So I don't want her to
be stopped by something
which should have been avoided halfway
before she becomes the best one.
I… I'm a little confused.
As for Tai,
when I was in the TAT team,
he's famous for his bad temper.
Calling him that
does not mean that he's so strong
or so professional.
Rather, he is more like
a midsolo quality inspector
without any mercy.
Once the TAT team wanted to
develop newcomers.
Those midsolo alternates,
after the training match with Tai,
some of them gave up on the career
after being beaten by him,
and others could not recover after a setback
and remained in the secondary league.
There are still many teams in South Korea
which refuse to pick up
a training game with TAT.
It's for this reason.
He deems powerful team members
as enemies.
In his eyes,
the so-called training matches
do not mean a technical exchange at all.
Rather, he is only interested in
testing the strength of the other side
and whether they can fight him.
I sometimes feel
if this guy doesn't play
the professional game
and works in other industries,
he will probably also be
a cold and powerful person.
Did you know the Star Team
called as Star of Celebrities?
I know, Ox and his team members.
At that time their output was really strong.
They won the championship.
The game company also
customized a season
commemorative skin for them
in memory of that
they have been unbeatable that season.
But haven't they already retired?
In last season's Spring Finals,
Tai uses this skin
while passing the middle lane
to send his opponents to heaven in person.
Tai is like this.
This time
the other party's intention is obvious.
Does he have some intention towards
first female professional player
with the title
of No.1 Tamamo-no-Mae in China?
(Why can this female anchor sign ZGDX?)
Tong Yao is a newcomer.
(Smiling can't be underestimated)
She joined the team with
a good training competition score,
a lot of striking operations
and confident and aggressive skills.
She also talks back.
Confidence is good.
It's fear that makes people feel annoyed.
She's being praised to the hilt outside.
They admire her extremely.
If this kid gets frustrated,
she will soon collapse
as she is not resistant to setbacks.
This is the reason
why I disagree with the club's
decision to let Tong Yao compete with him.
Cheng.
Tai would do these things to Tong Yao
in our training match?
He'll use Tamamo-no-Mae to defeat Tong Yao.
It's his best stratagem.
Prefers to take the opponent's best hero
to beat the opponent hard.
But Tong Yao is the best Tamamo-no-Mae player
on the Chinese server.
She won't necessarily lose.
That's the title he's running for.
He wants everyone to know
who is the world's No.1 Tamamo-no-Mae.
I was wrong.
I should have argued with the club.
I have to protect Tong Yao.
I told you, you would apologize.
This is not the time to talk about it, right?
So what do I do now?
Should I go and refuse a training match?
Cheng is right.
It is really not appropriate
to let Tong Yao play now.
But the official Microblog has made a reply.
There's no way to back out.
But being called coward is too bad, right?
Rui is also in a dilemma.
Yes, yes, yes.
I have to tell Tong Yao.
No.
What's up, Cheng?
Is it fun?
I didn't mean to do it.
I said,
I didn't hear anything.
Do you believe it?
How much did you overhear?
No eavesdropping.
Only a little.
You said I got good grades,
and made striking operations.
I am a good talent.
It's hard to find another.
And that I'm a gem.
What?
So is it true?
You said I was a gem.
I have been your teammate for so many years.
I haven't heard you praise me before.
You have a share of
the stepping stones in the latrine.
Wake up!
Wake up.
What's the matter with you two
standing eye to eye?
Romeo and Juliet?
It was just cleared up that
you two have nothing.
Then we hear the praise of gem and star.
Glacier melts.
Iron tree blooms.
The spring of a withered tree.
A group of stupid-idiots.
Let's get back to the point!
Now that you've heard it all,
we won't hide it from you.
This time Tai very likely
comes for you.
Just think about Ox.
I don't want you to be beaten to get retired.
just after signing
the professional qualification.
After all, you were selected by me.
I haven't attained national champion yet.
How can I retire?
It's not late to refuse.
Running away is shameful but useful.
I'll talk to the club about it.
No.
Rui, do not go.
I'll be the pretty girl who enforces justice.
Since one day we will face it,
running away from the problem
will not solve anything.
Being defeated now
is better than being beaten
on the real field.
- And...
- Yeah.
Even if he takes Tamamo-no-Mae,
I'll win.
Very optimistic.
Let's go.
(Being Banned)
It's not too late to ban Tamamo-no-Mae.
The opponents ban three midsolo roles.
It seems that he does not want to
give you a way out.
It's okay, I can use Higanbana.
Good.
Then ban Chin.
Got it.
(Selecting)
They really chose
Tamamo-no-Mae immediately.
Tong Yao.
Tai is here for you.
If you want to take Higanbana.
Must pay attention to development.
Do not directly fight against
his Tamamo-no-Mae.
I know it.
(Hannya, Yasha, Higanbana, Doumeki, Kuro Douji
vs. Ibaraki Douji, Youtou Hime, Tamamo-no-Mae, Hakurou)
The skills are so targeted!
Forget it.
If you can't beat them,
you should keep developing.
It's okay, don't worry.
(Seal · First Blood)
Chubby and I will play for the vision.
Good
K goes close to the top lane to protect Cat.
Note the position of Tamamo-no-Mae.
Support the middle lane steadily.
Don't fight directly with him.
K comes to support the middle lane.
Coming.
(Invincible Warrior)
(Seal · Double Kill)
(Defeat)
(ZGDX_Smiling Higanbana)
Don't be impulsive.
Leave.
(Ahead)
I can't carry it anymore.
Tong Yao, hold on.
(Defeat Assist)
(Legendary)
(Support Needed for Our Junction)
It's just a training game.
Tong Yao, it's OK.
That's right.
Tai has been targeting you all the time.
I'm fine.
It's really fine.
It's just a game!
It's normal to lose and win sometimes.
Just win back in the next game.
You guys think I'm too weak.
I'm really fine.
You…
It's getting late.
Get some rest, everyone!
Whoever can't get up tomorrow
will get their wages deducted.
Let's go to sleep.
Yes, yes. Sleep, sleep.
I'm sleepy.
Go, go, go.
Get some rest early. Let's go, let's go.
I'm so sleepy.
Have a good rest.
(Successfully matched. Accepted)
Beauty,
time to sleep!
I'll go to bed after finishing this.
(Defeat Assist)
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Whose reasoning and expectations♪
♪Don't seem to be my inner monologue♪
♪To be myself or to run away♪
♪Should I just sway with the wind?♪
♪You're the one
who came through the sea of stars♪
♪Those corners open unexpectedly♪
♪It seems someone will really understand♪
♪My helplessness♪
♪The loneliness that
comes with the gradual leave♪
♪I'm beginning to believe♪
♪The existence of a tacit understanding♪
♪That fate can be changed♪
♪Because persistence♪
♪Has never been pale♪
♪The successes and failures
we have gone through♪
♪The crowd of people cheering tomorrow♪
♪Your look fuels my passion♪
♪Welcome the sunshine♪
♪Let's welcome the sunshine♪
♪Do you still remember♪
♪That I watched the shooting stars
pass by with you♪
♪How many times I seem to have heard♪
♪The wish I made that night♪
♪We all made a promise♪
♪Youth is about no regrets♪
♪If I have a dream in my heart♪
♪I'll follow the light♪
♪The moment we ignite with passion♪
♪Will light up the night♪
♪How foolish the stubbornness
that no one understands♪
♪How strong the desire to return to glory♪
♪Remember that moment at the top♪
♪Let's welcome the sunshine together♪