fTiming and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ No longer panicking on the night of the blackout ♫
♫ You're by my side, illuminating a beam of light for me ♫
♫ Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet ♫
♫ Your breath brushes up against my cheek ♫
♫ With you warming up the stage,
happiness never comes to a close ♫
♫ Boring jokes add some sweetness to the dinner ♫
♫ Daily life is even more like a comic than comics themselves ♫
♫ Happiness and sadness ♫
♫ Make up the moments of life ♫
♫ Rainy days become very special because of you ♫
♫ Picked up a pitiful youngster off the street ♫
♫ No matter when and where, you always appear ♫
♫ Holding me tightly and spinning in circles ♫
♫ Rainy days make me so nostalgic because of you ♫
♫ Becoming some part of the memories ♫
♫ Walking down a street with lights lighting up
one after another ♫
♫ Warming up the whole world ♫
[Please Feel at Ease Mr. Ling]
[Episode 18]
If you want to gain the audience's favor, you must first understand them.
Are you okay?
Are you sure you can give a report like this?
I'm perfectly fine.
I-it's not like I'm nervous.
I can tell.
I believe that those born in the 90s
are more able to accept...
What are you doing?
Wake up!
The toothpaste you just squeezed is my facial lotion.
Hello everyone. Hello everyone.
Why are you laughing?
No reason. I just think that your plan is pretty good.
Of course it's good! It's perfect for pairs.
That's enough. Mister, you can stop here.
Miss, your destination hasn't arrived yet.
I can't arrive together with you.
If someone sees us get off together, that would ruin everything.
- Just let me off here. I can walk over myself.
- Dummy.
I'll drop you off at the next intersection, okay?
If you want to gain the audience's favor, you must first understand them.
I set our target audience as those born in the 90s living alone,
because I believe that those born in the 90s are more able to accept this cute style.
We can push this brand new style forward for our fall market
to strengthen our theme,
"Warm company, one of a kind."
What is the goal of designing a brand image?
It's for commercial use and brand marketing.
But this design is totally inconsistent with New Way's concept.
You've correctly captured our user demographic.
But the style you've designed is a little too childish.
I'm afraid it doesn't correspond to New Way's stylish impression.
That's true. These alternative designs lack a sense of novelty.
There's a tendency to mirror what similar businesses have done.
The probability of gaining audience acceptance and spreading amongst the public
is comparably weak.
I am truly sorry.
I have taken up your valuable time.
But I sincerely appreciate the suggestions you have raised.
We accept them all.
We trust that our team can use the feedback to present very good designs to you next time.
Have you finished your presentation? This is only the first evaluation.
Now that we have understood each other's requests,
I believe your side can provide better design proposals.
Meeting adjourned.
Wait a moment.
I ask that the chief designer stay behind.
I have a few suggestions I'd like to discuss with you one-on-one.
Are you okay?
No.
There was too much information.
I feel a little saturated.
But I'll be fine after I digest it all.
It's just the first evaluation. We have to look at the final results.
Did you not see their reactions just now?
There's no chance.
There's still time. In the meantime,
I can offer you some proposals to settle your direction.
- For example...
- Hey.
I don't want to get in by the back door.
Right now, I am just
in my small state. Once I have reached
my intermediate state,
I'll give you a pleasant surprise.
You seem very impressive.
Sorry, President Ling!
We won't block you from teaching a lesson to the second party.
Let's go now.
Alright, don't give yourself so much pressure.
Just be calm.
Don't you worry.
I am without a doubt the most energetic second party there is.
Just wait and see.
Alright, I trust you.
What do I do? I can't draw anything.
Take it slow. Something will come.
How about you look at the references again?
How about you help me?
Me?
Don't ask.
I told you not to move. Don't secretly move behind me.
Wouldn't it be the same if you stuck these on the drawing board?
I get more inspiration when they're stuck on your body.
Okay, just like that, don't move.
[New Way]
We have to observe and study on the ground.
Once we've seen the corporate culture in detail,
our designs will have a greater sense of reality.
It seems like everything will go smoothly this time.
- I will do my best. You can go do what you need to do.
- Okay, then I'll give this to you.
What is this?
A walkie-talkie. It's one of our company's specialties.
Who designed this?
President Ling, of course.
It does have his specialty.
- Alright, you can go do your work.
- Okay. If you need something, come find me.
Hello?
Walkie-talkie.
How come I never discovered these before?
How is this a company? It's like a large-scale Ling Yue fan club.
Are you the designer responsible for our corporate image?
I'm sorry, did I disturb your work—
Oh no, not at all.
I heard that a few days ago, you were criticized pretty harshly.
Oh, it's nothing. Every setback makes you stronger. It's normal.
Please don't misunderstand our President Ling.
President Ling is our B2M and B2C idol.
Sorry, what 2M...?
Don't worry about that. In any case, President Ling has so much charisma.
President Ling always does things swiftly and decisively.
Plus, he's very good-looking.
May I ask if you've dated before?
No. I've always been single.
What are you trying to say?
Nothing, I...
May Miss Anxin please come to the company tea room.
- Tea room?
- Ai Li is looking for you.
Is anyone there?
How come it's you? I clearly heard a female voice... Sorry, sorry.
You attacked me so seriously. Are you trying to murder your husband?
Then why did you sneak up on me and scare me to death?
Sorry.
It's clearly your fault. You were conversing so happily with another man.
The President of New Way eavesdrops on other people's conversations?
Well if your boyfriend hit on others, wouldn't you get anxious?
I wasn't! I—
I was afraid he was in love with you.
Some people look cold and icy, but secretly they're fixing up with all kinds of people.
It makes it hard to feel at ease.
- Are you jealous?
- What? No.
Calm down. Don't be impulsive.
Our boss sometimes is like this.
But over time, you'll find that he is really very capable
and is quite a good person.
It must be a misunderstanding. Everything's fine.
- Oh.
- Ahem.
It seems like the company's security system should be upgraded.
I understand. This time, I really was too impulsive.
I think it's quite difficult for you to have such a boss.
You'll get used to it.
Go back to your work.
What's wrong?
I got burned...
Why were you so careless?
Here.
Does it hurt?
Sit still.
If you were living by yourself,
you'd get bumps and bruises everyday.
If you were living alone,
you'd probably be worse than me.
That means...
we can't live without each other.
I'm fine.
Don't be so startled.
I, the first party, suggest that after you apply medicine, rest immediately.
Such a warm and caring first party really makes me
want to collaborate for a long time and maintain enthusiasm.
Alright!
-Here.
-You don't have to carry me.
This is the first party carrying through with their responsibility of protecting the second party.
Let's go to bed!
[Galaxy Cool Man]
[New Way]
You're drawing these all day...
Can you eat him for lunch? He's not even edible.
Not only can I eat him for lunch, he's also a fairy on Earth.
Wake up. The person eating and living with you has got to at least be living, right?
The turtle still needs to only see a green bean.*(Both sides like each other)
The green bean in front of you is still better than an unreachable idol.
Good news! Good news!
What? The store you like has a discount?
Of course it's because your design draft is finished!
See. Only I care if you're tired or not.
He only cares about KPI.
If there's no KPI, there's no money.
Dang dang dang dang!
This is...what new species?
Porcupine, mouse, sloth?
Nope. This is I, the designer's
personal creation based off of New Way's founder,
a near-extinction animal from the prairie, the armadillo.
It's ugly and pretty in an interesting way.
Then what's it holding in it's arms? A lightstick?
It's their logo.
It's certainly not normal. Very New Way.
As expected of the power of love.
Different inspiration comes from living together everyday.
Why don't you talk about the sweet meaning behind it?
Oh, right. The more stories behind the brand,
the greater the value of the brand.
Understood. I'll write it right now.
Dad.
You've come. Sit down.
Why did you think to come today?
I want to come and understand the business and prepare well.
I remember you used to
hate coming to the company the most.
I didn't understand before.
Then why have you changed suddenly.
I want to change the current situation, in which the Gu group is suppressed by the Ling group.
It can't be because Ling Yue and Anxin are together, right?
Not totally.
If I can truly defeat Ling Yue,
then that's my declaration of entry into Gu Group.
To tell you the truth,
I don't care about your relationships,
but you must think clearly.
Your decision today
is an important decision that will likely decide your life for the following decades.
Have you really thought clearly about it?
I have.
All these years, the pain
and difficulties were all undertaken by you.
Right now, I just want to prevent all your hard work from going to waste.
I want to rebuild our Gu Group's greatness.
Tell me, is it truly ok if we make a mess of first party's
fancy house like this?
You aren't in charge of the budget,
so you aren't aware of us entrepreneur's difficulty in saving money.
We need water and electricity at our place. Isn't that so expensive?
So you've come to steal electricity here?
-You're going to die of stinginess.
-No,
us two Zhu Geliang*(a strategist of the Three Kingdoms in Chinese history)
are willing to bring along a little stooge like you. Just be happy about that.
Zhu Geliang? You're a pig.
Pig head, pig brain, pig waist, pig everything!
If you two keep arguing like this, you'll definitely get married.
That's impossible. I'm too young to be blind.
That better be it. After all, I'm the man
-you're destined to never have.
-I-
It seems like it's really going to happen.
No way!
You're back!
Wait!
This is our company's new design logo?
That's right!
It's what you said I resembled...
the big turtle or something...
I...don't think I said you resembled a big turtle.
That's an armadillo.
-Why don't you represent New Way and try it?
-No!
I definitely won't wear it.
You're just like a huge doll right now.
We can put you in front of the company as
for good fortune.
Are you sure this is it?
How is it?
I can't judge it objectively,
because you are different to me.
Don't worry. It'll be fine this time.
Stand still. I'll take a picture and see.
Smile! Oh, you don't need to.
This design's pretty interesting.
It's not done yet.
It's already so lively incomplete?
-I really look forward to the final product.
-This can't be...
I really want them to get married right now.
I really admire their relationship...
Admire what? Just find one.
It's not something you can have just be wanting.
Just try hard. Maybe...
There's this one...
Why'd you glue them together? You're so stupid! Where's the remover?
W-wait, wait, wait. Don't pull on it. It hurts!
Gently, alright? Don't move, stupid.
Does it hurt?
Gently, alright?
We've used a clear combination
to emphasize the new idea of a 5G one-stop customer service.
We utilized internet resources
and the advantage of a collaborative network. Please look this way, everyone.
There are unique designs for the eyes and heart.
With different body monitoring devices in different environments,
it's a combined product using black technology and unique outer visage.
Use your eyes to see, and your heart to experience.
Slowly it will become
an invisible accompaniment beside people.
I have called named it Watch.
It means to gaze and protect.
Watching with you. To accompany and protect each and every one of you.
When I thought of this topic and this phrase,
it was actually because of one person.
In the beginning, I always thought I should take care of him
and protect him,
but slowly it became
where I was the one being protected.
In such a fast pace of living,
I can still feel warmth
and love.
Thank you, everyone.
Congrats.
This is the only proposal in which all of New Way's officials
have approved and passed since New Way's founding.
How is it? Did I make you feel surprised?
You've earned it through your own efforts.
Then right now...
Right now what?
Let me tell you-
I knew it.
She's definitely not normal.
So...they were just flirting earlier?
My girlfriend, Miss Gu Anxin,
in celebration of a passed design proposal, treats the entire company
to milk tea.
Are you crazy?
You have so many people in your company! I'll go broke!
Don't worry.
You treat, and I'll pay.
Idiot. Is your money not money?
What about the company culture and employee care that you spoke about earlier?
But some people don't like sweet drinks.
Alright.
Thank you for working so hard on our design.
There's a huge sense of achievement in designing something for the person you like.
Alright, I'll stop talking to you. I'm gonna go celebrate with Youyou and them.
I was thinking why you two left secretly, turns out you are on a secret date behind my back.
Who wants to go on a date with him? I'm trying to create an opportunity for you and President Ling.
Please, am I think kind of person who values love over frienship?
We have to celebrate together.
Indeed you're my good Xin Xin.
I have a piece of good news and a piece of bad news to tell everyone.
- Which one do you want to hear first?
- The bad one.
The bad news is we have a new assignment for the next month,
so we might have to work overtime again.
Then what is the good news?
The good news is
New Way's payment came. We can start preparing for a celebration soon!
How did the payment arrive so quickly this time?
That's because our leader is dating the President.
If we do well on the next assignment,
I will not be stingy with everyone's year-end bonus.
Does that mean the money I got
from following the advertising brand
Use it however you like.
Oh no, what's with my heart fluttering again?
Indeed you can see true feelings during hardships. Has she finally discovered my good qualities?
- Then how should we celebrate this?
Oh yeah.
Leave it up to me.
What the heck is Anxin planning?
Why are we doing a gift exchange in a dark place like this?
What happened? Why are so many candles?
Mike.
Why is the head a little slanted?
What the heck are you doing?
One, to save electricity.
Two, I did this for you.
What super big gift did you prepare?
You seem like you got your year-end bonus early.
I fell like you would like this.
Oh right, to thank you for
working so hard
I bought a pair of glasses for you.
They are light-adaptive. Try them on.
How are they? These are the newest style.
Very pretty.
Don't misunderstand, I'm just reminding you to work hard and make money.
We have to earn lots of money.
Work hard to make a lot of money.
Okay.
Why are you looking at me like this?
I know that I might not be your type
but for you, I can coexist with everything you like.
Wh- What do you mean?
You also think it's odd, right?
I always banter with you and roast you
but it's all because I like you.
I want you to pay attention to me; to see me.
I- I. . .
I won't disrupt the time you spend on your idols
but can you make some time for me
try dating me.
What do you mean by "try"? Are you confessing to me?
What else would I mean?
Who brings another man to their confession?
It's also my first time.
Then let's try.
President Ling, we join hands to publish the Ling-Xiao Plan early.
Utilize its Leverage effect. Not only could it quickly earn high profits
at the same time it can lead our two companies' other businesses.
This way, we can truly take dominate the 5G technology industry.
Ling-Xiao Plan is not fully prepared yet.
I need it to be perfect.
To get the advantage of being first, we have to publish it early.
We can deal with the other problems later.
And judging by economic situation right now
and in respect to current profits, it's more realistic.
Why do we do business?
Isn't the reason just to make more money?
If President Liu thinks the immediate profit is more important than future development
then we don't need to keep discussing this.
What a pity. I thought President Ling was smart.
Lots of businesses right now are fighting to work with me.
President Ling, do you really want to give up this chance?
Bid him farewell.
President Liu, please.
President Gu, your recent sale event received great feedback.
The colleagues want to have a celebration tonight
where do you think we should make a reservation?
In an hour and a half, notice everyone to attend the meeting.
We have to raise our market shares to at least 45%.
Also, tell all the departments
to raise their productivity. I want to hear useful content within ten minutes.
Okay, President Gu. I will notice them right away.
Wait.
Find a good place for your celebration dinner. Put the bill on my private account.
Okay, President Gu. But, President Gu, how will you get there?
I will not attend. You guys have fun.
Director Gu, Xing Ye Technology's Direction Liu is here.
Let him in.
President Gu, hello.
[Photograph]
Finally, you are willing to pick up my phone calls?
For company matters you can talk to Ai Li. Don't call me again.
Don't send packages home again. I don't want Anxin to misunderstand.
How do you always appear when I feel down?
I think this is called telepathy.
Somehow I felt that someone is feeling sad.
The dignified director of Sheng Shi Entertainment is now changed into a con artist.
- This is called being sincere.
- Okay.
Then I'll give you a chance to show it. Take me to work?
I was thinking about this. I just so happened to pass by to pick up my partner and take them to work.
Give me a break! You must have heard it from Lyon.
You have so many people keeing eyes on me
what is your purpose?
Putting in extra effort.
Here, Xin'er, eat it while it's hot.
Always getting me things for no reason, you must have a hidden motive.
You're right. The hidden motive is
I prepared a relaxation tool for you.
Ling Sheng, can no girl escape your soft attacks?
Then that's a pity. Somehow you escape it every time.
Xin'er, come here.
Come here. I'll help you.
No matter how brilliant someone is, there are always things they really cannot do.
Thank you.
You and Ling Yue are brothers, why are your personalities so different?
So are you starting to see my goodness in comparison?
Getting Ling Yue to do these type of things
is harder than reaching the sky.
Whether or not he does it is dependent on whether or not he likes you.
You're getting better at rubbing salt in my wound.
My neck hurts even more.
Xin'er, are you okay? How about going to a hospital?
I was joking. Did you take it seriously?
I take all of your words seriously.
Rare of you to not reject me.
I do not treat you that badly.
Not bad, just special.
Xin'er, I found a new restaurant. How about we try it out?
I want to drink alcohol.
If you want to drink alcohol, I'll keep you company tonight.
If someday you're not here either, then what would I do?
As long as you want, I'll always be beside you.
If you lie you'll become pinocchio.
Then fall into the belly of the whale.
You still remember middle school's musical jokes?
Aren't you the same?
Okay, let's get ready to leave.
That entertainment company's Director Sheng isn't easy to deal with.
Rejected me without a single glance.
Wasn't I just casually starting conversation? Simply shameful and humiliating.
Do you know what's the reason for rejecting me?
He was waiting for the person he likes to come.
Is only playing the pure and innocent character popular now?
Really.
You still remember.
I remember everything that you like.
But in the story, he didn't choose his love with Elina.
But the story didn't talk about how Elina had a fresh start again.
What memories won't fade?
I think the ones inside your heart.
This is the very special wine I collected. It's called Evermore.
From 2010 to this year, the flavor would be different
so I would collect one bottle each year
until the person I like marries me.
Why is it 2010?
Because that's the year we met.
Xin'er, do you know that its our first meeting anniversary?
I'm sorry, I can't remember it clearly.
It's fine, as long as I remember.
Xiao Shegn, I know you don't just want a "thank you,"
but I can't give you any promises right now.
I don't need any promises from you.
I only hope that you can go back when you were happy and that's enough.
Then let's forget everything today.
Then, cheers to your eyes.
In the movie Casablanca, the most romantic line.
Xin'er, you're awake.
Yesterday we...
We drank too much yesterday.
We did drink too much yesterday, but we...
We are adults. I don't need you to be responsible for anything.
Xin'er,
are you being serious?
Xin'er, look at me.
Your eyes clearly tell me that you're starting to slowly accept me.
Is this an illusion?
This is an accident.
We won't change anything because of this.
That person showing up in your world is an accident. I don't understand.
Why can't you give yourself a fresh start?
Could it be that you must hit the South Wall and get injured all over before you will turn around?
Because I'm not willing to give up.
Because I can't forget him.
Ling Sheng, I'm very confused right now.
Let me have some quietness, okay?
Xin'er.
Okay, I won't force you.
I already know your answer.
I respect you.
Remember to eat your breakfast.
Let's pause for awhile.
There's differences from what I expected
We still need to reinforce the base station's radius of frequency
and at the same time reduce the delay of the signal.
President Ling, we have already done the technical evaluations.
The program itself is perfect. If you want to enhance its capacity,
it still requires more funding.
Since you know there's room for improvement, don't be self-satisfied.
The funding aspect is not within your scope of consideration, you all only need to dive into technology.
- Do you guys understand?
- Understood.
These few days prepare the materials related to Ling Xiao's plan and initiate project funding.
Okay.
You're back.
Didn't I tell you to sleep first and not wait for me?
I didn't wait too long.
Why do you look so tired?
Are the superiors at your company
regretting after they found out that I was your girlfriend?
No.
They're making this decision because they like your design.
You've worked hard.
President Gu, Anxin's proposal plan is finished. Please have a look.
[Gu Ansheng]
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Soaking the memory wet ♫
♫ Fate works bizarrely ♫
♫ The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly beats out of normal ♫
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Obviously, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness,
for it has always been you ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Yet the reminiscing has never been able to stop ♫
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Using all of my most beautiful adjectives ♫
♫ Is still not enough to describe your name ♫
♫ Our story is exclusively ours ♫
♫ Our palms hold onto the key to the future ♫
♫ Using love to slowly open up a lifetime ♫