fTiming and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ No longer panicking on the night of the blackout ♫
♫ You're by my side, illuminating a beam of light for me ♫
♫ Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet ♫
♫ Your breath ♫
♫ brushes up against my cheek ♫
♫ With you warming up the stage,
happiness never comes to a close ♫
♫ Boring jokes add some sweetness to the dinner ♫
♫ Daily life is even more like a comic than comics themselves ♫
♫ Happiness and sadness ♫
♫ Make up the moments of life ♫
♫ Rainy days become very special because of you ♫
♫ Picked up a pitiful youngster off the street ♫
♫ No matter when and where, you always appear ♫
♫ Holding me tightly and spinning in circles ♫
♫ Rainy days make me so nostalgic because of you ♫
♫ Becoming some part of the memories ♫
♫ Walking down a street with lights lighting up
one after another ♫
♫ Warming up the whole world ♫
[Please Feel at Ease Mr. Ling]
[Episode 23]
Are you sure you didn't see them on the island?
We searched for a few days and found a suspicious couple. We followed them for a couple days and found out that it's not them.
Boss, didn't Brother Lun burn them to death? What are you worried about?
Without seeing the corpse, my heart isn't at ease.
It's been more than twenty years, so I understand Ling Yue too well.
Sinister, cunning
Just like the fish in the sea: slimy.
If they are still alive, we won't be able to catch them even if we wanted to.
Sprinkle some bait to get a bite, right?
Understood, Boss. I will send more people to continue searching.
Dad, what are you looking at?
While I am still lucid,
I'm looking through old photos.
Combing through the things in the past.
Dad, it looks like Second Brother's weight in your heart is still heavier.
Nonsense.
You three are all my biological sons,
and you all have the same weight in my heart.
There was something I originally planned to tell you first.
Right now, just rest first.
I will go get your medicine.
[The President of Ling Group Unexpectedly Dies, What Will be the Future of Ling Group?]
Ling Sheng, what exactly is going on?
Dad, Second Brother had an accident.
As for his funeral, I have already taken care of it.
I was afraid you would be upset, so I didn't dare to tell you.
Don't blame me.
Doctor! Doctor come quickly, my dad fainted!
I'm very sorry everyone.
My dad is still receiving emergency treatment in the intensive care unit. I'm not in the mood to be interviewed.
But everyone please be rest assured.
All the business of Ling Group will proceed as normal and will not be affected in any way.
Right now the most pressing matter is my dad's health.
I hope that my dad can smoothly get through this danger period.
But there have been rumors over the internet lately that  Ling Group's financial affairs have problems.
How do you explain this?
As they say, family disgraces shouldn't be spread publicly.
But according to the findings of our investigation,
this matter is directly related to New Way.
So you're saying, Ling Group did indeed appear at the asset transfer situation
and it was the dead Ling Yue's doing.
Don't speak ill of the deceased.
Even if my Second Brother has done some wrong things,
I, Ling Sheng, am here to implore everyone
don't mention it again.
Thanks, everyone.
This interview must be released on all internet, paper, and new media platforms.
Understood, Director Sheng. I will do so immediately.
Thanks, everyone.
This Ling Sheng really is shameless.
Exploiting you and your dad's father-son relationship and even slandering you.
Does he really think that we're dead and won't tear off his mouth?
But we don't have any evidence to prove that he is lying.
And with my dad's current situation,
I'm worried that Ling Sheng will do more excessive things.
But this is obviously something he designed.
If we hastily appear, wouldn't it be falling into his trap?
No matter what, I have to return.
I will go look at my dad's situation.
If my dad is also under his control,
the situation will be more troublesome than it is now.
Ok, I will go back with you.
Stay here. After I take care of these things, I will come back for you.
Didn't we say that we do things together?
Let me go with you.
Fine
Rest assured, I will protect you well.
It's better if I protect you.
Dad . . . look at me
Why . . . why why
Sorry for scaring you.
Has it been too strenuous recently?
Just now you were continuously sleep talking.
What did I say?
You're probably too worried about Uncle.
Uncle has the best medical treatments right now. He will definitely recover.
Xin'er, I'm scared.
I had a dream.
So many things happened in the dream.
I am really scared that the dream will become reality.
In the dream,
I remember that no matter how I waited for you,
but you didn't come at all.
When I wanted to give up, you finally came.
But you stood in front of me and said
"Ling Sheng, how could I like you?"
Silly fool
Xin'er, I'm scared.
I'm really very scared.
I really am scared that you will leave me.
I won't, I won't.
From now on,
you won't be alone again.
[Really?]
We finally meet.
What do you think? The movie theater I found is well hidden.
-Very well done, love you.
-As you should.
President Xiao Ling, your family really is a mountain of swords and a sea of flames.
Your own brother is really going to die.
That person does things to the extreme.
But since we don't have evidence, we must be passive.
The purpose of returning. First, is I'm worried about my dad's safety. Second, is to gather evidence.
Only by gathering sufficient evidence, can I confront him head-on.
How can you gather evidence? You can't enter the company or return home right now.
This requires you two, Conan fans.
-Us two?
-Yes.
All my people are closely followed by Ling Sheng.
You two usually have little contact with me, so it won't raise suspicion.
Understood. Zero suspicion.
At that time you pretended to be my boyfriend and helped me dodge a bullet.
It's time for female warrior to repay the favor.
It's not important, now we have the real deal.
I don't want you to be the female warrior, I want you to be the detective.
In this suspense, no one can play the detectives but us.
Unraveling the truth, just the thought makes people excited.
Have a drink. I want an orange tea cooler.
-Are they reliable?
-One hundred percent reliable.
What should we do next?
Ling Sheng and Yang Hong's interests are deeply intertwined. It will be very hard to discover their crack.
First of all, we have to create enmity between them.
Firstly, I can gather evidence.
Secondly, I can enter Ling Group to check Ling Sheng's account.
Right now he wants to control more shares, so he will definitely go to Yang Hong for help.
He wants Yang Hong's money, so he will definitely bring Gu Xin'er's marriage into discussion.
Merging their businesses through marriage.
Then how can we know about their progress?
Rest assured, I still have a hidden bargaining chip.
Director Sheng.
Why is it you?
Fang Xue, why are you here?
I come to this bar often.
Director Sheng, congratulations. You are now the head of Ling Group.
It's too early to say that, I haven't officially taken office.
Sooner or later Ling Group will be yours.
Thanks for your continuous care, Xiao Xue drinks to you.
Our cooperation has constantly been pleasant. No need to be so polite.
Director Sheng, our contract will expire soon.
Should we still renew it?
Of course. Provided that you have the desire to, we can renew it at any time.
That's great, Director Sheng! Then we can talk about the renewal matters.
Sorry, I am a little busy.
We can talk about the renewal matters later.
Xuer that was beautiful the show was spectacular
of course I can't forget about you
happy to cooperate
we must lower his status
can't believe he would do this
Is this the good news you give me?
they can't go missing, I will give you an explanation the by today
you better explain it well
'hospital'
In the name of protection, keep your family's old man captive here.
his heart is so cruel
I didn't think he wouldn't even let go Ling father
Lingsheng is already off the rails
but rest assured we are all watching him
he knows whats happening
Aili and I will do our best
Hello?
Yanghong is at the plaza
are you guys prepared
ready
we will stay in contact
this is my recorder
Zhaolei put it in Yaohong's purse
Alright
Hello miss! Welcome to our store event
excuse me, I'm in a rush
Miss Yang?
the honorable Miss Yang, thank you for the support of our humble shop
today we give you a special membership discount
how did you know my surname is Yang
Yanghong is super arrogant
If you flatter her she will give in
I've had the pleasure to serve you a few time
I couldn't forget such a stunning customer
and you are our VVVIP top three
Alright sure, why don't you share with me what promotion you have
of course
if it's Lingsheng, he would be extremely cautious to meet with Yanghong
then our recorder might get discovered
if it's Yanghong...
she is won't let her bag get checked
what do want?
Ma'am please cooperate
you think I don't trust you
It's fine
then get the recorder back
don't be too suspicious
everyday at 3pm she goes to LinMao restaurant to have afternoon tea, it's a perfect oportunity
Hello Miss
a latte and strawberry shortcake
yes
your taste is so great
this is... oh
what is wrong with you?
oh i'm so sorry
get a napkin
oh my gosh these pants must be expensive
i'm sorry miss
i won't be able to wash this off
Auntie Yang isn't it a vulnerable time to get caught
and scared about nothing
then we would still have to give them the opportunity to attack
Miss Yang do you believe these photos
If I didn't intercept these pictures
then it be posted everywhere
what do you think?
I have my limits
I would never hurt Xiner
Please believe me, mother
I can't accept such a promise
if it happened once then there will be a second
I can block it once but not forever
my patience is limited. hopefully you won't do anything like this again
please feel assured I only have eyes for Xiner
Our goal will quickly be accomplished
as long as you save me
it is saving Xiner and Gushi Company
I never knew before but...
all your words are flattery
as now we are on the same team
you are my mother and I am now your son
I will treat Xiner well and treat Ansheng as a brother
sweet words...
but you transferring the assets is illegal
if I am at risk
can you still keep the promise to Xiner
and place the promised equity under my name
I understand, what do you wish me to do?
sign an official transfer of equity
whats the matter? you are not willing?
of course
can you believe me now
did you take care of Anxin and Lingyue
relax
those two are now good as gone
You're so sure.
I couldn't even find them all the ICU's
I know him well, this is how he dies
as long as he is alive, he will even crawl to visit father, unless he is dead
then thats good
last time she brought up the past I think it would be bad for Xiner
I need her completely vanish then Xiner wouldn't be caught
this Yuguo is just so unlucky
the poison meant was for Anxin
if it wasn't because of her allergy...
don't worry it is all in the past
now I can give Yuguo an explanation
brother
Xiner, take a look
why did you buy this?
don't you like these
you always say I played favorites and only gave to Anxin
don't I know you?
you don't like sweets but you just wanted to eat with Anxin
you actually like walnut crepes
then why didn't you buy this sooner
hope it is not too late
thank you, brother
Xiner, I've been thinking
and couldn't figure it out
do you think living in reality is more important
or living happy more important
living in happiness
now if we have their signed contract and the recorder
then we can prove they transfered the equity
and not you
yes, thats true but we are running out of time
do as my brother says
him helping us is a little odd to me
don't have such prejudice against him
if he says he will help then he will do everything he can
your give him such high remarks
this isn't something to be jealous about
I am admiring him; he can inspire you to trust him so much.
Whenever we talk about him, you speak of him with so much pride.
Not so.
My adoration and trust in you is right in here.
It's packed full; I can't give it to anyone else.
♫ Watching as the street lights flash on and off ♫
Let's finish watching the movie.
♫ We can see how far away our future is just by turning our heads back ♫
♫ We've yet to part but longing has already begun ♫
♫  Let me love you. Let me use my sincere heart ♫
♫ and learn to use warmth to cover up the cold memories of the past ♫
♫ We've walked with the scenery along our journey and stopped ♫
Is it pretty?
Beautiful.
♫ The story continues on as the camera makes a full-length shot ♫
The wedding dress really is beautiful.
♫ Turns out happiness caused audible laughs ♫
Its name is Goya. In Urdu,
It symbolizes a dreamworld, as if it has become reality.
Just like what's in my heart.
The sight of you wearing a dress for me
I don't know how many times it's appeared like this in my dreams.
Now it's appeared in front of my eyes, I almost dare not believe it's real.
♫ Turns out happiness caused audible laughs ♫
♫  Let me love you. Let me use my sincere heart ♫
Xiao Sheng.
All of this is real.
From now on, every single instant
will be real.
I thought that this day that I've been waiting for would never come.
Thank you for your persistence. Thank you for making my dream come true.
The dream I've had for so long.
♫  Let me love you. Let me use my sincere heart ♫
I know
♫ and learn to use warmth  ♫
that we can't live life over again. But the time that's been wasted...
♫ to cover up the cold memories of the past ♫
let it be in the past.
Starting now, let's begin again. Okay?
♫ We've walked with the scenery along our journey and stopped ♫
♫ The story continues on as the camera makes a full-length shot ♫
Okay. I promise you that.
I will definitely give you the most beautiful wedding.
Bring you the most dependable happiness.
Dad. Dad, are you ready or not?
We're coming.
There's still time before this engagement ceremony. Why do we have to go so early.
It's an important event. Let's leave early in case something goes wrong.
Dad, you look smart.  You even put the brooch on.
After all it's Anxin's engagement party.
That requires a ceremonial presence.
It's Xin'er. Xin'er.
How can you be so confused?
Why don't you go wait in the car? I'll go see if Xin'er is ready or not.
Okay. Let's go.
Careful.
Mom.
Do me a favor and ask Xin'er why she's turned around and gone back?
She probably forgot something. She's forgetful.
We'll do this together.
How do you open this?
I've got the automation console now. I re-programmed the face recognition software.
I'll go keep watch.
[House Deed]
[Stock Transfer Record]
Wait a minute.
- Mom, why did you get out?
- I'm going to use the bathroom.
Xin'er, have you gotten everything?
- Yes, I've got it.
- I'm going to use the bathroom.
Is something wrong, Xin'er?
Don't worry, Brother. It's fine.
[Gu Xin'er and Ling Sheng]
Lao Gu.
Congratulations on your son's engagement.
Engagement?
- Who's getting engaged?
- Hey, Lao Gu.
You really are a joker.
Lao Jiang.
Thank you for coming to this event. These days, many people don't show this kind of consideration.
Of course.
- Congratulations, congratulations.
- Thank you.
- I'm going to talk with a friend.
- Okay.
What's wrong, Yuanchao?
Is... is today Anxin's engagement party?
- It's Xin'er.
- Xin...Xin'er?
Who...who are you?
Let's get something to eat. Don't drink anymore.
I believe that, with all of your support, our Ling Shi Group will become better and better.
It surely will.
President Sheng, we'll take a look over there, okay?
- Okay.
- Excuse us.
Third Brother, here. Spare me a few minutes.
Brother, I'm busy. If you need something. we can talk about it later.
Then...let's have a drink.
Since this is a happy occasion, I'll have a drink with you.
Brother, let's talk later.
The banquet will start soon; I'll go get ready.
Get this printed. Then put it over there. Yes. That should work.
Heavens!
Where did you come from, waitress? Can't you carry water?
What's going on here?
What are you doing? You're so careless. You're so pretty; do you use that instead of brains?
- I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. There's nothing important on this computer, is there?
- This has all the videos we want to show.
- Aiya....this...
Fortunately, President Ling already prepared a back up.
Go back to work. Be more careful.
I'm so sorry.
Come to my office this afternoon. I want to talk to you.
Okay.
It's like that. So, Miss Gu, we'll be going.
Thank you.
Our Xin'er is very beautiful today.
Brother.
Thank you, Brother.
But there are some other things that I want to talk to you about.
I saw Ling Yue and Anxin.
This is your hone, too. Do you know where the back door is?
What were you thinking?
They are okay so I'm at ease.
But what I thought before was that after this engagement is over,
everything will become easier.
Ling Yue and Anxin
would also come to congratulate us.
They.
Xin'er, are you ready? It's almost about to start.
I'm ready.
Brother. I trust you.
No matter what happens, you will be by my side.
What are you guys talking about?
We are saying that in the future, if you dare bully me
my brother won't let you go.
Brother, relax. Leave Xi'an to me.
Let's go.
We are leaving, brother.
Everyone, thank you for coming to the engagement party for me and Xin'er
and sharing our happiness.
The way I see it, Xin'er
is like the moon in the skies.
Glorious. Bright and clear.
I've worked to get closer to her
for so many years.
Right now
I am finally next to her.
Holding her hand
Laughing together
Crying together, and becoming old together.
Thinking about this,
I think I'm the happiest man in the world
And I...
will giver her happiness.
Xin'er, thank you.
Thank you for coming to my side.
Stupid.
Why are you crying?
I prepared a surprise for you.
What?
- Those are so nice.
- True.
- What's this then?
Your property transfer is illegal.
If I take the risk, you will be the biggest shareholder.
Will you still keep your promise
to list all the shares under my name?
- I understand. What do you want me to do?
Sign an official stock transfer document.
- What?
- Let me through.  Excuse me.
Mrs. Gu, is the voice in the video your voice?
- Give us an answer.
I really can't believe that Mrs. Gu is that kind of person.
That's true. It's even more hard to believe about the young CEO Ling.
How will you deal with Ling Yue and Anxin?
Don't worry. Those two are already wandering ghosts.
Soundman! Turn off the power! Turn it off.
My father is already in intensive care. We don't have to rush him out. He may die.
Xin'er, let me explain.
I can explain.
I don't know which statements you are saying are true.
Which ones are fake. Which ones are real?
I am true about you.
-What's going on? Can you tell us what's going on.
- Mrs. Gu! Mrs. Gu! Give us an explanation.
I originally believed that.
You know what the last part of that recording has.
If you love Xin'er, then you will let her leave with me immediately.
It's fine Xin'er. Let's go.
- What's going on? Can you explain this to us?
You're not allowed to take pictures!
Xin'er. I will explain to you when we get back, okay?
Xin'er. Listen to me. You have to leave here right now.
- Yes. That's right.
- Mrs. Gu! Explain all this to us.
Before, that girl said there was new evidence. I'm really afraid it won't benefit Xin'er.
Only if she completely disappears,
our Xin'er the matter from before may be revealed.
That Yu Guo really is bad luck.
It's that darn girl with Alprazolam.
What is she drinking?
If you can't sleep again, you can't take this medicine carelessly.
Once or twice is okay. More than that, you can become dependent on it.
Don't worry. I'm just helping out a classmate.
She's been rehearsing lately and it's quite difficult.
So she can't sleep.
Right, Xin'er.
When will that play be performed?
My darling daughter surely has a leading role.
Even in my dreams, I wouldn't have believed
that I'd be Gu Anxin's understudy.
I'm apologizing to you right now.
Ai! Yu Guo!
Yu Guo!
Mom. Is this all true?
It's not real.
Xin'er, you've done nothing wrong.
It has nothing to do with you.
It was all An Xin's fault. All her fault.
Mom.
Baby. Mom is doing this for you.
It was all for you.
For me?
Did you do it for me or yourself?
You kept it secret from me for so many years.
It wasn't until today that I realized that I was the reason.
Now it's great.
I have nothing.
Are you satisfied?
Xin'er, calm down. Let's leave this place.
Is the recording real? Is this the reality of the situation?
Please explain. Did you hurt An Xin because of your own daughter?
Please say something.
Give us a response.
Can you respond to our questions?
Dad.
Send your dad to the hospital. I'm begging you. Son.
Someone come.
You two, stop the reporters.
No more pictures.
Hurry.
Madam, madam, give us an answer.
Answer our questions, Madam.
Xin'er.
Just say a little something. Answer us, Miss Gu.
Did you really harm someone? Exactly what went on back then?
Did you really do those things?
Everyone wants to know the truth, Miss Gu.
- Give us a response.
- Clarify this for us, okay?
- Don't leave.
-What did that recording mean?
- Did you and your mother-in-law really transfer Ling Shi's property?
Is it true that you harmed your own brother because Miss Gu?
Please give us an explanation. Answer our questions in person here.
Everyone, be quiet!
The recording is a fabrication.  It's all nonsense.
Are you still lying at this point of time?
- You're still lying even now?
- It's President Ling Yue.
- He's still alive?
This is great. This is going to be good.
True. The company will be saved.
What is going on?
How is it that he's here. Didn't he die?
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Memories are soaked in rain ♫
♫ Fate works bizarrely ♫
♫ The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly beats abnormally ♫
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Obviously, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness, for it has always been you ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Yet the longing has never been able to stop ♫
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Using all of my most beautiful adjectives ♫
♫ Is still not enough to describe your name ♫
♫ Our story is exclusively ours ♫
♫ Our palms hold onto the key to the future ♫
♫ Using love to slowly open up a lifetime ♫