Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ No longer panicking on the night of the blackout ♫
♫ You're by my side, illuminating a beam of light for me ♫
♫ Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet ♫
♫ Your breath brushes up against my cheek ♫
♫ With you warming up the stage,
happiness never comes to a close ♫
♫ Boring jokes add some sweetness to the dinner ♫
♫ Daily life is even more like a comic than comics themselves ♫
♫ Happiness and sadness make up the moments of life ♫
♫ Rainy days become very special because of you ♫
♫ Picked up a pitiful youngster off the street ♫
♫ No matter when and where, you always appear ♫
♫ Holding me tightly and spinning in circles ♫
♫ Rainy days make me so nostalgic because of you ♫
♫ Becoming some part of the memories ♫
♫ Walking down a street with lights lighting up
one after another ♫
♫ Warming up the whole world ♫
[Please Feel at Ease Mr. Ling]
[Episode 8]
Where is Anxin? Where did you hide her?
Brother...
I think you're like a fly, buzzing around me.
You should go eat somewhere else. I'm not angry.
I don't want to talk about it or pressure you anymore.
No matter what happened between you two, he was in the wrong right?
Brother...
Mother, I can do it alone. You should eat more.
Eat more, you're about to move out.
You can't have such good food anywhere else.
My house is just in the downtown area.
You speak as if I'm going to study in another country.
Then live at home!
The house is so big. It's not like there isn't space for you.
Alright.
He's already grown up and needs his own independence. It's a good thing.
What are you doing?
Oh right, dad, Anxin especially asked me to spend time with you.
She's been thinking of you all this time.
She's thinking of me? If she doesn't anger me then I'm thankful to the heavens.
I was having such a nice birthday party and it turned out like that.
Embarrassing me in front of so many people!
- Dad, Anxin didn't do it on purp—
Brother...
It's so hard for us to finally eat a dinner together as a family.
Why does the topic have to go back to Anxin.
- Anxin is also —
- Speak less, eat more.
Apologize to my mother!
Starting today, you have no more relations with the Gu Family!
Take your things and get out!
It's been all packed up
- Go ahead and move it out.
- Okay.
- Slowly, be careful not to break anything.
- Alright, alright.
Here, there's this stuff too.
Got it.
Be careful with this chair.
Got it, don't worry.
- Quickly.
- Sister Li!
- Anxin.
- What's going on?
You're awake. This is perfect, we just need to move the things in your bedroom.
Sir, go ahead and move the things from the room.
W-Wait. What's the meaning of this?
Didn't I tell you early on?
Your lease was up last month.
If you don't pay rent I'm going to sell it.
Next week, the buyer is moving in. I need to clean up.
I haven't found another place. Also, this is so sudden where am I supposed to find another place?
That's not my problem.
Over here.
Be careful, it's on the ground.
Don't ruin my floor.
Young lady, where should we move these things?
[Fat Bears Moving]
- Brother.
- What happened?
I'm sorry, I'm late.
Your landlord is so difficult. Why didn't you tell me sooner?
Renting is always like this.
Don't worry, Brother is here.
I have an empty room. Why don't you move in?
That's not good. I'll be a bother to your personal life.
Also, if you bring over a sister-in-law..
What kind of personal life do I have?
I only came back to the country a few days ago, I don't even have a few friends.
Even if I do, you come first.
I can't watch my little sister living on the streets.
Brother...
Silly child. You don't have to be shy around me.
The room's empty anyway.
Then alright. Once I find an apartment I'll move out right away.
Okay, I'll listen to you.
[Text messages with Anxin]
[Most recent message: Cute.]
[What are you doing? You must listen to me. Don't contact her on your own!]
[Don't contact her on your own!]
I have an idea for how you can make amends.
To help you get Anxin back.
- Tell me.
- You already know, I'm an expert when it comes to relationships.
Since you've already sent her a lunch box
you can't be the first to contact her.
This is called giving a slap, then giving candy.
That way you seize the initiative.
President Ling, Miss Anxin moved.
What?
[This is my new address.]
[I just got off the plane. I'll come find you in a few days.]
[Did you move to a big lake villa?]
[I never thought my friend would realize her dream of becoming a rich woman so quickly.]
[Me? A rich woman?]
[I don't know if I'll ever have that prospect in my life.]
[I'm just benefiting off of my brother.]
[It's his house.]
[Your brother? The one you said is the most handsome boy in the school abroad?]
[That's right. Haven't you been wanting to...?]
[You wait for me! I'm going to drop off my luggage and come over.]
[You value boyfriends over friends.]
[WeChat]
We're eating braised pig trotters today.
Okay, is there anything I can help with?
Help me put on the apron.
Okay.
Here, let me help you put on your gear.
Alright
Alright.
- Hello?
- Hello? Is this Mr. Gu?
You have a package here. Please come pick it up.
Package? Alright, I'll come get it.
Gu Ansheng said he'll come get it soon.
President Ling, you were the one that said we'll head over after Gu Anshen leaves.
Yes, as long as he's there Anxin won't give me a chance.
- Brother, you need to go pick up a package?
- Yes.
Then when you go get the package, can you go to the supermarket to buy some good food?
I have an especially good friend coming over.
Okay.
Your drink!
This is how a guy's skin should be
pale and soft.
I really want to pinch it.
Oh mother, that face.
Why is he winking at me?
My blood will drain out.
That damn charm.
I got your drink.
Are you okay?
Wife
What is our child called?
-Let's call him Jeremy.
-What?
Uh, hi! My name is Xu Youyou.
Miss, your drink.
Then...
I will leave first.
Xu Youyou, Xu Youyou.
You should work out more.
You were almost successful in chasing the man of your dreams.
He came back so quickly.
How can you eat my food and not take responsibility.
I didn't eat it, I tossed it out.
You- whatever.
I don't have time to take care of you.
I will treat it as my own house, so no need to take care of me.
You're pretty rude to just treat this as your home.
As long as you are there, it's my home.
Wait, we knew each other for a few months,
so we aren't even that close.
Even though some people have known each other for a short amount of time, but it feels like a lifetime.
You don't have that feeling?
No.
I'm going to wash the dishes.
-I'll help you.
-I don't need you to help me.
-Then let me cuff up your sleeves.
-No need.
I don't need-
Okay.
Let me do it.
No matter how much you reject me,
I will use 100 ways to get closer to you.
Ow!
Hi, we meet again.
Hi.
Is this what they call
"If two are destined, they will meet across a thousand li."
Where do you live?
I live here.
I also am in the 28th building!
What a coincidence.
-Do you need any help?
-Yeah!
Wait, would it be a hassle?
No, it wouldn't be.
I was just waiting for you to say that, future husband.
Let's go.
With a face like that, it can kill anyone.
But he is very humble and warm.
He is sure my ideal type
Am I dreaming?
Miss Youyou
You didn't select a floor, which floor do you live on?
I live on the 18th floor.
What a coincidence!
Do you also live on that floor?
I live in 1808.
Can you be-
You are the guest for today?
You are Anxin's brother?
I am Anxin's brother, Ansheng.
This is retribution, you know.
What kind of design is this?
There are dangers everywhere.
Who puts the spoon that high? What happens if you forget to close the cabinet, and it hurts you in the end?
It's you who's incompatible with this place. I have no issues.
It's all Gu Ansheng's fault.
Apologies.
Is this my house?
You are...
Miss Ai Li?
You are Xiao Ba's lover, Ai Li?
Who is Xiao Ba?
The cripple who lived in Anxin's house.
-There must be some misunderstanding-
-See!
I knew it, the mistress main line!
I've seen it too many times in all the dramas I have watched.
I will repeat myself one more time.
If you continue to do this, then I will call the police.
The Ling Group's people like to go to other's home,
If that kind of news spreads, it wouldn't look too good on you guys.
You were the one who wasn't careful, why are you blaming my brother.
Your button.
-I'll help you button it up.
-I can do it myself.
-I'll help you.
-I don't need you to help me.
-Anxin-
-I don't need you to.
What are you doing-
Anxin, those types of things you need to go to the room.
No, brother, we were just-
Anxin, wait here for a second.
President Ling!
Let him hit me!
Brother!
Ling Yue!
Why didn't you block it?
Your rejection is worse than his punch.
President Ling.
Let's go.
Ansheng, your hand is injured!
Does it hurt?
It doesn't hurt.
I just hate that I didn't punch him harder.
FFFFFFFFFF
I saw everything, and you are still standing up for him.
-No, I-
-Wait Anxin.
Isn't Xiao Ba's leg crippled?
How, what is this situation between you two?
I'm getting confused.
I will explain it to you later on.
Let me do it, I learned first aid.
Brother no matter what hitting someone is wrong.
He bullied you so do you want me to stand there and watch?
Okay, don't let me see him ever again.
I am against you two being together.
I already explained to you that it was a misunderstanding.
- It was because my collar...
- Actually, I don't think this can be called bullying.
They both mutually like each other.
It's just a couple's flirty banter.
-We aren't a couple!
-They aren't a couple!
Be careful.
Who told you two not to listen to me.
You had to go find her.
What a good place we're in now. Not only did she not appreciate your kindness,
And you came back injured.
It wasn't completely without gain.
At least it's a good start.
See, his brain is broken.
President Ling, this time Miss Anxin
should have forgiven you.
What are you two whispering behind my back? Are you having a secret meeting?
It-t hurts!
If I have a fracture, no one will put on medicine for President Ling.
I can put on medicine myself.
At a time like this, if you're not going to help me, at least don't support her.
It' hurts!
But I need you to help me somewhere else.
I can't get up, help me.
The hands of someone who practices martial arts are quite soft.
If you do this again next time, you are dead!
I don't dare to!
No way! That is too exciting!
I announce from today on,
I am not a supporter of you two.
I am a hater of Xiao Ba.
Isn't he deceiving your feelings? He's a total jerk.
He is actually not a jerk.
Forget it, let's not talk about him.
But don't be too upset.
There's no man that my pretty little sister Gu Anxin can't get.
You're just letting go of a little sapling
in order to win a big forest.
Don't worry. You can choose any good man you want.
You're indulging me for no reason.
I feel like you have something you want me to help you in.
It's nothing.
Can you help me see
if your brother
Wow! Xu Youyou.
You want to be my sister-in-law?
I'm shy!
Don't worry, leave it to me.
Don't let your own fertile water flow into someone else's field, understand?
Thank you for your great kindness.
Don't! I'm going to throw up!
I'm going to hang up!
[Are you already sleeping?]
[What's up?]
[How can I help you?]
[I'm sleeping.]
Is there no signal?
Are you sleeping?
What is it, Brother?
If you haven't slept yet, then drink some milk.
Come on in.
Thank you, Brother.
Brother,
are you dating?
Why are you asking me this suddenly?
Have you dated?
I'm so...stiff
there probably aren't any girls who want to date me.
That's not right. I remember when you started university
every time you came home your backpack was filled with love letters.
What do you think of You You?
She's quite energetic.
But don't you think about doing anything.
- You're shy.
- No I'm not.
Ah you're shy! Look at you.
You're embarrassed, look!
Don't joke around.
I'm hungry...
Work didn't wake me up this morning,
it was breakfast.
You're up.
Why did you wear so little coming out aren't you cold?
It's hot today.
That's not good. What if you catch a cold.
Go wear some pants.
Go, listen to me.
Thanks for yor help.
Wait a moment.
Help me pass along a message. It's cooled down lately
Also Wear more clothing. Don't catch a cold.
And also, this breakfast is just for her,
not for the person named Gu Ansheng.
Remember, Gu Ansheng.
Gu Ansheng. Got it.
Hey, move over.
You don't even know how to flirt.
Let me tell you. Say this later.
Coming!
- Xiao Wang!
- Sister Anxin!
You moved so quickly.
This is the breakfast that Mr. Ling sent you.
Umm...just tell him that I already ate breakfast today.
Go ahead and give it back to him.
Ah, Sister Anxin, if you do this I'll be fired.
Lingyue, you dare blackmail me.
Ah then give it to me.
Why don't you stay and eat breakfast before you go?
No no no no.
My client has a message to give too.
Anxin, the weather outside is cold.
Remember to wear a coat when you go out.
Also, I know you're still mad at me.
That's why I have been good to keep away.
But please receive the heart I've put into
the breakfast I made for you.
Remember, you must eat all of it.
Don't give any to unimportant people. Good morning.
I love you more today than I did yesterday.
This is what Ling Yue said?
Yes.
I got it. I'll see you at work.
Love you.
You scared me.
Brother!
That's too...wasteful.
What do you want to eat? I'll make it for you.
Don't worry about him.
[New Way]
Hi sisters! What kind of small meeting are you in?
Come quick. I'll tell you a huge secret.
- Ai Li and President Ling are together!
- Ai Li and President Ling are together?!
Talk softly.
They're keeping a low profile relationship.
If you leak the news that'll be bad.
When did this happen?
Why so suddenly?
How is that sudden?
This morning when I went to report on my work,
President Ling suddenly stopped Ai Li.
Wait a moment.
Was the breakfast eaten?
Yes.
That's all.
You may go first. I have some business with Ai Li.
Alright.
Such a shame.
I didn't even get a chance.
Stop your mouth!
President Ling, I'll wait for you outside.
Okay.
It's good that you came.
I have to go on a business trip for a few days—
When I go to my business trip help me with
the plan we discussed to make Anxin happy.
Why are you looking at me like that?
You-you going on the business trip,
Is it with Ai Li?
Yes.
Then everything is true?
Otherwise it's fake?
Then you tell me,
it's fake that you like Anxin, isn't it?
Of course it's real.
What are you trying to say?
Honestly tell me,
you...haven't thought about...with Ai Li...
do something...since she is quite pretty after all.
Don't you like her?
How did you know? Does Ai Li know?
I don't have time to fool around with you.
I'm going. Don't forget our plans.
Ling Yue! Shh!
Don't tell Ai Li!
[Express Delivery Service]
- Oh my!
Look!
Anxin! You're finally here.
We've been jealous all morning.
Come quickly, look!
What's going on?
First Batman, right?
We're meeting so quickly.
What a coincidence.
Alright, come on in first.
I just need to get this package to you here. I'm leaving.
This is the service attitude from your company?
Isn't it no bad reviews?
Is it time for me to add some bad reviews?
Client, is there something you need?
Yes.
Here, come on in.
How is it? Surprised?
That was quite scary. You—
Don't be worried.
Please sit anywhere. Sit!
Have some wine.
This wine is too expensive, I don't want to drink it.
Expensive, then have some cake.
Can I not eat?
What do you think?
What... what does this mean?
It's a gift for you.
It's a gift for me? You shoved it into the cake?
What if I broke my teeth on it? I don't have the money to get fake teeth.
Director Ling, what exactly is it that you want?
I just want to sit and have a nice conversation with you.
Is that okay?
Did you receive what I sent? Do you like it?
You sent me those bags?
I like giving pretty girls like you
little things like that.
That's true. Only you would like that yellow color
which looks like poo.
What did you say?
Only you would like that yellow color
- which looks like poo.
- Hey!
Fine. It looks like you still don't know what you want.
Then I'll give you one more gift.
I hope you'll like it.
- What is this?
- Open it and see.
[Property ownership contract]
What move are you playing now?
Sign it.
- So I only have to sign.
- Yeah.
- And I'll have a big villa?
- Exactly.
- I won't have to be a delivery person.
- Right.
And I can stay at home collecting rent everyday—
Is there something wrong with you?
You're sending me bags, a car, and a house.
What are you trying to do?
Then what do you like? Whatever you like, I can...
I just like money.
Then that's perfect.
I have a lot of money.
Give me a number for you to leave Ling Yue and be my girlfriend.
¥1,000,000?
¥10,000,000?
¥100,000,000?
I couldn't tell from looking at you.
You're quite small, but your appetite sure isn't small.
- Fine, then I'll—
- One good review.
Anxin, why do you keep rejecting me?
- I'm sincere—
- You're sincerely trying to make things difficult for me.
Since you're so unwilling to give me a good review,
then you can do whatever you want.
Didn't you say you wanted me to be satisfied?
Yes.
You've already sent me so many gifts.
It's only right that I give you a gift.
- What gift?
- Perfume.
What perfume?
What did you spray?
How is Six God?
(a mosquito repellent)
I also took a suggestion to add some Sichuan hot pepper. Is it refreshing?
I won't go blind, will I?
It won't go so far as to make you blind.
Instead of wailing here, you'd be better off going to wash your eyes.
I'm warning you, don't try to casually seduce little women.
Remember this lesson. Goodbye.
She's interesting.
If you're so unfortunate as to meet a pervert,
use this Six God spray infused with Sichuan hot pepper
and spray it into his eyes.
[Hello, I am the #888 robotic vacuum that you drew.]
[I'll suck up your unhappiness.]
[Please go to the Lin'an Bridge to retrieve me.]
- Here.
- Thank you.
- This is yours.
- Take care.
- I'm sorry, Manager. Today is my last day at work.
I still haven't managed to get a good review. I've held everyone back.
How about this? You can deduct my pay.
That way I can feel more at ease.
Anxin, you have already achieved a perfect five-star review.
The customer specially made a phone call thanking you for sending his things to him just in time.
That guy seems pretty perverted, but his heart isn't bad.
- Anxin?
- Please, go on.
Everyone, come over!
Here, this is for you.
Anxin, even though you will soon leave Express Delivery Service,
I ask that you remember
we will always be your colleagues!
- That's right!
- Yes!
How has Anxin been recently?
Miss Anxin has already quit her job at Express Delivery Service.
Oh right, President Ling, recently Director Ling Fang has been rather active.
Don't worry about him. Let him do as he pleases.
It's not work-related. Recently, he keeps hanging around Miss Anxin.
- Make a U-turn.
- Okay.
Anxin.
We're really brought together by fate.
- Do you need something?
- I was in the wrong that day. I'm here to apologize.
This is a gift I prepared for you as a token of my regard.
Director Ling, we aren't friends just because you left a good review. Do you understand that?
We may not be friends today, but that doesn't mean we won't be tomorrow.
Plus, there's the day after tomorrow, and the day after that.
The bags and other strange things you gave me,
I sent them all back to you. You should have received them.
Don't do these things in the future. It's really childish.
How come I just can't seem to do it?
- You can't do it?
- Hey, hey.
I'm just giving you a gift to express my apology.
If you don't want it, throw it away.
Sorry about that, I didn't—
My heart is beating so fast it'll explode.
I'm going to throw up, you're disgusting.
Let her go!
Couldn't you see that Anxin and I were being intimate? Why are you running over to be a third wheel?
Who's being intimate with you?
Did you forget Six God?
Look, she's even concerned for me.
Elder Brother, is it here that hurts?
Or here?
No, no, wait.
It doesn't hurt.
- It doesn't hurt, does it?
- No, it doesn't hurt.
That's good then. I'll go now.
What about you?
Second Brother, your leg just got healed. Take care of yourself.
Are you hurt?
Let's go.
Are you okay?
You can first go to the briefing by yourself.
Alright.
When did she get so close to Ling Fang?
Could it be that something happened in the two days I was on my business trip?
My wrist hurts and he doesn't even show any concern.
- If you don't drive, I'll get off the car.
- Wait.
Q-Qiuhong Garden, thank you.
Then I'll go now.
What's wrong?
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Soaking the memory wet ♫
♫ Fate works bizarrely ♫
♫ The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly beats out of normal ♫
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Obviously, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness,
for it has always been you ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Yet the reminiscing has never been able to stop ♫
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Using all of my most beautiful adjectives ♫
♫ Is still not enough to describe your name ♫
♫ Our story is exclusively ours ♫
♫ Our palms hold onto the key to the future ♫
♫ Using love to slowly open up ♫
♫ a lifetime ♫