NEVERTHELESS,
ALL LOCATIONS, CHARACTERS,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND INCIDENTS
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
I'm sure…
that we feel the same way.
KWON YEO-JU
I don't think I can go today.
How about tomorrow?
Okay. That's fine.
Sorry.
PARK JAE-EON
Jae-eon isn't the dating type.
What do you mean?
He may flirt but never commits.
He just draws the line.
Did he say so himself?
That he never commits?
Na-bi, you know what?
Flowers don't bloom
just for one butterfly.
What are you saying?
Jae-eon is like that flower.
Full of vanity,
a symbol of seductive beauty
that withers once it's plucked.
That's what Jae-eon is.
What's with you?
I know we're an art major, but still.
You may not know it,
but his every move is calculated.
Well…
I sometimes felt that something was off,
but it's not like that.
That's how everyone
falls for his tricks or not.
Actually, everyone knows.
They say they won't get fooled,
but they do when he shows
an ounce of sincerity.
Because they want to believe it.
I'm telling you.
Park Jae-eon?
He has no interest at all in dating.
He just likes to play with girls
who are drawn to him.
So forget him.
You don't know how to keep things casual.
What are you on about? We're just friends.
Stop lying to yourself.
Men and women can't be just friends.
Says the one with tons of guy friends.
I keep them close
since there's a possibility.
Hanging out with guys
heightens sexual tension.
Even Jae-eon?
He's not bad to hang out with.
And he's totally handsome.
Is it good?
You're actually eating cafeteria food?
I suggested eating here.
Right.
I'll get some water.
Okay.
What is it? Are you sick?
Well, I…
I just bit my tongue.
Are you all right?
Yes. I'm okay.
I'll be off first. Enjoy your food.
Where are you going?
You didn't forget, right?
-What?
-I'm using my wish.
You already used your wish.
Aren't you granting me another one?
Fine, but nothing weird.
EPISODE 2: IT'S NOT ONLY ME.
NEVERTHELESS,
Dance.
No.
That's my wish.
Can't we just leave?
Let's hang out here.
I can't hear anything. It's too loud.
What are you doing?
Jae-eon keeps making me feel excited.
All I see is Jae-eon.
Are you feeling the same way?
Sorry.
Let's go.
What?
Why am I so red?
I'm smoking outside.
Can I see your ID?
Thank you.
Jae-eon.
You weren't reading my messages.
Were you hanging out here?
Are you alone?
Se-mi and Mi-so are inside.
Want to join us?
I'm with her.
You can hang out without me.
Come on, we can all hang out together.
We can call other guys, too.
Jae-eon…
makes me feel anxious.
Well…
I'm fine.
You can go hang out with her.
I'll head home first.
Why would you leave?
Why don't you just go?
All right, then.
Bye.
Why did you try to ditch me?
You made me feel awkward.
You two seemed close.
I thought you should hang out with her.
We're not close.
We went to the same academy, is all.
We can all hang out together.
We can call other guys, too.
Is that all?
She looked pissed when you told her to go.
Did she?
Right. Maybe it's not a big deal for you.
She had a butterfly
on her wrist, too.
I'm not sure
if it was a drawing or a tattoo.
She just got it by herself.
By herself?
Why?
Maybe she wanted to see my reaction.
You know how friends from academies
sometimes hang out together.
But she kind of obsessed over me.
She was delusional.
Why are you suddenly so serious?
It has nothing to do with you,
so don't worry about it.
I'm taking the bus over there.
You're really going?
Yes.
I'm a bit tired.
I'll take you home. It's late.
No, there's no need.
Bye.
Is he just keeping me on the hook?
What's with him?
Gosh, this is embarrassing.
Hey, you're…
Stay still, will you?
-Put your hands like this.
-How did you enter this department?
So I can see all your fingers.
Like this?
No, cross them like this.
Yes. That's it.
Where should I look?
Just look at me.
-Seriously?
-Hey, what are you doing?
What?
Focus here.
You sure don't know
how to compliment others.
Put your arms down.
You should work out. Look at that.
Lose some weight.
But Sol.
Your eyes, nose, and mouth
are all so pretty.
Even the shape of your face.
And your eyebrows are pretty.
I'm so jealous.
What should we eat for lunch?
How did you hurt yourself again?
Did you tell me earlier?
Gosh, why are you always randomly
jumping from topic to topic?
No, I'm not.
To me, there's always a flow.
Make that posture again.
Oh, what was it?
Just like before. Hurry up.
How was the blind date yesterday?
It was fine.
I think I'll meet him again.
We have a similar taste in films.
So we decided to watch one together
next time.
That's great.
Hey, be careful.
-Just do it.
-So what happened to your forehead?
Oh, my forehead?
Yes, that's nice.
Like this?
Yes, just a little more.
-More?
-Yes.
Gosh.
-Like this?
-Yes, that's it.
Like this?
Yes.
Hurry up, then.
It's looking great.
Hey, Bit-na. This is my limit. Hurry up.
Just a few more shots.
What are you trying to make?
-Raise your legs more.
-I'm falling.
-Just a bit more.
-I'm falling, okay? I'm falling.
Just a bit… Hey!
Na-bi.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
Right. I'm going to draw the line.
Yes, I'm fine.
What's up? I'm busy right now.
I just came to see you.
I don't want to be a fool again.
You didn't read my messages.
Did you send me messages?
I didn't see them.
Are you busy?
Don't you have time to eat?
I guess I should eat.
But…
Then let's eat together.
Sure, whatever.
Let's go.
WHERE ARE YOU?
DO YOU WANT TO EAT LUNCH?
What are you doing? Are you sleeping?
I'm sure he does this to everyone.
He's so frivolous.
Where are you?
Home.
PARK JAE-EON
Hello?
What are you doing?
Nothing much.
Why did you call?
I just wanted
to hear your voice.
You're ridiculous.
You always say that.
You always say I'm funny, too.
I really mean it, though.
Jeez.
Don't be ridiculous.
I know everything.
Jae-eon.
Thank you so much.
It's nothing.
Jae-eon.
Would you like to work with me?
Oh, thank you.
We need new part-timers
at our department office.
Just for this semester.
Well, I…
Come on. Just think about it.
We need two people.
Min-yeong's luring Na-bi in,
and I want to lure you.
I'll think about it.
Okay. Just a little more work. Thanks.
Right. I'll finish up here.
-I'll throw that away.
-Thanks.
Good luck.
Okay.
-I'm hungry.
-Me too.
Hey, Jae-eon! Did you have lunch?
We're going out to eat. Want to join us?
No, I have plans. Enjoy your lunch.
He always says he has plans.
Let's go.
Who is it?
Jae-eon?
What are you doing?
PARK JAE-EON
For the first time in my life,
I had a racy dream.
MISSED CALL
PARK JAE-EON
What?
Darn it. I'm late.
Darn it…
Darn it.
Why did it have to be Jae-eon?
And in my house?
Seriously…
-Hello, sir.
-Yes?
I'm Yu Na-bi from Sculpture.
-Oh, the morning class.
-Yes.
-You had a presentation to do.
Well, I…
I kind of overslept today.
Could I do the presentation
for this class instead?
Okay,
since you seemed to have rushed here.
You'll get some points off, though.
All right. Thank you.
Okay.
Darn it.
Where are you?
I'm sure Bit-na is taking this class.
He called me,
but he didn't read my messages?
Whatever.
Na-bi.
Do you take this class too?
Why have I never seen you?
Oh, well…
I usually take the morning class.
I'm only taking this today.
I overslept.
Are you with someone?
I asked Jae-eon to think about
taking the part-time job.
What about Na-bi? Is she in?
I don't know yet.
She said she probably can't do it, though.
Really?
Then I told Jae-eon something
I shouldn't have.
I'll just keep quiet for now.
Hello, it's Seong-yun.
Hey.
Mr. An.
I came for my package.
Oh, okay.
My goodness. Thank you.
Mr. An. I brought you a dessert.
Hey, you shouldn't have.
It's fine.
Take it.
-I appreciate it.
-Are you kidding me?
Is this the post office or what?
The pudding was expensive,
so I could only get one.
I'm really sorry.
Bye, then.
Gyeong-jun.
Receiving packages for the kids
is going too far, don't you think?
It's nothing difficult.
You know what it's like.
It's tough trying to receive packages
without your parents finding out.
It's a huge mess!
Should I tell our professor?
Hello.
Hey, Sol.
Have you still not decided on your school?
The professor always asks me that.
No, I haven't yet.
Our professor would obviously
want you to go to an elite university,
but you should choose the one
you really want to go to.
All right. I will. Thanks.
No problem.
-You can talk to me anytime.
-Okay.
Is this a counseling room now?
Did you order a package?
It could be the delivery guy.
-Take the call.
-For God's sake.
All right.
Hello?
Hello. This is Jung Ju-hyeok.
What? Who?
Oh, you asked me to call you.
We met at the cafe.
I'm so sorry.
I'm okay. Are you all right?
Oh, right. I'm sorry.
If you tell me your bank account
and price, I'll send you the money.
Well…
If you're free, could we meet up?
What? In person?
Hang on.
-Bye.
He's obviously trying to hit on her.
Stop being so nosy.
Gosh.
Romance is in the air now.
How adorable.
As you can see now,
sometimes a character looks directly
at the camera.
The audience watching the film
would feel like they've locked eyes
with the actor
-and be startled.
-Wake up.
We call this
the "Tension to Camera" method.
-The character points a gun
-What's wrong?
-at the camera
-Are you sick?
or throws a punch…
Why are bad hunches never wrong?
Then the camera shakes.
This is another example of that.
I'll get it.
-No, let me…
-No, I'm the one who dropped it.
I'll get it.
Director François Truffaut.
I'm sure you would've
heard his name before.
In the last scene
of the film The 400 Blows,
the boy escapes from the juvenile center
and runs toward the ocean.
I have rotten luck,
-and a zit pops up on my chin.
-And he looks directly…
-It's that day of the month.
-Back then, it was taboo for actors…
ARE YOU COMING?
CAN YOU GET ME A PAD ON YOUR WAY?
Come on, go easy on me.
All right.
Gosh, seriously!
Darn it.
My stomach still hurts.
-Drink that.
-Thank you.
I feel a little better now.
Hey!
Gosh, you're going backward.
Let's take a short break.
-Jae-eon! Aren't you going for a smoke?
-Go ahead first.
Do you want to come?
I have to prepare for my presentation.
Oh, you're presenting today?
I should really focus
and clap really loudly.
Go ahead.
What?
Well, your friends are leaving.
Go catch up with them.
Okay.
You sometimes suddenly act cold to me.
I didn't…
Let's go.
What a relief.
Gosh, what is this?
I got totally fooled by this.
You sometimes
suddenly act cold to me.
Gosh, it's really bothering me.
Hello, I'm Sculpture major, Yu Na-bi.
Well…
The film I'm presenting today
is known
as the first science fiction film…
Code red alert.
It's for real this time.
It's…
A Trip to the Moon.
Director Georges Méliès
was also a magician.
"Everyone, having your period
-is nothing to be ashamed of."
-He was praised for his filming methods.
-Yes. That's right.
-Most of all…
At the time, films were not much different
from theater stages.
The director made a unique mise-en-scène
that was different
from reality or theater stages
by applying perspective,
space, distortion--
Wait.
You're talking too fast.
Slow down and speak clearly.
Okay. Well…
But periods are…
disasters.
Hello, I'm Fashion Design major,
Kim Yeong-min.
Disaster victims must evacuate
-to a safe zone.
-It is about Nosferatu.
This film is actually an adaptation
of the novel Dracula by Bram Stoker.
He changed the character's names
and some details
to avoid copyright issues
when he made the film.
Yu Na-bi!
Did I do something…
What are you doing?
You said you have a night class.
You'll get cold later.
Should I take it back?
But still, it could get on your--
It's fine.
I feel like crying.
Why did it have to be Jae-eon?
Will you tell…
other people?
Is that what you think of me?
Then if you saw me
suddenly getting a boner during class,
would you tell the others?
That's different, though.
It's not the same,
but would you?
Of course not.
Really?
Of course.
Then I won't, either.
Would someone like him
really be considered frivolous?
THANK YOU FOR TODAY.
I WILL GET YOUR CLOTHES…
Did you get home okay?
Do people act like this
to keep someone on the hook?
You read my message right away.
What are you doing?
LAUNDROMAT
We're going to play basketball
and go out for drinks.
You should join us.
Next time. I have plans.
But weren't you wearing a shirt over that?
Where did you put it?
I lent it to my friend.
Friend?
Who was that pretty girl a while ago?
Are you two close?
Did we seem close?
I'm buying art supplies.
What are you doing now?
You said you're just friends.
Gosh. We are just friends.
We did get a bit close, though.
Why didn't you reply to my messages?
Don't change the subject.
Is there something going on?
It's not like that.
I'm just…
not pushing away someone
who's being nice to me.
You're really getting your hopes up.
So you're saying he's treating you
like someone special.
Well…
Maybe.
From what I've seen so far,
the things that made you feel special
might be meaningless to him.
I told you, he's nice to everyone
without any exception.
I don't know.
Maybe.
She has to realize it herself.
Don't blame me later for not warning you!
Are you free tomorrow?
-Don't you have a gathering?
-Jae-eon told you?
I guess you two did grow close.
Did you hear who's coming?
No.
You should come.
All persons of interest are coming.
"Persons of interest?"
It's going to be fun.
And shouldn't you check for yourself?
What?
Whether you're really special
to Jae-eon or not.
Thank you!
"Navi bobo"?
NAVI_BOBO: I LIKE YOUR NEW HAIR
2,432 FOLLOWERS
All of them are girls.
I want my heart to keep fluttering,
but I keep feeling anxious.
What do I want from Jae-eon?
Right.
I should just check for myself
and forget about him.
Bit-na, I'll join you tomorrow.
Hey, isn't Sol coming today?
She's close to you.
Not really.
She's only close to Ji-wan.
And our department ace would never
eat at the same table as us.
You have lunch with her often.
You're so dramatic.
Don't you know what a metaphor is?
What are you, a kid?
Can't you stay still?
He's always been like that.
You're excited thinking
about Sol, aren't you?
Do you have a crush on her?
She's so quick-witted.
Help me out, then.
Take charge of your own love life.
Yun Sol?
She's pretty.
She's also sassy and extremely skilled.
She's totally my style.
-But does she even like guys?
-What are you on about?
I mean,
I've never seen her hang out with guys.
Have you?
I've never seen Gyu-hyun
hang out with girls, either.
Then is he…
Are you?
-What about me? Am I a guy, then?
-Yes.
-You jerk.
-Wait.
-Let me give you a punch.
-Hey, stop.
What are you guys up to?
You haven't quit yet?
I knew it.
It was just a temporary project, anyway.
Ji-wan.
What's he up to now?
Can I ask you a favor?
A favor? What is it?
We're going out for drinks today.
Come join us with Sol.
Sol? Why?
Please bring her over.
Let him get rejected so he can shut up.
You have a crush on her?
I think I do.
Help me out, okay?
Come on. Help me get close to her.
Okay?
He's serious.
Well, okay. I'll ask her.
Nice.
But she might refuse.
She doesn't enjoy drinking.
I know. I'm pretty sure she won't come.
Okay.
-Let's go.
-You're coming? Really?
Why?
What do you mean? Didn't you want to go?
What?
Oh, right. You're right.
Okay, let's go together.
What's that reaction?
By the way,
what do you think of Yu Se-hun?
What about him?
You're not that interested in him, right?
He seemed pretty funny.
He's funny?
Yes.
Why?
I don't want this.
Se-hun, you look really stylish today.
Hey. This jacket's worth 20 million won.
-Really?
-He's loaded!
-Then buy us a big bowl of stew!
-He could just buy us this place!
-Se-hun!
-Keep it coming!
Hey, Na-bi's here.
-Hi, Na-bi.
-Any empty…
-Let's see.
Go over there.
Na-bi. Come sit over here. Come here.
Go sit there.
Come on.
It's been a while.
You're attending gatherings
since you broke up?
You're finally free of that old dude?
She's free!
What's with you?
Did you break up?
You broke up?
Why are you asking that?
Everyone's here except Jae-eon, right?
He's not reading my message.
He always replies late.
Right. He's always
holding his phone, though.
He just reads the alerts and ignores them.
No, he's not that type.
-Where should he sit?
-We can get a chair here.
"Not the dating type"?
It's like he's dating all the girls.
Jae-eon's really popular.
We should add more chairs.
Sol and Ji-wan are coming, too.
Really?
No way. Sol is coming?
Didn't you hear
that Ji-wan's coming as well?
Hang on. Let me get a chair.
It's nice that you never change.
-Why are you putting that next to you?
-Because I want to.
Aren't you taking it off?
What?
Your jacket. Why are you so startled?
What were you thinking?
You take it off too.
I wasn't thinking of anything.
Take off your jackets, guys. It's hot.
-You take it off.
-Oh, that's my water.
Oh, sorry.
-Is there a new cup anywhere?
-It's fine.
You're my senior, right?
It's nice to meet you.
I'm a freshman. Kim Eun-han.
We ordered some food already.
Have you tried the seafood stew here?
No, I never tried it.
Do you like seafood?
Yes, I do.
That's a relief.
-Hey, go check the order.
-We're selling food at the flea market.
You should come visit our booth.
We killed time with useless conversations,
-but the food wasn't served.
-Please.
Yes, of course.
-When things started to get boring…
-Really?
Yes.
-Did he reply?
-No.
…the main character appeared.
It's Jae-eon!
-Hey!
-Why are you so late?
-Jae-eon!
-Hey! What took you so long?
-Look at the time!
-Don't you see what time it is?
-Your pretty face won't cut it.
-Sit over here.
The sexual tension
rises dramatically at his arrival.
-He should drink for being late!
-Why are you late?
Sorry, there was a bit of traffic.
Na-bi, you're here too.
Yes.
He's here, so let's all drink!
-Let's drink!
-Here we go!
-Let's clink and drink!
-Cheers.
Air clink.
This tastes so sweet.
I'm going to drink so much today.
This is spicier than I thought.
-Just eat.
-Here, have some water.
-Where are they going?
-Hey, stop it.
Drink some water.
Thanks.
He's so popular.
It's pretty spicy.
It's so surprising that she came here.
I asked her to join us.
It was that easy?
Gosh, stop it.
-Is it spicy?
-Is it?
Look at you, you're all red.
Aren't girls better at eating spicy food
than guys?
Is that so?
I read somewhere
that women naturally endure pain better
since they have to give birth.
And you know, when it's their first time--
What did you say?
Damn it, I'm losing my appetite.
I should report you.
Stop the nonsense.
Hey.
Why do you always cross the line?
What?
Tasting spiciness
is feeling a sense of pain.
Stop treating me like a pervert.
Just wipe your dirty mouth.
Wow. Sol, you're so cool.
Stop it.
Hey!
Here. Have a drink.
You ruined the vibe!
-What have you done?
-Stop talking!
You want to drink something?
-Exactly!
-Do something.
-Yes!
-Let's bring back the vibe.
-Let's go!
-Should we keep it going?
-Keep it going!
-This one.
-Zero, zero, seven!
Lime? Is this good?
I don't know. I think you'll like it.
Me?
You said so at the club.
Here.
Is this lime?
I like lime.
You remember that?
It's strange.
Don't people try smoking out of curiosity?
You tried mine before.
What? When?
You always refused when I offered.
I was just curious.
Forget it. I feel so hurt now.
Na-bi,
you look like you're in a good mood.
What do you mean?
You looked a bit upset
so I thought you weren't feeling well.
I was uncomfortable with too many people.
Right. You're shy with strangers.
Even with me?
You weren't like that before.
You smiled all the time.
I thought you were angry.
Gosh. Why are you showing
so much interest in her today?
What?
Is there something going on
between you two?
It seems like it.
I did think it was strange.
It's…
It's nothing like that.
Don't lie to me.
I can tell by your expressions.
Aren't I right?
What's with you? There's nothing going on.
Right?
Yes.
Right.
No?
That's strange.
Didn't you keep looking at him, Na-bi?
You kept looking at him.
I'm going to the bathroom.
I'll come with you. Damn it.
He doesn't know how you feel,
so he said that in case
it would get awkward.
Forget it.
If that was really the case,
he would've just changed the subject
or said something vague.
Right?
I'm sure he didn't say that just for me.
He just drew the line.
Hey, don't say it like that.
-You're overreacting.
-Didn't you know this would happen?
What's with the pep talk?
Well, I thought maybe
I was being too harsh.
It's not like I can read his mind.
Plus, he kept looking at you.
No way. He was busy chatting with Yun-ji.
No! He kept glancing at you
whenever you spoke.
And most importantly,
he doesn't do stuff like this.
Bit-na, this is just a 3,000 won drink.
Anyway, this is different.
Honestly, I wasn't sure
when I heard your side of the story,
but seeing it in person,
I can sense something.
Are you going to stay?
No. I want to go home.
Let's go to your place with Jae-eon.
Are you crazy? Why would I do that?
I'll come with you!
We can't waste an opportunity like this.
But still…
Forget it. I'm going to go home.
I don't feel like it.
Let's at least ask him.
Goodness.
There's really nothing going on
between you two?
I know. You said you don't date.
It seems like she's hitting on you
without knowing that.
She was acting like she's all that
because she's a bit pretty.
Serves her right.
Min-sang, don't say stuff about people
you can't say to their faces.
-What?
-You're badmouthing her
just because you can't have her.
It's pathetic.
What did you just say?
I'm telling you to watch your mouth.
You asshole. You just said there was
nothing going on between you and Na-bi.
-Hey, where were you?
-Pajeon must be out.
Come on, or I'll eat everything.
Yes, I'm coming.
Let's go eat.
Jae-eon seems totally unbothered.
Don't worry about him.
-What?
-He goes around talking about me, too.
Like what?
That you don't date?
Do people have to date?
Not necessarily.
Right?
I have a friend who doesn't date either.
But unlike you, he's a bit cold.
Especially to girls.
Why can't two people
just be close?
Can't they look at each other
or stand near each other?
Do they have to pretend not to notice
if there's something in their hair?
That's not what I mean.
Right?
It's nice to get along well.
"Is that really all?"
But I didn't ask him that.
Who wants to go for another round?
Me!
-Just go home.
-You go!
-Let's go.
Are you going?
-Well…
-Jae-eon, are you going?
Well, if everyone's going…
I have other plans.
What? Is it important?
It's just a friend.
Today seems like a perfect day
to get rid of my feelings.
What is it?
I'm wondering if I should
see my friend or join the others.
What about you?
But I…
Well…
Bit-na and I are going to drink
at my house.
Do you want to come?
I give up that chance
and decide to become a fun girl.
National!
-Singing Contest!
All right. "Love."
-"Love"?
-"Love."
I've fallen in love
-I've fallen in love
Love, love, love, my love
You don't know?
Come here, my love
-You don't know this?
-Keep going. What's wrong?
We won't accept that. Drink up.
-Drink.
-But I…
-Drink up.
-I'll drink it for you.
What was that?
All right.
Keep it going
-Keep it going!
Let's do the Alphabet Game.
-"L"!
-"L"?
Lion.
Leaf.
I got it. Lie!
Love.
Oh, me! Left!
Life.
Long.
Gosh, what do I do?
-Only the two of you left.
-Wait. Let me think.
What do I do?
I know! Lust!
-Oh, come on!
-What? It starts with "L"!
Yes, you're right. Fine.
Gosh.
All right. Then Na-bi is the loser!
You have to drink the whole glass
-in one go. Here.
-In one go.
Who's going to drink?
-Yu Na-bi is going to drink!
The two people
the bottle points to have to kiss!
-One, two, three!
-Spin, spin, spin!
-Oh, my gosh!
-What the hell?
-Kiss!
All right. Be quiet.
-What? You're going to do it?
-Are you?
Okay, move over.
What? Really?
Let me do it properly.
Wait. I think I'm bleeding.
-Oh, sorry.
-I'm bleeding. But it's okay.
Your braces?
This is crazy!
No way!
-That's crazy!
Guys, be quiet.
The neighbors will complain.
Hey, keep it down.
What?
I told you to be quiet.
Sorry.
Yes?
Excuse me.
Don't you know how late it is?
Please be quiet.
You're being way too loud.
I'm sorry.
You have neighbors, you know.
I have some friends over, so…
We'll be careful.
We're taking an exam tomorrow.
Oh, really?
Then we'll silently pray for you
to get a good score.
Thank you.
We'll trust that you'll be quiet.
Bye, then.
-Bye.
-I'm sorry.
You were like a couple.
Be quiet.
-Stop playing drinking games.
-We can't stop!
-Come on.
-Come on!
Let's not stop!
Let's spin it one more time!
Spin it!
-Spin, spin, spin!
Just a little more.
-It's me!
-Yes!
-What are you talking about?
It's me.
-Sol. Come here.
-What?
-You're going to do it?
-She must be drunk.
You're really going to kiss her?
-Hey.
-Sit back down.
Sit down.
Come on!
Gosh.
-Where are you going?
I'm going out for a smoke.
-What about me?
-She left because of you.
Be quiet.
JUNG JU-HYEOK
This is Sol's.
Hey, Sol!
Hey.
Jung Ju-hyeok? Who is this guy?
Jung Ju-hyeok?
Yes.
That's not important right now. Spin!
Spin!
-Spin, spin, spin!
Did you plan this in advance?
What does this make us look like?
You kissed by choice, that's all.
Forget it. Let's go for a smoke.
Let's go.
I'm exhausted.
My legs hurt.
-My gosh.
-Gosh, my legs.
Hey, I'm wearing your shoes!
Oh, my back.
My shoes.
-I'll be back later, Na-bi.
-Okay.
Sol!
You're smoking too?
Yes. But who's Jung Ju-hyeok?
He just called you.
What? Oh.
Just someone I know.
Someone you know?
I thought I knew everyone you knew.
You don't.
It's cold outside.
Thank you.
What were you doing?
Just taking a walk.
Your place is so nice.
My aunt used to live here.
Why did you make things
so hard for yourself?
I know, right?
Hey…
Sol is so beautiful up close.
She's a goddess.
We get it, so just tell her!
Please stop torturing us!
Ji-wan.
What type of guy does Sol like?
He's driving me crazy.
I don't want to tell you.
You don't want to tell me?
What?
Why? You said you'd help me.
She doesn't seem to know, either.
There's no way.
Who else would know, then?
Sol…
Yes?
She hates boring guys like you.
Come on. I'm nothing but fun.
If you took the fun part out of me,
I'd be a zombie. Right?
Don't smoke so much.
But where's Jae-eon?
I don't know. Is he inside?
You're totally ignoring me.
He must be on his phone.
He's always calling someone.
Come to think of it,
I haven't seen Yun-ji, either.
Did those two leave together?
Call them. Come on.
Let's go find them.
Where did he go?
What?
What? It's nothing.
Can I borrow some sweatpants?
Sure. I'll get them.
Thank you. Let me use the bathroom.
That tickles!
Stop it.
It tickles!
Gosh, that startled me.
This is so embarrassing.
Listen.
I know this is shameless of me,
but can you keep this a secret?
Please don't tell the others.
All right. I won't.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
All right. I get it.
-Now go on.
-I won't let go of this hand.
Okay, don't. Just go.
-Bye, then.
-Bye.
I'm sorry.
-When did you…
-I'll tell you later.
Let's go.
I must've been crazy.
How could I have thought he was Jae-eon?
What? That's it?
Just tell me if you're not up for it.
It's not like that.
Go inside first. I need to make a call.
It was just a game.
I guess she wanted to try it.
You don't need to explain.
What about you?
Didn't you want to try it?
Why would I?
Not at all.
I wanted to do it with you.
What?
I thought…
you felt the same way.
I won't do it if you don't want to.
Sorry.
Just like that,
the gates of hell have opened.
NEVERTHELESS,
Subtitle translation by: Ju-young Park
Jae-eon still isn't contacting me.
How are your butterflies doing?
I'm going to set them free.
They're supposed to be free,
but they're locked up because of me.
I hope it's just love.
Not childish jealousy.
You know that he only hurts other people.
Were you two close?
Yes. We're close.
Closer than you and me, anyway.
That kind of presence
only comes naturally.
Some people are gifted like that.
Then what kind of person am I to him?
Do you want to meet right now?
Why are you doing this to me?
I've been attracted to you
from the beginning.
What is this emotion?
Could it be…
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs