[English subtitles are available]
[This beautiful place]
[is Donghu University.]
[My name is Zeng Li, I'm 26 years old.]
[Donghu University Library]
[I learn and work here]
[A Short History of Nearly Everything]
[Murphy's Law]
[and eight years
went by without noticing.]
[Gone with the Wind]
[Many people don't understand]
[why I chose to stay in school]
[as a librarian.]
[It's probably because]
[I like simple, and interesting things.]
[Each book I read]
[is like]
[having a chat with an interesting soul.]
[They will bring me to explore]
[Geek Physics]
[those unknown and mysterious realms]
[that I'd never get to experience myself.]
[Sometimes, I also make mistakes.]
[But as long as I surrounded by books,]
[I'd feel secure.]
[And the small island, away from
hustle and bustle of the city]
[where the university is situated,]
[became my dwelling place.]
[CAROL'S]
[This cafe next to the university,]
[me and my friends pooled our money]
[to take over
the ownership two years ago.]
[Each object in the cafe]
[was sourced and bought by us with care.]
[Us who are insignificant,]
[keeping each other company
in this big, big world.]
[Looking forward to next second,]
[CAROL'S]
[who is the someone we're going to meet.]
[Sweet Teeth]
[Episode 1]
Am I seeing things?
[Popularity Ranking]
The hottest male ranking
of Donghu University,
the top 2 aren't students.
[Mu Cheng He]
[Ai Jing Chu]
Instead, both are male teachers.
Last year, this Lecturer Mu
from Department of Physics was No. 1.
And then there's Dr. Ai from
medical school this year.
[TOP: 2 Genius Doctor: Ai Jing Chu]
Ai Jing Chu.
Is he a newcomer?
He's way more good-looking
than these generation Z male students.
Look.
He's an attending physician
at such a young age.
[TOP: 2 Genius Doctor: Ai Jing Chu]
Ai Jing Chu?
[Genius Doctor: Ai Jing Chu]
Mu Cheng He, Ai Jing Chu.
[Popularity Ranking Forum]
Their names combined,
[Their surnames sound like the
lingerie brand when put together]
[Mr. Mu and Mr. Ai are both so
talented, I don't know who to vote.]
would be Aimer, the lingerie brand.
It's...
Sometimes, I couldn't help
but admire myself.
Ai Jing Chu, Mu Cheng He.
The two surnames put together, really.
Now, it feels like they...
You know.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
Oh, no.
What we said just now,
did he hear it?
Dr. Ai
is so handsome
and so cool.
I'm going to vote for him.
[CAROL'S]
I went to look for him
at the hospital earlier.
-He said the same thing.
-Please enjoy.
Let's calm down for now.
When a woman says to calm down,
she means "keep on
coaxing me, don't stop."
If a man says to calm down,
it means
he wants to break up with you.
[Ma Yi Yi,]
[self-proclaimed best livestreamer
of Donghu University,]
[an expert at relationships.]
[Any topic which is related to men,]
[she would have endless
theories to talk about.]
All I can think about is him.
Sister Ma, I'm so sad.
Whenever I look for him,
he'd tell me he's busy.
Hi, I'd like to pay the bill.
One moment.
Sorry.
I'll do it.
This type of men.
You should just break up with him.
I'm sorry. That'll be RMB50.
Sister Zeng,
I'd like to take the day off.
OK.
Thanks, boss lady.
[CAROL'S]
Dou Dou.
What's wrong?
Sorry, Sister Wu.
What happened?
[Wu Yin, doctor at emergency department.]
[An experienced gamer.]
[She seems distant,]
[but she's in fact a childish tomboy.]
Wu Yin,
where were you?
I don't want to talk about it.
Last night,
I stayed up to work overnight.
What's going on?
The sofa.
Wu Yin, any interesting happenings?
I'm all ears.
Tell me, quickly.
Ma Yi Yi, you're always
so excited for no reason.
Move. I need to place my legs.
What exactly happened?
I was on night shift last night.
Around 11pm,
a group of men came
who got into fight after drinking.
They were bleeding all over.
One of them,
a man in his 30s,
when I was about to stitch his wounds,
he grabbed my wrist
and called for his mother while crying.
That's work for you.
I'm too sleepy.
I need to make up for lost sleep.
Good night.
Dr. Wu,
this cafe of ours,
are you not an investor
or something?
So, for the dividends this month,
me and Zeng Li won't share with you.
Good idea.
Get up.
Dividends?
As if it's so profitable.
I saw Dou Dou just now.
What happened to her?
She just broke up.
So,
we gave her a day off
so she can have a good rest.
Was Dou Dou dating?
Dr. Wu,
you should care about your employee more.
She's your junior after all.
She's been smiling at her phone lately.
Didn't you realize?
I remember now.
She's in love with a senior, right?
Last month, she was
asking me about him.
They got together so quickly?
The point is,
they broke up so quickly, OK?
That's it.
I just heard Dou Dou's boyfriend
is a dentist,
but I don't know who he is.
What's his name?
It's Ai Jing Chu.
Zeng Li,
what is it this time?
Are you all right?
[I almost choked to death.]
[Why am I always drinking water]
[when someone mentions his name?]
[So, Dou Dou's boyfriend]
[is him.]
No, wait.
What did Ai Jing Chu do to Dou Dou?
He's been dating Dou Dou
and flirting with other women.
Is this Ai Jing Chu so handsome?
When we were in university,
a lot of girls, when they see him,
they'd go crazy over him.
But I don't feel anything when I see him.
So, who do you have feelings for?
Mother, you're here.
Why?
It sounds
as if you don't welcome me here.
That's not true.
I'm beyond happy.
Mother, why are you dressed this way?
What do you think?
Isn't it good enough
for "Stage 33 Boom"?
Great.
It's my favorite pork knuckle soup.
Since
it's your favorite pork knuckle soup.
I'd like to ask,
why didn't you touch
pork knuckle soup from last week?
I was too busy last week.
As you know,
I'm an enterpreneur.
I'm sorry.
All these collagen.
Look, it's all wasted now.
Don't you think it's such a waste?
If you don't take nourishment,
your cheeks are going
to lose its plumpness.
It's going to be even harder
for you to find a boyfriend.
Got it.
I promise
I'll drink the pork knuckle soup you make
and become as beautiful as a flower.
Anyway,
you aren't that young anymore,
yet you've never been in a relationship.
I suspect when Yue Lao
unites predestined couples
with a silken cord,
he missed out your name.
It's very likely.
So, you should stop
introducing men to me.
It's all in vain anyway.
It's exactly because of your
indifferent attitude,
that you can't find a partner.
This year, you're 20...
26 years old.
Do you have any
crisis awareness at all?
In two years' time,
how are you going to
compete with those females
in their early 20s?
Mother,
you're too inconfident
towards your own daughter.
Look at you.
Second marriage at the age of 41,
and third marriage at the age of 45.
Look at me.
What's all this?
There's no rush.
If you had a clear target in mind like me,
and knows what you want,
I won't have to worry about you.
Mother, why are you
looking at me that way?
You're no longer a youth,
but you're quite pretty still.
Why couldn't you get a boyfriend?
You have the figure
and looks.
What could be the problem?
I know.
Your teeth aren't aligned.
It affects your overall appearance.
Especially when you smile.
You aren't
bringing me to
an orthodontist, right?
My daughter knows me best.
Come on, hurry.
I'm not going.
I'm too old to wear braces.
It's because you're not young anymore,
that's why it can't be delayed.
Solve the issue when you realize it.
Maybe when your teeth become aligned,
you'll find a boyfriend.
I don't want to.
Let's go.
No, no.
[Dou Dou?]
[Ai Jing Chu, it really is you.]
Since you aren't suitable for each other,
you should stop contacting him.
Let's calm down first.
But I think we're suitable for each other.
[What is this guy doing?]
I still have other patients.
Go home first.
[Dou Dou is crying so sadly.]
[How ruthless.]
[Is he even a man?]
[It's good that she broke up with him,]
[or else she'd be bullied again.]
What are you staring at?
Do you know them?
No.
Why are you hiding if you don't know them?
Come on.
Dou Dou's already gone home.
Thank you for helping me, Dr. Ai.
I don't want to interfere
with your personal issues,
but you and Dou Dou
are my students.
Had Dou Dou
not asked me for help relentlessly,
I wouldn't meet her in your place.
You ought to clear things up with her.
OK.
I'll talk to her later.
What time?
After going off work today,
I'll make sure to do it.
Your molars,
4 teeth in total,
have to be extracted.
My teeth need to be
extracted to wear braces?
I'm not doing it anymore. I...
Your dentition is crowded.
In between teeth,
there's not much space to start with.
If you want to align your teeth,
you have to make space for it.
Unnderstand?
This needs to be exracted,
OK?
Listen to the doctor.
OK.
So, can we do the tooth extraction today?
Today?
No, it's not possible.
My schedule is full.
Tomorrow.
Sure.
Let's visit again tomorrow.
What?
Mother, aren't you
going back to Henggang today?
No, today I have to
work overtime in the library.
I can't keep you company today.
It's fine.
You've never had a tooth extraction
ever since you were a kid.
It's a major surgery.
How can I let you come alone?
I'm worried.
It's just tooth extraction.
What's there to worry about?
That you won't even come.
This is good.
[Share blessings or withdraw from group]
Sisters,
[Zeng Li: Sisters,]
who would've thought
as someone who's going
to turn 30 in few years,
I'm going to become
a braces and glasses girl?
Zeng Li,
in the near future, will
your mother ask you
to go for LASIK.
Rhinoplasty,
and double eyelid surgery?
[Share blessings or withdraw from group]
[Wu Ying: What do you think about this?]
What about this type?
It's too ugly.
No way.
Do you think my teeth need to be aligned?
I'm on Aunt's side this time.
I didn't think it's an issue,
but after Aunt pointed it out,
all of a sudden, I also
find it problematic.
Especially when you smile,
it becomes even more obvious.
Oh, right.
I visited the dental center today
and ran into Dou Dou and Ai Jing Chu.
[Share blessings or withdraw from group]
[Zeng Li: I met Dou Dou and Ai Jing Chu. They seemed to have broken up.]
[That Ai Jing Chu]
[seemed to have broken up with Dou Dou.]
Sorry, Granny.
My legs hurt.
You bumped into me.
Granny, your legs hurt?
How can my legs not hurt?
I didn't bump into you.
I'll help you to call an ambulance.
I'll help you get a doctor.
You bumped into me.
Where are you going?
Are you going to run away?
I'm not...
You bumped into me,
and now you refuse to admit it?
I didn't bump into you.
What are you talking about?
If you didn't bump into me,
why are my legs hurting?
Granny,
it's year 2020.
Aren't scams a little outdated?
So, next, are you going to tell me
to give you money
so you could go to the hospital?
That's right.
You just have to give me some money.
RMB300 or RMB500,
the more, the better.
I...
I'm just a worker.
I have no money either.
I just want money.
You can't leave.
Stop pulling.
My pants are falling off.
You just have to give me money.
My legs hurt.
All right.
What about this?
Hospital, or police station.
Choose one.
Why did this have to happen to me?
Granny, did you make a mistake?
Didn't your legs hurt just now?
Why is your heart aching now?
Fine.
I'll give you, OK?
Granny, stop pretending.
The flloor is cold.
Get up, all right?
Granny!
Mother, look at that granny.
She seems to be feeling unwell.
Granny!
Granny, what happened to you?
Wake up!
Help, anyone!
Someone fainted!
Help.
Someone fainted.
CPR,
how do you do it?
Zeng Li,
calm down.
Zeng Li, you can do it.
Granny, don't scare me. Granny!
Granny!
Someone help me.
Did you call the ambulance?
Yes.
It's him again.
Carotid artery fluctuations, none.
Granny!
-Ma'am.
-Granny.
How do you feel?
She's having a hypertension episode
which causes sudden
cardiopulmonary arrest.
I just fed her a nifedipine.
Are you her family member?
I happened to pass by.
I'm a dentist at the dental center
of Donghu University-affiliated hospital.
I think I'll go with you
in case something happens.
Sure.
Thank you.
Good work.
You handled it quite well.
But I suggest you to learn
CPR technique.
[So long-winded.]
[Forget it.]
[Since he saved someone's life,]
[I'll let him off.]
[Wait, what is he doing?]
[Is it an insect?]
[That scared me. So it wasn't an insect.]
Granny.
She bumped into me.
I did not. She's lying.
It was her.
She was arguing with
the old lady just now.
No.
She was trying to scam me.
I didn't.
[It's a scam.]
[You could tell, right?]
No, I...
[Why aren't you saying anything?]
[Are you dumb?]
[Is Mercury in retrograde today?]
[Mother made me wear braces
and I even got scammed.]
[Don't tell me, later,]
[he expects me to pay the hospital bill?]
[No. 178, He Xiao Xuan,]
[please go to Emergency Room No. 2.]
What's this?
She fell onto the ground because of you.
You even argued with her.
This is the least you can do.
How many times did I tell you?
I didn't bump into her.
She was trying to scam me. She...
It's already come to this.
Do you have any conscience?
What do you mean I don't have conscience?
You're talking about my
conscience? You jerk...
What did you say?
Stop arguing.
It's a mess as it is.
Yin, how is she?
She's fine now.
Dr. Ai,
luckily the CPR
was performed in time.
She's asleep now.
She just has to stay another
24 hours for observation
and get some IV injection
before she is discharged.
Did you contact her family?
Yes,
but her family members
didn't say they'll come.
Unfilial offsprings.
When the old lady has come to,
you should apologize to her.
I...
Zeng Li!
It really is a misunderstanding.
That old lady
is a regular at emergency department.
She always says someone bumped into her,
but once she did check-up,
the result turns out fine.
And yet she asks them to pay her
psychological injury compensation.
Otherwise, she won't let them leave.
Some people think it's troublesome,
so they'll give her the money.
But somehow,
she had a hypertension episode today.
Probably it's her family members
who mistreated her.
She's quite pitiful.
Give me a copy of the invoice.
I'll sort out the payment.
OK.
Give me your hand.
I already footed the bill.
However, to apologize is impossible.
I don't want to see you ever again.
You're looking at me right now.
You...
Yin, I'll get going.
Watch where you're going.
Watch out for people!
Are you OK?
So stubborn.
She's really walking with her eyes closed.
I'll go in first.
[How far did I walk?]
[I need to make a turn soon, right?]
[I don't want to walk into walls,]
[or he'll laugh at me.]
I've never seen
such a conceited person before.
Dou Dou must be blind.
What an unlucky day.
Is Mercury in retrogade?
Wait!
Wait...
Wait up!
One more passsenger!
Wait!
Let me board the bus.
I haven't boarded yet.
There's no seat.
I'll sit here for awhile as I wait.
I'll stand.
You're kidding me.
It's raining.
Why is it raining all of a sudden?
I knew I should bring an umbrella.
Don't... Don't push.
Aunt.
Aunt,
you dropped your concession card.
Aunt.
You were talking to me?
[Middle-aged people nowadays]
[prefer]
[to be called Sister.]
Sister.
[What an unlucky day.]
[Can't something good
happen for a change?]
Why is her boyfriend
so handsome?
I know.
I'm so envious.
About what happened earlier,
I was wrong about you.
I'm sorry.
Since you purposely made a trip here
to apologize to me,
I'll forgive you.
You overthink.
I drove past just now
and saw you.
Could it be you're thinking
to give me a lift home?
You don't have to.
You overthink. My house is
in a different direction.
Here, you can have the umbrella.
What kind of person is he?
He acts so strangely.
Wait a second.
I didn't tell him
where my house is.
How does he know it's
in a different direction?
You're too insincere.
Mercury in retrogade.
[Outpatient building]
[When someones]
[is having the worst luck,]
[good things will finally happen, right?]
Director Wang is on leave?
Yes.
[Great!]
[Thank God.]
Why don't you switch to
consultation with another doctor?
I'll switch...
Mother, let's go for now.
We can consult Director Wang
when he comes back to office.
I'm afraid Director Wang
won't be working for some time.
I heard he's hospitalized due
to coronary artery disease.
That's too bad.
Mother, let's go.
Any other doctors we can consult?
You still won't give up.
Resident doctor, Xu Heng Heng.
Resident doctor?
[Hospital Appointment Management
System, Ai Jing Chu]
Dr. Ai
freed up a slot for consultation.
[Dr. Ai?]
[Don't tell me it's Ai Jing Chu.]
Attending physician, Ai Jing Chu.
Attending physician it is.
-OK, sure.
-No, no.
We'll have a queue number
for the resident doctor.
Why resident doctor?
This... It's a long story.
Although Dr. Ai's title
is attending physician,
he's really skilled.
It isn't easy to get his queue number.
You hear that?
You're in luck today.
I'll register if they don't want to.
I'm here to consult Dr. Ai
for a dental check-up.
Mother!
No, you...
After you.
No, no.
We came here first.
Mother.
What's gotten into you?
That Dr. Ai
is bad.
What's wrong with him?
Didn't you hear her just now?
It's not easy to consult Dr. Ai.
Please,
we'll consult resident doctor.
Thank you.
This girl.
You refuse to be treated
by an attending physician,
and insists to have the resident doctor.
I don't know
what you're thinking.
Mother.
Since we already registered.
[Is this a dental visit or interrogation?]
[Love and peace.]
All right, first, let's disinfect.
[It's going to begin already?]
[Disinfection won't hurt, right?]
OK, open your mouth.
Wider.
All right.
We'll inject the anesthetics now.
[Such a huge syringe needle.]
It might hurt a little.
After the anesthetics later,
you won't feel a thing
during tooth extraction.
[Help!]
All right.
OK, open your mouth.
The anesthetics might not have
fully worked yet.
Endure it.
[It's not working.]
[Can't you wait a while longer?]
We'll begin tooth extraction now.
[With such huge pliers?]
OK.
Open your mouth.
[Don't you dare come over.]
What's wrong?
Didn't you say it won't hurt?
But I gave you anesthetic just now.
It hurts.
Don't panic.
Wait here.
I'll be right back.
I don't want to get my teeth extracted!
My tooth.
[Is it because I didn't
cry hard enough?]
[A different dentist. It's
going to hurt all over again.]
[Who's there? Don't come over.]
[Why does he seem so familiar?]
It hurts a lot.
Open your mouth. Let me have a look.
Wider.
[It really is him.]
[I ended up in his hands anyway.]
It should be
she is resistant to lidocaine.
Bring me an articaine.
Sure, Dr. Ai.
Don't cry.
It'll be over before you know it.
Very soon.
[Seems like he]
[has quite a nice voice.]
Come on, open your mouth.
[Why is the world so small?]
[What is this,
endless encounters with him?]
[Zeng Li,]
[why are you tied to this man?]
[How unlucky.]
Dr. Ai.
It'll hurt a little.
Just endure for a while.
[Feels like my teeth are going numb.]
[I can't feel a thing.]
How does it feel? Does it still hurt?
Should be fine now.
Dr. Ai,
they want to come in to learn.
Come in.
[What's this?]
[Watching a panda at the zoo?]
The plan given by Director Wang
is upper and lower molars,
four teeth in total to be removed.
[I forgot I was going to
have four teeth extracted.]
But I think we only need to
remove the two above,
because her lower dentition
isn't too cramped.
So, we're keeping those for now.
We'll decide again
after a consultation with Director Wang.
Usually, extraction of such
bigger-sized teeth
which are attached to the gums,
we need to make a small cut in the gum
and remove it,
followed by stitches.
[Cut open the gums?]
However,
though her teeth are bigger in size,
there isn't
pathological connection.
So, it isn't necessary in this case.
[Ai Jing Chu,]
[don't stop your sentences midway.]
Let's begin.
Open your mouth.
[It's happening. He's going to remove it.]
[Did he get the wrong tooth?]
[Is this the right tooth?]
[My tooth,]
[it's... It's moving. It's moving!]
All done.
[It's done?]
[Why didn't I feel anything?]
I'll leave the rest to you.
Thank you, Dr. Ai.
Good work.
Good work, Dr. Ai.
We'll get going.
[They're gone?]
Doctor,
how is my daughter?
Just now, I heard her
wailing pitifully.
She was resistant to anesthetics,
but she's fine now.
You can go in and check on her.
Bite on the cotton swab for an hour.
When the anesthetics effect is gone,
refrain from eating food for awhile.
It's done?
You look like a catfish now.
If it wasn't you
who insisted that I wear braces,
I won't have to go through this suffering.
Just now, when Dr. Ai
was extracting your teeth,
did it feel like
it's done before you realized?
So, it seems this Dr. Ai
is quite a skilled doctor.
What is the use of that?
He has a bad character.
Don't talk nonsense.
I'll go and pay the fee first.
Let me show you the way.
OK.
Dr. Ai.
This should be
our first meeting, right?
Why would you say I have a bad character?
Our first meeting?
Yesterday, because of you,
I spent so much money.
I remember now.
You're that person
who bumped into
the old lady, right?
Wait, can't you recognize people?
You misunderstood me yesterday
and even... You even made me...
Lie down.
Open your mouth.
It hurts.
I haven't even touched you.
I'll remember you this time.
[You'll remember me? Is this blackmail?]
What did you give me?
You even made markings on me?
You overthink. It's an
orthodontic separator
to move the teeth apart slowly.
This way,
it'll make wearing
braces easier in future.
[Outpatient medical records, Zeng Li]
Thanks for taking over my patient.
Zeng Li.
That's quite an interesting name.
So, I'm going to transfer
this koi for good luck to you.
You'll have good luck the entire year.
You're now
a resident doctor.
You can't just back away
before difficulties.
I made a mistake during tooth extraction.
Besides, orthodontics
isn't my strength,
and the cycle is so long.
I'm also worried the patient distrusts me.
The more I look,
the more you resemble one.
You're still laughing.
I'm in such pain here.
Zeng Li.
Zeng Li,
I have good news for you.
Your situation is unique,
being resistant to anesthetics.
Dr. Ai decided
to personally take over your treatment.
I'm the nurse
in charge to work with Dr. Ai.
My name is Zhou Wen. You can contact
me anytime if something happens.
Can I turn it down?
I think she trusts you
more than me.