(Episode 14)
Take your necklace off.
In Bum. In Bum!
In Bum!
Are you okay?
What happened?
Mom. Mom?
This is the same as that time.
I...
killed my son.
I killed him.
The unrested spirit
didn't choose to leave behind.
She's keeping him from leaving.
Ma'am.
It's time to let him go.
It's my fault.
The sun has been up for ages.
How can you get up this late
and still want to eat?
Hey, I'm trying to eat.
How dare you glare at me?
You're guilty as charged.
It's not like I don't want to get a job.
I'm frustrated too.
You need to go make money!
You'll realize how precious money is
once you start making it.
It's always money!
Fine. I'll go out and make money.
Gosh. As if.
Yes, go make some money.
Don't even think of coming home
until you make some!
Only if I didn't
let him go like that...
Why is he making a scene this early?
Chang Hwa wouldn't have died.
I didn't even...
let him eat his breakfast in peace.
I didn't know...
that would be the last time I see him.
I killed my own son.
No.
Your son...
didn't die because of you.
No.
Only if I held him back,
only if he didn't go out on that day,
he wouldn't have died.
I killed him.
It was an accident.
It could happen to anybody.
It wasn't your fault.
My son. My poor Chang Hwa.
My poor son.
Chang Hwa, my poor son.
Chang Hwa!
No, my son...
(Changhwa Restaurant)
What happened?
Why couldn't you finish
the exorcism ritual?
Great job today. You may go.
(Daebak Realty)
I killed my own son.
Mom.
Mom!
No, right?
It's not me that's
holding you back, is it?
That can't be right.
I tried doing everything to let you go.
No, that can't be right.
How can I be the one stopping her?
My obsession,
my regret,
and my guilt...
have been holding you back?
No.
No!
I...
I killed mom with my two hands,
and I'm also the one
who has been stopping her from leaving?
Please give me a little more time, Mom.
I need to vanish.
Once I disappear,
everything will be over then.
I've definitely hit the jackpot.
But whom should I make a deal with
to get a hefty amount of money?
The chairman...
will die of shock
if this gets revealed.
Should I demand to get
my nightclub back?
No. He can always take it again.
Fine. I'll just ask him for cash.
It'll be my severance pay.
I'll ask for a huge amount.
A humongous amount of cash.
He never lets anyone live
if they ever find his weakness.
You of all people should know that.
That does make sense.
Yes. I'll play it safe.
I'll go to our poor In Bum...
and ask for just this much.
A teeny bit of money.
That's so little, though. Darn it.
Boss, must you only choose one of them?
What do you mean?
You could get a huge load
if you add them together.
You son of a gun.
You're a genius.
Hello, Ms. Hong.
Hey.
You're up already?
You should sleep more.
What are you doing here?
Changhwa Restaurant closed,
so we had to move out.
So?
Let us stay here
only until we find a place.
No.
- What?
- You're out of business anyway.
Be nice and let us use
your spacious house.
We'll only stay here until you move out.
Two days.
Look for a place in the meantime.
Come on. That's too short.
As someone who runs a realty,
you should know.
Ten days sound nice.
Okay. One week.
- No more bargaining.
- Sounds good.
Did she just give her permission?
I expected her to grab us
by the collar and kick us out.
Ms. Hong.
I have a question.
What is it?
Where's the hammer?
It's in the toolbox next to the fridge.
I want to cook some ramyeon
but can't seem to find any pots.
Look for one.
We're out of coffee.
Do you have any in the house?
No.
I bought some snacks.
Do you want to eat with us?
Where are you going?
Wait up.
Don't follow me.
I want to take a walk alone.
I also want to take a walk.
You guys are distracting me too much.
- Give me some alone time.
- No.
How can I leave you alone
when you look so unstable?
My grandfather passed away...
the year I was born.
The year after that,
my parents died in a car accident.
When I was seven, my uncle died.
My grandmother...
blamed it all on me.
She said...
I had brought misfortune
upon my family.
That's ludicrous.
You're right.
It was ludicrous.
When I was little,
I despised her for saying that.
But now, I understand.
I get why she said that.
When we encounter...
an unfathomable tragedy,
we tend to look for someone
we can resent and blame.
That's because it's easier...
to blame someone than to deal
with the tragedy itself.
Ms. Hong,
I hope you don't make
the same mistake my grandmother did.
Don't blame someone who's innocent.
Even more so if it's yourself.
It's not your fault.
So...
don't think about disappearing.
(Changhwa Restaurant)
Is Chang Hwa eating well?
Yes.
Is he enjoying the kimchi stew?
It was his favorite.
He is.
Chang Hwa.
My harsh words...
must've hurt you badly.
I'm sorry. Okay?
This is the last meal...
I'm making for you.
I hope you enjoy it...
and find peace.
Did the unrested spirit really eat
the food?
No.
Then how did he leave?
No one was possessed.
Her deep-seated grudge...
was what kept him here.
Her deep-seated grudge?
The guilt she felt for her son's death,
regret, and obsession.
Feeding him for the last time...
helped her let go of her grudge.
I don't think her feelings...
kept him here.
Perhaps,
they both couldn't let go.
It wasn't an obsession.
They were just worried about each other.
Give yourself...
some more time.
(Daebak Realty)
(Kim Tae Jin's Minion)
Finally.
Hello?
Yes.
Yes. Okay.
(Daebak Realty)
I think this is the place.
Where is he?
Did you bring the money?
Yes.
Where's Kim Tae Jin?
He's inside.
Let me check the money first.
I need to see if he's here first too.
I told you he's inside.
Okay.
No! My money!
No. No!
Ji Chul!
Hey, In Bum.
- Did he take the money?
- Yes, he did.
Okay.
He just grabbed it and bolted.
So he barely checked the box.
Good work.
He could have just used his words.
Gosh, that hurts.
I think my jaw is broken.
Hey, it's up.
- Okay. Nice.
- You're dead meat.
Hurry!
- Hey, how did it go?
- Tae Jin.
- What? Yes!
- Look at this.
We did it. We got it!
My gosh. That poor guy, Chief Heo.
You know, he's a big guy.
But he still fell for that.
Exactly.
- What? What is this?
- What?
- This is...
- You idiot!
How could you not check it
thoroughly before taking it?
- Darn it.
- I'm sorry.
Gosh. You're driving me crazy.
How could he fool us like this?
Gosh. Seriously.
I can't trust anyone.
Fine. We were too greedy.
We still have the chairman.
Let's go to him.
- Okay.
- Darn it.
(Kind, Present, and Swift Police)
- Thank you.
- Okay.
When should I come back?
I'll call you.
Okay.
Yes.
Ms. Yeom told me...
if I cut ties with people
whenever things go wrong,
I would have no one left around me.
And having such a life would be...
no different than living
as an unrested spirit.
She hasn't changed.
Well, she's the one to talk.
She's alone too.
Aunt.
When I came back
to Daebak Realty ten years ago...
and called you to say
I was going to run the realty,
you didn't even ask me twice.
You just came to help me.
Ever since that day,
you've always been with me.
So I wasn't alone
like the unrested spirit.
Thank you.
I have never...
told you about my daughter, right?
My daughter, Bom.
Giving birth to her wasn't my choice.
But she was my only family.
Bom. Hang in there.
Things were tough,
but I really wanted to raise her well.
I'm sorry.
Bom. Please?
Let's go to sleep. Please?
Sleep tight, Bom
Bom. I'll be back.
I'm sorry.
Bom. I'm back.
My gosh...
Bom. Oh, no. My baby.
What's wrong? Bom.
I don't even know why my baby died.
Did you plan it
before going into the motel?
People thought I killed Bom.
Why did you kill her?
You didn't have to kill her.
I didn't want her to become a burden.
Isn't it obvious?
I didn't want to forgive myself
for failing to protect my daughter.
- Gosh. You got through this.
- It must've been tough.
- I said not to hang out with them.
- It was tough, wasn't it?
(Gimcheon
Juvenile Correctional Institution)
The day when I decided
to follow my daughter,
your mother showed up.
Who are you?
I know that
you didn't kill your daughter.
Your mother did
more than send off Bom's spirit.
She saved my life too.
Two decades ago,
when your mother...
asked me to look after you
before she left,
I made up my mind.
I wasn't able to protect my daughter,
but I would try my hardest
to protect you.
You did protect me.
I was able to keep doing this job
instead of quitting...
all thanks to you.
You sacrificed
a lot of your good years for me.
You can stop now.
Are you firing me?
How can I possibly fire you?
How am I supposed to find
a competent secretary...
who would put up with my temper?
So you know that you have a nasty temper?
Chairman Do, it's me.
Hey, where are you?
I'm on my way to see you.
Chairman Do, I'll think of this
as my severance pay.
So you want ten big ones?
Yes, sir. If you pay me this time,
I'll keep my mouth shut for life.
All right. I have everything ready.
Take your time.
Okay.
- Get it ready.
- Yes, sir.
(Chairman Do Hak Sung)
Severance pay.
Severance pay sounds great.
What are you doing?
I have an appointment with the chairman.
I'm here for my severance pay.
Don't let him get away!
Darn it.
- Sun Nyu.
- Don't lose him!
Stop right there!
Hey! You!
Hey, man. Call the police! Darn it!
Darn it.
Darn you!
- Don't let him get away. Get him.
- Come here!
Hey, you!
(Dohak Construction)
Man, this is where he stopped.
Gosh.
What now?
Do you think
he already gave it to Do Hak Sung?
Gosh.
- Hey, you!
- Stop right there!
- Get him!
- Don't let him get away!
Kim Tae Jin! Hop in. Now!
- Where is he?
- You can't lose him!
- Darn it.
- Get him!
Get that guy!
- Hey, get him!
- He's getting away!
- Hey!
- Stop the car!
Stop!
Stop right there!
You jerk.
Where's the memorandum?
They took it.
What?
Stop lying.
Darn it.
I mean it.
I kept it...
in my inner pocket all along.
How can you just leave it there?
This is driving me insane too!
That could've been my jackpot.
"Jackpot?"
Do you know what that meant to me?
It was the last evidence.
- But you...
- You idiot!
What do you want from me?
I'm not the only bad guy here.
You, me, and Do Hak Sung,
we're all the same!
You two conned me too.
Do I seem like a joke to you?
Do I look like a pushover?
Darn it!
(Daebak Realty)
Why are they so quiet today?
They're making me more concerned
now that they're finally quiet.
What's going on, you two?
Hey.
Ms. Hong.
I just sat around quietly
without doing anything.
Exactly. Why are you two so quiet?
Where's In Bum?
Ms. Hong.
What do we do now?
The memorandum is gone for good.
What are you doing all alone,
looking so pathetic?
Nothing. I'm just sitting here.
Why aren't you doing anything?
You gave up already just because
that memorandum is gone?
The In Bum I know...
is a guy who is persistent
to an extent that he seems reckless.
He wouldn't give up this easily.
Get up.
Someone needs to stop Do Hak Sung...
before he creates
yet another unrested spirit.
- Secretary Ju!
- Good evening.
Everything became a wreck
while I was gone.
We're all here now,
so let's get started.
Okay.
This is the mid-investigation report...
from a detective I've been working with.
We found Do Hak Sung's
paper company in Manila.
It'll take us a while...
to locate the person
who gets the money laundered here.
He bribes people
with the laundered money,
then those who got bribed...
hand him inside information
and watch his back,
then they get bribed again.
While this is all happening,
the weak and the poor are...
suffering from all the damage.
If they did a proper investigation
of the fire 20 years ago,
he wouldn't have come this far.
Can you find more information
on Do Hak Sung's secretary?
Nothing official,
but personal information.
Of course.
Goodness. Why is this open?
(Out of Business)
Oh, dear! What's that?
Ma'am, it's me. It's me.
Is this hide-and-seek?
What are you doing here?
I almost had a heart attack.
I had nowhere else to go.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't going to stay for long.
You left without saying goodbye.
But here you are once again
because you needed a place to stay.
Ma'am.
Are you out of business? Why?
I see.
Is it because Chang Hwa came back?
You'll be getting a lump sum.
Didn't Chang Hwa tell you about me?
I gave him your number
and told him to call you.
Were you the one...
who gave that note to him?
Don't I deserve a compliment?
How did he look?
What do you mean? He looked fine.
What did he say?
Did he miss his parents?
When you gave him the note,
did he say he'd come back?
Hold on.
Did he not come here?
He...
died.
While working at a construction site,
he had gotten into an accident.
What are you saying?
Nevertheless, thank you.
Thanks to you, we could give him...
a proper burial on time.
Thank you.
I truly mean it.
I'm sorry.
This was his.
I don't know if it'll fit you.
Of course, it will.
I look good in anything.
Gosh.
Look.
What do you think?
It's a perfect fit, right?
Thank you.
Why are you always a wreck
on an empty stomach...
whenever I see you?
Beats me.
Do your parents know about this?
I don't have any.
I know you're a good kid.
You should stop being a thug,
get a small place to live...
and settle down.
You don't need much in life.
You just need food in your stomach...
and a place you can call home.
I have such...
a crummy life.
(Daebak Realty)
Darn it.
In Bum!
Oh In Bum!
You fraud.
(Daebak Realty)
What are you doing?
Have you gone crazy?
It's in there.
Darn it. I could've gotten
a hefty sum with that.
That's worth...
my life.
Promise me you'll use that
to catch Do Hak Sung.
That's the only way I can survive.
Hey, you know what?
I want to be able to have
some warm food...
and live a normal life
like everyone else.
So use that...
Use that...
to catch him!
Bye.
(Daebak Realty)
(Memorandum
Payment by an Apartment Unit)
Goodness.
Now that we have the memorandum,
let's do this right.
Based on a written document...
that claims Chairman Do Hak Sung
of Dohak Construction...
was behind the Yongnam Village fire
in 2001 that took 7 lives,
we have begun our investigation.
In his dying letter, Oh had claimed
to have set the fire while drunk.
However, we have obtained
medical records that prove...
that he wasn't able to drink
due to his medical condition.
We have opened up the possibility
that he could've been murdered.
Please explain this investigation
you're doing...
regarding Dohak Construction's
slush fund.
We have identified
their paper company in Manila...
and are looking into it.
About that...
The police have announced
that they've received a warrant...
regarding Dohak Construction's
paper company...
and will be doing a search
and seizure of the headquarters.
It's been a while, sir.
(Chairman Do Hak Sung)
You told us to bring you one,
so we came back with a warrant.
Your cooperation is appreciated.
Detective Choi, you may begin.
Take all the documents you want.
You still won't be able to catch me.
We'll see...
about that.
(Dohak Construction)
Put it in the back.
A cop named Kang Han Seok came by.
He's a passionate one.
I have full trust in you, sir.
You still need to come by
for an interrogation.
It's all over the news,
so I can't help you with that.
Sure. That's not a problem.
We should grab a meal sometime.
Goodbye, sir.
(Chairman Do Hak Sung)
Have you called Assemblyman Han?
He's abroad and won't pick up.
These darn scumbags.
How dare they ignore me
after gladly receiving my money?
Darn it.
- Cheers!
This beer I'm having
after catching Do Hak Sung...
sure tastes sweet.
I'm going to get drunk tonight.
I called him.
I thought he could join the party as well.
Don't be a nuisance
by standing there and come sit.
Okay. Thank you.
Hello.
Thanks.
You're so kindhearted.
Really.
What? My baby must've seen the news.
I'm the one who caught him.
Don't you know how good I am?
You had a girlfriend? How?
What? What is this fancy smell?
Yes. This is good.
It's perfect with beer.
Of course. It's my favorite snack
to have while drinking.
Pour it on the plate.
This isn't some snack. It's a dish.
Soo Jung wanted me to tell you guys
that she misses you.
I miss her too. Ask her to come
see us when she's on her day off.
She stays at her dorm and studies
on her days off.
Ms. Hong. We haven't had
a get-together for a while.
Why don't you make a toast?
This is a small get-together. Why...
Let's not be unrested spirits
after death.
- Cheers!
What was that about?
It'll be helpful.
- Keep that in mind.
- Hey.
Please.
- I should just punch you.
- This is good.
I'm digging this snack.
It's so good.
Do you really have a girlfriend?
I can't believe it.
She's so pretty.
- I don't believe it.
- She's so pretty.
Do Hak Sung will be punished
for his crimes this time, right?
It won't be easy.
A lot of people will want to protect him.
But since we started this,
we should see it through.
It's nice.
What's nice?
The weather is nice.
It's a nice day for a walk.
(Kind, Present, and Swift Police)
I did instigate him to start a fire...
two decades ago.
Back then, I was young and eager
and didn't know any better.
But I really don't know anything
about Oh Sung Sik's death.
Secretary Choi said she'd handle it,
so I entrusted her with it.
I had no idea
that she would kill him.
Then, the paper company in Manila...
was set up by Secretary Choi
without your permission?
Oh, that?
I'm looking into that
with my legal team.
It looks like Secretary Choi
embezzled the money.
Seriously. You can't trust anyone
in this world.
Ms. Choi Sun Mi.
Why would you go this far
to show your loyalty to Do Hak Sung?
Do you think you owe him...
for paying your tuition
and living expenses...
when you were
financially struggling?
He didn't help you
out of the goodness of his heart.
He needed someone
to do his dirty work.
So he took advantage
of your financial struggles.
I don't care if he's using me or not.
Even my parents abandoned me,
but he was the only one...
who was willing to help me.
Once you're no longer of use to him,
he will abandon you
the first chance he gets.
He will not.
Ms. Choi, you are smart and competent.
Do not waste your life...
for a piece of trash like Do Hak Sung.
(Trustworthy Police)
I'll wait for your call.
Hong Ji A from Daebak Realty...
met up with Secretary Choi?
I saw Ms. Hong giving
her business card to your secretary.
You don't think
she's going to betray us, right?
She wouldn't betray me.
But...
she does know a lot of things.
Right.
Then,
what should we do?
What would you do
if you were in my shoes?
Mr. Do pulled a lot of strings
to get you out, Ms. Choi.
Thank you.
Don't thank me. Your ride is here.
Bye.
Rest up.
Sky Building in Haengun-dong, please.
(Bluetooth Audio, Unknown)
But I really don't know anything
about Oh Sung Sik's death.
Secretary Choi said she'd handle it,
so I entrusted her with it.
I had no idea that she would kill him.
Oh In Bum...
Did you hear that?
It wasn't easy to get my hands
on this recording file.
You just wasted your time.
This won't change anything.
In exchange for your testimony in court,
the police will not charge you
for all the crimes...
you committed...
because you committed these crimes
under Do Hak Sung's order.
But if you turn this down,
you will go down with all the crimes
Do Hak Sung committed.
Are you planning to take the fall
for the murder charge as well?
I'm not taking the fall.
I killed him. I killed Oh Sung Sik.
No.
You didn't kill my uncle.
You weren't even there.
I'm going to make Do Hak Sung pay...
for murdering my uncle.
Ms. Choi.
Yes, she just went in.
She heard the recording file.
And I told her everything.
Let's wait.
It will be hard
to make a decision right away.
But I really don't know anything
about Oh Sung Sik's death.
Secretary Choi said she'd handle it,
so I entrusted her with it.
I had no idea that she would kill him.
Are you planning to take the fall
for the murder charge as well?
(Daebak Realty, Hong Ji A)
Once you're no longer of use to him,
he will abandon you
the first chance he gets.
Do not waste your life...
for a piece of trash like Do Hak Sung.
Ms. Hong?
I'll testify.
He's that guy.
Stop right there!
Breaking news.
At 10:30 p.m. tonight,
at Sky Building in Haengun-dong, Seoul,
a fire incident that is suspected
to be a gas explosion took place.
The rescue team is working
at the scene now,
- Oh In Bum.
- but the casualties continue to go up.
Ms. Hong. Sky Building...
- Call In Bum.
- Okay.
(Land, Private Properties,
Commercial Buildings, Rent)
(Daebak Realty)
In Bum!
In Bum.
(Sell Your Haunted House)
There are a number of people
who saw a ghost at Sky Building.
The faceless man will kill us all!
This is the CCTV footage from the police.
He'll be wanted as a key suspect.
We have to spot him before the police.
Push ahead with the safety test
of Sky Building.
How dare he treat me
like a toothless tiger?
As long as the egg ghost is there,
we're bound to see a disaster.
Are you saying In Bum will end up dead?
We aren't vanishing him,
so this might work.
Ji A, are you trying to...
Let's not do this exorcism ritual.
I can do this.
I'm different from you, Mom.
I took care of everything.
No. No!