We'll arrest everyone on the list
before the night is over.
We must find out
who is behind all this,
so round them all up.
Every disaster is preceded
by warning signs.
Spies from the North...
have infiltrated Gwangju
to incite a coup.
If you encounter anyone...
who seems to defy the government,
arrest them immediately. Understand?
- Yes, sir!
Just like you can smell gas
before an earthquake,
and just like animals ascend
the mountains before a tsunami.
- Stop right there!
- The strange, ominous feeling...
that only those who are sensitive
can pick up.
Because I grew up with anxiety,
I was always sensitive and alert.
And now that I had someone
to protect,
I had to be more alert
to sense such warnings.
Why are you praying
first thing in the morning?
I prayed...
that you wouldn't snore.
Liar.
Did I snore?
Sleep some more.
The sun hasn't come up yet.
Why are you changing the subject?
I asked you if I snored.
You didn't snore.
Come here.
(Episode 9,
Warning Signs of a Disaster)
Lads. Get your act together, okay?
- Yes, sir!
Oh, boy.
I was wondering why it was so quiet
for a few days.
I guess
we'll cry our eyes out again.
If they want us to do this,
shouldn't they at least give us
some gas masks?
Goodness.
I'd like to report a missing person.
Oh, no. Is your child missing?
How old?
No, it's an adult. Age 26.
(Electronics Store)
I had caught you red-handed...
What?
No, it's nothing.
Okay, so the missing person
is 26 years old.
Is it a female?
No, a male.
Oh, a male? Okay.
Then what is your relationship
with him?
- Is he your boyfriend?
- Sorry?
No, he's my friend.
I see, a friend.
Oh, no.
Has your friend gone missing?
You must be worried.
By any chance, did you receive...
any accident reports last night?
No, not really.
Hold on.
Can you give me your number?
But...
what do you need my number for?
We need to know the number
of the person making the report.
I'll call you right away
if we receive news of an accident.
So...
Can you write down a number
where I can reach you?
It's standard procedure.
Okay.
The Government held
an emergency meeting...
at 21:30 last night...
and decided to enforce
martial law nationwide as of 24:00.
What is he talking about?
- The government spokesperson...
- Enforce martial law nationwide?
commented at 23:30 last night...
Didn't you read the paper yet?
They decided to enforce martial law
nationwide last night.
On these grounds,
starting 24:00, May 17, 1980,
the emergency martial law
is in effect nationwide.
Considering the current situation...
Wait a minute, ma'am...
- The entire nation is deemed...
- What the?
to be in a state of emergency,
and as of 24:00, May 17,
- the emergency martial law...
- Come on, what's this?
is in effect nationwide.
Myeong Hee.
Before we go,
let's drop by Hye Gun's.
I need to get some stuff.
Then why don't we split up
and meet back here?
Why do you want to split up?
Where are you going?
I want to go see Myeong Soo.
I just want to say goodbye.
No. Let me go with you.
What if you come with me
and bump into Jung Tae?
Then I'll stay hidden somewhere.
It's just that I had a bad dream.
My gosh.
Didn't you say you want to leave
as soon as possible?
We'll be able to save time
and leave earlier if we split up.
So let's go about our business
and meet back here, okay?
Okay then.
Isn't Soo Ryeon answering yet?
No.
I heard there was a huge protest
in Seoul last time.
What if something happened to her?
Come on, I bet she's just busy.
They're probably looking around
real hard to find a new house.
Then shall I send your aunt
to check on her?
Gosh, they're not babies.
They're probably doing just fine.
I'll tell her to call you
once I get in touch with her.
So go to your room
and get some rest.
Okay.
Hye Gun, I came to get my guitar...
Hye Gun. Jung Hye Gun!
You...
Hwang Hee Tae?
Hye Gun told me to come over
last night...
and we were supposed to meet here.
But when I came,
this place was totally empty.
The door wasn't locked,
and the chairs were all busted up.
They enforced martial law
nationwide last night.
The martial law was in effect
the whole time anyway.
Are you stupid?
This means that
the new military regime...
is on the verge of starting a coup.
I know.
But what does that have to do...
with Hye Gun's disappearance?
I'm afraid
the Defense Security Command...
is behind this.
So...
- I was thinking...
- No.
What? I didn't say anything yet.
It's obvious.
You want me to ask my father...
if Hye Gun was taken, right?
Do you still not know
what kind of man my father is?
If I ask him, he won't stay still...
and make matters ten times worse.
Things will turn more dangerous
if I get involved.
Then...
what will you do now?
You said
Myeong Hee will be in danger...
if she gets involved with you.
That's why Myeong Hee and I
are leaving today.
What? Where to?
Anywhere.
As long as it isn't Gwangju.
If you're going to keep fighting,
go do it in Seoul.
If you're thinking of staying here,
wear a hat at least.
Sun Min?
Where's Hye Gun?
Did he not come home?
Myeong Hee.
Hey, little bear.
Don't you have training today?
We're human beings too, you know.
We need our rest on Sundays.
What brings you here suddenly?
Myeong Soo.
I...
will be leaving Gwangju for a while.
What? Why?
Where are you going?
When are you coming back?
I'll call the training camp later...
Are you going abroad?
You said you weren't going
last time.
Goodness, I'm not going abroad.
I promised I'd go see you
compete at the Nationals.
I always keep my promise
no matter what.
You know that, right?
Are you going alone?
I'm going with a friend.
That's good enough for me.
Promise you'll come
to the Nationals.
You promised.
Goodness.
We need to take a detour
because of the protest.
Passengers headed
to Geumnam-ro or Gwangju Station...
- need to get off at this stop.
- Those darn demonstrations.
Don't they even get tired of it?
Darn it.
- Wait a minute.
- What's going on?
What's happening?
Drag off all the college students!
Hey, come here.
I'm not a college student.
I'll show you my ID.
Come with me.
Let me go!
I'm not a college student!
You brat, how dare you?
Do you think this is a joke?
You little...
Who are you?
What are you doing? Go after them!
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
No. I'm okay.
What on earth is going on?
I don't know.
I heard something about martial law.
The situation seems pretty serious.
Let's head to the station.
We'll be okay if we stay
off the streets and go around.
Hee Tae.
- Hee Tae...
- What? Why?
Darn, what is this?
I said I'm okay.
Hey, Myeong Hee.
What brings you here?
- Hello.
- It's me again.
Myeong Hee, what are you doing here?
You're off today.
I'm here as a guardian.
What?
Who is this gentleman
being protected by you?
He has a guitar. Is he a singer?
His head is busted,
so maybe he's a college student.
He's my boyfriend.
Your boyfriend?
Is he really your boyfriend?
Yes. So please hurry up
and take a look at him.
Well, okay. Please have a seat.
Let me take a look at your wound.
Well...
He doesn't need any stitches,
but he may need a CT scan.
How long will a CT scan take?
You'll have to wait
until this evening.
We have so many patients
with head wounds.
Then I'll just leave
after you disinfect my wound.
Come on. Are you a doctor?
Give me that.
Myeong Hee's boyfriend,
Mr. Hwang Hee Tae...
Hwang Hee Tae?
Your name sounds familiar.
Hwang Hee Tae... Hwang...
It's from the banner!
Are you that Hwang Hee Tae
who went to SNU with top marks?
My gosh.
So you are a doctor, after all.
As per Dr. Hwang's self-diagnosis,
just disinfect his wound.
Please do a CT scan too. We'll wait.
Myeong Hee.
- Get ready for a CT scan.
- Yes, doctor.
Is this the CT Scan Room?
How many patients are waiting...
Myeong Hee, I'm really fine.
It's just a little scratch.
But that scratch is on your head.
You need to get a CT scan, at least.
Fine. Then let's get out
of Gwangju first.
I'll get a CT done
as soon as we get to another city.
We're at a hospital right now.
What's the point?
We're not going anywhere
until you get tested.
Myeong Hee. Seriously...
Seriously what?
What's with that face?
If you're unhappy about something,
just tell me...
Stay still, you little punk.
All right. Let me ask you once more.
Who is behind
the recent torch protest?
I already told you.
College students...
It was all college students
who came out voluntarily...
Are you kidding me?
I know there is someone
behind you all.
He made you start a rebellion,
didn't he?
What are you talking about?
I've never even met such a person.
Are you still enjoying this?
Hey.
Dip him.
No! I'm sorry!
- Get up, you punk.
- Please don't!
- Get off me.
- I'm sorry!
Please don't do this!
Go on in.
Go on in, you little...
Gosh.
Here.
Go ahead and eat.
You didn't even eat your dinner.
Thank you.
If I go home,
my father would probably prepare
a feast for me.
Are you from around here?
I was born and raised here.
Anyway, I wonder how those spies
crossed the border.
And why did they have to crawl
all the way down here to Gwangju?
By the way, Corporal Lee...
How do we tell rebels apart
from ordinary students?
Do you want to skip dinner
tomorrow too?
Just follow the orders.
I'm sorry, sir.
The problem with smart ones is...
that they think too much.
You don't have to stay here with me.
Forget it.
The test results aren't out yet.
I'm really fine.
Come on.
Thank you for waiting.
Here you go.
Since you're a top student,
I'm sure I don't have to explain
anything to you.
Doctor.
Take it easy. I was just joking.
It's a concussion.
Luckily,
there's no internal bleeding.
Are you still feeling dizzy
and nauseous?
Not anymore. I'm totally fine now.
Come on.
Don't shake your head like that.
Okay. Well then...
- What's that sound?
- It's curfew.
What? There's still a few hours
until curfew.
Didn't you know?
With the martial law expanded,
the curfew has been moved up.
Hold on. What do we do then?
What else?
You're stuck here until morning.
- What?
Don't go wandering out after curfew
and get hit in the head.
You can sleep in the lobby
or in an empty treatment room.
Now if you please,
I need you to empty that bed.
Gosh.
I've never met anyone
as stubborn as you.
I've never seen a grown man...
throw a tantrum like you either.
I didn't do that.
If only we had gone straight
to the train station when I said...
Then you would've thrown up
on a moving train...
from that concussion you have.
Exactly.
If we'd stayed together
this morning,
I wouldn't have had a concussion
in the first place.
So what?
Are you saying it's all my fault?
No, that's not it.
I don't like your tone.
Whatever.
Just hurry up and lie down.
Come on.
I'll go and check
if there are any extra beds.
Hold on.
Why do you need an extra bed?
We can share the same bed.
Have you lost your mind?
We can't do that.
What are you talking about?
Last night...
- Gosh.
- You're embarrassing me.
Keep it down.
Last night, we shared a bed...
even smaller than this one. So what?
Fine. You sleep in this bed.
- I'll go find an extra bed.
- Come on.
Forget it. I'll go.
You're a patient right now.
Stop talking and lie down.
- I can help you.
- Just lie down.
What a stubborn woman.
I like that.
Hello?
Soo Chan, it's me.
Soo Ryeon.
Why is it so hard to reach you?
I'm sorry. I've been a little busy.
How's Father? Is he feeling better?
Yes, he just took his medicine
and fell asleep.
What about you? Is everything okay?
I'm good.
Is everything okay with you?
I heard there was chaos
in Gwangju today.
Hello?
Lee Soo Ryeon.
Where are you right now?
Where else?
I'm at my place in Seoul.
Then hang up.
I'll call you back at your place.
No, you can't.
Hee Tae is asleep.
He's a light sleeper.
I'm going to bed now.
I'll call you tomorrow. Good night.
Hey, Soo Ryeon.
Gosh.
What's wrong? Did it break earlier?
No, it's just a little scratch.
I'm sorry. Did I wake you up?
I had a dream.
What's wrong? Was it a nightmare?
It was about what we saw earlier
in the day.
Why do you think
the soldiers did that?
Myeong Hee,
let me tell you a secret.
I've been struck by lightning,
a long time ago.
What?
- Really?
- Yes.
I went under an awning
to take cover from the rain,
and it hit my elbow like this.
Crazy, right?
I couldn't believe it either.
So all I did was study
how lightning works for a while.
But the reason was simple.
I was...
right next to a payphone,
that's why.
So I still...
try to avoid being close
to payphones whenever it rains.
Same goes for what happened today.
It's like being struck by lightning.
We just...
happened to be standing
next to a payphone.
Everything will be fine
once we leave Gwangju tomorrow.
But what if it's like this
everywhere else?
Don't worry.
My intuition is always on point.
I'm almost like a human canary.
Okay, Mr. Human Canary.
Yes, ma'am.
Try playing the guitar...
and see if it sounds okay.
Okay. But in return,
we must go to the station
as soon as we wake up.
Don't be stubborn.
Let's see.
(Changsoo Bed and Breakfast)
Attention.
- Yes, sir!
It's supposed to rain
in the afternoon,
so the training session
will be replaced by indoor practice.
- No!
- Darn it.
Be quiet.
We were stuck in our rooms
all day yesterday.
Do we have to practice indoors
again today?
You heard him.
It's supposed to rain later.
Then we can go out for a run
before it starts raining.
I feel all cooped up.
Things are getting tense
in the downtown area of Gwangju.
We'll be okay.
Make sure you lock it well.
- My gosh.
- Why are they taking them?
- Look at that!
- They're dragging him!
- My gosh!
- Oh, no!
- What are they doing?
- Did you see that?
It's gutsy of you
to gather around like this.
All of you, be on your way.
Officer.
You saw that too!
How could you not stop them?
The police can't stop them.
So please, just go home.
Are soldiers above the law?
- Move aside.
- You'll get everyone killed!
Go home already.
Hey, let's just go to the bakery
and come back quickly.
The class won't start until later.
Didn't you hear
what the teacher said?
The teacher told us not to go
anywhere near downtown.
That just means
we shouldn't protest.
- Did you actually believe it?
- Hey, come on.
Why are you doing this to me?
Hey, isn't that the director?
My gosh. It is him.
Don't hit innocent people!
- Don't hit him!
- Stop this now!
Don't hit our teacher!
What? What is going on?
Hey, let's go. Come on.
(Emergency Room)
Myeong Hee.
What do you think you're doing?
You promised you'd leave with me
in the morning.
The hospital is full of patients,
and we're running out of beds.
You saw it yourself.
I did. That's why I'm saying this.
Can't you see?
This isn't a normal situation.
No, it isn't.
Are you telling me
to leave my patients behind?
Yes, let's just go.
Hee Tae.
You might be disappointed in me,
but I can't help it.
For me, our safety comes first.
I do understand.
But can't you wait
until the worst is over?
No. We must leave immediately.
Don't you understand
what's going on here?
Why are you two
just standing around?
Even interns
from other departments...
and students are helping out.
I wonder why Mr. Hwang,
the top student
with a medical license, isn't.
If you want to help out,
put it on and step inside.
If you don't want to,
give it to Myeong Hee and leave.
Only medical staff are allowed
in the Emergency Room.
- I can't leave right now.
- Myeong Hee!
Seven o'clock.
What?
We're leaving
at seven o'clock sharp.
I'll carry you out on my shoulders
if I must.
Gosh, I can't believe this.
The one who loves more always loses.
Hee Tae, you can stay
in the treatment room if you feel...
Seven o'clock, okay?
Yes.
Then we'll proceed as planned.
Pardon? The martial law?
No, that's no problem.
It's not going to have much impact
on the general public.
We'll proceed as planned.
Man, this is bad.
What if they barge in here too?
Aren't you going for lunch?
Why? Is everything okay?
The thing is...
There's a big ruckus outside
because of the martial law.
If you're worried,
you can leave early today.
Well, that's not why
we brought it up.
Goodness. Just go home.
Your family must be waiting for you
at home.
I'll also head home
as soon as I wrap things up.
Come on!
Hey, what are you doing here?
He's my little brother.
You said you were going
to the academy.
I'll take him.
You wench!
All of you, on your knees.
And hands behind the back.
Your head on the ground.
(Geumnam Police Substation)
- Head on the ground, you punk!
- My goodness.
When will you be here?
- In 5 minutes, sir.
- 5 minutes?
Why are you standing around?
Get them!
Go get them.
I'll watch these punks.
Keep your head down!
They're gone. Get up.
Hey, look at me.
Mr. Officer.
Everyone, get up.
It's okay. It's all right.
There are a lot of soldiers
over there,
so go this way.
What are you waiting for? Run!
- Really?
- Yes, it's okay.
Come on. Let's go.
- Go, hurry.
- Come on.
Let's get out of here.
- Will you be okay though?
- Yes, just go.
(Samyang Garden, Aquariums)
Soo Chan.
You said you were in Seoul
last night.
Did you come back to Gwangju
with Hee Tae after that?
Yes, this morning.
You're lying again!
Do you think I'm an idiot?
You said I could come back
if things don't work out.
That's why I came back.
When I said you could come back,
I didn't mean...
you could join the protest
and take part in that ruckus.
I didn't join the protest,
nor did I take part in the ruckus.
You didn't?
You were being chased by soldiers,
covered in blood.
Are you still going to deny it?
Soo Chan,
this isn't a normal situation.
I saw the soldiers dragging a kid...
barely old enough to be
in middle school.
Would you have done nothing
if you'd seen it?
Are you okay with them dragging you?
What would you have done
if you'd run into Mr. Hwang, not me?
You're still scared of him,
knowing what's going on?
Why? Are you afraid
he'd hurt your business?
No! I'm afraid he'd hurt you.
Mother said this one thing to me
in her final moments.
She asked me to look after you
in her place.
I can just close the business
if things go wrong.
But if something happens to you...
Father is bedridden too,
so if something bad
happens to you...
How would I live?
Let's go home, okay?
If this is an abnormal situation
like you said,
let's stay home
until things calm down...
and try to look for another way.
Okay?
You can look...
for another way.
I'm not going home.
Soo Ryeon.
Even if you throw yourself
into that mayhem,
nothing's going to change.
I may not be able
to change anything,
but there are things I can do.
Tell Father...
that I'm...
in Seoul.
Soo Ryeon.
If you walk out that door now,
I'll no longer think of you
as my family.
Mr. Hwang.
Dress the wound...
and use this to triage the patient.
- Pardon?
- Take this.
Write down the patient's symptoms,
name, and age, and stick it on him.
If the patient can't be identified,
just make up a name.
If anyone needs emergency surgery,
tell us right away.
Wait.
I haven't even completed
my internship yet.
Why would you trust me with this?
You said you passed the exam.
- It's the same as the practical.
- But...
he's not a simulated patient.
Just do it.
I'm sure you're better
than that fool over there.
(Cho Young Hoon, 22, Head trauma)
Coming through! Make way.
A new patient!
Doctor! Hurry!
Please treat him right away.
Hee Tae.
- This looks like a stab wound.
- A stab wound?
He's been stabbed with a bayonet.
The other patients waiting outside
all have stab wounds.
Excuse me. Move aside please.
Myeong Hee,
get a saline drip started...
and call Surgery.
- I'll see if we can book an OR now.
- Okay.
Sorry, excuse me.
(Emergency Room, Nurse's Station)
Send them to the OR in this order.
- For this, just suture the wounds.
- Okay.
Excuse me, doctor.
When will Kim Bong Seok
get his surgery?
Kim Bong Seok...
Oh, we booked his surgery just now.
Really? Thank you so much.
Doctor, we need to book
an emergency surgery.
A stab wound of the femoral artery.
What? What are you saying?
Who are you to change the order?
I'm sorry, but we must prioritize
emergency surgeries...
- My gosh!
- My son needs urgent care too.
He needs to undergo surgery
immediately!
This patient will die
if he doesn't undergo surgery now.
Sir, please let go of this and...
Who do you think you are?
The Almighty?
Are you the Almighty?
Who are you to decide
who should go first?
If my son dies
because he can't get surgery now...
Will you take responsibility for it
if he dies?
Will you take responsibility
for his death?
Goodness, calm down!
This will only delay
your son's surgery.
I'm sorry, doctor.
Hee Tae, we've finished
triaging all the patients,
so go back to ambulatory care.
- Let's go.
- Thank you, doctor.
Goodness.
Ms. Kim Bo Yeon?
I'll disinfect your wound
and stitch it up for you.
Hee Tae.
Jin A.
Who knew I'd get to see you...
in your white coat?
I see this brilliant light
radiating from you.
Is this what they call an aura?
Keep your mouth shut, will you?
It's done,
but you'll have to wait a little
for the CT scan.
My, look at the precise stitches!
It almost looks like
you used a sewing machine.
Jin A, are you all right?
No injuries?
I'm totally fine.
I'm very nimble,
unlike this slow turtle here.
They hit you on the head too.
I heard it.
They hit you on the head?
It's nothing serious.
Just like a teacher's finger flick
when you doze off in class.
Let me have a look.
Keep your eyes on my finger.
My gosh, what is this?
You crazy fool!
Your friend is dying here...
and you get excited enough
to get a nosebleed?
Do you have a death wish?
Hee Tae, this isn't because
I'm overexcited or anything...
You should get checked out
by a doctor too.
Myeong Hee is over there,
so go register with her. Okay?
Mr. Hwang, you need to stitch up
these patients too.
Oh, okay.
- Get yourself checked out.
- Okay.
What? You little...
Gosh, what should we do?
- What is going on?
- Why? Is something wrong?
I went to the supermarket...
that opened over there
for some side dishes.
The owner of that place
is from Gwangju.
He said Gwangju is
in a state of chaos right now.
Gwangju?
What do you mean, chaos?
He said soldiers have taken over
the streets of Gwangju.
It's as if a war has broken out.
That's plain nonsense.
If a war breaks out,
it would be on the front lines.
Why would it be in Gwangju?
Who knows?
Anyhow, he said soldiers
are beating young people up...
and arresting them.
It's a total mess.
Bo Yeon? It's time for your CT scan.
Where's Jin A?
She went to call my family.
Did she register to see a doctor?
(Cashier)
(Registration)
Excuse me.
Hey, In Young.
Is there another payphone
besides that?
Oh, there's one in the Annex.
- It's through that corridor.
- Thanks.
I told her to see a doctor.
She just doesn't listen.
Goodness, that stubborn girl...
Jin A!
Jin A. Jin A!
Hello?
Is anyone there?
Hee Tae. Please save Seok Chul.
Please save her.
Jin A, what is your dream?
My dream is to become
a radio producer.
Can you show me around Seoul
this summer break?
Show me TBC's broadcasting station
and your university too!
It's a Teacher's Day present.
Write a song that will win
the University Song Festival.
Hee Tae.
Please save her. You must save her.
In Young. Did you see Hee Tae?
He went to the Annex
to make a phone call.
Why wouldn't he just use the phone
at the nurse's station?
Please.
Jin A, please.
You said you wanted to go
to the TBC broadcasting station.
Please come back.
Hello?
Can anyone help me?
Hee Tae!
Myeong Hee. Please go and get help.
Jin A, please.
Please come back, please.
Jin A. Can you hear me? Jin A.
Hang in there a little longer.
Be careful.
- Here, Sun Min.
- Okay.
(Yushin remnants, step down!)
Sir, are you okay?
Hang in there.
Oh, dear.
Hey!
Mister!
Mister. Hey!
Name...
What?
Your name...
Wait here.
I didn't get to...
Mister. Hey!
I had caught you red-handed...
What?
No, it's nothing.
Can you write down a number
where I can reach you?
Hey, look at me.
Mr. Officer.
- Will you be okay though?
- Yes, just go.
Mr. Officer.
Mr. Officer!
Please don't do this.
Do what? We didn't do anything.
I know.
Stop it.
She's just a young student.
Why are you harassing her?
Who are you?
Just let her go.
I can vouch for her...
Hee Tae.
The surgery went well,
and her vitals are stable.
She just went up
to the recovery room.
Thank you so much.
If the CPR had been any later,
she wouldn't have made it.
You...
saved Jin A.
We're already short of beds.
Patients are lying on mats
in the lobby.
There's no way
we can accept more patients.
But we couldn't refuse to accept
patients in this situation.
Deputy Director.
More than half of the patients
are unidentified.
With their medical bills aside,
the military might suspect
we teamed up with the protestors...
and attack the hospital.
What kind of hospital
refuses to accept patients?
Deputy Director.
Close the main gate
and continue to accept patients.
The soldiers might see,
so turn off all the lights...
except in the operating rooms
and the emergency room.
(Gwangju Pyeonghwa Hospital)
Eat even if you're not hungry.
You haven't eaten all day.
I guess...
you really do have good intuition.
I saw Jin A earlier,
and we even talked a little too.
But I didn't even notice
she was hurt,
let alone see any warning signs.
She looked the same as usual to me.
See? I'm a human canary.
I'm sorry.
For what?
I shouldn't have been so stubborn.
I put you through so much.
If I had believed your hunch...
and left with you
either yesterday or today,
you wouldn't have had to
go through this.
Thanks to your stubbornness,
Jin A lived.
By nature,
I avoid risks before they happen.
You're a person...
who remains where you are
even when lightning strikes.
Anyway, thanks to you,
for the first time in my life,
I didn't run away...
and could be there
when Jin A collapsed.
That means...
your stubbornness saved Jin A.
It's time.
Shall we head to the station now?
Let me tell you something
as the human canary.
Getting more patients
with stab wounds...
is not a good sign at all.
Let's wait until the worst is over.
Just until Jin A wakes up.
Will that really be okay?
I don't know.
Maybe getting struck by lightning
made me reckless.
We had a belief that we could handle
anything together.
And that inexplicable belief...
trumped all warning signs.
But little did we know...
Welcome, sir.
The lightning was also...
nothing more than a warning sign.
What was actually coming
toward us was...
a tremendous storm.
Lights off.
In the face of the storm,
the only thing we could do was...
hold each other's hands
so that we wouldn't lose each other.
(Youth of May)
How many times must I tell you?
Don't step in unless you're told to.
- I get it. Stop nagging.
- "Stop nagging?"
A person collapsed here.
I have to go.
I have to go there right now.
Are you out of your mind?
The soldiers are firing.
That's Myeong Soo's shoe.
You want to wage war
against armed soldiers?
They're massacring civilians.
Why must we remain immaculate?
Hee Tae, you were right.
I'm a hypocrite.