♪Memories of the past are always vivid♪
♪They accompanied me to take every step♪
♪On the road♪
♪Going through heat and cold♪
♪The bumpy journey
has rendered my longing♪
♪Rock solid♪
♪The same moonlight
shines on our shoulders♪
♪Even if we are far away separated♪
♪We are close in our hearts♪
♪The wind blew away the past♪
♪I look for your distant location
on the starry night♪
♪In the ocean of faces♪
♪For you, my heart burns and races♪
♪Despite its turns and twists,
fate is in my hands♪
♪May waiting convert regrets
into a happy ending♪
♪May solitary figures
find right companions♪
♪And become a pair♪
=Time Flies and You Are Here=
=Episode 22=
(The one I miss is
at the south of the sea)
(Tangjiao Village)
Countless of people,
over the ages,
worked hard for years
just for the title of
the principal graduate.
Countless of people
were trapped for life.
I wish my father
was never the principal graduate.
I heard
that you may make a wish
if you see a divine beast.
If we manage
to encounter Kun,
let's make a wish together.
All right.
Kun!
It's Kun!
Look.
Just like Teacher Liu,
I want to be a teacher.
I shall take over Su Chang Ji
and become an upright shopkeeper
just like my mother.
Xingzhou,
it's your turn.
I want to attain the fourth rank
by the age of 30,
the third rank by the age of 40,
and enter the privy council
as the grand chancellor
by the age of 50.
Live up to my conscience,
to upkeep the promise for the people
and uphold peace of the state!
All right!
Zhao Xiaoqian, look.
You've yet to...
This is my wish.
You're going to emerge
as the principal graduate.
I will charge my own fate.
(Wujiang Examination Hall)
Take the cloak with you.
It's getting cold.
Do not fall ill.
Here are some snacks I made.
Do not forget your meals
when studying.
All right.
Do your best.
I'll be waiting for you.
Thank you.
Go on.
Everything is fine.
Minggu.
What's in your mind?
Grandmother.
A friend of mine is undertaking
the civil examination.
I'm not sure if things are going well.
I'm rather concerned about him.
You're concerned about someone?
Are you worried that he might fail?
If you wish for him to score well,
you should wish him the best.
In order to do so,
your spirits must remain high.
Yes, grandmother.
(Wujiang Examination Hall)
Mr. Frog.
May Xingzhou be blessed
and pass his civil examination.
If he succeeds,
I'll provide everything
you need.
Once it's done, I'll even
find you a female frog.
All right?
Please keep him blessed.
I'm begging you.
I'll provide everything you need.
What are you doing?
Father.
I'm pleading Mr. Frog
to bless Ziyan with success.
After this,
I'll get your mother to introduce
some respectable ladies to you.
All right.
The weather is getting chilly.
It's raining again.
I wonder if there are heaters
at the examination hall.
Is Xingzhou in cold?
With the cloak you gave,
he will be fine.
Don't worry.
Things will surely go well this time.
(Wujiang Examination Hall)
(Differentiating right from wrong)
How many days has it been
since the appeal was submitted
to the capital?
Including today,
it's been ten days.
Arrange a meeting with Lingniang.
I shall treat her to a meal
at Taiping Tavern.
(Wujiang Examination Hall)
Why isn't he out yet?
It is not late.
(Wujiang Examination Hall)
There he is.
Xingzhou.
How did it go?
Where's Hanchen?
I'm not sure.
He was gone early in the morning.
It's fine.
It's Mid-Autumn today.
We're having dinner at
the Commandery Prince's Mansion.
Let's make a move.
(Yayi Workshop)
Hanchen,
did you come to see me off?
Here's a toast to you.
Have a good journey.
I knew what the capital is planning.
However, I'm afraid I'll have
to disappoint you once more.
I'm not going to marry you.
I'm not returning to the capital either.
You're a wonderful woman.
You deserve a better man.
You haven't tried.
How would you know
you're not the right one?
Because you're Shen Zhaowen.
You're Lingniang.
You're Commandery Princess Rong'an.
If you are to marry
someone who doesn't love you,
as your brother,
I'll not allow that.
You deserve better.
On the day of your marriage,
I'll be the one to send you off.
I wrote an appeal to His Majesty.
Both of us grew up in the palace.
His Majesty
treats us as his own children.
He will not make things hard for you.
Have a safe journey.
Hanchen.
Huazhong.
Hanru.
Shi Deng'er,
has he returned?
In the future, pass your knowledge
to Minggu.
These children...
Yes.
Xiaoman.
Have a seat while waiting.
What's the matter?
What are you doing?
The elderly has yet to eat.
It's not your turn yet.
Allow the child to eat first.
He's still ignorant.
I beg your pardon.
You should wait for the
Commandery Prince's return.
If he'd like to return,
he'd be here by now.
Sit upright.
Xingzhou,
I need to tell you something.
Mother.
Since they are doing well,
I'm relieved.
The Mid-Autumn celebration
sure is merry this year.
We're in the company of many guests.
Xingzhou.
There's something
I'd like to say to you.
Honestly,
I've said this before.
You just didn't hear it back then.
I don't know
if you did.
However, do you remember
on the night of Qixi Festival
on the bridge?
We were admiring the lanterns
by the river together.
We also watched the fireworks.
The moon that night
was just like the one tonight.
It was really bright.
I'm saying all these
to tell you that
I've always had a crush on you.
Since the civil examination is over,
you're heading to the capital
to undertake the Spring Exam.
You're going to enter the palace
and meet the Emperor.
You have a bright future ahead.
After becoming the principal graduate,
you'd meet a better girl.
However, it's different for me.
I need to stay at Wujiang Prefecture
and play my role as a regular merchant.
Our futures are completely different.
Perhaps, we might never end up together.
However, I just want you to know that
I like you.
(How I wish you could understand
my feelings for you.)
You know what?
You're great.
You truly are a good man.
You're the best man I've ever met.
However,
loving you is all I can do.
It's a blessing to have met you.
You're the best lady
I've ever met as well.
I'm not fortunate enough
to accept your feelings.
You're a great woman.
You'll definitely meet someone better.
Minggu,
haven't you noticed
Zhanzhi's feelings for you?
Zhanzhi is in love with you.
Are you aware of that?
The imperial edict has arrived.
Poor Xiaoman.
It's the Mid-Autumn Festival.
I wonder what's wrong.
Why hasn't His Highness return?
He should be here soon.
It's an important moment
yet he hasn't shown up.
I'm not waiting anymore.
Declare the edict.
By great grace,
by the accomplishments of the ancestors,
peace was sustained for 30 years,
The divine responsibility is to great,
exceeding one's capacity.
The boundless mercy of the ancestors
places importance in
succession of the will.
My nephew, Zhao Xiaoqian,
was taken into the palace as a prince.
Due to an ailment,
he was sent to southeast to recuperate.
Unexpectedly,
he was arrogant and imperious.
Commoners were affected.
Great commotion was stirred.
Such dominance
is against the expectations
set before him.
He shall be demoted as Duke of Wuguo.
He shall remain as
the regional governor of Wujiang
and be relieved of political duties.
A declaration to
the public and the family.
What happened?
He's demoted as a duke.
He's grounded as well.
This is serious.
I have no idea.
He's demoted to a duke?
Grounded?
Do not blame me for failing to explain.
The Commandery Prince submitted
an appeal and requested for this.
Zhao Xiaoqian.
Where are you?
Did you know?
Once this appeal reaches the palace,
you will be demoted to a duke,
and His Majesty will ground you
within Wujiang Prefecture,
there's nothing you can do.
I know.
Why are you doing this then?
(Zhao Xiaoqian)
Master, you knew all along.
Although I'm the Commandery Prince,
I'm just an abandoned child.
I'm sure you realize
there are a few people that
I care about in this world.
Xingzhou is one of them.
Not to mention, Xiaoman.
What about your ambition?
You wanted to head to the borders!
If I have to leave for
the borders on my own,
and abandon Xingzhou
and Xiaoman,
I'm afraid I can't do so.
The politics of the capital
intend to manipulate me once again.
It doesn't help even
if I go to the borders.
I'm just a pawn.
If I don't do this now,
I can never do it.
I beg for your understanding
and submit this appeal to the Emperor.
I'm willing to be demoted as a duke
and remain in
Wujiang Prefecture forever.
Let me take you somewhere.
Zhao Xiaoqian.
What's going on?
I, Hanchen of Zhao Family,
bear the royal blood of Zhao Clan,
the son of Prince Pu, the Regional
Military Governor of Wuchang Region.
I've been granted many titles.
The Regional Military Governor,
the Regional Commander of E'zhou,
Minister of Guanglu,
Provincial Governor under
the Supreme Government,
and was even once
Commandery Prince of Julu.
Right now,
I'm just the Duke of Wuguo.
Hanchen of Zhao Family
is in love with female scholar of
Wujiang Prefecture, Xie Xiaoman.
I would like to take you as my wife.
I'll love you and you only.
For the rest of my life,
I will never leave you.
Here I ask.
Will you marry me?
Love each other
till death does us apart.
I will.
I will!
Thank you, Lady Xie.
Have a safe journey, Lady Shen.
General, thank you for the escorts.
As for the war at Baichuankou,
I await news of your victory.
General Xu has never lost a battle.
Besides, I shall join him.
You don't have to worry.
I'm worried
exactly because of you.
You've been arguing since young.
Are you done?
May you return in triumph.
Thank you.
Lady Shen is returning to the capital.
I've arranged for soldiers
to escort her journey.
Master, thank you.
Let's depart.
In the appeal submitted to His Majesty,
I mentioned your predicament as well.
Don't worry.
His Majesty has agreed
not to force you into the palace.
You may return to the capital with ease
and reunite with your family.
In order to cast me out,
you requested to
be demoted as a duke,
do you really hate me that much?
I didn't do this for you.
I know.
It was for the sake of Xiaoman.
Do you really think
the capital would
let you go just like that?
(Capital)
If that's the case,
head to Wujiang Prefecture.
Whether he marries
Lingniang or not,
you must bring him back.
I understand.
(Residence of the Su Family)
Zhao Xiaoqian said
he was dropping by.
Why isn't he here yet?
He went to see General Xu off.
He should be here soon.
General Xu is leaving?
If that's the case,
General Xu left and
Shen Zhaowen left as well.
Those who do not belong here have left.
When will you get married?
Around spring next year.
Duke of Wuguo
is irresponsible.
Bed, mattress, blanket,
veil and curtain
are all ordered by me.
You're about to
become the Duchess of Wuguo.
You shouldn't be occupied
with trivial matters like these.
If it were me, I would do this.
Watch me.
Liangji.
Come here.
Serve me some tea.
Teacher Liu told me that
you're planning to pursue
your studies with her.
You're going to help
prepare the syllabus as well.
Is that true?
Minggu,
have you ever imagined
what kind of person you'd be
in the future?
I'm going to be a merchant
and make money.
What about you?
I want to be a teacher in the future,
just like Teacher Liu.
However...
What's it?
I'm worried that
Zhao Xiaoqian would disagree.
Duke of Wuguo has arrived.
There he is.
You're late.
Miss me?
You're not properly covered.
Aren't you cold?
No,
as long as I look good.
You're the prettiest.
Wick.
Help me back.
It's suffocating here.
How annoying.
I need to discuss something with you.
We're husband and wife.
What's there to discuss?
After getting married,
logically speaking,
I don't need to study in
the academy anymore.
However, I talked to Teacher Liu.
She's willing to take me in
as her disciple.
Isn't it great?
In the future,
I would like to become a teacher, too.
No.
There's no room for discussion.
Why not?
In the future,
if you become a teacher,
you'd spend all your time
at the academy.
You'll not have time for
the household affairs.
After having children,
you'll not have time for them either.
Not to mention
the academy is filled with men.
We're getting married.
Why are you being so petty?
Teacher Liu is extremely talented.
Besides, it's going to take years
for me to become a teacher.
Well, I do not agree.
I'm telling you.
I'm of the Zhao Family.
If you do not
raise our children well,
the future of the clan will be at stake.
You...
You're so unreasonable.
Yes, that's who I am.
What can you do about it?
I insist on going.
No way.
You cannot convince me otherwise.
(Residence of the Su Family)
Grandmother.
Take it easy.
I'm fine.
Have some water.
Take it easy.
I'm getting old.
My health is deteriorating.
Don't say that, grandmother.
The weather is cold.
That's why you're coughing.
Everything will be fine
once spring comes.
Xiaoman.
You surely know how to cheer me up.
I've been working all my life.
I spent the first half of
my life as the shopkeeper.
My brain is exhausted
from managing the accounts.
Things are rather muddled.
I should leave when it's time.
It's exhausting.
Grandmother.
Once I'm gone,
I'm leaving Su Chang Ji
to your aunt and Minggu.
Xiaoman.
Why is Minggu
still so immature?
I'm not sure if
she will be able to manage Su Chang Ji.
Mother.
Xiaoman.
You should check it out.
Your father is chasing Li'er
all over the courtyard.
I'm not sure what happened.
Grandmother,
I shall check it out.
Hurry on.
Stand right there!
- No!
- Uncle.
I'm about to get a beating!
Stand right there!
You said you're not hitting me here
at Residence of the Su Family!
I'm not going to hit you?
You're lying!
I can't let this slide!
You're not taking
your study seriously!
All you do
is pester your brother-in-law
for new toys!
You rascal!
You might injure him!
Father,
Li'er is still young. Go easy on him.
I'm going easy on him!
Father.
I'm warning you!
Let's just talk things out.
Why do you hit him?
What?
Go ahead and ask him.
What's the matter?
I didn't do well in my exam.
How bad is it?
Third grade.
Third grade?
Look at him.
You shouldn't evade father
over such horrible results!
Get back here!
You should deliver the medication
to grandmother.
Get back here!
Xiaoman.
Hurry up and deliver the medication.
I'll check on him.
Third grade?
How's that possible?
He said
he was doing fine back then.
He understood what was being taught.
He was lying.
He's full of nonsense.
He doesn't pay attention in class.
All he does is play around all day.
He's not allowed outside anymore.
He needs to return home
after school immediately.
Otherwise,
let's employ a tutor
to teach him.
My daughter,
you're right.
I'll think about it.
He's still young.
We can't leave him like this.
You're right.
Come on.
Why are you laughing?
Stop laughing at one's misfortune.
Do not buy him anything from now on.
Li'er.
Don't be upset.
Let me tell you.
My mother hit me all the time
when I was young
with a wooden stick.
But...
But I'm stupid.
I'm unlike brother.
Who called you stupid?
You're still young.
Your brain isn't
completely developed yet.
I'll figure something out for you.
How about this?
If you encounter something that
you don't know,
memorize it.
When you're questioned,
just answer as you memorized.
Trust me.
They'd be impressed
by how brilliant you are.
Try it out.
If I memorize all,
they'd find me brilliant?
Of course.
Fenniang would...
Fenniang?
Who is that?
Who is Fenniang?
Sister Minggu, do you have a crush?
Don't be ridiculous.
You...
You're still young.
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm not married.
Li'er,
do you have a crush on someone?
That's a good thing.
You're still young.
If you like her,
you must express your feelings.
Don't end up like me.
After so long,
I thought I had everything.
In the end, I lost everything.
Express my feelings?
Yes, make it clear.
(Yan's Mansion)
Boyang,
you're not young anymore.
You're still frisky.
Recently,
I introduced some
respectable ladies to you.
Are you not interested at all?
No.
You rejected every single one of them
without any explanation.
What's not good about them?
Mother,
I can't help it.
Who are you interested in then?
List down your requirements then.
The ladies I found
are the daughters of
reputable households
in Wujiang Prefecture.
If you reject them all,
that will upset them.
Besides, your father is an official.
You're putting him in
a difficult position.
Mother.
A tortoise and a mung bean
can't possibly fall in love.
What are you talking about?
Anyway, the next lady I will introduce
is the daughter of Prefect Xue,
Xue Yanwan.
I do not care about the tortoises.
You shall attend this blind date.
Wait.
You even got Xue Yanwan involved?
I'm not going.
Are you sure?
Fine.
Forget about the academy as well.
Do not step out of Yan's Mansion.
It's my fault
for giving birth to a brat like you.
Mother.
Don't be upset.
If this blind date doesn't work,
it's no longer up to you anymore.
Marriages are decided by one's
parents anyway.
Take it seriously.
Seriously.
Wait.
(From Zhanzhi)
(To Minggu)
My brother wasn't
like this when he was young.
I scored good grades
when I was young, too.
We were raised under
the same circumstances.
How could Li'er
even fail to memorize The Analects?
Perhaps, the teachers did not
pay enough attention to him?
Why are you staring at me?
Don't you find it
difficult to be a teacher?
Look.
When students fail to
memorize The Analects,
the teachers have to take the blame.
If I were his teacher,
I would be able to teach him well.
Is that so?
Yes.
Let's make a bet.
What's it?
Let's teach Li'er about The Analects.
If you succeed,
I'll reconsider
your decision to become a teacher.
Are you serious?
Yes.
Pick Li'er up from school tomorrow
and drop him off to Lotus Garden
for extra lessons.
Yes, Your Highness.
You're the best!
♪Ask the moon whether it has seen♪
♪The other end of the earth♪
♪Your feelings fluctuate
like the moon's wane and wax♪
♪Have they ever been the same?♪
♪Carried by misty clouds,
the moon came into your eyes♪
♪As a substitute for me, it appeared♪
♪Cast our eyes over the bustling street♪
♪Don't shed tears when we part♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪