♪Memories of the past are always vivid♪
♪They accompanied me to take every step♪
♪On the road♪
♪Going through heat and cold♪
♪The bumpy journey
has rendered my longing♪
♪Rock solid♪
♪The same moonlight
shines on our shoulders♪
♪Even if we are far away separated♪
♪We are close in our hearts♪
♪The wind blew away the past♪
♪I look for your distant location
on the starry night♪
♪In the ocean of faces♪
♪For you, my heart burns and races♪
♪Despite its turns and twists,
fate is in my hands♪
♪May waiting convert regrets
into a happy ending♪
♪May solitary figures
find right companions♪
♪And become a pair♪
=Time Flies and You Are Here=
=Episode 21=
(Youth is short,
waste no time on entertainment)
As a delicate woman,
Princess Consort Ming
was forced to marry a foreign
man she has never met,
and forced to spend the rest
of her life with him.
After she passed away,
she can only be buried in the desert,
forbidden from returning
to her homeland.
To Princess Consort Ming,
isn't it a great sacrifice?
If what you uphold is true,
Princess Consort Ming was tired of
living her life as a caged bird,
so she volunteered to embark up north,
why were the songs of grievances
sung through the world?
From the palace to Xiongnu,
isn't that just moving from one cage
to another?
Lady Xie,
do you concur?
Spring is everlasting.
The willows never sleep.
The lonely moon lit up the skies while
the stars kept each other company.
In the future,
dreams are far from reach,
remaining in Yuyangli Village.
Literati of the past often
shaped Zhaojun
into the epitome of bitterness.
Baseless presumptions of her loneliness
and her regrets were formed.
Everyone presumes that once
she leaves her motherland
and marries off to
the land of the savage,
she'd only suffer,
and wallow in pain and grievances.
However, is it likely that
she led a life of happiness?
Do keep in mind, that men of the past
scorn upon ladies.
For this reason,
the country came up with excuses,
imagining
how Princess Consort Ming expressed
her sentiment for the country.
During the reign of Han,
she was nothing but a mere tool.
Nobody cared about her.
However, after marrying off to Xiongnu,
the sky was vast,
and the land was boundless.
Stars spread out to no end.
She was free of restrictions.
Imagine.
She would be much happier
than she was back in Han.
Am I right?
Bravo!
Xiaoman,
well done.
During the discussion,
both Lady Shen and Lady Xie
made compelling opinions.
Lady Shen's opinions were
true to the materials
while Lady Xie's were
critical and sharp.
She provided a completely new,
unique and unconventional
point of view.
She expressed the suffering that
women of generations endured.
Therefore,
the best scorer of
this term's examination
is Lady Xie.
- Bravo!
Xiaoman.
Since you've accepted the hairpin,
you're now a disciple of mine.
I need to let you know.
History is vast and rich.
To devote ourselves to compiling
the historical books
is like sailing off into the sea.
We will go wherever the boat takes us.
We're recording
true insights of the
respectable women of history.
At the same time, these materials
will exceed time and inspire
the ladies of the future.
I'll keep your teaching in mind.
(Shuntian Gate)
Xiaoman,
why didn't Minggu attend school today?
Zhao Xiaoqian
left all of a sudden.
What's going on with both of you?
Lady Xie!
What's the matter?
Bad news, Lady Xie.
I went to visit Old Madam Su
back at Su Mansion.
Lady Su
stole the money
for Madam Su's new store.
It's a total of 500 strings
of 1,000 cash.
Madam Su is panicked right now.
What?
Minggu took 500 strings of 1,000 cash?
Yes.
This was found in her room.
Let me take a look.
(Zhong Ziyan's personal profile )
What does it say?
We need to find Minggu.
(Principal Yang)
I received a letter from an old friend
in the capital yesterday.
The letter mentioned that
your father, Li Guangwen,
was alleged of involving in a major
corruption of the imperial court.
He's being investigated.
He's temporarily grounded
in his own residence.
Nothing is concluded yet.
It's Grand Secretariat Qin.
Political strife leads to one's demise.
Your father sided with Chancellor Xu.
Due to the corruption within the court,
both parties, Xu and Qin
were in constant strife.
Your father was implicated.
Actually,
the donation sustaining
the academy over the years
came from your father.
We exchanged letters several times.
He always asked about you
at the end of the letters.
I know
disparity exists between
you and your father.
However, blood is thicker than water.
The capital is
transitioning to winter now.
You should head home and
pay your father a visit.
I understand.
Minggu.
- Minggu.
Where is she?
Minggu.
- Master Yan.
- Minggu.
I found her.
According to the guards,
she was seen at the brothel
with Xu Shu.
Xu Shu?
Hurry up.
Master Yan.
I brought the cash.
Will you come with me
to clarify the situation now?
Go with you?
If I do,
I will be insane.
If I go with you,
my father is going to
reprimand me again.
Am I going to testify for Zhong Ziyan
and end up imprisoned?
No way.
You have to clarify the situation.
Hurry up.
Come with me.
I'm begging you.
Zhong Ziyan
devoted his life to the examination.
He is innocent.
He had no idea.
Please help him out.
I'm begging you.
Please...
Minggu.
You...
Yan Boyang.
Let me go.
What are you doing, Yan Boyang?
No one forces her to do this.
It has nothing to do with you.
Su Minggu,
do you know what you're doing?
Do you think this would help Xingzhou?
Come with me.
What can I do?
Tell me. What else can I do?
I can't stand by and do nothing.
He should impress
everyone with excellent results.
He should serve in the
capital as a great official.
He should be given the principal
graduate's residence at Wujiang.
He had no idea.
He was wronged.
I have to help him.
Minggu.
I'm begging you.
Ziyan had no idea what's going on.
Su Minggu,
do you know what you're doing?
My father is Yan Nengfu.
Xingzhou's matter can be
easily resolved.
Why are you kneeling down before him?
Xu Shu,
you're threatening the heir
of Su Family.
Aren't you afraid of the laws?
You have a father.
You have a father, too!
You just want me dead!
You just want me imprisoned, right?
Fine.
We're all going to die together.
Minggu!
- Yan Boyang.
- Boyang.
Boyang.
Boyang, are you all right?
Am I a fool?
Boyang.
Do not move.
Boyang, wake up.
Seize them.
- Yes.
- Boyang.
- Move it.
Boyang.
Are you sure about this?
The battlefield is not a game.
Yes.
I don't plan to return.
All I've ever wanted
is to become a warrior.
For any battles to come,
I'm at your disposal.
All right.
Here.
Your Highness.
General Xu.
What's the matter?
Master Yan's attendant sent news
that Mr. Zhong cheated
in the examination.
He's banned from
the examination permanently.
(Bailu Academy)
(Lonely Boat At Night, volume four)
Trash!
I'm trash.
If it wasn't true,
I wouldn't have been cast out
from the examination hall.
A true man,
even at the brink of death,
would not
grovel on the ground like you!
What can I do?
For this matter,
I can't possibly drag you into this
and do you harm.
What about you then?
Zhao Xiaoqian,
what can you do?
It's the civil examination,
not a kid's game.
This is my business.
Stay out of this.
(Studio of Artlessness)
How is Xingzhou?
You've caused enough trouble.
What's the progress of the exam?
Is there really nothing we can do?
It's fine.
I'll talk to Shen Yan.
His uncle is part of
the Division of Personnel.
There must be a way.
You are not on good terms with him.
Would he lend us a hand?
We'd never know if we never try.
Liangji,
convey my words to Shen Yan.
I would like to meet him.
I'll meet him at the prison.
All right.
It's going to be fine.
Don't worry.
I'm concerned
about Yan Boyang's injury.
(Yan's Mansion)
Well,
Lady Su.
Master Yan
is not in.
I just want to check on him.
I'm worried about his condition.
Please allow me to visit him.
Lady Su,
Master Yan isn't home.
It's true.
He went
to the infirmary out of town.
At night...
He will return tomorrow.
I suggest
you should go home.
All right.
I understand.
Tell him
to take care.
Do not worry about Mr. Zhong.
We...
We will figure something out.
Also...
Remember to tell him
I'm sorry.
(Yan's Mansion)
This time,
my friend has caused you trouble.
What's your plan?
Get Liangzhe Circuit to
issue an official document.
With the document,
we will be able to acquire the reserved
topic from the examination hall
and allow Xingzhou to retake the exam
alone.
I know Lord Feng of
the Division of Personnel
is your uncle.
If you're willing to write a request
for the appeal,
I believe Lord Feng
will consider this.
Retake the exam?
Easy for you to say.
Zhao Xiaoqian!
You're aware of
what Xu Shu did!
I have respect for you so
I did not lay a finger on him.
He schemed
and harmed Xingzhou.
A man like this
should be eliminated.
Do you think the capital
would be oblivious about Zhong Ziyan?
Let me be honest with you.
Your mother knew that
you'd ask for my help,
so she informed me beforehand.
If you insist on joining the military
and refuse to marry Lingniang,
Zhong Ziyan will not be able to
participate in
the examination ever again.
What do you mean?
The incident of Zhong Ziyan
was made known to the capital.
The capital has replied.
In the whole of Wujiang Prefecture,
whoever that lends a hand to you
is opposing Prince Pu.
Zhao Xiaoqian,
you're really naive.
Do you think, with your abilities
and the influence of General Xu,
you'd be able to go against
the imperial power of Prince Pu
and the capital?
You intend to go to war.
His Majesty agreed.
What about the Empress?
Will Her Highness allow you
to attain merits
and threaten the Crown Prince?
How absurd!
How absurd.
Hanchen,
I'm heading to the battlefield soon.
I'll be disembarking to Baichuankou
with General Xu Zi in a few days.
I know.
Fighting in the war
has always been your dream.
Shen Yan.
Do you know what's the root
of all my troubles?
The identity as the Emperor's
adopted son, the title of
Commandery Prince of Julu!
I will spare Xu Shu,
but that doesn't mean
I'm letting this slide.
After this,
send him to guard the city gates
at Shanhai Pass.
Master Shen.
Do you know how much
trouble you've caused?
Master Shen.
I let you down.
Let me down?
What do you mean?
Do you know how much
clamour you've evoked
in the capital?
Zhao Xiaoqian would spare your life
if you leave Wujiang Prefecture
and guard the city
gates at Shanhai Pass.
Are you willing to go?
My father
removed my name
from the genealogical records.
I'm no longer Xu Shu.
I have no rights
to refuse His Highness' order.
Don't worry.
At Shanhai Pass,
I'll set everything for you.
Here in Wujiang Prefecture,
I'll take care of your mother
and sister.
Master Shen.
(Studio of Artlessness)
I have a favour to ask.
Go ahead.
Mid-Autumn Festival is approaching.
Our family is planning for
a reunion dinner.
They are unaware...
of our relationship.
On the night of the festival,
I hope you'd be able to attend.
Invite the elders over to
the Commandery Prince's Mansion instead.
During the past celebrations,
we have a lot of leftover supplies.
There are fireworks left, too.
Invite your family over.
I'll get the cooks to
prepare a good meal
for everyone.
What...
What about Xingzhou's matter?
There is still no hope.
(Studio of Artlessness)
Let me tell you a ghost story.
Let's go.
Once upon a time,
in Tengzhou,
there was a man named Liu Yixian.
He was great at drawing portraits.
His neighbour
was a father and son duo.
The father passed away all of a sudden.
The son went to
purchase the coffin
and requested Liu Yixian for a portrait.
Liu Yixian went over.
He realized the gate was unlatched.
He opened the door and entered.
There was no one in the house.
He figured,
the body must be upstairs.
He followed the stairs
and went up to the second floor.
He sat by the corpse
and started painting.
Suddenly...
What happened?
Suddenly, the corpse
sat upward!
Liu Yixian thought to himself.
Such bad luck.
He encountered a living corpse.
However, he dare not move.
The corpse did not move either.
It just stared at him.
After a while,
the neighbour returned.
The neighbour witnessed the scene
and fainted right on the spot.
Then,
the coffin carriers came by.
They fainted on the spot as well.
No.
Liu Yixian suddenly recalled that
living corpses feared brooms.
He shouted to the people.
"Bring me a broom!"
The carriers understood immediately.
They found a broom
and waved it in front of the corpse.
The corpse fell down.
Afterward,
they woke the son up
with some ginger tea
and moved the old man's corpse
into the coffin.
Is that it?
Yes.
What kind of a ghost story is that?
Quit complaining.
Back when I was young,
the story frightened me
so much that I couldn't fall asleep.
Silly girl.
I'm going back now.
I'll come by again tomorrow.
Xiaoman.
If...
I'm just asking.
If your friend needs your help,
but it comes with a great price,
would you help your friend out?
I don't know.
I really don't know.
Can I sleep here with you tonight?
I'll take the ground
while you take the bed.
Why are you leaving me?
What's the true reason?
It's because
you're going to marry a wife.
Even if it isn't Lady Shen,
it'd be someone else.
I don't want to be stuck
in the back court
and share my husband
with someone else.
I don't want to part with you.
Come up here.
Zhao Xiaoqian.
You're the best man
I've ever met.
Thus, I hope all things
will go well for you.
I hope that you'd become
a well-respected general
in the days to come.
I hope you'd attain success
through your hard work.
By your grace,
please help
Zhong Ziyan overcome this hurdle.
Help him. Help him.
(Lotus Garden)
Pervert!
This is natural.
Where did you learn this?
Who taught you that?
I...
Lady Xie!
Lady Xie, you slept with His Highness?
What's the matter?
Lady Su came by just now.
She said...
What?
Xingzhou is gone?
(Lotus Garden)
What do we do now?
Inform His Highness about this.
What happened?
Mr. Zhong is gone.
It's daybreak.
We checked the entire mansion.
Nobody knows where he went.
I told Shi Deng'er to ask around.
The captain of the city guards
said he left the city alone last night.
He is not sure where he went.
Your Highness.
Sir.
Here's your noodle.
Enjoy while it's hot.
Your chopsticks.
You're welcome.
Ziyan.
I'll leave the noodle here.
All right.
What would you like to have?
A bowl of noodles
with bamboo shoot and pork
and a pot of hot tea.
All right.
A bowl of noodles
with bamboo shoot and pork.
Please hold on.
It'll be served soon.
What's the matter?
Hurry up and serve the noodle.
(Noodle stall)
Why are you here?
Xingzhou wanted to visit home.
It's been a long time
since I paid you a visit,
so I dropped by to check on
you and Yun.
Hurry up and greet His Highness.
How impolite.
My brother is the principal graduate.
He's going to become
a great official in the future.
I'm not going to greet you.
Little brat.
You can't
say that in public.
You're right, Yun.
When your brother emerges
as the principal graduate,
you shall be the sister of a nobleman.
By then,
let's see if you'd still
play with rocks.
Pardon the child.
Go and have fun.
I'm going to wash the dishes.
Things are
great here.
I'm just concerned.
He's out there alone.
There's nothing much I can do.
As his mother,
I'm greatly concerned about him.
Fortunately,
Ziyan has been under your cover
since he was young.
Otherwise,
he'd end up
at somewhere else.
Xingzhou is outstanding.
He'd do well no matter where he goes.
It's good that
the civil examination this year
is finally over.
Xingzhou said he did fine.
Mother.
What if I
quit taking the examination?
Don't be ridiculous.
My son is brilliant and sensible.
In the future,
he's going to soar in success.
Don't worry about the family.
I'm here.
Who said you're not going
to take the examination?
You're going to emerge
as the best scorer.
When you do,
tell them you came from
the Commandery Prince's Mansion.
That's right.
Your Highness,
I will
leave my son to your care.
Do guide him.
Xingzhou!
I'm going to check on him.
I'll take you somewhere tonight.
We'll enjoy some fruits.
What do you think?
(Tangjiao Village)
Here.
What's this?
I don't know.
I ate this fruit with Hanchen
the last time we came.
We even saw Kun.
However, in your heart,
you must yearn to see Kun.
I want to see Kun.
Xingzhou,
have you ever wondered?
After participating in the examination,
how will
your life change?
Of course.
I think about it day
and night.
After entering the examination
passing the second round,
going through the final screening
and becoming His Majesty's protege,
I'll serve as a local officer
for three years.
Then, I'll return to the capital
and serve under the chancellery.
I'll attain the fourth rank
by the age of 30.
I'll attain the third rank
by the age of 40.
Then I'll enter the privy council.
I'll become the grand chancellor by 50.
I'll live up to my conscience.
Live up to the promise to the people
and live up to uphold peace
of the nation.
What do you think?
Isn't it dumb?
You've never told me about this.
It no longer matters.
I'm afraid they are all illusions.
Don't say that.
Zhao Xiaoqian said that
nothing is certain yet.
Don't give up.
Everyone used to tell me that
since my father was
the principal graduate,
I'd become one as well.
However, things
aren't that simple.
Countless of people,
over the ages,
worked hard for years
just for the title of
the principal graduate.
Countless of people
were trapped for life.
I wish my father
was never the principal graduate.
I heard
that you may make a wish
if you see a divine beast.
If we manage
to encounter Kun,
let's make a wish together.
All right.
Kun!
It's Kun!
Look.
Just like Teacher Liu,
I want to be a teacher!
I shall take over Su Chang Ji
and become an upright
shopkeeper just like my mother!
Xingzhou,
it's your turn.
I want to attain the fourth rank
by the age of 30,
the third rank by the age of 40,
and enter the privy council
as the grand chancellor
by the age of 50.
Live up to my conscience,
to keep the promise for the people
and uphold peace of the state!
All right!
Zhao Xiaoqian, look.
You've yet to...
♪Ask the moon whether it has seen♪
♪The other end of the earth♪
♪Your feelings fluctuate
like the moon's wane and wax♪
♪Have they ever been the same?♪
♪Carried by misty clouds,
the moon came into your eyes♪
♪As a substitute for me, it appeared♪
♪Cast our eyes over the bustling street♪
♪Don't shed tears when we part♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪