[English subtitles are available]
[My Dear Guardian]
[Episode 14]
Zhuo Ran.
Did you notice that
you're especially unlucky
when you're with me?
You either injure yourself or fall sick.
Perhaps we're not meant to be together.
How about this?
I'll stay away from you.
I know I'm quite annoying at times.
Mi Gu.
It's not your fault.
I don't mind.
Did I interrupt you?
We're coming in.
Hello, Mr Zhuo and Ms Mi.
With regard to the incident
outside the banquet hall at the hotel,
it's indeed tricky and troublesome.
Now, we need cooperation
from both of you
to give a statement.
He's still bleeding.
Can we do it later?
No.
Please cooperate with us.
It won't be long.
-You...
-Mi Gu.
It's okay.
Do we do it together or...
Do it separately.
Come with me.
He's a lunatic.
He's been pestering me a long time
insisting to date me.
Have you ever given him any promises?
Of course not.
I don't know.
Don't know?
Ms Mi Gu and I
met each other not long ago.
I'm not quite familiar
with her romantic experience.
So,
both of you are not close with each other?
Yes, you may say so.
All thanks to Zhuo Ran.
That's why I escaped.
Why did he
ask for your help to obtain
the licence of the forum?
He's a businessman.
Isn't it normal for him
to expand his connection?
I couldn't help but wonder
why you chose to attend
a medicine related forum?
My company
is mainly about 3D printing.
Lately, we're doing a collaboration
with the hospital.
Therefore, I'm interested
to get an understanding
of the related industry information.
You're indeed far-sighted
and in the full vigour of life.
Do you know this person?
No.
Does Zhuo Ran know him?
How do I know?
Why do you keep asking about Zhuo Ran?
He's not the person who assaulted me.
We need to get a better understanding
of every detail at the scene.
Take off your shirt.
We received complaints
from the public
that you
illegally possessed a gun.
We need to confirm on that.
Can you give me a hand?
Okay, no problem.
What a nice material.
Please raise your hands.
It seems that it was just a mischief.
Mr Zhuo, I'm so sorry.
People who simply take up police resources
should be taught a lesson.
That's all for today.
You're working for the people.
I can understand that.
All right, see you again.
Please sign the document
if everything is okay.
It's not working.
Do you have any other pen?
I have a pen.
Do you?
It's done.
Use it.
Thank you for your cooperation.
What do you keep in your bag?
It looks quite heavy.
It's camera.
I need it for working purposes.
Let's go.
Mi Gu.
It's not your fault.
I heard from my dad
that someone assaulted you.
Are you okay?
Are you injured?
I'm fine.
Zhuo Ran injured himself though.
Is it serious?
According to the doctor,
his nerves and bones are intact.
I think he should be fine.
Where is he?
He's undergoing debridement.
Well...
I went to the hotel
for film shooting on location.
He was there to attend a medical forum.
We...
We were there for work
and we ran into each other by chance.
Something unexpected occurred.
As he's bleeding profusely,
-I sent him to the hospital.
-Actually...
Don't mind it.
Take a seat.
I mean,
to Zhuo Ran, I...
Yes.
When I saw him,
I still felt something
which couldn't be explained.
However, I think
it's not because of him per se
but it's because of the memories.
Everything in the past happened for real
and it won't happen again in the future.
Hence, I won't forget it.
Sometimes, we couldn't help reminiscing
those guys in white shirts
who played basketball on the court.
However, it's just nostalgia.
Life goes on no matter what.
The story between Zhuo Ran
and I has ended.
As for you,
if he really makes you happy,
then you should go ahead.
I thought
you wouldn't talk to me anymore.
Just because of a former lover?
Am I so petty?
To me,
a serious friendship
is more memorable than
romantic relationship.
I love you, Mi Gu.
Any man
can never take your place in my heart.
I've to get back to work.
Call me if anything.
Why did you bring me to the hospital?
Didn't I tell you to send me home?
We're here to apologise.
What?
Hello.
Is Xia Chu here?
I think she went to the emergency ward.
You may give her a call.
All right, thank you.
-I don't want to go there.
-Let's go.
Thank you for your help at the hotel.
Have you taken the medicine?
What?
-What are you doing?
-It's tranquillizer.
I told Mi Gu to replace the tranquillizer.
Have you taken it?
The tranquillizer is not for myself.
I gave it to Liang Mu Ze.
Tell him to throw it away.
What's wrong?
My company had a collaboration
with a medicine manufacturer before.
We attempted to use 3D printing technology
to produce hypnotic
which is made of Chinese medicine.
However, the first batch
contains excessive birthwort.
Long term consumption
may lead to kidney failure
or worse, liver cancer.
Hence, we decided to destroy the products.
My assistant took it by mistake.
I didn't know that
and I gave it to Mi Gu.
Normally, when a man and a woman
are together
and they did not pick up the phone call
at first instance,
it's either they're busy
or they're having fun.
Don't ask for embarrassment.
Xia Chu.
It was an accident.
Luckily nothing happened to you.
I'm fine
but my friend almost took
substandard medicine.
Do you know
how much of trouble you caused me?
If his health is affected
because of my negligence,
I won't be able to forgive myself.
Also,
before you make any decision
that has something to do with me,
will you please
inform me about it?
Don't simply do whatever you want.
Don't get Mi Gu
involved in your so-called accidents.
Please don't hurt me over and over again
in the name of protecting me.
I'm sorry.
She looks like she's having fun.
Where did you go?
Take a guess.
Where did you find her?
Well...
Sorry to have troubled you
to pick her up at the airport.
Mu Ze.
I'm tired.
She...
What's wrong?
She fell asleep due to her illness.
Let's go to your office.
Let's go.
Zhuo Ran.
You're still here.
I went to pick up the medicine.
The doctor prescribed medicine
for tetanus and antibiotics.
Thank you.
Let's go to the injection room.
Okay.
Do you plan to leave her here?
Yes, if I send her home,
she'll run away once she's awake.
Even if you leave her here,
I can't be watching her all the time.
Are you busy?
Of course.
At night, if any emergency
happens to any of the patients,
I have to handle it at the first instance.
Why were you
hugging a man in the lift?
The test result of the medicine is out.
I know.
It's Chinese medicine
produced by 3D printing technology.
Zhang Yi Chi told you that?
No, it's Zhuo Ran.
Zhuo Ran told you about it?
He told his assistant to get the medicine.
His assistant got confused.
-So, he's the one who gave it to Mi Gu?
-Yes.
However, he didn't know that
his assistant made a mistake.
Was that his explanation?
I believe that it's the truth.
Otherwise, he wouldn't
have had come to to see me
at the first instance.
Did he know that
I was testing the medicine?
I didn't tell him anything.
How about Mi Gu?
I'm not sure of that.
He's...
trying to get us before we get him.
It's just an accident.
You don't have to come down
on him too hard.
Accident?
Of course it's an accident.
Otherwise,
why would Zhuo Ran harm me?
The medicine was for me.
He didn't know that.
How did he know
that you have the medicine?
How did he know?
For a very long time
after he left,
I could only fall asleep
with the help of drugs.
When I had insomnia,
I sent many emails to him.
In some emails, I scolded him.
In some, I begged of him.
He didn't reply any of the emails.
He didn't reply
but I think he knew
what was going on with me.
Therefore, when he came back,
he worried that I got agitated.
He told Mi Gu to keep a close watch on me
just in case.
As a result,
he accidentally discovered the medicine.
Trust me, Liang Mu Ze.
Zhuo Ran wouldn't harm me.
There's no reason for him
to make things personal against you too.
This is just
an odd coincidence.
In short,
I'm sorry for this incident.
If you get mad at me or hate me for that,
I can totally understand it.
However, I can't doubt my friend.
This is my principle
when it comes to dealing with people.
Are both of you just friends?
Liang Mu Ze, what do you mean?
There's an eight year gap.
Are you sure you still know him well?
Also, how old are you?
Running away from home
was a trick I used when I was young.
You can't be using the same trick
all the time.
It'll become ineffective.
Think like an adult.
You may fight me or mess around
but you're not allowed
to run away from home.
Got it?
You just want me to stay home
and take care of your cousin.
That's right.
[Zhuo Ran didn't have a gun with him.]
[The meeting concluded successfully.]
[I'm back to the camp.]
Zhuo Ran switched my medicine.
It's not a coincidence for sure.
Something must be wrong with him.
Keep a close watch on him.
What's wrong?
Professor Xia is receiving
physiotherapy treatment. It's ending soon.
Tang Lin wants us to wait for him.
Zhuo Ran.
Officer Liang.
Why did you attend the medical forum?
What's wrong?
Are you going to question me again
like those police officers?
At that moment, you behaved
as if you're fully prepared.
It's all about upbringing.
I must protect a lady
who was assaulted by a violent guy.
How about changing away my medicine?
Who were you trying to protect? Xia Chu?
It was me.
I'm asking you a question.
I'm sorry.
What happened?
Xia Chu doesn't need your protection.
Stay away from her.
Can you stay by her side
twenty-four hours a day?
When I am by her side,
what can you do for her
being in the military camp?
Try me.
Who is he?
Why did he mention about Xia Chu?
Do they know each other?
Professor Xia.
He
is Liang Mu Ze.
He's an officer with
the Special Forces Brigade.
He's just an uncultured person
who is not good at
controlling his emotion.
It seems that he's one of
Xia Chu's admirers too.
Rao Zhi, finally he said something.
He wants to see you.
Have you thought it through?
Are you their leader?
Yes.
Leader.
No, I mean Chief.
I really had no idea that
there were many other things in the car.
[I trust you.]
[But would the person who met you
believe you?]
No, Chief.
Please believe me.
I accepted a job on the internet.
I was told to get a new car
when I reached there.
That lad didn't escape, did he?
What do you think?
Not only did he not escape,
he sold you out.
He said you betrayed him.
He's talking nonsense.
[I get nothing if I betray him.]
[Betraying him]
is no different than betraying myself.
Fine.
I'm no stranger to people like you.
Hurry up.
Tell me everything that you know.
Listen, Chief.
I'm
always unlucky.
You know what?
I ran into a silly lady.
That lady...
You'd better contact her parents
as soon as possible.
That young lady is crazy.
Something is truly wrong with her.
I'm worried about her.
When her illness strikes,
in just a split second,
she may destroy her whole family.
She always...
You don't have to worry
about that young lady.
You'd better worry about yourself.
Okay, got it.
If I come clean,
will you protect me?
You're not in the position to negotiate.
We'll ensure your safety.
Answering all the questions honestly
is the best way to save yourself.
The cross-border crimes
is unique.
The criminal knew that
we wouldn't conduct security check
on the VIP's car.
They filled the door
and other compartments
in two identical commercial vehicles
with gold and drugs.
They intended
to get the transaction done in a fast way
by exchanging cars.
According to Liu Zheng Min,
the real owner of the sapphire
is someone by the name of Old Master.
He's the one
who made Liu Zheng Min
took a photo of the sapphire.
In the name of Old Master,
he also transferred the sapphire
to the deceased in the bungalow,
Sang Kun.
Sang Kun
is kind of a big shot.
Under his financial aid, T4
developed along the way.
However, in recent years,
he's down with kidney failure.
As such, T4
has been controlled by
Old Master who has the real power.
As for him,
he's been
looking for a kidney for transplant.
Not long ago, the kidnapping case
that happened to
the Isaia Joint Medical Team
is also related to him.
His murder
is most likely a result of
the internal conflict in T4.
Judging from the current situation,
we're unable to ascertain
the identity of Old Master.
Liu Zheng Min also said that
he's never seen Old Master.
He always
contacted him through a middle person
on City of Desire.
Middle person?
Was it the person who met with him today?
No.
That person is Gui's lackey.
According to Liu Zheng Min's statement,
the person who was supposed
to meet up with him for transaction
was Sang Kun's younger brother,
Bai Sen, whose nickname is Gui.
Last year,
when Gui came to China
to find a cure for his elder brother,
both of them met once.
According to Liu Zheng Min's description
and the surveillance recording
at the scene,
we did a comparison.
We've targeted the suspect
who was blended in with the guests,
Gui.
He disguised as Ba Song.
He pretended to be a legal representative
of a foreign listed company
as a cover.
He was invited to attend
the medical forum.
Why did he send his lackey
to meet Xiong
but he attended the forum instead?
What was his plan?
Xiong is unsure of his plan.
It looks like
only when we find Gui
can we find out more.
At the nearby street of the scene,
we stopped a Chevrolet car
which was ferrying Gui.
We only found a severely injured driver.
He was announced dead
not long after he reached the hospital.
As for Gui's whereabouts,
we're still locating him.
Did the sniper who was hiding
in the residential area
find any clues?
We contacted the management department
to get the surveillance recording
and we found that only the recording
of the said building had gone missing.
We could only leave it to
the technology department
to recover the recording.
At the same time,
we tried to find out
the relevant information
by interviewing the residents.
However, the progress is slow.
We're unable to ascertain his identity
at the moment.
All right, let me
explain the coming work arrangements.
For Team A,
continue locating Gui's whereabouts.
You may send the relevant information
to the Command Center.
Ask them to look out for us too.
Got it.
Team B,
continue look out for the hidden clues
on City of Desire.
Find out if Gui and the sniper
share any form of contact.
Team C,
follow up with Zhuo Ran, the man
who was suspected of possessing a gun.
No doubt we didn't find
any gun on him,
but taking into consideration
there was a time gap,
he's most likely
transferred the gun to somewhere else.
Besides that,
based on the surveillance recording
at the scene,
when Gui saw Zhuo Ran,
he behaved strangely.
Hence,
we must find out his background.
Make sure you leave no stone unturned.
-Got it?
-Yes.
Slow down.
I live next door.
Let me know if anything.
Okay.
Thank you for your help.
Rest early.
Mi Gu.
The interview...
It's okay, Mr Xia.
We can talk about it when you feel better.
That's great.
Let me...
Rest early.
Mr Zhuo.
Please send Mi Gu off.
It's okay. I should do that.
This is my name card.
When Professor Xia is in Ningjiang
and if he needs anything,
he may contact me at any time.
Thank you.
If it weren't for you,
god knows how huge of a mess
that madman would make.
I'm glad that everyone is safe.
Let's go.
Sure, let me get ready
for tomorrow's forum.
I'll see you off.
Goodbye.
Zhuo Ran.
I'm home.
You should go up.
Hold on.
I've something to return to you.
Is this yours?
Don't you think you need to explain to me?
I'm exhausted, Mi Gu.
I'm exhausted too.
I was on tenterhooks at the hospital.
I wanted to ask you
but I worried that someone
might find out about it.
Where did it come from?
Why did you keep a gun with you?
It's fake.
It's just a toy.
Then why didn't you inform me before hand?
It was an emergency.
I did it subconsciously.
You knew that the police officers
would conduct a search on you.
I only know that all the police officers
in the world are the same.
If they found out that
I brought a toy gun with me,
they would interrogate me non-stop
and then choose to believe
what they want to believe.
I didn't want to put myself in trouble.
What if I got myself into trouble?
If that ever happened,
I would explain to them.
You hugged me
just to hide the gun
and avoid the risk, right?
Am I right, Zhuo Ran?
No.
At that moment,
I wanted to give you some comfort.
I'm going upstairs.
Have you found Gui?
You're asking me?
He ran away under your nose.
Why are you asking me?
The situation was a chaos.
It was chaotic, yes.
You've been making errors
in the past few missions.
Don't tell me it's an accident.
What else could it be?
What do you think it is?
Don't think that you can
check and balance Old Master
by releasing Gui.
If you don't want your mum...
Don't talk about my mum!
For your mum's sake,
you'd better stop playing tricks!
Old Master.
[Are you done with Gui?]
I'm sorry.
[You know that I hate apologies the most.]
I know.
However,
though Gui escaped,
we finally got to meet Xia Guang Yuan.
He's changed his mind about me
due to the incident.
Hence,
it's not completely a bust.
What went wrong in the process?
Liang Mu Ze.
Who?
[He's the Chinese military officer]
who I had bugs installed at his place.
Xia Chu is living at his place.
They're quite close.
Because of him,
Gui escaped.
[His presence has made my attempt]
[to approach Xia Chu even harder.]
I wanted to kill him before
but I failed.
He's a Special Forces soldier
and he usually live in the military camp.
It's difficult to go near him.
Even if I get to approach him,
it would be
too risky
to take action in China.
Unless...
[Unless what?]
Unless we can find a chance
to end him
when he receives training abroad.
The difficulty
[will be much lower.]
End him abroad?
Zhuo Ran.
[You're really something.]
Just by one line,
you passed the problem to me.
You can send Long Yi.
Are you trying to get rid of me?
You serve no purpose here.
[Enough.]
[Your mission]
[is to look for Gui
and nail Xia Guang Yuan.]
As for Liang Mu Ze who may spoil our plan,
send his particulars to me.
Got it.
What should we do?
It's not difficult to trace Gui.
It's easy for you to say.
Keep a close eye on
the police and Xia Guang Yuan.
The police are looking for him
and he's looking for Xia Guang Yuan.
We'll find something eventually.
What on earth is this?
Who is she?
Meet each other.
She's Liang Mu Ze's cousin.
Her name is Liang Shao Xue.
Be careful.
Don't let her crush you to death.
This is my place!
Look after her. I need to take a rest.
Please don't leave.
Where is this?
What's wrong?
It has nothing to do with me.
Where is this?
This...
This is Liang Mu Ze's place.
How is it possible?
No way Mu Ze has a pet cat.
It licked my face!
Don't be dramatic.
Calm down.
It's early in the morning.
Don't make a ruckus.
Don't irritate our neighbour
or they may report it to the police.
Leave me alone!
I'm about to explode!
Calm down.
You're completely awake.
If I hadn't woken up,
I might have been sold off
without knowing it.
Do you remember
yesterday, in the afternoon,
you suddenly fell asleep
at the corridor in the hospital?
Falling asleep is normal.
I was dealing with jet lag.
I didn't say that it's abnormal.
I just want to remind you that
when you were in a deep sleep,
it was me
who brought you home
despite being completely
burnt out after a night shift.
Not only did you not thank me,
you're dubious of me.
You suspected that I would sell you off!
Fine, it's okay.
You can question me all you want.
But now,
I beg of you.
Will you keep quiet
and let me take a nap?
That's because I need to work
in the afternoon.
Okay?
Repeat!
-What?
-Repeat
the last word.
I said so many things.
The last...
What did I say?
I said I need to work in the afternoon.
Okay?
OK?
What should I do? I forgot about OK!
How could I forgot OK?
My OK!
Report.
Come in.
Brigade Commander.
The police have forwarded the summary
of the action to me.
I'm waiting for
a detailed report from you.
Something happened in the process.
However, it went on smoothly in general.
Sure, it's okay.
Later,
please submit a report in detail.
By the way,
have an internal meeting
with everyone who took part in the action
to conclude the matter.
Yes.
Also,
I received instruction
from the higher authorities
to send a team to
the Central Asian military training
which will be held by Willick
at the end of the month.
End of the month?
We don't have much time.
You'll be leading the team
during the training camp.
How long will it take?
It's tentatively scheduled for a week.
However,
it depends on the training progress.
Do you have any question?
No.
Get ready.
Military reform is just around the corner.
This is a rare opportunity.
Don't make any mistake.
Yes, sir.
[Can you stay by her side]
[twenty-four hours a day?]
[When I am by her side,]
[what can you do for her]
[being in the military camp?]
Brigade Commander
wants me to check on you.
Why?
He thinks that you're not in a good mood
after executing the mission.
It turns out that
Xia Chu is also suffering from insomnia.
Why can't she fall asleep?
It's because of her first love.
You...
Are you in a bad mood?
No.
I'm worried.
I think this guy
has some hidden agendas.
Hello.
[Old Master.]
[The military]
[invited the special forces of China
for a training camp.]
[It seems that]
[the person who you're interested in]
[is in the participant list.]
[I've sent you his particulars
through email.]
You may take a look.
Got it.
Judging from the X-ray,
it's aortic regurgitation.
You can't wait
any longer.
Many problems will manifest as time pass.
Therefore, I suggest that
you undergo the surgery
as soon as possible.
I can't do that, doctor.
I'm really occupied at work.
I can't make it.
Let me be frank.
You will have to undergo the surgery
sooner or later.
It's better to do it early.
I think my body is doing fine.
It's okay.
Why are you here if everything is okay?
Why do you come to me if you're okay?
I'm busy.
Don't take up my time for nothing.
Doctor, don't be mad.
I'm not mad.
It's your body.
You should think for yourself.
I know. How about this?
Please prescribe some medicine for me.
I'll start with taking medicine.
What do you think?
Please do me a favour.
Thank you. Please do me a favour.
Don't stretch yourself thin.
If you are down with flu or diarrhoea,
you must seek medical help
soonest the possible.
Sure.
If your heart contracted a virus,
it would become a serious problem.
-Okay.
-Bear it in mind.
Okay.
Thank you, doctor.
That's all for today. Come again tomorrow.
Dr Zhang, it's me.
It's you.
Yes.
Where is Xiao Jun?
Xiao Jun has gone to school.
I'm out for groceries shopping.
That's why I brought you
some steamed cakes which I just made.
Try it.
Great.
I was thinking
what I should have for lunch.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I should be the one to thank you.
Xiao Jun recovered well after the surgery.
Therefore,
I'm here to thank you officially.
Don't do that.
What are you doing?
You don't have to do that.
Well...
I'll not take up your time.
Enjoy the food.
Sure, thank you.
I'm leaving.
-Goodbye.
-Sure.
Chen Meng Zhen.
My name is Zhang Yi Chi.
The next time we meet each other,
you may address me by my first name.
You're being so polite all the time.
You sound distant.
We're almost the same age.
The way you address me
makes me sound old.
Okay, I got it now.
-I'll go now.
-Goodbye.
Goodbye.