(All characters, locations, organizations, religions,)
(and incidents in this drama are fictional.)
(Episode 11)
Tell me everything.
Tell me, Dong Kyung.
I want to live.
I really...
I really, really want to live.
I...
I want to live with you, Sun Kyung,
my aunt, Ji Na,
and everyone else that I love.
I really do.
I really want...
I want to live so badly.
Me too.
Me too, Dong Kyung.
I want to be alive...
so I can...
So I can die with you.
When Sun Kyung and I were young,
he asked me where our parents had gone.
I told him that they were up there.
But when he asked me why they had left,
I had nothing to tell him.
So one day, I sat here to no end.
When I kept staring at the sky, I realized it.
We all go back to where we came from.
People say that our bodies come from the stars...
because all the energy that make up our bodies is from the stars.
So when we go back, deeper and deeper into the past,
we basically originate from the same place.
We all go back to the same place...
and meet there again.
So we will never be apart.
Hey!
Bring Lee Hyun here right now.
Make her apologize.
Where's Mr. Cha?
Mr. Cha!
- Where is he? He should be working. - He's working outside the office.
Call him.
Gosh.
I heard that you made the situation worse.
He was about to go and see a plastic surgeon.
I barely managed to stop him.
- Why did you do that? - Why did I...
Hey, our company will go bankrupt with him.
If losing a writer would bankrupt the company,
the company was bound to fail then.
Hey!
"Hey." "You." "That." "This."
I told you not to address people like that.
Anyway, call Lee Hyun right now.
If she can't apologize, pay for the laptop, at least.
Just deduct it from my pay.
Your pay?
Gosh. You don't even make that much money. It's chicken feed.
So you know that what you pay me is chicken feed.
You think this job is easy because you get paid...
every month without doing so much.
Go check out the job market.
There's a line of people...
who are willing to work for your chicken feed.
Seriously. Kids these days have no love for their company.
You should treat the company as yours...
and work as if you're running your own business.
You should be frugal like you are with your own money.
How can I treat it as my company when it's not?
You're not successful because of that attitude.
Mr. Cha.
Don't you want to be more like me?
Do you want to end your life after earning...
that chicken feed all your life?
Gosh. I can't put up with this ridiculous job.
- What? - I can't put up with this dumb job.
I'm sure you know what I mean by that.
I'm quitting.
Deduct the laptop price from my severance pay.
My gosh. Your severance pay isn't even that much.
Hey. I've lived my life 10 more years than you.
I've seen a lot of guys...
ruining their lives because of their petty pride.
Since you're the team leader here,
you must think other companies would hire you.
Listen, young man. The world out there is a tough place.
You have a long way of saying that you're a dinosaur.
Hey, Cha Joo Ik.
Are you really quitting?
What are you going to do with your life then?
Seriously. People might think your dad owns several buildings.
What? How did you know that?
What?
My dad owns buildings.
This building, too.
Ji Na came here on her school trip.
Remember the hotel we passed by on our way here?
That's where she stayed.
I was doing my side job to make some pocket money.
What was the side job?
It was just a job.
It was a way to make memories when I was in school.
Gosh. It was a good side job.
I had never seen anyone jump over the wall...
as cool as she did.
She said that she liked me when we first met.
What did she like about you?
She liked me for my bubbly personality.
Anyway, we exchanged numbers and stayed in touch.
And she told me to apply to her school.
But don't you know how smart I am?
And I got into her school just like that.
Our food is here.
This is great.
It looks delicious. Thank you for the food.
Look at you eat.
Do you know how many times Sun Kyung changed his mind...
on what he wanted to become?
One day, he wants to become this.
The next day, he wants to become something else.
But you know what's funny? He means it every time.
And in the end, I'm the one who deals with it.
Sun Kyung would go to internet cafes after telling me he's off to study.
My job was to go around looking for him.
It's like everyone in your family either chases or gets chased.
The one getting chased always ends up getting caught.
You saw how my aunt caught me by my collar, right?
As for me, I used to drag Sun Kyung by his ear.
Hello!
Hi.
What?
It's nothing.
When my aunt and uncle were dating,
they ran into Sun Kyung on a path like this.
Sun Kyung called me that day...
and cried his eyes out saying we lost our aunt forever.
So do you know what I did?
I looked for a job.
I figured I should hurry up and start making money...
in order to help my aunt get married quickly.
I started working at the publishing company...
because they called me first.
But I had no idea I'd end up working there for so long.
What does your earning money...
have anything to do with your aunt getting married?
I had to have the ability to earn money...
so my aunt would feel at ease and live her own life...
thinking I was all grown up.
Otherwise, she would've spent her entire life looking after us.
So tell me. Are you all grown up?
No, I'm still growing up.
I'm no longer alone.
I once saw a dolphin here.
Later on, I found out it was an Indo-Pacific bottlenose dolphin.
They're an endangered species. Isn't that sad?
I can't say that's not my fault,
but you humans need to work on it too.
Yes, you're right. It's our fault.
But for your information, I wasn't blaming you.
Why are you laughing?
Because I find it funny.
What's so funny?
You.
What's so funny about me?
What's funny about me?
We're heading somewhere together.
As we sympathize with and love each other.
We're in this together.
Is something bothering you?
How about a bet?
The winner gets to ask for whatever he wants from the other person.
- What do you want? - Your car.
Or...
maybe something else.
Sure. Let's do it.
Tell me.
What do you want?
I'll save it.
I'll tell you once there's something I want.
Why? Don't you want anything from me yet?
You asked for my car, right?
You can have it.
Don't give it to me like you're being nice.
I'm going to win it.
I'll save it.
I'll tell you once there's something I want.
Welcome...
Let's go on a date.
- What? - Let's go on three dates.
I want to know if these are just lingering feelings...
or if I actually still like you.
Let's decide after three dates.
- Sure. - Don't ever call me first.
And don't visit without calling.
Okay.
I'll be the one to call, so wait until I do.
Okay, I will.
- It might take some time. - I'll still wait.
I'm going to go now.
I'm going to wait, okay?
- Hello? - I just asked Hyun Kyu...
to go on a date with me.
Let's cancel our contract.
Don't worry. You won't have to pay a penalty.
I'm guessing you won't want to see me again.
You won't ever see me again because of work.
No.
Why?
Because I want my novel to fall into the top 10.
Is that the only reason?
Yes.
Then either email me or text me.
If you break our contract,
I'm going to tell Hyun Kyu that you kissed me.
- Can you really do that? - Do you think I won't be able to?
I don't think you can.
If you can, go ahead and tell him.
Seriously.
He's so annoying.
Make sure you don't get exposed to these elements.
What is it?
What?
I'm coming. Fine. I'll be right there.
My aunt left my place as is.
She says I need a place to return to.
I didn't know I'd end up coming here with you though.
I have a wish.
A wish?
- My birthday wish. - That's...
Not the one I made then. Something else.
- Forgive me. - For what?
I told them that you were here.
I thought they'd worry.
Dong Kyung!
What? Let go!
Darn it.
Auntie.
Let's eat. I'm hungry.
I asked you out here because I wanted to talk to you.
I think I must be a real coward.
Jeju is beautiful. Look at the sea.
I couldn't even run away for real.
All I did was hurt everyone.
This is where I got my family.
I don't know what to do.
If I live, he dies.
If I save him, we all die.
What should I do?
What do I do?
"What do I do?"
Don't worry. We're family.
I want you to think of me as family and lean on me.
- Family? - Yes, family.
I know how you feel.
Let me do my best to find a great hospital.
The best option was for me to die by myself.
That was why I came here.
But I can't not love, Kevin.
I love you too, Dong Kyung.
I love everything Soo loves.
Just hang in there. Everything is going to be better.
Love.
Yes. That's what scares me.
My love is too burdensome.
You're welcome.
Family doesn't have to say, "Thank you."
"I love you" is enough.
Doctor.
Would you get me the onions from those groceries over there?
Wash them over here.
Thank you...
for telling me.
I thought you'd worry.
Dong Kyung was worried too.
- She was? - All day long,
she talked about her aunt, brother, and Ji Na.
Know something? My motto in life is "Go all in."
Only our faces were the same.
My sister and I had opposite personalities.
It was like she gave me all the bad temper.
She was calm and soft.
When I heard that she had died,
I felt like I lost half of me.
My other half left them to me.
How could I not go all in?
Naturally, I lived for them.
But she...
Dong Kyung was like that ever since she was a child.
She won't tell me if she's struggling.
She always went somewhere and hid.
Then I'd have to go look for her.
Whenever I found her, she was sitting by the sea.
It was heartbreaking.
She acted like she had no home.
I guess she has a home now.
Given how she came back here.
I'm glad she doesn't look like she's in pain.
Her heart is the problem, not her body.
Keep a close eye on her.
You know how good she is at pretending to be okay.
Why is she so good at pretending to be fine?
That was her all her life.
She hates being a burden on other people,
so she's always anxious.
That must be why she came here.
So she wouldn't burden us.
Stop crying.
I'm not crying. The wind is cold, that's why.
I tear up when the wind is cold.
I was born this way.
Hello, Mr. Lee.
Yes, I saw my sister.
I'm sorry for calling out all of a sudden.
The beans?
They're arriving in the morning.
Yes. Good night, boss.
Boss? Do you have a job?
Yes, at a cafe.
A cafe?
Every schmo has a cafe nowadays.
It's always about a guy when you get angry like this.
Remember that guy I said I would kill?
I saw him again recently.
He owns a cafe.
I'm so jealous. I want to run a cafe too.
- He wants to get back together. - Oh my gosh.
- So I said okay. - Oh my gosh.
I'm so annoyed.
I wanted to kill him,
but when I saw his smile, my heart just melted.
That's good.
Rage is never good for you.
But the problem is...
there's another guy I want to kill.
- Another guy? - And they know each other.
They even live together, but he didn't tell me.
He was totally toying with me, right?
Gosh, that's confusing.
So you decided to date the guy you originally wanted to kill.
And then, there's another guy you want to kill. Is that it?
Yes.
What? Does it mean you like the guy?
- Which guy? - The second guy.
No. I decided to date the first guy.
Why are you dating the 1st guy when you like the 2nd guy?
You're so stupid. You got low scores on language art, right?
What are you talking about? You're the fool here.
When you like someone, you say you want to kill that guy.
You wanted to kill the first guy. That's in the past tense.
You want to kill the second guy now. That's the present tense.
Gosh.
Stop talking nonsense. And bring the side dishes.
Why isn't this coming off?
Hey. It's snowing!
It's snowing!
It's so beautiful.
Do you want to make a snowman?
Let's make a snowman. I want to make a snowman!
I ran away to this place because I wanted to leave everyone.
But it turned out I wasn't running away.
I thought I ran away from you guys, but once I got here,
I had everything I loved right here.
So...
I really missed all of you.
You need the experience to run away from your family.
You always live your life,
ready to tackle the world. You're never going to be that type.
I can't run away with you.
But I'll always be on your side when you're tackling the world.
By the way, this place looks amazing.
I don't remember the last time I'd been on Jeju Island.
There's no one here because it's a weekday. I love it here.
This is why people love to be freelancers or unemployed.
Let's continue our friendship until our hair turns gray...
and travel around the world when other people are working.
What? Are you telling me I should be unemployed...
for the rest of my life?
Just spend money like water.
I'll make money like a slave.
Take out your phone.
The weather is amazing. Let's take a photo.
Sure.
All right. You can take the photo.
Let me see.
By the way, what happened the other day?
What do you mean?
You left after getting a call.
Oh, that? It's nothing.
I cursed him out, broke the laptop, and scared him a bit.
What?
That jerk, Jijo King, accused me of plagiarizing his stuff.
It's fine. I handled it.
By the way, the laptop was Mr. Cha's.
Ji Na.
Do you like Mr. Cha?
What?
Do you think I'm crazy? I'm dating Lee Hyun Kyu again.
What? Lee Hyun Kyu? The Lee Hyun Kyu I know?
Do you know what's crazier?
He works at the cafe on the first floor of your company building.
Who knew he would be so close?
Are you talking about the handsome cafe owner?
The guy who could be in movies and whose smile lights up the room?
I guess he is handsome.
Ji Na, how are you going to fix this?
You like Mr. Cha.
No, I don't!
It's obvious!
Goodness.
Are you going somewhere?
- I'll see you inside. - Okay.
I'll be back.
Where are you going?
The hospital.
Something happened to her, right?
I won't take long. I'll be back soon. Wait for me.
Let me go with you.
No. You should go first.
I'll leave right after you. I'll be with you.
You're here.
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm okay.
Everything is predetermined.
I remembered why I didn't want to be in love.
Love brings pain.
When your loved ones are gone,
the pain is unbearable.
Creations by humans are indeed great.
Sins and love...
always turn the world upside down.
I shouldn't have fallen in love with anyone.
It's okay. Everything is okay.
I will be born again.
What should I do?
I'm sure you know.
Don't pretend to be clueless. Just tell me.
Deities are meant to live for humanity.
That's the purpose behind their birth.
They live for the people...
and leave the world for the people.
That's our duty.
What are you doing?
Consoling you.
Just like how you consoled me.
Is it bad?
She doesn't have much time left.
It's okay.
This always happened.
Really? What do you want for dinner?
Your dad's calling.
- Sweetheart! - Mom!
Oh, dear.
Thank you. Thank you.
Are you...
- allowed to do that kind of stuff? - No.
What?
I'm not allowed, but I couldn't help it...
because you were watching.
Sometimes, I find myself portraying you in things.
Now that I love you, I sometimes find myself...
pitying humans...
and loving them.
I think I finally understand...
why she loves humans so much.
(Incoming call, Unknown Number)
- Hello? - You're finally picking up.
Dong Kyung, where are you right now?
Mr. Park?
I want you at the office right now.
If you don't come, I'm going to sue Lee Hyun.
Should I keep up what I've been doing?
- Just say the word. - No.
This one's mine.
I'll deal with him myself.
Follow me.
Can you help me just this once?
What are you doing?
Get off me.
Please. I'm dying here.
Will you please let go first?
I mean, now that you and Mr. Cha are both gone,
none of the writers are willing to renew their contracts.
This is really killing me.
Why are you asking me for help?
This is all your fault.
You must've really convinced all those writers...
What? What did you just say?
No, I mean...
You must've worked really hard...
seeing that they're all acting that way.
No one wants to work with a bad guy.
It's like that wherever you go.
- I bet the writers have had enough. - Of course.
I wasn't able to take your side that day...
because I was too flustered.
But I was always on your side.
It's so nice to see you again.
How's your health?
Is everything okay?
I knew he'd get himself in trouble one day.
This is how hard it is to make a living, Dong Kyung.
There are people I need to take care of...
regardless of how much I hate him.
You have no idea how hard it is for me to humor him.
Think of those guys out there.
At this rate, I won't even be able to give them their monthly pay.
If my company goes bankrupt, the same will happen to them.
They're still young. Don't try to ruin their lives, too.
You're right. I'm the bad guy.
Dong Kyung. Dong Kyung.
- My gosh. - Okay.
I'm begging you. Please do me a favor.
Please meet up with Mr. Cha.
Meet up with him just this once and try to convince him.
I get that you can't work here anymore...
because of your health.
But that's not the case for Mr. Cha.
If you refuse to cooperate,
I'll have no choice but to sue Lee Hyun.
Sue her for what?
For damaging our property and obstructing our business.
You know I'm a man who keeps his word, right?
I mean, how...
How do you expect me...
to meet a guy who quit?
Mr. Cha...
Mr. Cha has always been near us.
What?
Up there. That's where he lives.
Mr. Cha...
is the landlord's son.
Can I have some money?
Money? Why?
I got myself in trouble. I need to deal with it.
I didn't buy new golf clubs to beat you with them.
I'll pay you back once I succeed.
How are you going to succeed?
How much are you asking for?
I'm going to start a company.
Why would you start a company?
Then who's going to take care of that building?
I'll continue to take care of it.
The company will be like a hobby for me.
You punk. Who starts a company for fun?
It won't be as expensive as your hobby,
and it'll surely make more money.
You never lose an argument.
How much are you going to pay in interest?
Why would you ask your own son for interest?
Then ask the bank for money.
Okay, fine.
I'll pay you enough interest.
Now we're talking.
If only you were as good of a businessman as Hyun Kyu...
By the way, why did he behave like that on that day?
- What day? - The day he suddenly...
hugged me and called me "Dad".
Oh, he did it to protect me.
My gosh.
Having taken care of him must be paying off.
I shouldn't have taken such good care of him
Why?
Is he rude to you now that he's all grown up?
Well...
He doesn't make things easy.
That means he's ready to compete with you.
Go ahead.
(Tak Dong Kyung)
Welcome.
Unbelievable.
So this is why you always came to work early...
and went home late.
Are you talking to yourself, or are you omitting honorifics now?
I must say, this is a scary world.
I guess I really can't trust anyone.
This time, I can tell you're just omitting honorifics.
Are you really the landlord?
No, not me. My dad is.
Then is the sports car parked in the basement...
- also yours? - Yes.
Does your father own buildings other than this one?
Yes.
This is the smallest one.
My brother and dad manage the rest.
If you're the landlord's son,
why did you work for a company that pays so little?
Because it was close to home.
How clever.
Why did you quit in the first place?
The same reason as yours. I couldn't take it.
You've been good at taking it.
You're right.
But I can't these days.
Why not? Because Mr. Park criticized Ji Na?
She told me everything.
I doubt she told you everything.
I guess there really was something as I suspected.
I guess she told you enough for you to suspect it.
So? What do you plan to do?
I'm going to start a company.
That's why I wanted to see you.
Recover quickly.
I'll make you a team leader if you come to me.
That wasn't my question.
Forget it.
Furthermore, I'm going to demand an insanely high salary.
I'll just give you a higher title. How about director?
No, thanks. I want a high salary.
What's your current salary?
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
You had your reasons.
I'll work even harder.
Is your sister doing better?
No.
But she will.
I'm sure.
Sis.
Are you Sun Kyung's sister?
I saw you several times before.
Why are you here? Did you come to see me?
I'm working hard.
He's a very good worker.
He works hard and...
It's fine. I was just passing by and dropped in.
I was just passing by.
Okay. Would you like some coffee? On the house.
Sure. Yes, please. Thank you.
Why didn't I realize?
Pardon?
What? Nothing.
I was wondering why I didn't realize...
how nice this cafe was.
What is it?
Here's your coffee. You like iced Americano, right?
You always got that.
You have a good memory.
Oh my.
Coffee made by people who studied abroad tastes different.
How did you know I studied abroad?
It smelled. I smell a runaway.
Oh dear. My mistake.
The coffee scents.
What's wrong with you?
Do you feel sick? Do you need a doctor?
Are you confusing your words?
I'm not sick. I'm fine.
The coffee woke me right up.
I heard that you used to swim.
Where did you hear about that?
Just from people who heard from people.
It wasn't me. I didn't tell her.
If you swim, are you good at submerging too?
Well... It's probably easier for me than regular people.
It's easier.
That must be why it's easy for you to submerge and disappear.
Pardon?
What do you think...
about people who ghost girlfriends to break up with them?
I think...
they are cowards...
Right? It's totally cowardly, isn't it?
Why do people do something so cowardly?
What's wrong with you?
Did Myul Mang ghost you?
No.
I was just passing by...
and dropped in,
so I'll go now.
What's wrong with you?
Why did you come?
Are you leaving? I'll see you again.
What's wrong with her?
Your sister seems fine.
Sure.
Ji Na. All you care about is looks.
I am stopping the series for personal reasons.
I'd like to thank all the viewers who read my story, flaws and all.
I'll see you again with a new story.
(Notice of Termination of Series)
I read all of your novels.
And you need one thing.
A new male character.
(Who said)
Who said first loves never work out?
Ji Woo was overcome with the desire...
to find the person who said that and kill him.
Although it wasn't his fault that her love failed,
that was what she wanted to do.
Because she couldn't kill her first love.
But then again,
she may not have the energy to kill him even if she met him.
Ji Woo was sitting, crying, in front of her first love's home...
for three hours.
(For three hours)
I can't.
"What?" The unfamiliar voice made her look up,
and a man with an equally unfamiliar face...
was standing in front of her.
The man that she saw with her blurred vision...
distorted by the rain and tears...
showed no emotion on his face and simply looked down at her.
I can't go in if you sit there like that.
Her first kiss with the man she first met...
tasted like a rain shower.
Ji Woo knew right then and there.
"I won't be able"...
"to avoid him"...
"or loving him."
Yes, I'm almost home.
Are you home?
No.
I was able to hold back and didn't commit murder.
My aunt?
She said she had to go somewhere, so she isn't coming over.
Really?
Seriously.
This reminds me of old times.
It wasn't that long ago.
It was quite recent.
Your problem is that you nitpick about everything I say.
You are such a mood killer.
I'm not nitpicking. I'm pointing out the truth.
You haven't changed. Not at all.
You were a real jerk back then too.
Why was I a jerk?
For a bunch of reasons.
But you were cute every once in a while.
Cute? Me?
I know you turned off the lights for me that night.
I always thought...
the darkness was scary and frightening.
But for the first time,
I realized that sometimes, kindness and consideration...
are dark.
You're wrong.
I turned them off because I liked the dark.
Hey. I said to stop killing the mood.
You're not even reading.
I flipped the page.
You're not reading, are you?
Want one?
I don't eat.
You pretend to though.
- Want me to play along? - Yes.
There's no one by that name.
That can't be.
I met with that doctor just a few days ago.
This is the list of neurosurgeons...
at our hospital.
Why isn't he on this list?
I'm positive.
My niece and I met with Dr. Lee Yoon Ho.
He said she was on the list of patients for the new drug.
You seem to be mistaken.
Why don't you talk to your niece?
That can't be.
I'm positive I spoke with him.
Soo, what's wrong?
I apologize.
Right now, there's nothing I can do for you.
What...
What?
That's not possible.
I definitely talked to him.
Why isn't he here?
Kevin, something is off.
I definitely...
I definitely saw him and talked to him here.
But how...
My gosh. That ghost must have been sighted again.
Excuse me?
There's a ghost roaming around this hospital.
- A ghost? - Yes.
This rumor has been going around for several years.
A lot of people had seen that doctor.
My guess is that people here are exhausted,
so it's easier to get bewitched by the ghost.
You should look for another hospital.
But I have no choice now.
What are you talking about? A ghost?
That's ridiculous.
If that's not it, you must've been conned.
So if you're the one who's been deceived,
those two must have been in on it together.
But you said she's your niece.
Why would she want to deceive you?
But is that possible to pull off at a big hospital like this?
The security guards must be watching.
Gosh. I'm telling you. It must've been the ghost.
Gosh.
What's wrong?
- What's wrong with you? - Doctor.
Doctor! We need help over here.
- What's wrong? - Are you okay?
I love this place because the moon is so big and bright.
- When it's the same moon. - Right.
Even when it's the same moon,
it looks a lot more beautiful from here.
If I were to be born again,
I want to be born as a moon like that.
You know, inanimate things like the sun, moon, stars, and wind.
They just exist instead of living.
I want to be one of those things in my next life.
Then, what would you be if you could go back?
If you could go back in time?
- I'm not sure. - Even if I go back in time,
I'll make the same decision.
Meeting you,
falling in love with you,
and walking out here like this.
I know. You probably won't make the same decision.
I don't have any regrets.
My world changed after getting to know you.
This...
I got this from the girl at the hospital.
She said everything inside this depends on my love.
She asked me if I was scared.
I was scared.
But...
I'm not scared anymore.
I'm not scared.
Not anymore.
Hello?
Aunt!
I'm fine. Don't make a fuss.
It was a stress-induced stomach cramp.
A stomach cramp? Does it hurt a lot?
Should I go outside and buy you some porridge?
Kevin didn't have any food either, right?
Tak Dong Kyung.
Yes?
I came to the hospital...
and heard something that didn't add up.
- Okay. - I want you to explain it.
I came back to meet with the doctor we met the other day.
But I was informed there was no such doctor here.
Then,
everything the doctor told me cannot be true.
- Well, Aunt... - I don't want to hear it.
Don't argue with me. Let's get you admitted.
Kevin will look for a new hospital.
Aunt.
The new hospital will be as good as this one.
We already booked an appointment. Go get admitted there.
- And get all the exams. - Aunt.
I will...
die even if I stay in the hospital.
How could you say that to me now?
I will...
die...
even if I get the surgery.
Why...
Why are you dying?
- Why are you dying? - Soo, take it easy.
Let's get you admitted to this hospital right now.
Please. Let's get you treated, Dong Kyung. Please?
Stay in the hospital.
You must get admitted now!
- Aunt. Aunt... - My gosh.
Are you okay?
Doctor!
Dong Kyung, please get admitted.
Let me check her first.
Aunt.
Right now, Soo needs...
to be stable.
Soo and Dong Kyung...
If you guys stay together, it won't be good.
Just...
Maybe, you should go somewhere and wait until she calms down.
And then, I'll call you. Okay?
I'm sorry, Dong Kyung.
(Registration, Payment, Admittance and Discharge)
This is way too hard.
Please help me.
Help me.
I don't know what to do.
There's no way to explain...
that I will die no matter what I try.
If I didn't know that... If I didn't know that would be my fate...
I'll help you.
Will you let me live?
No.
I can't do that.
That is your fate.
But...
I can change his fate and yours a bit.
I can remove you from his fate, and vice versa.
As if you had never met.
Then, you will die as fated...
without knowing anything.
Like any other patient, you'll get treated and try to get better.
You will slowly face your death.
You won't remember each other, and the contract will be void.
But instead, your choice...
won't make the world collapse or bring death to the one you love.
Will you choose to do that?
There's not much time.
Hurry.
You need to make a choice.
(Doom At Your Service)
I don't remember much.
It comes with the illness.
She knows nothing.
I want a clear answer.
- Will you take? - Or forget?
Or love on your own.
Dong Kyung.
Tell me what you did to me.
I didn't do anything to you. I did something to her.
Help me.
Who are you?