[English subtitles are available]
[My Dear Guardian]
[Episode 10]
I still remember
the time he was unconscious,
he kept calling out Xia Chu's name.
When a man doesn't have you in his heart,
there's no point pushing it.
I'm not pushing it.
I'm just trying to stop my own thoughts.
Xia Chu still doesn't know?
Here's an advice for you.
A friend's ex,
is like a used car
driven by your friend.
Avoid it at all cost.
It's too troublesome.
If you really want it,
then be honest with your friend upfront.
It'll save you both
from awkwardness in future.
I'm speaking from experience.
Miss Gu, the scenery shot is done.
I'll show you the sample video
once it's ready.
If there're further ideas,
we can discuss more specifically.
Sure.
Thanks, Dr Zhang.
-Thank you.
-Goodbye.
"A potential long-term partner."
Zhang Yi Chi, are you so desperate?
I'm single. Of course I am.
It's not like I cheat on my partner.
You're bringing this up again?
Are you going to hold onto this
for the rest of your life?
-Don't start with me.
-Hold on.
Your patient, Luo Xiao Jun
sent this postcard to the department.
I just saw it.
I'm willing to offer my help
to your charity project.
I have no say in that charity project.
Please think of something to help me out.
Won't you help me, please?
I'm applying for
an overseas graduate school.
A background in innovative
scientific research
will improve my chances by a lot.
Why are you asking my help for everything?
That's your problem.
I'm no longer obligated to help you.
You're the reason
I stayed here in the first place.
I don't even have a single friend here.
I have nobody to help me.
I don't know where to get help.
Fine.
I'll try to ask Director Chen later.
Thanks.
What are you doing?
She's insane.
I'm almost done.
I'll wait.
I mistook you for my colleague.
Xia Chu.
Are you feeling better?
Yes. I've recovered.
Why are you here then?
To sign a contract.
I just met up with Dr Zhang and his peers.
Are you free tonight?
No, I'm not. I've made arrangements
with my friend.
It's Mi Gu, the one the other day...
She's meeting Dr Zhang later.
Didn't she tell you?
Maybe she sent a message.
But I haven't read it yet.
So you're free tonight then?
I'm off to settle some matters now.
Wait...
What happened?
Let me take a look at it?
I have to get help from the
IT department.
So how is it?
Can all the information be retrieved?
No problem. It's almost done.
Great.
But why did this happen suddenly?
Maybe it was a heat dissipation problem.
Also,
try not to open too many pages at once.
After work,
remember to switch off the computer.
Got it.
Okay.
It's done?
Thanks.
I really appreciate it.
What do you plan to have for dinner?
I'm not done with my work yet.
I'll wait.
It's just dinner.
You'll have to eat after all, don't you?
Okay then.
Both your parents are in Dongan.
Your home is there too.
Why didn't you transfer
to the military hospital there?
After graduating from
military medical school,
I just went with the military order.
Or is it because
you know my home is in Ningjiang?
I've almost forgotten it.
I don't believe you.
There are many good things in this world.
After we've experienced them,
it's hard to forget.
For example,
grilled eel.
you and me.
Hi there.
Where's the classroom for twelfth grade?
That way. The third classroom
after you turn left.
-Thanks.
-You're welcome.
♫ I'd like to find out ♫
♫ If my mask of foolishness ♫
♫ Could deceive you ♫
♫ I'm putting on my best performance ♫
♫ Is it a little too cruel? ♫
♫ The game of adults ♫
♫ The moments of joy
along the way ♫
♫ Do not bring them up ♫
Thanks, Zhuo Ran.
You're welcome, Xia Chu.
♫ Whatever evidence ♫
♫ Requires no validation ♫
♫ It is our shared secret ♫
♫ Keeping it close to the heart ♫
♫ The embrace I long for ♫
♫ Comes up in my dreams often ♫
♫ If I endure the suffering ♫
♫ Will I no longer be afraid
of love's late arrival? ♫
[I waited very long for you that day.]
[I didn't dare drink too much water]
in case I missed you
if I went to the toilet.
I was afraid you couldn't find me
when you came back.
It's like the television dramas.
I didn't want to let you go that easily.
I waited until the shop closed,
but you never showed up.
And you never showed up since.
That won't happen again.
Xia Chu.
What makes you believe that
we have a future together?
Because you still care.
I'm over it.
If you really did,
you wouldn't have said those things.
Hi, my darlings.
I'm almost home.
I don't know why
I'm so easily tired these days.
Maybe it's my age.
Really?
When women feel tired,
that's when they want to get married?
I think I need sleep more than
I need a husband in my life.
I'm entering the lift.
The connection might be bad inside.
How are you guys doing lately?
Did you miss me?
Miss.
You dropped your phone.
Do you remember me?
No, I don't.
It's me.
The other day,
we met in an alley
behind the hotel.
The night you went jogging.
Do you recall?
You've mistaken me for someone else.
I fell in love with you at first sight.
How can I mistake you for somebody else?
Why don't we be friends?
I know you're Mi Gu.
You're 32 years old and
your Chinese zodiac is a dragon.
You're a psycho.
Am I right?
Help. Help!
Who are you? Get your hands off her.
Get away, you psycho.
-Get away.
-Stop hitting me.
Xia Chu.
Forget it.
What's happened? Who is he?
A psycho.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Feeling better now?
Drink with me.
I can't.
The hospital might call me anytime.
I'll have soda.
That one, please.
When did you come here?
Not too long ago.
I knocked but no one answered.
I also called but you didn't pick up.
I fell asleep waiting at the front door.
I'm sorry.
I was extremely busy today.
The shots that were done needed editing.
I get it.
-Workaholic.
-And that's coming from you?
Speak for yourself, Dr Xia.
I don't have that sort of
aesthetic capital like you do.
I can't afford to slack at all.
That's not true.
Such things are unreliable.
No matter how much aesthetic capital
one possesses,
it won't withstand the pull of gravity.
If I don't work hard now,
once I'm old and grey,
what can I survive on?
How was your date with Dr Zhang?
Zhuo Ran told me about it.
We just discussed about work over a meal.
It doesn't count as a date.
And you?
Did you have dinner with Zhuo Ran?
Do you still
have feelings for him?
We went for Japanese cuisine.
He knows what I like.
He knows I prefer
fresh ingredients,
plain dishes,
sweet and sour ones
and Ramune soda.
On the matter of food,
he knows all my preferences
very well.
That's great.
It would be if relationships are only
about three meals a day.
Isn't it so?
Don't our daily habits often times
make up the most important aspects
of a relationship?
But i think that sometimes
commitment is more important
than love itself.
Cheers, Mi Gu.
It doesn't matter if love ever comes,
I'm all good as long as you are here.
I am here.
I'll definitely be here.
[From tonight until tomorrow,]
[most coastal regions of Dongan]
[will be continuously hit
by heavy rainstorms.]
[Various areas will be affected
by the flooding.]
[Notice on the recruitment of volunteers
for disaster relief]
Thanks, Xia Chu.
Xia Chu.
Look at these cakes. Pick one first.
Xia Chu. I want this matcha cake.
It looks so cute.
Settle down.
We've got to ask her something.
What's this about?
"To Xia Chu and all medical officers
of the Cardio Surgery Department,
have a great working day.
Yours truly, Zhuo Ran."
Who is Zhuo Ran?
Xia Chu, who is this Zhuo Ran?
He even knows
everyone's palates.
Did you tell him?
It seems like
that military officer is out of the game.
Xia Chu.
We've received the desserts.
Everyone enjoyed it.
Thank you.
Director Zhang.
Isn't the participation voluntary?
I don't want to go.
This is your job.
If everyone doesn't want to go,
what should we do about it?
But why must it be me?
I'll tell you why.
Many times before, when our sister unit
requested medical security,
every resident doctor has all participated
on rotational basis,
except you.
Remember,
we've all got to give back eventually.
Give me the medical records for ward 9.
But I...
I'll go.
You want to go to the flood-plagued areas?
Yes.
Forget it.
Your leg...
It's healed completely.
I should let you know.
A patient with heart failure
from emergency department
will undergo heart transplant next week.
Moreover, it will be done by the director.
He said that
all resident doctors
can be present for on-site observation.
Listen.
This is a rare opportunity
even for our hospital.
Are you still sure you want to go?
I'm sure.
In peaceful times like this,
experiences similar to being a war doctor
is quite rare too.
Alright then.
Make two photocopies,
fill them up
and the both of you submit them
to administration.
No, wait.
Do I still have to go
even when she's going?
She's going out of enlightenment.
You're going because it's your duty.
Stop staring at me with those big eyes.
What bad luck.
Reflecting it back to you.
[Which flooded area did
your handsome landlord go?]
[Will you meet him there?]
I don't know.
He said nothing about it when he left.
But special forces like his
will usually be the first
to arrive on site
but but the last to leave.
They're the first line of defence
and the last as well.
They just leap to where danger is.
They must be super courageous then.
Yes, that's right.
[So Liang Mu Ze's insomnia]
[is pretty tough on him.]
Why does something sound off.
[What is it?]
When you talked about him before,
you'd say he's strange,
doesn't sleep and how psychotic that is.
When have I?
[You're denying? You did say that.]
Fine, I'm hanging up now.
I've got to pack.
Remember to come pick Er Miao up.
I'll be gone for quite some time.
I can't let it stay all alone at home.
Got it.
Hanging up now, bye.
Alright.
[Er Miao.]
[Should I bring Liang Mu Ze]
[some medicine to help him sleep?]
Let's do this.
If you meow twice, I'll bring it.
If you meow once, I won't.
You get to decide.
Hey, you have to meow twice.
Meow.
Alright then.
I'll get the medicine.
[You can do it, Liang Mu Ze.]
I'll take a head count.
We'll move out once everybody is here.
Has everyone arrived?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I'm late.
It's okay. You arrived just in time.
-Let's move out.
-Yes, sir.
To the left, march.
♫ Romance makes little things feel warm ♫
♫ Warmth softens even a stubborn heart ♫
♫ Heart is filled
with your little company everyday ♫
[Liang Mu Ze, where are you stationed at?]
♫ Can't miss a thing about you,
hence there is no regrets ♫
Are you okay?
How are you?
Here.
Hang in there.
How much longer till we reach?
Let me check.
Another 50 over kilometres to go.
What happened?
I've never done an operation yet.
I don't want to die.
Is everyone okay?
We're fine.
-What happened?
Are you okay?
I've cleaned your uniform
and placed it in the bus.
Have some water.
No, thanks.
If you have something to say,
just say it.
Stop pretending to be generous.
You stop pretending to be petty too.
Me?
At the moment of danger just now,
I heard you scream out
not wanting to die
because you haven't taken on
the operating table yet.
At that moment,
I decided to forgive
all your peculiar, selfish
and petty behaviours in the past.
It's because I know
you want to be a good doctor
like me.
Peculiar, selfish and petty?
Listen here, Xia Chu.
Just because I hugged you back there
doesn't mean that
you get to say all that to me.
I'll not accept that.
Why is it taking so long to change a tyre?
Do you need help, sir?
I can't change it. My tools won't work.
Then what should we do?
Stop.
Stop, stop. We need help!
Xia Chu.
We need help.
What's the matter?
Our tyre got punctured.
My tools can't repair it.
-Tian Yong.
-Yes, sir.
Get our men to help.
Yes, sir.
Grab the jack lift.
You had them come over to help?
You think I’m capable of that?
What's the matter?
Sir, are you okay? Where does it hurt?
Come over and help get him on the truck.
One, two, up.
His blood pressure has
plunged to 60/90mmHg.
Heartbeat is at 105.
You two are the only doctors
from the Cardiac Surgery Department.
Think about something.
What should we do?
I don't know.
How's it?
Can he be saved?
I said I don't know!
Close those blinds now.
Have your men block the road
to prevent further accidents.
His blood pressure is still falling.
Could it be myocardial ischaemia?
No, his heart rate indicated
a lot of blood in the pericardial cavity.
It could be acute haemopneumothorax.
-We can inject dopamine.
-No.
Dopamine and noradrenaline could increase
myocardial oxygen consumption.
You two have to give him an operation.
But I've never seen
this operation done before.
This remote place
has no signal at all.
What if we send him back
to the station first?
We'll figure it out after that.
He won't make it.
His pulse is already very weak.
You'll need to open his pericardial cavity
and identify the location of the bleeding.
Who's going to do it? Quickly now.
No, it can't be done here.
I'm just a resident doctor.
[After sedation, make a 5 to 6 mm
longitudinal incision]
[along the left border
of the Xiphoid process.]
You do it.
Sterilize her and prepare for surgery.
Yes.
This road is blocked.
Go that way.
That way.
[Disaster relief goods]
Have you found the location of bleeding?
Remove the excess blood.
The patient is in shock.
Quick, administer the
anti-shock treatment.
Suction.
I found the location of bleeding.
Get ready to stitch the wound.
Trust yourself. You can do it.
His blood pressure has risen.
-Tian Yong, push the van.
-Yes, sir.
Here, get it moving.
♫ I had a quick glance at your eyes ♫
♫ It could be the destiny
but it is not practical ♫
♫ Your expression popped up on my mind ♫
♫ I learn to face the music
instead of evading it ♫
I didn't mean to shout at you just now.
It's okay.
You sure?
Where's your jacket?
I think I left it in the bus.
Before I forget.
I got you a bottle of medicine.
Take it when you can't sleep.
But don't take more than one pill.
Take this.
Why?
Put it on.
I'm fine.
I have a long sleeve in my suitcase.
Where's the bag?
I think I left it in the bus too.
But someone will send it over soon.
Sir.
Arrangement for the wounded personnel
is done.
Take him back.
Yes, sir.
Team Thunder, all aboard.
Take care, Dr Xia.
Take care, Captain Liang.
♫ I am afraid that
I might lose you one day ♫
♫ Every minute, every second,
how do I resist? ♫
♫ I can't help but look forward
to your return ♫
♫ To relive the moment
my heart skipped a beat ♫
Hurry.
-Don't let go.
-Okay.
-Hang in there.
Hang in there.
Why are you back so late?
A patient suddenly had a high fever.
So I went over to check.
Keep it down. Everyone's asleep.
[Liang Mu Ze.]
[Where are you stationed at?]
[Take care.]
[Don't catch a cold.
Wait for me to come home.]
Left, right, left.
I'm coming.
Someone forgot his keys again,
I assume.
Xia.
Hi, Aunt Xia.
You are?
I'm Zhuo Ran.
Zhuo Ran?
Xia Chu asked me
to check on you and Uncle Xia.
Come in.
Have some water.
Thank you.
Xia Chu never mentioned you were coming.
I think she left in a hurry.
So she couldn't inform you in time.
Where did she go?
Her hospital formed a medical team
for the flood relief.
No wonder she didn't answer my calls
these days.
The calls never went through.
Rural areas tend to have bad signal.
Moreover, there's the heavy downpour too.
It's normal that the calls
can't get through.
Please don't worry yourselves too much.
You've always been in contact
with Xia Chu?
Yes.
I heard that you left for some time.
That's true.
My mother was sick.
During senior year of high school,
her condition worsened.
After that, a distant relative
introduced her to an overseas doctor.
I left in quite a hurry.
That's why I didn't manage
to properly say goodbye to Xia Chu.
How is your mother doing now?
She's dependent on medicine.
I'm sorry.
It must be hard to talk about.
No, it's fine.
In fact I've been keeping it inside
for quite sometime.
It's kind of a relief for me
to have shared it with you.
Anyway,
how are you and Uncle Xia doing?
We're both fine.
I read on the international news online
that Uncle Xia and his team
had some new research findings.
You don't seem too concerned
with Uncle Xia's work?
It's not that.
There are many people
who are concerned about his work.
For me, the real concern
is whether he has taken
his three meals everyday
or if he's eating well.
What more can a husband ask for
with such a loving wife?
Xia, when did you came home?
Last night.
I was afraid to wake you up.
So I slept in the study instead.
Look at you.
You haven't eaten, have you?
Don't worry.
I'm leaving soon.
So soon?
You spend a night home
just to leave again next morning?
Why come back in the first place?
I had to use the toilet.
What's wrong with saying that?
You know I'm very particular
with the toilet I use.
I had constipation for days.
Last night, I suddenly had an urge to go.
So I came home to give it a go.
Did it go well?
This is Xia Chu's friend, Zhuo Ran.
I meant the experiment.
I heard the conversation between you two.
Back then, my daughter shed
quite a lot of tears for you.
I'm sorry.
I won't let it happen again.
Thanks for visiting us.
If you're trying to impress Xia Chu
by going through us,
it probably won't work.
I'm going to wash up now.
Hopefully once I'm done,
you've already left
along with your gifts.
[Dongan University Parking Permit]
Xia.
Did you know that Xia Chu
went to the frontline
for the flood relief work?
Has that wild brat ever
told us anything?
But it's good for her too.
Good? I beg your pardon?
She's a military doctor.
It will give her
valuable field experience.
So she's a military doctor,
but not your daughter?
She's a single young lady.
Flood relief is dangerous work.
I can't ignore it.
I'll have to get my father
to transfer her back here.
She's just drifting from place to place
and it worries me.
He doesn't need to get involved
in my daughter's matter.
What are you talking about?
He's Xia Chu's grandpa
and your father-in-law.
But he was never fond of me.
I got it, Director Zhang.
Okay, got it.
Why haven't you left?
I needed to answer a phone call.
Professor Xia.
Can I be of any help?
I saw a few kids
running around with some scissors.
Where did they go?
My ride just arrived at the main entrance.
Are you heading back
to the research institute?
I'm on my way to the airport.
I can give you a ride.
It's hard to hail a cab at this hour.
What kind of job are you doing now?
3D printing.
I just signed a deal
with 109 Hospital
on the research and development
of using 3D printing technology
for medicine and organ printing.
Thank you for today.
You're welcome.
This is my business card.
Please take it.
It's unlikely that
we'll have any business dealings.
Please take it.
The applications of 3D printing
may exceed your imagination.
Thanks a lot.
[Xia Guang Yuan]
Make sure everything is sorted out well
before handing over to our colleagues
arriving in the afternoon.
Yes.
We're finally done
with this horrible place.
But, this horrible place turns out to be
an integral milestone
for Xia Chu's profession.
Isn't that right, Xia Chu?
Although I appreciate the chance
to act as a chief surgeon,
I'd rather hope
no one needs to suffer from it
in the first place.
A doctor must have a heart of a parent.
Well done.
I must get Zhang Yi Chi
to give you a big Red Flower badge.
I'm afraid Dr Zhang
does not have red flowers,
but only roses.
Request to enter, sir.
Please enter.
Are you feeling unwell?
Not me, doctor.
I'm here to collect some medicine.
You're from the Special Force Brigade?
I've been expecting you for some time now.
Xia Chu.
Pass him those cold medicine.
Yes.
Thank you, Dr Xia.
Did someone catch a cold?
It's not our captain.
Few of our men are down.
Our poor captain
had to hold it up all alone.
He's been at the dam for nights.
He's not eating or sleeping.
He won't listen to anyone.
Even our brigade commander
can't do anything about him.
He scolded our lieutenant instead.
Dr Xia, why don't you try to persuade him?