♪Following the way she walked through♪
♪He searches for every piece
of memory that he had with her♪
♪An unexpected encounter in the crowds♪
♪Was the start of their destined journey♪
♪No one can tell the end of the story♪
♪Since every heart is overloaded♪
♪The dream about
blooming flowers is illusionary♪
♪Painful yet addictive♪
♪Love is too wild to be reined♪
♪Too deep to be forgot♪
♪The pain will forever
stay with the scar on the chest♪
♪He wants to linger in his dream♪
=Tears In Heaven=
=Episode 27=
Why are you following me?
I wasn't asking you,
what are you doing here?
You give up work of Yutian?
Yes, I gave up.
I don't want to be annoyed
by Lin Xiangyuan.
That's better than in this KTV,
serving people with tea and water.
You used to be
an assistant of president.
You don't have to worry about me.
I'm fine.
But you.
What?
Siqi, I saw everything.
What did you see?
You mean what happened just now?
He is a friend of Shangguan.
I knew they would come here.
You don't need to mention this anymore.
Siqi, I'm telling you,
if he dares to bully you,
don't endure it, please.
You have to let me know,
and I'll help you teach him a lesson.
You help me teach him a lesson?
Why?
You'd better mind
your own business first.
He Qunfei.
I’m telling you,
I'm doing great.
I'm doing really great.
You don't need to worry about me.
You just take care of yourself
and get a good job.
Didn't you say that
you want to treat me with dinner?
How will you do that?
How can you pay for that?
At last, I have to pay the bill.
I have to go.
Let me take you home.
No.
I will call Shangguan.
I will ask him to pick me.
I'm so sorry for today.
Wasn't He Qunfei working in Yutian?
Why does he work here for you?
I heard that Mr. Lin of Yutian
can’t tolerate him.
So, I asked him to work here.
He just started the job today.
I didn't expect that he was such a fool.
Don't be angry.
I'll fire him soon.
It's ok.
Let him stay here.
He used to be an assistant of my friend.
Now, my friend is in trouble.
He is also implicated.
Forget what happened today.
But he already quit.
Then, get him back.
Dad.
Here,
take a sip.
I still have to remind you
that you're nothing now.
Yuzheng,
Du Xiaosu comes again.
She brings
Mr. Lei's favorite marshmallow.
It's so cold outside.
She has been standing outside
for a long time.
What about…
Marshmallow.
Marshmallow is coming
Hurry up! Let her in!
Miss Du used to come every day.
Mr. Lei is quite miss her.
Shall we…
Duan,
let her in.
Let her go.
Duan,
Hurry up.
Ask her to leave.
Ok.
Hurry up!
Duan, why are you taking so long?
Let marshmallow in!
So?
May I come in?
Lei  Yuzheng,
would you please
stop treating your dad like that?
Let me in.
Lei Yuzheng!
Why? You have to make it clear to me.
I'm so sorry, Miss Du.
I can't let you in.
Uncle Duan,
would you please
take these to Mr. Lei?
Please let him eat less.
Never let him eat too much.
Miss Du!
Please tell Lei Yuzheng,
I will come again.
(Employee Layoff List of Yutian Group)
I hear that there are big layoffs
in our company.
I wonder if it will be our turn.
Since Mr. Lin came,
our company is in a mess.
Besides, the assistant Xie...
You're right.
If only Mr. Lei were here.
I wish he'd come back.
(Employee Layoff List of Yutian Group)
Manager Xie,
I think it's too hard for me.
Zhang,
do you know why Mr. Lin and I
can get here step by step?
Because we
"talk less and do more work".
I don't care how you do it,
just fire these people right now.
Don't wait until your name is on
the announcement of next batch.
I have to go.
Take your time.
I heard Lei Yuzheng will be back.
Mr. Lin laid off so many staff.
Is it because he is afraid of us?
Xia, what are you thinking about?
Lei Yuzheng can do nothing at all.
As you can see,
since Mr. Lei is so sick,
Lei Yuzheng is now tied up with
taking care of him.
If anything more serious happens
to his father,
Lei Yuzheng would be done.
Then, why did Mr. Lin do that?
He's making people so nervous.
Every new sovereign
brings his own courtiers.
Since Mr. Jiang is not in power
any more,
it is for sure that Mr. Lin wants to
use people on his own side.
Xia, even though
you are on Mr. Jiang's side,
there's still the chance
that Lin may lay you off one day.
How dare he! My length of service
is even longer than his time of life.
To this company,
I at least deserve credit for efforts.
If he is so unreasonable,
I will talk with Mr. Jiang about it.
Lay off Xia!
I hate people
who depend on their seniority.
OK.
(Signature: Du Xiaosu)
Mr. Liu,
wish a wonderful cooperation!
Wish a wonderful cooperation!
Thank you.
Xiaosu,
our studio is saved.
-Congratulations to Du Xiaosu Studio!
Mr. Liu.
They're all young staff.
Please, don't mind.
They are too happy.
We haven't formally thanked Mr. Liu.
Come on, one, two, three.
-Thank you, Mr. Liu.
You're welcome.
Cut the cake.
Ok, you can go on.
I will go and make a phone call.
(Lei Yuzheng)
(Du Xiaosu)
Hello, Qunfei.
I have been unable to reach Lei Yuzheng.
Has something happened to him?
Isn't that Mr. Lei from Yutian group?
Isn't the boss of Yutian Group
surnamed "Lin"?
You didn't know.
When Mr. Lei
was not in trouble,
he was the dream of all women.
He used to have many fans and followers.
(He Qunfei)
Now,
he is in trouble.
But,
a sleeping lion is stronger than
a barking dog.
Hello, Mr. Lei.
My name is Linda.
May I buy you a drink?
Seems that Mr. Lei likes alcohol, right?
Waiter,
a row of depth charges here.
Xiaosu.
Qunfei, here you are.
What's wrong with Lei Yuzheng recently?
I have called him for a few days.
He didn't answer.
He didn't let me in his house, either.
Even he loses his temper,
he should pick another time.
Mr. Lei is just a little better.
What if he were to suffer
any further irritations.
What can we do?
Would you please call him again?
-Come on.
(He Qunfei)
Hello, Mr. Lei.
Who is that?
We are in Phoebe.
You, go there.
Come on,  no talking.
Drink!
Lei Yuzheng.
I'm sorry.
I mistook you for someone else.
Wait, lady.
You didn't mistake me. Come.
You didn't.
No.
Have a drink together.
I'm sorry.
I did mistake you for someone else.
I'm so sorry.
-Come on.
Come here.
Drink.
Lei Yuzheng.
Lady,
we met again by fate.
Let's have a drink.
Have a drink.
Excuse me.
Where are you going?
No offense.
Just have a drink.
What are you doing?
Have a drink.
Let go of me. Let me go.
What are you two doing?
Don't leave. Have a drink.
What are you doing?
Come on. Have a drink.
Let go. You, let go of me.
What do you want?
Come on. Have a drink.
Stop it.
Lei Yuzheng.
Stop it, Lei Yuzheng.
Go.
Yuzheng,
let's go home.
Why do I have to go home with you?
I just couldn't stand
those two bastards.
Don't think that I was helping you.
It's none of your business here.
I'm busy. Go away.
Go.
Why did you do that?
What?
What should I do to you?
Should I send them away
and have you drink with me?
Why is she crying?
How come a girl like you
dares to play with our Mr. Lei.
No wonder you were dumped.
Mr. Lei.
Finally, I found you.
You even have a back-up?
How can you say that?
Why are you with such a person?
Since when who am I with
is any of your business?
Leave them alone.
Lei Yuzheng, you are a jerk.
Yes, I'm a jerk.
You're right, Du Xiaosu.
Take it easy.
With you, I am not serious at all.
What?
Do you really love me?
Wake up.
Go.
Xiaosu.
Let's go.
Go away.
Such a jerk. What's the matter with you?
What's the matter with you?
Wanhua.
Marshmallow.
Yuzheng. Wanhua.
Mr. Lei.
You really shouldn't do that
to Du Xiaosu.
When you were in prison,
if it wasn't because of her,
I'm afraid your father would...
I'm a jerk.
Take it easy.
With you, I am not serious at all.
What?
Do you really love me?
Wake up.
Many times,
the hospital issued a critical notice.
We didn't tell you.
It was Du Xiaosu to handle everything.
She was very busy and tired.
She found the best doctor
for your father.
That's the reason why he was able to
recover to what he is now.
Even if you don't appreciate her,
you shouldn't have hurt her at least.
I don't know what you are thinking.
Mr. Lei,
are you ok? Have you got hurt?
Where is Yuzheng?
I…
Mr. Lei. Please, don't...
I... what's wrong with me?
It's so hard to get out of bed.
Mr. Lei.
You are...
Duan.
Why do you talk in such a weird way?
Mr. Lei.
Make a call to Yuzheng.
I have called him in the morning.
He should be back.
You're right.
He went to the police station
just to answer some questions, right?
Yes.
It should have finished.
What are you doing?
Hurry up, call him.
I'll call him right away.
I will make the call.
Mr. Lei, you come to yourself.
Mr. Lei.
Great. Great. Mr. Lei comes to himself.
Mr. Lei comes to himself.
-Hello.
-Mr. Lei comes to himself.
(WeChat. He Qunfei)
(Mr. Lei comes to himself!)
I just fell down.
It doesn't matter.
How can it not matter?
Your son is very worried about you.
My son. For these years,
you've suffered a lot.
Dad did not take good care of you.
Dad, it's my fault.
I didn't take good care of you.
I was so unfilial.
I can't maintain Yutian.
It is not important.
You're back, now.
This is the most important.
It is the most important that
Mr. Lei comes to himself.
Yuzheng,
I have one thing
in mind for many years.
I have to tell you.
My son.
In fact, it wasn't your mother's fault.
It was my fault.
I failed your mom.
Dad,
those things are in the past,
and can never go back.
Forget it.
In future, I will be with you.
I will not go anywhere.
Son.
These years,
I always hated myself,
as I didn't give you a complete home.
Dad, it's the past.
Forget it.
This is dad's Yutian.
It's also your Yutian.
We have to
keep it and build it
Let it be
the most magnificent building.
Yuzheng,
the ground you're standing on
is our business
and destiny.
Dad.
What's going on, dad?
Wake up.
Dad, wake up.
Dad.
You need to start shaving.
Don't move.
Don't move. Be careful.
Why don't you try it?
Ignore him.
Ok, I will let marshmallow to do it.
How is it?
She is better than you.
How do you know since I haven't tried?
It's my fault.
I didn't take good care of you.
I am unfilial.
I can't maintain Yutian.
It is not important.
You're back, now.
This is the most important.
Look forward and keep moving.
Mr. Lei, I am so sorry.
Don't be so sad.
Stand up.
Don't cry.
The Leis never cry when they fall.
The Leis never give up.
I wish I were not your son.
I don't want this kind of dad.
Now, I'm telling you that,
as long as I'm in the hospital,
you should stay.
Yuzheng,
auntie Shao is always your family.
Fanlv, you should not go there.
How could I?
That's uncle Lei who sees me grow up.
How could I not go?
Fanlv, it's bad luck
for a pregnant woman to go to a funeral.
You go back first.
Mr. Jiang, let me go with you.
No. You don't have to.
Just stay with Fanlv.
Dad.
Lei.
You
didn't keep your word.
We have made a deal.
After retirement,
we will learn fishing together.
I have prepared the fishing rod for you.
How can you just leave like this?
From now on,
no one will play chess with me anymore.
No one will argue with me anymore.
What are you doing here?
You can come but I can't?
I'm here to mourn, too
Go away.
You don't need to be here,
crying crocodile tears.
Yes,
I did have some disputes
with Lei Yuzheng.
But I think
you are the most inappropriate person
to accuse me.
If it weren't because of you,
it wouldn't be like this.
Lin Xiangyuan!
I'll beat up you.
Lin Xiangyuan.
What are you doing, Lin Xiangyuan?
Do you know what day it is today?
Today is the day of Mr. Lei's funeral.
What are you doing here?
How come your morals are so bad?
Xiaosu,
I'm here to mourn…
Don't talk to me now.
I don't want to see you.
Please get out.
OK, I'll go.
I can explain to you later.
Dad.
Everyone left.
Now, it's just the two of us.
I want to talk to you.
Can you hear me?
Could you please tell me
what you wanted to tell
before you passed away?
You're back.
How is Yuzheng?
I am asking you.
Why don't you care about me,
but always care about others?
Why not just put Lei Yuzheng
in the bottom of your heart?
You're a jerk.
What are you talking about?
Fanlv.
Fanlv, are you ok?
I'll take you to the hospital, Ok?
Let's go to the hospital.
Fanlv.
I'm sorry.
Please, forgive me.
Dad.
Daughter, what happened?
Dad, it is me.
I had a fall myself.
You tell me, Lin Xiangyuan.
What happened?
What happened to the baby?
Dad.
Fanlv fell down accidentally.
Is that true?
Yes, dad.
I don't dare to be  bad to Fanlv.
I'm telling you, Lin,
you are promoted by me.
I know your mind too well.
You'd better give Fanlv
your full attention.
Fanlv is my daughter!
If you hurt her,
I will hunt you down.
(Year 1986, Lei Ting in Shanghai)
March 17. Sunny.
My first date with Wanhua.
I bought the wrong movie ticket.
There was a person between our seats.
She didn't blame me for it.
What a lovely lady!
April 3. Cloudy.
I asked Wanhua to marry me.
Her parents don't agree of
our being together.
But I will prove it to them.
We will be perfectly happy,
for the whole life.
August 19. Rainy. Wedding.
Wanhua cried.
She said, all this has not come easily.
December 1. Sunny.
Our son was born.
I named him Yuzheng.
A little man.
From now on,
my life is complete.
November 6. Cloudy.
Unhappy.
Is our marriage to Wanhua
really a mistake?
Why did we keep arguing?
Are we really not right for each other?
December 1.
Wanhua quarreled with me again today.
I hit her by mistake.
The rift between us
will be healed in no way.
January 25.
Wanhua really left me.
Maybe,
this is destiny.
January 26.
I met Wanhua today.
In that moment, time stood still.
I held her hand.
It was cold.
I don't know what to do.
I am not sure what to do with
the rest of my life.
I also don't know
how to face Yuzheng.
February 6.
Heavy snow.
I dreamed of Wanhua.
She is as beautiful as ever.
It's like she has never been away.
Honey, you're awake.
Fanlv, I'm taking a day off today
to take care of you.
This soup is your favorite.
Here you are.
It's a little hot.
Let me cool it for you.
Lin Xiangyuan, there is no one at home
but us.
Stop pretending.
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle in pain and delight♪
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle in pain and delight♪
♪Your love weeps for a withered soul♪
♪That teardrop of sadness brings extreme beauty♪
♪Indulged in the black whirlpool of your eyes♪
♪Dreams have never been this quiet♪