♪Following the way she walked through♪
♪He searches for every piece of memory that he had
with her♪
♪An unexpected encounter in the crowds♪
♪Was the start of their destined journey♪
♪No one can tell the end of the story♪
♪Since every heart is overloaded♪
♪The dream about blooming flowers is illusionary♪
♪Painful yet addictive♪
♪Love is too wild to be reined♪
♪Too deep to be forgot♪
♪The pain will forever stay with the scar on the
chest♪
♪He wants to linger in his dream♪
=Tears In Heaven=
=Episode 28=
Fanlv, I'm taking a day off today
to take care of you.
This soup is your favorite.
Here you are.
It's a little hot.
Let me cool it for you.
Lin Xiangyuan, there is no one at home.
Stop pretending.
Fanlv,
I sincerely want to apologize to you.
That day, I don't know why
I beat you.
I promise I'll never do it again.
Trust me.
I love you so much.
But you mentioned
Lei Yuzheng so many times.
I...
Love?
I just want to ask you.
You beat me because of love?
Don't mention the word "love"
in front of me.
Fanlv,
no matter how wrong I was,
I really love you.
Go away.
Fanlv,
I'm sorry.
Please give me a chance.
Last chance.
Fanlv, have a bite, please.
It's cold by the window.
Let's go inside.
Mrs. Zhao,
do you think Yuzheng
lives a hard life?
You care and love him.
No matter how much I love him,
I can't be the same as his own mom.
When Wanhua passed away,
how little he was!
He was just a kid.
Now, Lei passed away.
Mrs. Zhao, is that Yuzheng?
Mrs. Shao.
Yuzheng.
Yuzheng, it's so cold today.
Don't catch a cold.
Mrs. Zhao, please cook
a bowl of ginger soup.
Aunt Shao,
can you please tell me
whether my mom is still alive?
Why are you asking this?
If you treat me as your own son,
please tell me the truth.
Did you hear or see anything?
Wanhua and I have had no contact
for a long time.
About where is she now,
no one knows.
You still keep the truth from me.
You have been doing this
for twenty years.
How long are you planning to
keep doing this to me?
My mom,
did she already pass away?
Yuzheng.
You have been keeping the truth
for such a long time.
You don't even feel a little bit guilty?
Yuzheng,
I understand that at this moment,
you are not easy to be persuaded.
I don't want to persuade you, either.
In the past twenty years,
I always wanted to give it to you.
Now, it's the right time.
(Yuzheng)
From now on,
I will not hide anything from you.
No matter what you want to know,
I will tell you.
I still remember that
it was a rainy day.
What did I do to you?
Out there, you always
pretend to be pitiful.
I can’t stand this kind of life anymore.
If you can't, just leave.
Fine.
I want a divorce.
Divorce? It's you who said that.
Fine. You get out of here right away.
Go away.
Mom.
Mom, please don't go.
Mom, please stay.
Zheng.
Yuzheng.
I'll come back to see you.
Mom.
Mom, please don't go.
Yuzheng.
Please stay!
Mom, please don't go.
Let me go.
Mom.
Aunt Shao,
I just want to know
where my mom is buried?
Huaxi Cemetery.
Yuzheng,
if you have resentment in your heart,
resent me.
Your dad has been guilty of this
for all his life.
He wished to spend his whole life
to atone for Wanhua.
(Miss Forever)
(Tomb of my beloved wife,
Wanhua 1960-1993. Lei Ting)
Mom.
Sir,
you already drunk too much.
Leave me alone.
Leave me alone, please.
More, please.
I want one as well.
Du Xiaosu,
you were right.
The person I've been resenting
is long gone.
Who am I?
Monster.
Lei Yuzheng, don't be like that.
Lei Yuzheng, I know you're sad.
I know you want to vent.
But you can't torture yourself
like that.
I don't need your sympathy.
Go.
Go away.
Lei Yuzheng, think about Mr. Lei.
Think about the people
who care about you.
Cheer yourself up, please.
Don't mention him.
He's gone.
All is finished.
What about me?
Mr. Lei,
had his own pain.
He was doing that for you.
He had no other choice but to do so,
right?
Lei Yuzheng, where are you going?
What do you want to do?
Du Xiaosu,
for you or anyone else,
I don't want to have any relationship.
Lei Yuzheng.
Slowly.
Mind the step.
Lei Yuzheng, are you OK?
Slowly, please.
How is he? Wipe with a warm towel.
He seems to have a fever.
Does he?
Getting hot.
Have to take some medicine.
Uncle Duan, please get some medicine.
I will take care of him.
OK.
Mom.
Please don't go! Please!
Don't worry. I will not leave.
Yuzheng.
Mom.
It's been many years,
and you still remember me?
You're my son.
Once I've seen your face,
and heard your voice,
Mom will never forget.
Mom, please don't go.
Please stay with me.
Mom has never forgotten you.
But I hope you can forget me.
Yuzheng, remember that
to forget one person
is to love another person more.
Mom has left you.
But she is with you.
Cherish the people around you.
Don't be like realizing
the past happiness until separation.
Yuzheng,
don't hate your dad.
We are now with each other.
Very, very happy.
You don't need to worry about us.
Mom has to go now.
Mom.
Take good care of yourself.
♪Following the way she walked through♪
♪He searches for every piece of memory
that he had with her♪
♪An unexpected encounter in the crowds♪
♪Was the start of their destined journey♪
♪Surging love raises a storm
in the city♪
♪The world is deceived while a
true heart would not be cheated♪
♪Frantic pursuit of the marks
on the chest♪
♪The one and only in destiny♪
♪When will the surging love calm down♪
Lei Yuzheng.
♪Love is never forgotten♪
(To Du Xiaosu)
♪The pain on the back and the marks
on the chest♪
♪Continue to indulge in the dream♪
Du Xiaosu,
when you are reading this letter,
I already left this city.
Thank you for taking care of my dad
during this period.
And really thank you
for being in my life.
Before I met you,
I've always lived alone.
At that time,
I didn't know what loneliness is
and what emptiness is.
Because I had no time
to think about it,
to think about why I'm not happy,
and what is missing in my life.
If I didn't meet you,
I would never believe
there is such a pure smile.
I would not believe there is a voice
that I want to listen to all the time.
(Letter from Lei Yuzheng)
I would not even believe that
a lady's tear
can make me so painful.
I began to fear of being alone,
(Yuzheng)
fear of loneliness,
and fear of losing you.
(Yuzheng)
Gradually, I realized that,
with you around,
life can be so wonderful.
Du Xiaosu.
Thank you so much.
You came into my life just as sunshine.
But unfortunately,
it is always dark in my heart,
and it will never be lightened.
I don't want to be
the burden of your life.
So I left.
Don't come to look for me.
At last,
one more thing,
please operate the studio well.
In that case,
all the things I did for you
will be meaningful.
Farewell, Du Xiaosu.
Wish you happiness.
Xiaosu,
sorry. I'm sorry. I'm late.
Siqi,
I'm so tired.
But I tried my best to find him,
and I can't find him anywhere.
Lei Yuzheng really disappeared
this time.
He will never come back.
No way. I have to find him.
Xiaosu,
listen to me.
Mr. Lei chose to leave.
He just wanted to be alone.
What we can do now is
to stay here until he comes back.
Think about it.
He has done so much for you.
He just wants you
to run the studio well,
hold on to your dream,
and be happy every day.
If you cannot hold it anymore,
do you think there's still hope for him?
Xiaosu,
we will always be with you
until he comes back.
Fell asleep?
Where on earth does Mr. Lei go?
It doesn't matter where he goes.
He left that letter and
just wanted to make Du Xiaosu give up.
He has underestimated Xiaosu
and her love to him.
It's not easy for Mr. Lei either.
He was in agony,
and he doesn't want us to see it.
If there is any difficulty,
they can work it out together.
If there is any problem,
they can face it together.
I don't understand why he just chose to
run away from his friends
and not to face his true feelings.
Siqi...
Fine. Save it.
It's too late. You have to go.
Xiaosu,
You up?
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
I'm going to the studio now.
I'll probably be back very late tonight.
You can start dinner without me.
Have some breakfast before you go.
It's OK. I'm not hungry.
Bye.
(Weekly Project Progress Chart)
No matter where you are,
as long as you are happy.
Xiaosu, there's something wrong.
What happened?
Some environment-friendly materials
are out of supply.
We can't find a substitute for now.
I'm afraid the construction schedule
is really going to be delayed.
You...
Got it.
Mr. Yang,
this is Du Xiaosu.
Mr. Song.
Hello, Mr. Wood.
Yeah, we haven't met for a long time.
OK. Well...
I...  I'll call you later.
You are busy?
OK.
Thank you. Bye.
Siqi.
Have a look.
Just have a look, please.
I have to say something?
You can't hold it anymore
if I keep being quiet.
This diamond ring is too bright.
An old leftover girl like me has waited
for my true love for a long time.
Am I still not allowed to show off
for a few days?
Blind date may look old-fashioned,
but it works.
Look.
This is a photo of me and my husband.
We met on a blind date.
This was in Bali.
A photo from our honeymoon.
He works in the finance industry.
Our apartment is on Financial Street.
It will be ready next month.
You're welcome to come.
It's nice.
How happy you are!
How did you find your true love?
To be honest,
you are getting older and older.
You should find someone
to take care of you.
I have to tell you
my husband
works with several single men.
Do you need me to introduce them to you?
I'm good. Don't worry about me.
No, thanks.
Fine. I have to go.
Just go.
Enjoy your coffee.
Bye.
Shangguan...
All right. Deal.
I'll transfer the money to you now.
Thanks.
Done.
Xiaosu, I admire you so much.
You've got the materials
that are so hard to buy.
Awesome!
You did a good job as well.
Go and have a rest.
You are here.
Come here.
I finally see you again.
Still angry?
A small gift.
Don't be angry anymore.
You figured it out?
Yes, I did.
I can't live without you.
You really figured it out?
For sure.
I want to be with you.
For you,
I can stop dating other women
for a while.
For a while?
What do you mean?
This gift
is just a gift.
Me?
I won't be thinking
about marrying anyone.
Shangguan,
we may not belong to the same world.
I've asked you many times
about whether you figured it out.
Actually, I'm the one
who should figure it out first.
Thank you for favoring me.
And thank you for giving me a chance
to dream about having a good life.
From now on,
don't come to me again, please.
Bye.
Siqi, are you serious?
Siqi...
Engineer Zhang,
the design of this part
is different from that on the drawing.
It was Mr. Liu who made the changes.
I couldn't do anything about it.
Mr. Liu?
However, if we do so,
not only will there be security risks,
but also the overall design
will be affected.
I have to call Mr. Liu.
Mr. Liu, this is Xiaosu.
I'm at the construction site now.
Our project
is not quite the same as
what we designed before.
So I...
You are still young and inexperienced,
so your design still has defect.
I have personally
helped you make the changes,
and you still have concerns?
No, Mr. Liu. I...
No need to say anything more.
Last time, because of the raw materials,
you've already delayed the project.
Let's do this the same way we did it.
Catch up on your work.
Mr. Liu...
One more, please.
You are alone today. Where is Shangguan?
Don't mention him. We broke up.
What are you laughing at?
You don't sell wine to singles?
What are you doing here, Siqi?
I just thought of you and you showed up.
Where is Shangguan?
You are so drunk.
It's not safe for a girl to stay here.
Who is Shangguan? I don't know him.
I only know you.
OK. Stop drinking. Let me take you home.
He Qunfei,
do you think I'm pretty?
What?
Do you think I'm pretty?
You are the prettiest
and loveliest girl I have ever seen.
So do you want to be my boyfriend again?
Mr. Lei senior just passed away.
Mr. Lei junior is missing.
I'm really not in the mood right now,
Siqi.
Besides, you already have Shangguan.
Shangguan is a jerk.
I, Zou Siqi, am more of a jerk.
You were so good to me.
Why didn't I cherish it?
How could I...
For that temptation, I just let you...
Qunfei,
in this world,
there is no way to turn it back?
No matter how much money I provide now,
it's still too late?
Don't say anything more.
Go. Let's go home.
Go.
I did drink a little too much today.
But I know, in my heart,
I love you, He Qunfei.
I just don't know
if there's still a chance,
I can keep loving you.
When you don't expect it,
destiny always surprises you.
Let you know that
your previous ambition
was just a joke.
After all of this,
I realized that
realizing the value of my life
is what I really want.
Maybe temporary absence
will be a new start.
Xiaosu,
two groups of clients
will visit this afternoon.
One at three clock
and the other at five clock.
Is that OK?
Xiaosu.
Sorry, what did you say?
I said there will be
clients to visit us this afternoon.
Xiaosu,
you have been so absent-minded recently.
Anything happened at home?
No, nothing.
Oh, I'm going out in a minute.
Would you please look after
the business for a while for me?
Well, what about the clients' visit?
Cancel it if you can.
(Lei Yuzheng)
...put it behind a child,
and don't let him know.
Be quick and catch him.
Be quick
and catch him.
Throw the handkerchief.
(Dream Primary School)
Quietly put it behind a child,
and don't let him know.
Miss Du.
Uncle Duan.
You bought these things again.
Has Lei Yuzheng called these days?
No.
Any mails?
Have you checked the mailbox?
Just in case, the place he lives now,
has no signal.
Miss Du, I have checked the mailbox.
Nothing.
Let me get the door.
Please take the things in.
Fine.
Hello, may I help you?
Lei Yuzheng lives here, right?
Yes.
Who are you?
Mr. Lei passed away.
Just passed away.
Lei Yuzheng is missing, right?
How did you know that?
If I were him,
I would have done the same.
Please have a seat.
May I have your name, please?
I'm Liu Siyang.
Lei Yuzheng called me Siyang.
You can call me the same as he does.
Please take a seat.
I'll make you a pot of tea.
OK.
Yes, it's hard for you right now.
But in this world,
which family or person
has no difficulty at all?
Yuzheng,
it's really you.
I was just thinking
who has brought so many
presents to the kids.
Hello, Uncle Lei.
Mei. Doudou.
Do you miss Uncle Lei?
Hello, Uncle Lei.
Doudou. Mei.
Can you please take your classmates
there to play?
OK.
Sweetheart, go over there to play.
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle in pain and delight♪
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle in pain and delight♪
♪Your love weeps for a withered soul♪
♪That teardrop of sadness brings extreme beauty♪
♪Indulged in the black whirlpool of your eyes♪
♪Dreams have never been this quiet♪