=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 24=
Except for the undeserved
title of Goddess,
I’m not special at all.
Yet you keep making advances to me.
Why?
Who said you were not special?
Instead of asking about this,
why don’t you ask
who doesn’t say that about me
in the Three Realms?
Allow me to remind you that
both immortals and demons
value strength.
I’m not good enough for you.
Please do not bring it up again.
Come with me.
Taking a walk?
Where are they taking a walk?
No one is here in the woods.
Paper boy?
Paper boy!
Jingyuan must have found it.
Who are you?
How dared you stalk me!
North Sea Lord, please spare me.
I’m not a bad guy.
I’m Jiaye from the Qingchi Palace.
Jiaye?
Houchi told me about you.
I never expected a lord like you
to know me.
It’s my honor.
No.
My great honor.
Why did you stalk me?
Don’t worry.
I didn’t mean any harm.
I just didn’t expect
to see you in person.
You mean I’m famous
in the Qingchi Palace?
Yes, you are.
All storybooks we read
are about you.
You met the princess in the Heavenly
Palace when you were drunk.
You swept girls off their feet
only by wielding the sword.
All right. Stop it.
People made those stories up.
They’re not true.
Tell me.
Now that you heard such rumors,
did Houchi hear them, too?
She didn’t.
She focused on cultivation
over the past tens of thousands of years
and she wasn’t interested
in such stories.
That’s fine, then.
Lord,
you mean
you truly like
Her Grace?
Sure, I do.
Does she know?
I’ll let her know now.
Can you do the Condensing Spell?
Show me.
Try again.
Why?
In the Xuanjing Palace, I found that
there was a strong seal
inside your body.
Because of it,
your spiritual power’s been suppressed.
But this bracelet
gives you enough power
to protect yourself.
Houchi,
go to the Demon Realm with me
and I’ll try to break the seal.
Then you’ll understand
what Bai Jue’s soul said was true
when you were on Mount Lookout that day.
You should have been
the most respected one.
(Always Acquire New Knowledge)
Go to the Demon Realm
and get my spiritual power back?
If I’m as powerful
as a Goddess should be,
maybe,
the Qingchi Palace
will return to normal.
After searching
the entire Qilian Mountains,
I found the most beautiful flowers.
They’re for you.
There’s something
I’ve kept in my mind for a long time.
I want to tell you...
Where did you
get the flowers?
In the west behind the mountains.
Did you only find some there,
rather than any other place?
How do you know?
I picked all of them.
They’re the priceless treasure
Chang Que begged for
from the Flood Dragons
and they’re used as medicine.
It took him over a hundred years
to have finally grown them
on Qilian Mountains.
There’re only a few of them.
He has been expecting day and night
to see them bear fruits
after they wither.
But what have you done?
You’ve destroyed them.
Shall... Shall I...?
Shall I put them back?
I don’t think they’ll survive.
Who on earth
stole my flowers?
What’s wrong with him?
Are these flowers for picking?
I...
I’ll find the seeds for him.
Idiot.
Now that Qingmu has owned
the Taicang Spear,
he’s really become
the strongest immortal.
Heavenly Mother,
what do you think of him?
According to your father,
you adore him?
I’ve never adored anyone
like that before.
All I want is to spend my life with him
and love each other forever.
Many immortals like you.
Why do you like him only?
I’ve been the princess
in the Heavenly Palace.
All immortals flatter me or fear me
every time they see me.
Only Qingmu is different.
He’s neither humble nor pushy to me.
When he told Jingjian about his journeys
in the Three Realms,
he gave animated narratives.
I like how free he feels.
I hope that
I can go travelling with him
and be a happy couple.
But forced love does not last.
I heard that
Houchi took him away.
Don’t believe rumors, Heavenly Mother.
In the Three Realms, I know him best,
second to Jingjian.
He never got close to girls.
Houchi must have used some spells
to lure him away.
Heavenly Mother,
I’m your own daughter.
Don’t show partiality for Houchi.
Why would I be partial to her?
I just don’t want you to lose
in the relationship.
I know.
You gave me the Feather Umbrella
so that I wouldn’t lose to Houchi again.
But on Mount Lookout,
it felt as if
it weren’t of one mind with me.
It didn’t take my order for a while.
Really?
Take it out
and let me check.
I’ll kill you!
It’s him!
Demon Power?
Heavenly Mother,
who was able to put Demon Power
on your weapon?
Leave me alone.
Yes.
(The Pilgrimage Hall)
Since the God Realm was closed,
the Pilgrimage Hall came down
to the Heavenly Realm.
I had thought that
I, Muguang,
and Gu Jun were the last Gods.
Unexpectedly, he...
Sixty thousand years have passed.
Four True Gods are forever sealed
with the God Realm.
Even if you’re Tianqi, so what?
In the existing Heavenly Realm,
I won’t let you enjoy your life.
Qingmu,
why are you here?
Where’s Jiaye?
I sent him away.
I want to make a good breakfast for you.
I’m making some pear soup.
I don’t think there’re pears here.
Where did you get them?
I got up early and bought them
in the Human Realm.
You haven’t recovered yet.
Why did you...?
Be seated.
You know what?
It’s complicated to make such soup.
I could have used the Fire Spell
to control the degree of heating.
However,
it’s our way to cook.
I’d like to use the way humans do.
Leave the soup to simmer.
It takes a long time, then.
It’ll taste good
when it’s crispy and soft.
Why are you staring at me?
I never expected that
apart from that you look handsome
and you have strong power,
you even cooked well.
I didn’t cook well.
I just learnt it.
Last time when I made
steamed stuffed buns for you,
I nearly burned the Xuanjing Palace.
No matter what you cook for me,
I’ll enjoy it.
I’ll cook for no one but you.
Let me help you.
All right.
It’s almost done, isn’t it?
Let me try some.
What?
Nothing.
It’s not good enough yet.
It needs to be simmered longer.
Who? Come out!
Who on earth are you?
Why don’t you dare to show your face?
I never expected Demon Lord Ziyue
to collude with the Qingchi Palace.
Now that you came,
never dream to leave.
You don’t dare to fight me?
Why?
In case I recognize you?
Such strong spiritual power.
Wait for me here.
It’s you?
Before I go see you,
how dare you come to me!
Considering your existing power,
you can’t scare me!
Who are you?
How dared you intrude into
the Qingchi Palace!
Bai Jue?
No.
He isn’t Bai Jue.
He’s just Qingmu.
Who was it?
Just a humble phoenix.
Houchi, are you hurt?
Your Highness.
Is something bothering you,
Your Highness?
I went to the Qingchi Palace today.
I found out that Demon Lord Ziyue
used to be Tianqi.
The Demon God of Destruction?
Wasn’t he executed by Master Bai Jue
sixty thousand years ago?
I don’t know why he’s still alive.
But luckily,
he hasn’t got back
the power of True God.
He isn’t a threat yet.
Your Highness, you’d better
tell His Majesty about it.
When the Demon God of Destruction
is alive,
it’s a threat to the Three Realms.
He knows one of my secrets
and he could threaten me with that.
I can’t let His Majesty know that.
You mustn’t tell anyone else, either.
I’m loyal to you alone
and I won’t ever betray you.
Fengnyu,
I picked you as my personal maid
from the Feng Clan.
I trust you.
But I can’t let Demon Lord Ziyue live.
All I can do now
is keep making enemies of demons
and never give him a breathing spell.
But immortals and demons have been
in a stalemate for years.
His Majesty wants a peace negotiation.
What can we do?
Qingmu.
The Taicang Spear.
We don’t know who Qingmu really is.
If he really is Bai Jue,
maybe I can make use of him
to fight the demons.
If he isn’t,
I can also use him
to fight for me.
Heavenly Mother.
Leave us.
Yes.
Greetings, Heavenly Mother.
Why are you saluting like this?
I want to beg you for something.
Please ask Heavenly Father
to...
to grant me a marriage.
Who on earth is she?
Why did she come to my Qingchi Palace?
Ignore it.
I’m her target.
Now that she saw me,
she wouldn’t come again.
She’s an immortal
and she broke into my Qingchi Palace.
I’m afraid I can’t ignore it.
Don’t overthink.
If you get too much time,
why not bother about my love affairs?
She’s your old sweetheart?
That low phoenix...
It’s none of your business, anyway.
I’ll take care of it.
Can I not take care of it
or do you think
I’m too weak to take care of it?
Both.
You said that
you could remove the seal in me?
Yes.
We must pay a price for everything.
Now that you found the seal in me,
my father must have found it, too.
Yet he didn’t tell me.
Must I pay the price
if I want to remove the seal
from my body?
It’s wise of you.
Houchi,
there’s this Spiritual Strength
sleeping in your body.
To have it sealed,
your spiritual veins are sealed, too.
If you want to unseal it
and cultivate your power,
when you do it,
the Spiritual Strength wakes up, too.
If it wakes up,
what will happen to me?
I’m not sure.
Maybe you can exist with it.
Or maybe you two will become one
and you will no longer be
who you are now.
Lord Qingmu,
however powerful you are,
you can’t get her back
by staring at the door, can you?
Houchi,
if it’s unsealed,
you’ll become the most powerful being.
It will protect you
and the Qingchi Palace.
No one can bully you again.
I simply pushed you.
Why are you bleeding already?
I was just raided and injured.
Now you...
Houchi,
don’t leave.
It hurts.
I’m not leaving.
I’ll stay with you.
Feeling better?
Much better.
Let me check.
Houchi!
Qingmu.
Now that you’re injured,
go back for some rest.
Don’t catch a cold.
I was injured in this Qingchi Palace.
Houchi should take responsibility.
North Sea Lord,
aren’t you interfering too much?
Qingmu, stop it.
What a blood deficiency
and vein disorder!
It’s a sign of death.
You’re indeed badly injured.
Houchi,
I’m too weak to leave.
I’m afraid I have to stay here
for a few more days.
Sure.
Stay here for recuperation.
I don’t think
ordinary medicine can cure you.
You need acupuncture.
Houchi,
where are your needles?
How can you cure me
with a mere medical skill
from the Human Realm?
I have great medical skills.
You have more spiritual power than me.
But you were injured
in the Qingchi Palace.
It’s my duty to cure you.
Aren’t you an immortal
from the Heavenly Palace?
What do you have to do
with the Qingchi Palace?
It had nothing to do with me before.
But from now on,
its problem is also mine.
Houchi,
I want to go back to my room for a rest.
Demon Lord, do you feel better?
(Fuyao Hall)
Heavenly Father,
I thought a lot when I was grounded.
I was so shortsighted
that I valued Ziyuan
to pay my personal favor
and caused disharmony among immortals.
I was wrong.
I’m relieved
to hear that.
You’re my eldest son.
You must value the Three Realms
above everything else.
Don’t act on impulse again.
Yes, Heavenly Father.
You may rise.
We know where the Twin Spear is.
The Taicang Spear has picked its owner.
The Demon King also allowed me
to look for the Purple Moon Whip
in the Demon Realm.
Now, I want you and Jingjian
to look for the Ancestral Sword.
Let Jingyang do it.
Yeah.
What a poor memory I have!
Jingjian,
stay here.
We’ve got another mission for you.
It’s been many years
since people gossiped
about Jingzhao and the North Sea Lord.
Jingzhao was young.
But now she has grown up.
As her parents,
we should care more about that.
Now that North Sea Lord
doesn’t want to come,
go invite him for us.
Now, he owns the Taicang Spear
and he means a lot to us.
I want him to come
and command the armies.
Now that Jingzhao likes him,
Jingjian,
go to the Qingchi Palace with my edict
which makes him the commander
and grants him the marriage
with Jingzhao.
It’s wise of you, Your Majesty.
When he’s the commander of armies,
he’s good enough for our daughter.
Heavenly Father.
Heavenly Mother.
Qingmu always lives a free life.
I don’t think he wants
to be the commander.
Besides,
the thing between him and Jingzhao
is just a rumor among troublemakers.
Don’t take it seriously.
But Jingjian,
I’m serious.
Jingzhao,
if Qingmu really loved you,
he would have come and proposed to you,
instead of hiding in the Qingchi Palace.
Heavenly Father,
Jingzhao is an excellent girl.
She will have a good husband.
Why must we force Qingmu?
Jingjian,
you’re my own brother!
you mean
Jingzhao isn’t up to
Qingmu’s preference?
Heavenly Father, that’s not true.
Jingzhao.
Jingjian,
you’re a close friend of Qingmu’s.
But it’s about love stuff.
How do you know
he’ll turn us down?
But he...
Say no more.
Just go and invite him.
Yes.
Mother knew Qingmu wouldn’t agree.
Why did she force me to invite him?
Isn’t she making me unwelcome?
If I tell them why I come,
Fengran will blame me.
How about this?
When I reach the Qingchi Palace,
I’ll tell Qingmu about it secretly
and ask him to write a letter
to decline the offer.
Your Highness,
the Queen of Heaven ordered us
to go to the Qingchi Palace with you.
Do we really need so many people?
The Queen of Heaven said that
demons often made trouble
to harass the Heavenly Realm.
She didn’t want you to get hurt.
She wasn’t worried
when I went to the Demon Region.
But she is worried
when I’m going to the Qingchi Palace.
Leave me alone.
I’m going by myself.
What?
Didn’t I make myself clear?
Don’t blame us, Your Highness.
We’re taking the order.
We dare not disobey the order.
Your Highness,
please don’t embarrass us.
Demon Lord Ziyue is fastening
on Houchi every day.
I can’t just wait and do nothing.
I’m taking her to Dibei Town
in the Human Realm
where no one could disturb us.
I can then tell her
all my feelings.
Do you think she’ll turn me down?
If she turns me down,
I’ll burn you.
Houchi.
Lord Qingmu.
Where’s Houchi?
Demon Lord Ziyue said
he didn’t feel well
and early this morning,
he asked Her Grace
to take a walk with him
behind the mountains.
What a demon!
He always tricks her.
Why did you bring it out?
Be careful!
Luckily, it’s not broken.
Lord Qingmu,
give it to me
and let me put it back.
It’s her treasure
that she never allows anyone to touch.
Treasure?
It contains no spiritual power at all
and it’s her treasure?
Lord Boxuan gave it to her.
She values it.
Boxuan gave it to her?
For her birthday
every five thousand years,
Lord Boxuan
would carve something
and give it to her.
It’s a birthday present for Houchi?
Yes.
(The sixth of the ninth lunar month)
The sixth of the ninth lunar month.
Today?
Today is Houchi’s birthday?
Lord Qingmu,
don’t mention the birthday thing
in front of Her Grace.
Why?
After Lord Boxuan left,
she hated the birthday thing most.
She didn’t allow us
to celebrate it for her.
If anyone dared to mention it,
she would not speak to him
for half a month.
Father is travelling around
to find treasures for me
and he seldom comes back.
Fengran wasn’t there yet.
The Qingchi Palace was cold and lonely.
No one accompanied me, but Boxuan.
Later, Boxuan left, too.
I never left Qingchi Palace.
So,
that’s how
you grew up.
I kind of envy you sometimes
that you lost your memories.
Jiaye,
could you do me a favor?
Are you sure
you’ll celebrate her birthday?
We didn’t forget her birthday,
but she...
I know.
She doesn’t like to celebrate it.
Then why do you take the trouble?
From this day on,
I’ll celebrate
all her birthdays with her.
You’d better keep your promise.
As for the seal inside me,
I’ve made up my mind
not to unseal it.
I’m Houchi.
I’m not going to be anyone else.
Keep this instruction feather.
If you’re in trouble,
you can find me with it.
Thank you, Demon Lord Ziyue.
But we’re always neutral
and we won’t show partiality for demons.
What are you thinking about?
This thing is my personal belongings.
It represents my friendship towards you,
instead of anything else.
But...
Demon Lord Ziyue.
Houchi,
it’s my...
Your Grace,
I know you’re busy.
But you have many men around you.
Shouldn’t you be equal?
You can’t ignore someone, can you?
What do you mean?
What’re you here for?
Come with me and you’ll know.
Let’s go.
Houchi.
What’s he doing?
What else can he do?
Just something for you.
Look.
I wonder if she’ll like
the birthday noodles.
Birthday noodles?
You told him?
I didn’t.
The noisy rabbit did.
I didn’t tell him anything.
Houchi?
The noodles taste best now.
Try some.
Are you hungry?
I don’t celebrate my birthday.
Try some.
Come on.
Taste good?
If they do, I’ll cook them
for you every year.
Don’t tease me.
I’m serious.
I’ll make birthday noodles
for you every year.
Not only on birthdays.
Whenever you want some,
I’ll cook them for you.
Come on.
Try some more.
Qingmu,
why did you take me here?
You like fireflies.
There’re many fireflies
on Qilian Mountains.
But it’s indeed hard to catch some
in the daytime.
It took me much trouble
to find 9,900 fireflies for you.
Now that it took much trouble,
why did you still do that?
Because you like them.
I’ll do anything that you like.
And I’ll avoid anything you don’t like.
If you like enchanting scenery,
I’ll go travelling with you to enjoy it.
If you like a peaceful life,
I can live a peaceful life with you
in this quiet place.
Qingmu,
what I want is unchangeable love.
If you can’t do it,
say no more.
We’re still friends.
Don’t stir me
from my cultivation resolve.
I can do it.
I’m serious
from the first word I said.
Houchi,
I like you.
♪Hold tightly with your warm hand♪
I really like you.
So what?
In the past tens of thousands of years,
I watched the Qingchi Palace decline.
Flowers wither.
A good time never lasts long.
♪To exchange it for you♪
No one
can accompany another forever.
I can.
Houchi,
♪Until I meet you♪
Boxuan might leave you.
Your father might leave you.
Everyone may leave you,
but I won’t.
♪When we meet again♪
I’m as true to you
as eternal landscapes.
Just give me a chance.
♪Listen♪
Let me stay with you
so that I can prove it to you.
♪And get close♪
♪For a little talk♪
♪If it’s such a good time
and such a beautiful scenery♪
♪Hope♪
♪Go with me♪
Plants and insects
live and die.
Even if I trust you,
I don’t trust myself.
Besides,
I have to go look for Boxuan.
And the Qingchi Palace...
♪Time disturb my feelings♪
♪Like you do♪
Houchi,
I’ll prove it to you.
Fireflies will fly away.
But I won’t leave you.
♪Your tall figure♪
♪Is even clear in the haze♪
♪I save some time♪
♪To exchange it for you♪
Why did you take me here?
Don’t say anything.
♪Until I meet you♪
♪I make every attempt♪
♪To have the next life♪
Look.
This is where I was born.
It’s an uninhabited place,
with only the sound of the sea.
It’s lonelier,
compared to the Qingchi Palace.
I kept cultivating myself
and killing wicked demons
day after day.
♪And get close♪
I didn’t know
who my families or friends were.
I didn’t know why I was here, either.
I didn’t even know where I was going.
♪Hope♪
But when I met you on Mount Lookout
for the first time,
I knew you were the girl
I had been looking for.
♪I am so sure♪
I know we will stay close
and spend our lives together
like the connection of the sky and sea.
♪The way to happiness♪
I know.
I know you have many responsibilities
you can’t get rid of
and some people you can’t forget.
♪Listen♪
I just want you to look around
when you’re away.
Unless the sea dries up,
I’ll always be there for you.
♪For a little talk♪
♪If it’s such a good time
and such a beautiful scenery♪
♪There’s you♪
♪And me♪
Where have they gone?
Why aren’t they back yet?
If she isn’t back,
her birthday will be over
after 12 o’clock.
It’s Her Grace!
Houchi.
Your Grace.
Your Grace, you’re back.
Your Grace,
it’s the liquor your father hid
behind the mountains.
Lord Chang Que just dug it out.
Try some, Your Grace.
Tastes great.
Houchi.
Since I was born,
this sword has been
my most precious and cherished thing.
I’m giving it to you.
Hope when you carry it,
it’ll always defend you and protect you.
♪Where are you♪
♪Your young face♪
♪Goes with memories♪
♪And is sealed in time♪
I’m so happy today.
Since Father and Boxuan left,
no one has ever done this for me.
♪I can’t see the injuries♪
Thank you, Qingmu.
♪Dreams are imperfect♪
♪I can’t help missing the past♪
♪What’s in my hand is
what I can’t get over♪
♪How are we destined to meet♪
♪Tide rushes and the moon rises♪
♪The trip takes a thousand years♪
♪Wake up the clouds♪
Houchi,
happy birthday.
♪It’s dreamlike♪
♪And it’s also aimless♪
♪For one single glance at you♪
♪I don’t regret cultivating myself♪
♪Even if I have to love alone♪
Shanggu,
I’ll always be your elder brother.
No matter what happens between us
or what we experience,
I’ll always be by your side.
I like you.
I’m already satisfied
when I’ve told you.
You can turn me down,
but you can’t keep me away.
No matter it’s ten thousand years
or a hundred thousand years,
I insist on loving you
and haunting you
until death.
Master,
aren’t we here
to celebrate her birthday?
Why don’t we go to her?
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪