So why do you keep provoking them?
They think you're the bad guy.
I don't care what they think.
The more I think about it,
the more baffled I get.
There are plenty of seniors.
How dare they order you to protest?
They're obviously trying
to dump it all on you...
because they don't want
to be dragged to Namsan.
It's my choice.
No one put me up to it.
Sure. Whatever, Mr. Fighter.
Everything you do bothers me.
And what's with this lame taste
in music?
You told me to request a song
I wanted to listen to.
Why must you nitpick
about everything?
We really don't see eye to eye.
You say that all the time.
Why did you team up with me then?
What do you think?
Probably because you couldn't find
anyone else to write lyrics.
I'm sorry, but there are many people
who can do that.
Then what?
- Because I'm a nice person?
- You're saying that about yourself?
Have you gone mad?
That's what everyone else says.
They say I'm nice.
And that's why they all like me.
My goodness.
Kim Kyung Soo.
Don't be delusional.
You're not a good person.
You punks.
Do you think you're on a picnic now?
Hurry up! You're all so slow.
Hee Tae, the ambulance is arriving.
Oh, okay.
(Episode 10,
Goodness, Hypocrisy, Utmost Effort)
The martial law army headquarters...
Can't you write it properly?
What is this?
Do you have an accurate count?
Yes, I think so.
What are you doing here?
I thought you moved to Seoul
to get married.
I'll just get the medical supplies
and leave.
Don't mind me.
Why? Did your father-in-law
send you here to spy on us?
What?
Am I wrong?
Are you the Grim Reaper
or something?
Everyone who met up with you
has disappeared.
Did Hye Gun also go missing
after meeting up with you?
It was me, not her.
Hye Gun met with me
before he went missing.
Does that make me
the Grim Reaper too?
Why are you taking it out on her?
That's because her fiance is...
She moved out.
What?
Look at her. Can't you tell?
Both she and I have been helping
the victims for days, nonstop.
So don't waste your energy
attacking someone...
who's working toward the same goal
as you are.
Boo Yong, that thing...
Did you finish it?
What's with this handwriting?
Make the letters bigger.
Keep your head down, please.
- This will be quick.
- This is only his second day here,
but he's better at intubation
than Dr. Song,
who's been an intern
for half a year.
He already got the hang of it.
I know.
He passed the exam
with the highest score, you know.
Don't blatantly stare at him.
Let's just take a quick glance.
Does anyone have a moment to spare?
Please go take care of Kim Duk Bae.
Kim Duk Bae? The delirious patient?
The one who beats up everyone?
That's right.
He's just not getting better.
Give him more sedatives.
- And take this urinary bag...
- What?
- Attach this urinary bag too.
- Goodness.
Here.
I'll do it.
Really?
Myeong Hee, what are you doing?
What?
We have to admit the new patient.
The ambulance is arriving now.
It's an emergency patient.
We'll be right back.
Wait...
Clearly, he's already made himself
at home here.
- No one's coming?
- I'm coming.
How many times must I tell you?
Don't step in unless you're told to.
Why would you volunteer
to do the difficult tasks?
Why should that matter?
I just want to do the things
that I can do.
Does it mean other people...
avoid it because
they don't know how to work?
See? They keep forcing
everything on you...
since they know you'll say yes.
You do all the hard work too.
You covered the windows
with mattresses yesterday...
Do you think I did that
because I wanted to?
When bullets were literally
flying in through the windows?
I did it
because you were about to do it.
If I didn't,
you would've done it instead.
- I get it. Stop nagging.
- "Stop nagging?"
I'm saying this for your sake.
Wait, a patient has arrived.
(Emergency Medical Center)
The patient is 18,
and he's been shot in the hand
and lower abdomen.
He's been shot?
Let's prepare for surgery
right away.
Prepare plenty of blood
for transfusion.
Darn it.
Those darn punks.
Now they're even shooting civilians
with the guns meant to protect them?
Can you believe this?
What did the kid do to deserve this?
Jung Tae,
can't you come sleep at home?
I can give you a ride
back and forth.
I'm really okay.
No one has gone home.
They're all sleeping here.
I'm just so worried.
And your father may ask
to see you soon.
He never asks to see me.
What?
Anyway, I won't go.
I'm going to stay here.
Yes, ma'am.
Our training is being carried out...
strictly within the training camp.
No one is taking
a single step out of here.
So don't worry about Jung Tae.
Please call me if something happens.
Yes, of course.
Okay, goodbye.
Yes?
We're training strictly within
the training camp.
(Emergency Room, Nurse's Station)
What did they say?
Is Myeong Soo okay?
They're staying
strictly inside the training camp,
so he said not to worry.
If you're concerned,
shall we bring him here?
I'll go get him.
It's better for him to stay there
instead of seeing what goes on here.
It's safer too.
That punk.
You think you're so darn fast?
Are you crazy?
Soo Gon, get out of here now!
- You darn...
- Sergeant Hong!
Don't come any closer!
If you do, I'll kill this jerk!
You crazy punk.
Private Kim, what are you doing?
Shoot him now! Shoot him!
I'm going to kill you!
Shoot him!
Due to the military's excessive use
of force,
hundreds of innocent civilians
have been injured.
Someone even died yesterday.
We must make
the troops withdraw immediately.
Withdrawing suddenly like this
won't solve anything.
What?
Do you think they were dispatched
for no reason?
It's more important to suppress
the mob...
that's causing this whole frenzy.
Whose side are you on right now?
We're gathered here
to sort this situation out.
We're not here to take sides.
Or perhaps, Father,
are you here
to represent one side in particular?
Please watch your mouth.
You're the ones
who should watch your mouths.
- What? What did you say?
- Did I say something wrong?
How could you say that
to an assemblyman?
These are the minutes from
today's emergency committee meeting.
Did you participate in the meeting
and write this yourself?
No, sir.
The officials who were present
at the meeting wrote them...
Mr. Hwang.
We are...
in positions
that require some legwork.
How will you control the situation
if you sit behind a desk...
and simply receive reports?
This really...
troubles me.
I mean it's safe to say
that the martial law...
has been expanded
mainly because of Gwangju.
I'll make sure to participate
in future meetings myself.
You loaded the bullets backwards.
- Did you do this on purpose?
- I'm sorry, sir.
Hey. Did you join this place
to protect the commies?
How can you call yourself a soldier?
Answer me, you punk.
How dare you load your bullets
backwards?
You stupid punk.
I can't believe you.
You're a darn disgrace.
Corporal Lee.
I'm sorry
about what happened earlier.
I just couldn't get myself
to shoot...
Do you think I fired that shot
because I wanted to?
Hey, Kim Kyung Soo.
Do you think that makes you
a nice person?
This is the army.
If you don't shoot, I have to.
Can you call yourself nice...
if you force things on others
to keep your own hands clean?
That's what you call being selfish.
I'm sorry, sir.
If you don't want to shoot anyone,
arrest them as quickly as you can,
before someone else shoots.
What on earth is that sound?
I've been hearing it all day.
Don't worry. It's probably nothing.
Chang Geun,
it's time to take your medicine.
Did Soo Chan really go to work
this morning?
Why?
Is he not answering the phone
at the office?
Did you actually see Soo Chan leave?
Tell me. What is going on?
Chang Geun.
You need to calm down first.
Tell me! What happened to Soo Chan?
Sir.
Over here. A person has collapsed.
A man has collapsed. Please...
- My gosh.
- Who told you to move?
Do you want to die?
Get back in your position.
What are you all looking at?
Eyes down!
Take him away.
Sir...
Hey. Get back in your position,
you punk.
What? Who was arrested?
Soo Ryeon's older brother.
I'm not sure,
but can you check
if he's really been arrested?
What a hassle.
Tell them I'll check.
But what is going on?
People are calling all day,
asking me to find people.
There's no need for you to know.
Just keep to the house for now.
By the way...
Has Hee Tae called?
No.
You should check on him first.
Don't sit back and do nothing
just because he doesn't call first.
He never asks to see me.
Why aren't you asking
about Jung Tae?
Why are you asking me that
out of the blue?
Jung Tae is your son too.
You haven't seen him in days.
Aren't you worried about him?
Do you think I have the time
to worry about the kid?
That's enough of your nonsense.
Just give me that.
I finally got in touch with Mr. Lee.
He'll be here early in the morning.
That's a relief.
Once he gets here,
let's leave immediately.
Immediately?
Our plan was to stay here
until Mr. Lee comes to get Jin A.
What's with that face?
It's not like that.
Then what is it?
If something is bothering you,
just tell me.
It's just that...
if we leave,
the others will have to do
more work.
That's what I was worried about.
What? Were you thinking
that I'm a pushover?
No way.
I was thinking
you are such a good person.
But listen, Myeong Hee.
If you really want to be good,
you must put yourself first.
If you put others before yourself,
that's hypocrisy, I think.
Don't people normally call that
a sacrifice?
They would normally.
But...
to someone who loves you,
it's hypocrisy.
So for now,
let's put you and me first.
We'll be training indoors
again today.
Get ready and come out
as quickly as you can.
Gosh, I feel so cooped up.
Why can't we go out?
It's my birthday today,
and I'm stuck indoors all day.
Oh, my.
Is it your birthday today, Sung Il?
Gosh, then we should celebrate.
You said
you love comic books, right?
Should we go borrow some comics?
If we can't even train outside,
how can we go to the rental store?
My gosh.
We have two fast runners here.
You two can rush over there
and borrow some.
Gather around. I have a plan.
I'm going grocery shopping.
See you.
Excuse me, Coach.
Do you have any digestive medicine?
I think I have an upset stomach.
You have an upset stomach?
You, Jin Kyu?
- Then let me prick your fingers.
- What?
I think some medicine will do.
Medicine won't do any good.
Pricking all ten fingers
is the best remedy.
You still can't reach them?
You can't make
any long-distance calls?
It's just Gwangju
that's out of reach.
This won't do
I'll have to go there myself.
Go where? To Gwangju?
By yourself?
I've heard some terrible rumors.
That's why I should go there.
(From Kim Hyun Chul,
To Kim Myeong Hee)
I hope everything's fine.
Hyun Chul, where are you going?
Mother, I have to make
a quick trip to Gwangju.
Don't go. Stay with me.
Mother, have a seat for a second.
I'll come back as soon as I know
the kids are fine.
Don't worry and stay put, okay?
My goodness,
you look so beautiful, Mother.
See you later.
You don't have to come out.
- Be careful.
- Don't worry.
Hey, let's get a box
of Choco Pies too.
We'll pretend it's a cake.
Is it your birthday?
You're not the one paying...
My goodness. You should stop.
What if the man dies or something?
You're going too far.
Round up everyone here!
End the martial law!
- End the martial law!
Denounce media corruption!
- Denounce media corruption!
End the unlawful firearms training!
- End the unlawful training!
- This is a democratic nation!
- End the martial law!
End the martial law!
Denounce media corruption!
- Denounce media corruption!
- Take your positions!
- End the unlawful training!
Denounce media corruption!
- Denounce media corruption!
- This is a democratic nation!
- End the martial law!
And halt!
- Until Mount Baekdu is worn away
- And the East Sea runs dry
- May the Lord protect
- And preserve our country
- Mugunghwa, the whole of Korea
- Aim!
- Such a splendid land
What's that sound?
(Release all arrested students!)
Run. Run, now!
Come on, run!
I told you all to leave!
There aren't any tickets.
No tickets at all.
Goodness, why is everyone
gathered around here?
What do you mean?
There aren't any bus tickets?
My goodness.
All the Gwangju-bound buses...
aren't running at the moment.
Then how can I get to Gwangju?
I guess you'd have to walk.
No vehicle is allowed to enter.
You don't have any tickets left?
Goodness, no.
There are absolutely no tickets.
What do I do?
Excuse me. If you have an extra map,
may I borrow it?
You'll actually walk there?
Everyone's trying to flee
Gwangju now.
Why would you go there?
It'll take him over three months
to get there with that limp.
My gosh...
I'm looking for Lee Jin A.
Lee Jin A. Jin A...
Excuse me...
Myeong Hee.
Jin A...
Oh, dear.
Jin A.
Jin A, Daddy is here.
Open your eyes, please.
She regained her consciousness
in the morning.
She's just asleep now
because of the drugs.
So don't worry.
Thankfully, the surgery went well.
Yes, Myeong Hee told me everything.
Thank you, Mr. Hwang.
I didn't really do anything.
It would've been really dangerous
if it weren't for Hee Tae here.
He saved her life.
Thank you, Mr. Hwang.
My gosh... Thank you so much
for saving Jin A's life.
Oh, Myeong Hee.
Go to the ER
and say goodbye to everyone.
I'll go see Seok Chul and join you.
Sure. Take your time.
Myeong Hee.
I forgot to say this earlier
because I was so frazzled.
On my way here, I saw the protest.
And the soldiers were beating up
the protesters...
and even firing their guns.
It was utter chaos.
You didn't know what was going on,
so you must've been shocked.
I sure was shocked,
but that's not important. Your...
Your brother.
Is he still in Gwangju?
My brother? Why do you ask?
I can't stop thinking...
that I saw your little brother
in that mayhem.
The kid looked
just like your brother.
He was wearing a tracksuit
like your brother always does.
Gosh. But I couldn't go up to him...
because I was dodging bullets
in that chaos.
Please... No...
Goodness, the phone's been ringing
off the hook.
Hello, we're training
strictly within the training camp.
You'd like to speak to him?
Just a moment, please.
Hey, Digestive Drink.
Your sister's on the phone for you.
Kim Myeong Soo.
What's going on?
Where is Myeong Soo?
It hurts so much...
Doctor, please hurry.
(Emergency Room)
What happened?
Why are there so many patients
with gunshot wounds?
The troops opened fire on civilians.
The soldiers shot them?
Are these all the victims?
No, the victims lying in the streets
would fill an entire truck.
We're already so short-staffed.
But we were told
they'd even shoot ambulances,
so no one wants to go out there.
What? They'll shoot ambulances?
They even shoot little kids.
They obviously don't care.
Let's go out there and help.
We can't let people
die in the streets.
Let's take our cars...
and pick up the injured.
Who wants to come with me?
Goodness, please help her.
- Doctor, will my son be okay?
- Of course.
Have you lost your mind?
Where do you think you're going?
I'm going to get patients.
There are people
with gunshot wounds everywhere.
They're not the only people
out there.
There are soldiers everywhere too.
Are you saying
we should just sit back and watch?
Someone has to go there.
But why does that someone
have to be you?
Do you have two lives?
I have to go.
Stop being so righteous!
Don't tell me what to do!
What do you think you're doing?
Get out.
I'm not getting out until you do.
Get out. You don't have to do this.
Don't tell me what to do.
Mr. Hwang, are you coming with us?
Yes.
(The 61st Preliminaries
of the National Sports Festival)
Man, I can't believe this.
Doctor, this way.
Are you okay? Can you hear me?
Myeong Hee,
I'll carry her on my back.
Careful, easy.
Let's go.
Get in the ambulance! Hurry!
Myeong Hee, get in. Hurry.
Get in. Hurry up.
If you leave it tangled,
it's your loss,
whether it's your shoelaces
or training.
Isn't running fast
the most important thing to you?
Where are you going?
Get in the car.
Let's get out of here.
Hee Tae, I hear a kid crying
from over there.
Have you gone mad?
The soldiers are shooting at us.
I must go. I have to go check!
Kim Myeong Hee!
What if it's Myeong Soo?
Why would he be here now?
Mr. Lee said he saw Myeong Soo.
He saw him here looking all lost
when the soldiers were firing.
That's Myeong Soo's shoe.
Myeong Hee. Myeong Hee!
Darn it. Who's that wench?
I got this. I'll go get her, sir.
Hey!
Myeong Soo.
Myeong Soo...
If you don't want to shoot anyone,
arrest them as quickly as you can,
before someone else shoots.
Kim Kyung Soo.
Hee Tae.
Myeong Hee, what are you doing?
Get in the car! Mr. Hwang!
Myeong Hee, let's go.
Come on, Myeong Hee.
- Get in, Myeong Hee.
- Quick!
Myeong Hee.
Myeong Hee!
Goodness. How will you find them...
in this mayhem?
Please fix a meal for the kids
if I'm late.
You rascals!
Coach, the North Korean army...
The North Korean army
has invaded our country!
What?
Be careful.
Go.
Are you two all right?
Your brother called earlier.
He says he's back
at the training camp safe and sound.
Stop. What brings you here?
Good day, sir.
I have some urgent business
in Gwangju.
Civilians are not allowed to pass.
Please go back.
Sir.
I'm a vendor at Yangdong Market.
My kids are in Gwangju
at the moment.
Please let me through.
One per person, okay?
Those who have served in the army
get first dibs.
Come forward.
Hey.
Where did you guys get the guns?
We got them
from the Reserve Forces' armory.
What are you planning to do
with the guns?
You want to wage war
against armed soldiers?
Then what?
Are we supposed to do nothing
and just let them shoot?
Did you not see the flyers
they distributed today?
They're trying to make us
look like mere rioters.
Why give them a reason...
They're massacring civilians.
Why must we remain immaculate?
Is it lawful for soldiers
to shoot innocent civilians?
And is going against it unlawful?
What is the law to begin with?
The law was made
so the people could be protected.
You do what you need to do.
I'm going to do
what I think is right.
Those who have served in the army
get first dibs.
Come forward.
Are you sure it's Lee Soo Chan?
Don't bother. I'll handle it myself.
Okay, keep me updated.
What was that call about?
Oh, that.
The rioters robbed another armory.
Things are going according to plan.
(Head of Anti-communist
Investigation, Hwang Ki Nam)
Why do you look so worried?
Is it because of your son?
My son? What do you mean?
Well...
Your son was arrested in the past...
while helping commies.
Oh, that...
If you're referring to his arrest
for treating a suspect,
it was just a misunderstanding
that happened...
because my son is a medical student.
They released him right away.
So he was just in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
Then I'm relieved.
But you know...
Your son.
Where is he now?
He recently moved to Seoul
with his fiancee.
Oh, he's in Seoul now?
Are you sure?
Sir, are you here
to keep an eye on me?
I'm saying this just in case.
Make sure your son stays away
from trouble.
If he's caught in the wrong place
again at this critical time,
it'll definitely look suspicious.
This punk...
Myeong Hee.
Hee Tae, you were right.
I'm a hypocrite.
Earlier, in that alleyway...
the moment I checked the face
of that injured kid,
I felt relieved,
because it wasn't Myeong Soo.
He was probably someone's son...
and someone's little brother too.
But at that moment, I felt relieved.
Is that wrong?
I feel relieved too...
whenever I see that
you're not the one who's been hurt.
Is it wrong to hope
for someone you love...
to be safe?
If that's the case,
I'll just be a bad person then.
Nice people always tend to regret
their wrongdoings.
Bad people feel nothing at all.
A real hypocrite...
never thinks of him or herself
as a hypocrite.
I didn't tell you
about Myeong Soo...
on purpose.
In case you wouldn't let me go.
You did the right thing.
If I knew it was
because of Myeong Soo,
I would've never let you go.
I would've gone alone.
Is it okay for you to be in danger
but not me?
Well, I have nothing left.
Even if something happens to me,
you'll have Myeong Soo...
and your parents.
But if I lose you,
I'll have nothing left.
So from now on,
just leave it to me...
when it comes to doing
dangerous things.
I'm not telling you what to do.
I'm asking you sincerely.
Come on, no need to worry.
I'm just feeling a bit cold.
What's going on out there?
Did the North Korean Army
really invade us?
It's not the North Korean army.
It's our own army.
I'm telling you,
it's the North Korean army.
Why would our soldiers
shoot our own people?
Why did the soldiers
suddenly turn bad?
Guys, don't you remember
"Mazinger Z?"
The real villain was Dr. Hell,
who tried to conquer the world.
There's probably a real villain...
who's controlling the soldiers
like his puppets.
Take that punk away.
Let's get going.
- Hey, you!
- Come over here!
- Come here!
- Follow me.
- Let go of me!
- Take him away.
Then...
Who's the real villain?
What is he trying to conquer?
I can't stand
this childish nonsense.
Mr. Hwang.
So I've come to help you after all.
I won't help you twice,
so be careful.
By the way,
do you know where your sister is?
I can't reach her.
There's a car waiting outside,
so don't go outside
and take care of yourself for now.
Sir.
Please release the others too.
They're all innocent people
who were dragged here. Please.
At least the injured, or the kids...
Stop blabbering
and just live a quiet life.
I'm holding myself back...
from throwing your whole family
in prison.
Stop moving around, you punks.
Private Kim Kyung Soo...
still doesn't want to fire
his weapon.
Open your eyes.
You should see this yourself.
See how much they're suffering
because of you.
What do you think?
Do you think you can shoot now?
I knew it.
You don't care
if your comrades die or not.
All you care about
are those hopeless rebels.
Get back up, you punk.
Kim Kyung Soo.
You're not a good person.
There's no such thing
as a good person to begin with.
It's all about making
the best choice for each moment.
But...
at least you don't force others
to make that choice for you.
That doesn't make you a good person.
It just means you're strong.
I like you
because you're a strong person.
She was a nurse.
What?
I can't shoot someone
who isn't a rebel.
Myeong Hee, what are you doing?
Get in the car! Mr. Hwang!
Come on!
Seok Chul is alive.
She's in Gwangju right now.
You don't have to give us a ride.
I'm just dropping you off
on my way to get more blood.
That's the least I can do
for a comrade...
that shared a near-death experience
with me.
Shall I drop you off at the station?
Oh, how about...
we go see Myeong Soo
before going to the station?
Can we?
You'll feel reassured
once you see that he's okay.
You should give him back
his shoes too.
Goodness, all this romance
is making me cringe.
Then what?
Where shall I drop you off?
- It's near the terminal...
- Myeong Hee.
What are you doing here?
Just come with me.
Myeong Soo is waiting too.
Oh, we were headed
to his camp right now...
Let's go back to Naju.
We should get out of this place
right now.
Just take Myeong Soo with you.
- I can take care of myself.
- Kim Myeong Hee!
I'll go help Dr. Yoo for a bit.
No, you don't have to.
My, I'm relieved.
We're short-handed here.
I'll go start the ambulance.
I'll leave you to talk.
(Gwangju Pyeonghwa Hospital)
How can a father and daughter
be so icy to each other?
It won't be easy for you
once you get married.
Now I know how she turned out
so hard-boiled.
"Hard-boiled?" No way.
She's as soft as tofu.
It worries me.
You must be blinded by love.
And there's nothing
you can do about that.
Anyway, how did the other hospital
get so much blood?
Through donations.
They got that much
from employee donations?
No, from the citizens.
They made announcements
about a blood shortage,
and people are still lining up
to donate their blood.
Why? Is it a piece you like?
Not me. My friend likes it.
What in the world?
(Gwangju Pyeonghwa Hospital)
How many times must I tell you?
I'm not going.
Why? Did he ask you
to stay with him?
Does he want to marry you?
Stay out of my life.
What about his parents?
Do they even know
you two are dating?
If he can't even introduce you
to them,
how can you trust him?
You're going to regret this.
Come with me to Naju.
Don't say that.
You don't understand.
Ms. Kim!
Dr. Yoo and Mr. Hwang...
(Youth of May)
What are you talking about?
The two left together.
But there was only one person there.
He might be dying somewhere.
And there's nothing I can do.
They say they found Hee Tae
and are keeping him there.
Did they really say that?
He's going to ruin your life
in the end.
He's not the one who ruined my life.
It's you.
I'll kill everyone in your family.
Hee Tae might die.
What are you talking about?
I'll stay right here
even if lightning strikes...
so that Hee Tae can find me.