♪Memories of the past are always vivid♪
♪They accompanied me to take every step♪
♪On the road♪
♪Going through heat and cold♪
♪The bumpy journey
has rendered my longing♪
♪Rock solid♪
♪The same moonlight
shines on our shoulders♪
♪Even if we are far away separated♪
♪We are close in our hearts♪
♪The wind blew away the past♪
♪I look for your distant location
on the starry night♪
♪In the ocean of faces♪
♪For you, my heart burns and races♪
♪Despite its turns and twists,
fate is in my hands♪
♪May waiting convert regrets
into a happy ending♪
♪May solitary figures
find right companions♪
♪And become a pair♪
=Time Flies and You Are Here=
=Episode 17=
(Playing with my sword while drinking,
hearing the sound war wakes me up)
Don't be upset.
I dispatched all the employees
of Su Chang Ji to search for the Helu.
Look.
We're of noble households.
With so many employees,
I'll search the entire
Wujiang Prefecture.
I refuse to believe
that
we'll not get the sword back.
If it was that easy,
Zhao Xiaoqian wouldn't have
been enraged.
It's all my fault.
If I was more cautious,
just a little more,
this wouldn't have happened.
Today is the day of the selection
to pick the main dancer.
Do not worry.
Let's remain positive.
We need to hurry to the brothel.
Yan Boyang
is gambling with Xu Shu
over a sword.
He is about to lose everything.
Is that true?
Let's hurry.
I'll check out the brothel.
Inform Zhao Xiaoqian.
Don't you have to head to the academy?
The sword
might not be the one you're looking for.
If you do not participate
in the selection,
you're going to lose
against Shen Zhaowen.
My goal
was never to defeat her.
Hurry up.
Xiaoman.
Let's go.
Xu Shu!
Big!
Open up!
Mr. Yan,
what's wrong?
You haven't had your
fair share of losses?
After Commandery Prince fed you,
you've returned to bark at me.
Cut the crap.
Let's play on the bet.
Before I could retrieve the Helu,
none of you are allowed to leave.
Bet?
What are you talking about?
You even lost your trousers to me.
Do you still want more?
Dream on.
Forget it.
Let's go.
Hold up.
Xiaoman?
This hairpin is made of Hetian Jade.
It's an valuable item of
the Commandery Prince's Mansion.
What do you say?
I'd place this as leverage.
Lady Xie,
we're rolling dice.
A mere lady like you
have no rights
to bet with me.
I'm a member
of Commandery Prince's Mansion.
It doesn't matter.
Even if the Commandery Prince
himself was here,
I cannot bend the rules.
Men,
bring up some good wine.
A person's tolerance for alcohol
depicts one's capabilities.
If you're able to finish
this jar of Meishou Wine,
I'll play the bet with you.
Fine.
I'll do it.
Sure.
However, it's up to me
if I'd place the Helu
as leverage.
Fine.
I'll drink.
Xiaoman.
How impressive.
You...
You rascal.
You tricked Yan Boyang to frame me.
I am not done with you.
Come on.
Hanchen,
she didn't mean it.
No one would wish for
something like that to happen.
We shouldn't harm the living
for a lifeless object.
A lifeless object?
Why do all of you think of
my brother's possession
as a lifeless object?
Your Highness.
Lady Su insisted on
barging into the mansion.
Nobody could stop her.
Hold it right there.
What are you doing?
You are being rude!
This is the Commandery Prince's Mansion.
It's not a place for
a meagre peasant like you
to enter as you please.
I do not care even if you kill me.
I need to see Zhao Xiaoqian today.
You...
I...
Stop it!
What are you doing here?
Xiaoman and Boyang are caught
in trouble at the brothel.
You should head over immediately.
Brothel?
What are they doing there?
It's an emergency.
Quit asking unnecessary questions.
Don't you feel bad enough
for casting Xiaoman out?
She cried all night because of you.
In order to recover the Helu,
she headed straight to the brothel
to confront Xu Shu alone.
She's forsaking even her reputation.
What else do you want from her?
Your Highness,
do not believe this wench.
Xie Xiaoman lost the remnant
of the late Duke of Yongguo
and challenged Your Highness.
This peasant is Lady Xie's cousin.
You mustn't buy her lies.
Zhu Momo,
His Highness will have the say here.
She cried?
She did.
She was heart-broken.
Are you satisfied?
Prepare the horse.
Depart for the brothel.
Your Highness!
There are rules!
Xu Shu!
I'm extending the challenge.
If I win,
not only do I want the Helu back,
you
are going to offer three kowtows
as an apology to Zhao Xiaoqian.
What happens if you lose?
If I lose,
I'll kowtow three times before you.
All right.
Bet with her.
Accept her bet.
Accept it.
Xu Shu!
Open it.
Small.
Open up.
Three fours and a six.
It's the Xiaojinzhang.
That's four points.
That's awesome.
I have a good feeling about this.
He'd win this round.
It's his win.
Come on.
Reveal it.
Open up.
Open.
It's the Hunjianglong!
It's a win by five points!
No way.
We won!
That's amazing.
That's right.
What do you think, Mr. Xu?
You didn't expect
a village girl like me
could roll the dice well.
You're a respectable man.
You should concede defeat.
Not only am I retrieving the Helu,
you are going to kowtow
three times before my husband
as an apology.
That's right.
You cheated.
They cheated.
Seize them!
We did not!
We did not cheat.
Clearly, it was you instead.
You went against your words.
You're shameless.
I'm going to beat you to pulp.
Commander Prince of Julu has arrived.
His Highness is here.
Your Highness.
My husband is here.
He bullied me.
What?
Are you trying to accuse my wife?
Are you even worthy?
Your Highness.
It's
Mr. Yan who lost the bet.
I can't embarrass myself
and give everything up.
Do you want it?
No, not at all.
Put it down.
Xiaoman.
You said, objects remain lifeless
while men were given life.
What do you mean?
Men cannot live forever in the past.
Everyone has to move on.
Here, Xiaoman.
Your Highness,
I beg your pardon.
Return home and inform your master
to meet me tonight.
If he doesn't show up, he's a loser.
Watch out.
How is she doing?
Your Highness.
Fortunately, it was Meishou Wine.
If she was given
other types of liquor,
she would have
caught a bad fever.
She was fed some hangover soup.
I'm afraid the alcohol is kicking in.
Just attend to her accordingly.
She will be fine once
the alcohol subsides.
All right.
Thank you.
I shall excuse myself.
Hanchen.
I...
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
I...
I shouldn't have taken the Helu.
I shouldn't have
taken the Helu
from Xiaoman knowing
that it was with her.
I'm sorry.
Zhao Xiaoqian!
You deserve this!
Boyang.
After this blow,
this is over.
Do not bring this up again.
Boyang, are you all right?
I'm fine.
This peasant is treated like a princess.
I even have to take care of you.
Rascal.
You're so mean.
It's the day of the selection
for the main dancer.
You might miss it.
Will you be unhappy?
It's all right if you're upset.
The others perform
for Xingzhou and the rest.
You may perform it for me.
Isn't that right?
Lady Shen.
Young Master Shen...
Young Master Shen is here.
I interrogated Xu Shu.
He said you asked him to steal the Helu.
Why?
Spill it!
I just wanted to teach
Xie Xiaoman a lesson.
Shen Zhaowen,
I can't believe you resorted
to such lowly methods.
Do not forget who you are.
You and I both know why
Zhao Xiaoqian wouldn't
bring out the Helu.
The incident caused big troubles
back then.
Hanchen
hasn't been able to get over it!
Look at you.
For your own sake,
in order to sabotage Xiaoman,
you even had your eyes on the Helu.
Shen Zhaowen,
I haven't been away from the capital
for long,
yet you employed
such detestable means!
What do you know?
You left home when you were young.
You cared only about yourself.
You left without saying anything.
What about me?
If Zhao Xiaoqian doesn't marry me,
I'll be sent to the palace.
All you do is chastise me.
You showed no concern for me.
Everyone
is only concerned about your future.
For the sake of your future,
I'm forced to enter the palace.
Why?
I'm still young!
Enter...
Enter the palace?
The Empress did not bear a son.
All Her Highness has is
an adopted Crown Prince.
The Crown Prince's
influence is deteriorating.
Noble Consort Zhang is in favour.
Guess what?
The Empress wants me to earn
His Majesty's favour on her behalf.
Father dare not disobey.
It's all for the sake of your future.
Young Master Shen,
Lady Shen suffered a lot at home.
I'm you're aware.
The issue of
Commandery Prince's concubine
has evoked commotion in the capital.
Your words
will only hurt Lady Shen more.
Besides, Xie Xiaoman has
to be eliminated anyway.
It's a good thing to sow discord between
Commandery Prince and her.
A family of aristocrats?
Wealth and honour?
Life of affluence and extravagance?
These can only be exchanged
with a woman's dignity.
At the capital,
the date of my wedding with
Hanchen has been decided.
If Xie Xiaoman isn't out of the picture,
are you going to
allow your sister to bear the shame of
losing against a concubine
for the rest of her life?
That's enough!
Do you think
what I did was despicable?
Lady Shen, do not say that.
We can't possibly enter the palace.
His Majesty is already in his fifties.
Your entire life would be gone.
Besides, Xie Xiaoman was the one
who crawled into
His Highness' bed first.
We...
We should...
We should fight for ourselves.
We should fight
for ourselves.
I'm running out of time.
I received news from the capital.
Princess Consort Pu has
entered the palace many times.
The Empress started to given in.
The marriage
would be final.
Do not give up.
You're right.
I cannot give up.
Fetch me the costume
for the Dance of Nuo.
I'm going to show Xie Xiaoman
that I, Shen Zhaowen,
am the Commandery Princess Rong'an,
granted by His Majesty.
I can't admit defeat.
Yes, Lady Shen.
(Bailu Academy)
Hit whoever you like.
Why must you come to me?
If I spar with others,
it will be an insult to the Helu.
I have anger built up in me.
It's suffocating.
That's why I asked for you.
I haven't sparred with you for a while.
Come on.
You haven't used
the sword in many years.
What makes today different?
Someone told me,
if you do not treat a wound,
it'd remain there forever.
That's why, I would like to see
what happens
when I tear it.
Enlighten me.
Please go easy on me.
One loses by pride
and gains by modesty.
The capable will find their place
for the sake of the nation's peace.
Back when we wielded
the sword for the first time,
I lost to you once.
His Majesty said my heart was disturbed.
After my brother's death,
I abandoned the sword and bow.
You once asked me why.
Today, I'll tell you.
Once I wield the Helu again,
nobody will be able to
take it away from me.
The capital has its eyes on us.
Both of us cannot run
away from our destinies.
Lingniang came
bearing
the promise of marriage
between you and her.
Are Your Highness going to
deny the promise as well?
It's not going to be easy.
I'll never marry Lingniang.
You know that well.
I will not
accept the marriage.
Please go easy on me.
Same for me.
You left for the examination,
drape in white during early fall.
Your focus harmonizes with
the gushing of branches.
You obtained excellence with
your future laid before you.
As the peach blossom blooms,
the doors of your future opened up.
As vast as the sea stretches,
as far as the phoenix could soar,
you took your books
and left as far as it took.
By the same day next year,
you've attained success.
You'd sigh at the endeavour of others.
Although I'm a lady,
through prayers,
I hope all fellow scholars will
live up to your conscience,
live up to the promise for the people,
live up to the teachings of the sage,
and live up to sustain
the peace of the nation.
Live up to your conscience.
Live up to the promise for the people.
Live up to the teachings of the sage.
Live up to sustain
the peace of the nation.
Are you doing fine, my brother-in-law?
As the concubine of
Commandery Prince,
I came to pay you respect.
Commandery Prince granted
the Hulu to me for a ceremonial dance,
so I came to inform you.
Commandery Prince is filial and loyal,
abiding by religious teachings
is part of his nature.
The brotherhood you shared,
not even a single meal
together could be forgone.
The yearning and grievance
are expressed through emotions.
Fervency and ardor
are displayed through actions.
Your wish
is known to Commandery Prince.
You wished to devote yourself
to the people and the state.
It's the conviction of a virtuous man
and the principle of an ambitious man.
Commandery Prince has
the most admiration for you.
Of lowly origins,
I met His Highness
in marriage.
I share His Highness'
pain and happiness.
I'll accumulate virtues with gratitude
towards you.
Please guard over your brother.
Today is a great day.
May your spirit
rest in peace.
I offer my respects to you,
my brother-in-law.
Maoya.
I made three wishes today.
Would you like to know?
Firstly, may all things
go well for Xiaoman.
Secondly, bless Hanchen
with a long life.
Thirdly, may Xiaoman
fall in love with me.
We shall stay by each other forever.
There are some things
I haven't told you.
I'll confess them all today.
I love you.
I want to be with you
for the rest of my life.
I want to practise calligraphy with you
and watch the clouds
as they drift and flutter.
♪Approach you slowly♪
I want to eat the cakes you make
and wear the garments you sew.
♪Your shadow under the moonlight♪
I want to spend the
rest of my life with you.
Do you understand?
♪As detailed as the poem♪
♪The word spoken softly♪
Fool,
it's time for you to shut your eyes.
♪When you smile,
you fill up all my view♪
♪When I close my eyes♪
♪You dance like the cloud♪
♪We grow old together slowly♪
According to the disciples,
Mr. Li, you burnt the midnight oil
to compose poetry
and articles.
You also sneaked in
three jars of Lihuabai Wine.
That article
consists of the unspeakable.
As for the wine,
since you
have yet to clear them out for me,
I shall wallow deeper in
and finish them before
I leave the monastery.
I'm just curious.
Over the days spent here at the temple,
did you gain anything, Mr. Li?
Not yet,
but my tolerance for
alcohol has increased.
I guess you could consider that a gain.
Before coming up the mountain,
I told myself,
I'll only do two things once I'm here,
composing and drinking.
I've written everything I could.
My wine almost runs out.
It's time for me to depart.
Where will you go?
I'll go back to the capital
to take the civil examination.
What about the works you composed?
They do not worth a dime.
Instead of piling up the trash,
I shall burn them all to ashes
to get rid of them.
Mr. Li, you've yet
attained clarity in your heart.
Of secularity,
release the obsession.
Go with the flow.
Remain aware of the self
and stay true to yourself.
What I currently want
is to give up
and leave.
Mr. Li,
this is bad.
Your compositions were blown away.
I...
I shall clean it up.
Forget it.
It's the heaven's will.
(Jingnv Pavilion)
Fellow ladies,
you're exempt from classes tomorrow.
Since the civil examination
is approaching,
Principal Yang is taking fellow
scholars to Mount Kunyan Temple
to pray for divine blessings.
Those who are interested
may sign up with Supervisor Xu
at the Teachers' Office later.
That's all for today.
Class is dismissed.
Thank you, teacher.
Xiaoman.
Are you going to
Mount Kunyan Temple?
Yes.
I heard
Congwen is undergoing cultivation
up in Mount Kunyan Temple.
What's going on?
You're acting weird.
Zhao Xiaoqian told me...
What did he say?
He said that he wants to
spend the rest of his life with me.
Everyone knows this.
You're the only one
who's ignorant about that.
When he said that to you,
what were you thinking?
It's decided then.
Tomorrow, we shall head to
Mount Kunyan Temple together.
It's my pleasure
to befriend Lingniang.
A daughter of nobility
will not mingle with
the peasant households.
What's going on?
Don't you think
Shen Zhaowen has been
acting weird lately?
What do you mean?
I'm not sure.
It's a gut feeling.
Really?
In a monastery deep in the forest,
listening to the pointless
debates of philosophers.
In the freezing winter, at the halls,
entertained by the woodcutter.
You've changed.
You're
always saying things
I do not understand.
What has she become?
You resemble a rooster.
You're the rooster.
What do you say
about what I told you a few days agi?
What do you mean?
I need to study.
Go away.
I'm talking about my feelings for you.
What's in your mind?
Lecher.
Zhu Momo told me
that Lady Xie
refuses to consummate with
Commandery Prince.
How unruly
and absurd.
You're constantly
tormented by Zhu Momo.
Let me give you a hand.
I'll spend the night here
to shut Zhu Momo up.
What do you think?
Lecher.
You thug.
Tell me.
What do you want?
Do you like me?
I like...
I like flowers, not you.
Xie Xiaoman.
Fine.
When...
When we arrived at
Mount Kunyan Temple,
Lake Nanming,
I'll give you my answer.
All right.
Tomorrow, at Mount Kunyan Temple,
Lake Nanming,
I'll be waiting for you.
Lecher.
You told me that
the capital is reconsidering
your marriage with
the daughter of Shen Family.
You haven't
told Xiaoman about this, have you?
I'll never marry Lingniang.
But no matter how hard
you try to resist,
it's pointless.
Do not
tell Xiaoman about this.
After I resolve everything,
I'll tell her.
Amitabha.
It's an urgent matter.
The Supreme Venerable Sovereign.
Gautama Buddha.
Lord of the Soil and the Ground.
Goddess of the Moon.
Please manifest the answer.
What's the answer in Xiaoman's heart?
Please give me an answer.
What does this mean?
Two suns and a moon.
Possessed by love.
This girl is in love.
You're ridiculous.
I do not believe you.
You're lying to yourself.
Recently,
you were occupied with
the affairs of Zhao Xiaoqian.
Everyone could tell.
You're the only one
who remains ignorant.
If you do not have feelings
for Zhao Xiaoqian,
list out his flaws.
Hu Momo said,
when a person is in love,
they believe their lovers to be perfect.
Since you do not love Zhao Xiaoqian,
tell me
his flaws.
He's fierce.
He screams at me all the time.
However, it seems like
he's doing it for my own good.
He's a lecher.
All of a sudden, he'd...
What would he do?
Hanchen.
I'm talking to you.
Everyone is heading for
Mount Kunyan Temple
to pray for good results.
On the other hand,
you insist to see the stupid lake.
What are you up to?
I have a feeling
Xie Xiaoman is really going to
be your sister-in-law today.
Really?
Not bad at all.
However, we're on the holy ground.
Don't go too far.
Return to your seat.
Look at you.
You're still in denial.
I suggest you accept his love.
Otherwise,
his childhood friend, Lady Shen would
come before you to get him.
Is Shen Zhaowen's feelings
that obvious?
It's more than obvious
to everyone.
Even the woman
who sells baked bread
outside my house could tell.
You're the only ignorant one.
There's one thing I find weird.
I can't figure it out.
On the day of the Dance of Nuo,
only the members of the mansion
knew I took the Helu to the academy.
In the academy,
you're the only one I told.
Look.
In Jingnv Pavilion,
who else would recognise the Helu?
Are you saying...
The one who ordered Xu Shu
to steal the Helu
was Shen Yan's men.
Shen Yan is her brother.
Without a reason,
Why did Xu Shu want the Helu?
Shen Zhaowen?
Shen Zhaowen tried to frame you up.
She must know
how important the Helu is
to Zhao Xiaoqian.
She took the Helu
in order to provoke Zhao Xiaoqian
and cast you out.
But we don't have any proof.
Once we arrive at
Mount Kunyan Temple,
I'll question her.
That's right.
She employed such detestable
measures to harm you.
We can't sit by and do nothing.
Once we arrive at the temple,
I'll confront her with you.
(Namo Amitabha)
Abbot,
this is the director of our academy.
Amitabha.
For prayers regarding
the civil examination,
over the century,
Mount Kunyan Temple
proves to be most efficient.
The principal sends us
to offer our prayers
until the civil examination
comes to an end.
We apologize for interrupting
serenity of the monastery.
Principal Yang has
informed me beforehand.
Prayers and worships
are things to rejoice over.
I'm eternally grateful
for the donation for the temple.
The chambers are cleaned.
The fellow scholars may
enjoy a meal first.
After the meal,
they may head to the main hall
to offer their prayers.
Thank you, abbot.
As a man,
you should just do it.
As usual, wooden plaques
will be distributed to all tonight.
After settling down at
your rooms,
you may head to the back halls for food.
After the meal,
we shall offer prayers together.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Wang Weicheng.
Supervisor Xu.
Can you pass it to me first?
I share a room with Lady Xie.
Thank you.
Wang Weicheng.
(Room number one)
What are you doing?
I've got the plaque.
We're husband and wife.
We should share a room.
I do not want to sleep with you.
Are you expecting us
to sleep separately?
Let's go.
Return to the room
to pack up with me.
No.
We have matters to attend to.
Quit pinching me.
How about this?
Go ahead first.
I'll meet you later.
I'll force an answer out of her.
Dear, I can't wait any longer.
Why are you not moving?
Lang Mengzi.
Present.
Let go.
Minggu and I are up to something.
Let me go.
You...
We're on the holy ground.
Such insolence.
♪Ask the moon whether it has seen♪
♪The other end of the earth♪
♪Your feelings fluctuate
like the moon's wane and wax♪
♪Have they ever been the same?♪
♪Carried by misty clouds,
the moon came into your eyes♪
♪As a substitute for me, it appeared♪
♪Cast our eyes over the bustling street♪
♪Don't shed tears when we part♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪