♪Memories of the past are always vivid♪
♪They accompanied me to take every step♪
♪On the road♪
♪Going through heat and cold♪
♪The bumpy journey
has rendered my longing♪
♪Rock solid♪
♪The same moonlight
shines on our shoulders♪
♪Even if we are far away separated♪
♪We are close in our hearts♪
♪The wind blew away the past♪
♪I look for your distant location
on the starry night♪
♪In the ocean of faces♪
♪For you, my heart burns and races♪
♪Despite its turns and twists,
fate is in my hands♪
♪May waiting convert regrets
into a happy ending♪
♪May solitary figures
find right companions♪
♪And become a pair♪
=Time Flies and You Are Here=
=Episode 18=
(Once the happening temple
is now covered in dazzling rain)
Let go!
Minggu and I are up to something.
Let me go.
You...
We're on the holy ground.
Such insolence.
Stand right there.
Don't move.
Each time you move,
I'll remove one Su Chang Ji branch.
You...
Aren't you silly?
I just want to bring you to
take a look at Lake Nanming.
There were too many people just now.
I brought you here to speak to you.
What do you think?
Are you going?
You bully.
Let's go.
I don't believe it.
You keep bullying Xiaoman.
Minggu.
Why do you keep following me?
Do I?
I thought today's weather is quite good.
Why don't we go to the back mountain
to pluck cassia twigs?
I don't know if the weather's good,
but I'm not in a good mood.
Leave me alone.
You're wearing pearls.
It's beautiful.
Each of them is plump
and shiny.
I can tell right away
it's Naga Pearls of
the Eastern Sea right away.
What's that saying again?
Good pearls match good people.
It's nice.
I don't know what kind of pearl this is.
Anyway,
it's a family heirloom
my mother gave to me..
Where are you going?
Bring me along.
No way.
It involves resentment between women.
Go elsewhere.
No.
(Puguangming Hall)
Little monk,
is Li Su
staying at your temple?
Then,
where is he now?
He won't tell.
Your believer, Shen Zhaowen,
is willing to become a
vegetarian for three years
in exchange for a happy marriage
and harmony between me and my husband.
Since you are so sincere,
Buddha will definitely grant
you and His Highness
a lovely marriage
and happiness as a couple.
Lady Shen,
if you want Buddha to bless you,
should you also ask yourself
if you did something
against your conscience?
Watch your tone, Lady Su.
What do you mean by that?
What do I mean?
Lady Shen
should know what I'm talking about.
Lady Su,
be careful with what you say.
I've always been careful,
but someone
isn't so careful in her ways.
Tell me.
Why did you instruct someone
to steal the Helu?
Watch what you say, Lady Su.
Lady Su, you're so vulgar
to be blaming others
in a Buddhist temple.
What evidence do you have
to make you say so?
Evidence?
Across the entire Wujiang Prefecture,
who doesn't know
Xu Shu is acting on
Shen Family's orders?
What other evidence is needed?
Say it!
Why did you frame Xieman?
I didn't.
Frame her?
She doesn't deserve it.
Lady Su is willful and impulsive.
Is that your family teaching?
Our family teaching
isn't up to you,
a servant, to judge!
Today, I'm asking you.
Why did you get someone to
take away the Helu?
Ridiculous.
My lady is from a noble family.
She doesn't need to
argue with you vulgar people.
Lady Su,
your sisters
are so vulgar,
dirty losers who cannot
amount to anything.
Even if Lady Xie gets divorced,
it isn't our lady's fault.
Fine.
Yan Boyang,
come in!
Go!
What are you trying to do?
Coward.
Move aside!
You...
Let go of me!
You evil woman.
Let go!
How dare you bully my cousin.
I didn't.
Go away!
Who told you to bully my cousin?
I didn't!
Do you think I'll go easy on you?
Let go!
Let me tell you!
You can bully anyone!
Oh no, the jade bottle's broken.
It's Principal Yang's offering.
Master says
women are fierce like tigers.
What are you all doing in our temple?
You even broke
Principal Yang's jade bottle.
Evil woman!
Go away!
Su Wei!
Evil woman!
I'm going to teach you a lesson today!
Lady!
Go look for His Highness.
I'll donate money if you found him.
Go now!
Wake up, my lady.
My lady!
What are you trying to tell me?
What do I want to tell you?
Don't you know that very well?
Why did I fall in love
with you,
a heartless person who says
one thing and means another?
I know.
Do you know
this place is where we first...
Stop there.
In fact, when I was little,
I never thought that
I would fall in love with someone.
Never.
Back then,
I didn't have time to
think about all these.
Yet, this young lady
came into my life.
She and I are totally different.
She grew up in the countryside
and led a carefree life.
However, this young lady
doesn't know.
It's as if she has supernatural powers.
Before I knew her,
my heart
had never felt
so alive before.
I mean it.
You can say I'm selfish if you want,
or overbearing,
but I'm thinking
if she could forever
stay by my side,
then does it mean
my life doesn't have to
be so lifeless anymore?
I...
Your Highness,
it's bad!
They're fighting in the hall!
Lady Shen is injured!
(Buddha's Light Shining)
Lady!
Lady, wake up!
His Highness is here.
Your Highness.
Please save her, Your Highness.
Are you all right?
Lady.
Go get a physician!
Sure. Hurry up!
Let's go and get a physician.
It wasn't me.
It really wasn't me.
She fell on her own.
Minggu,
you'll be fine.
She fell on her own.
It wasn't me.
Outrageous!
It isn't severe.
Just a wound on the skin surface.
However, don't let the wound come
into contact with water for few days,
and apply medicated ointment.
When the scab forms,
don't touch with your hand.
Otherwise, there will be a scar.
I don't want a scar.
I get that.
Thank you.
I don't want a scar.
Don't worry.
There won't be one.
The physician said
there won't be a scar if you're careful.
Don't look anymore.
How's Lady Shen?
The temple's in the mountains,
with no physicians or medicine near us.
Why don't we send her to
the clinic for treatment?
She'll be fine.
She only needs to rest for a few days.
Okay.
It's lucky that she is fine.
Thank God.
Hanchen,
can you keep me company for a while?
I'm a little scared.
What do you mean she'll be fine?
Su Wei's the one who
challenged her first
and hit her.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Director,
you have to
seek justice for Lady Shen.
Or else...
Or else, is the reputation of
all the ladies in Jingnv Pavilion
going to be affected by them as well?
Shut up!
I need to check how Xiaoman's doing.
I'll ask Zipei to keep you company.
Hanchen,
I don't want Zipei.
I only want you.
Just like when we were young,
you stayed by my side
to keep me company.
Director Xu, how do you
plan to handle this matter?
Since Lady Shen's all right,
and she also realized she did wrong...
Director, that's easy for you to say.
You should see what kind
of barbaric thing
your student did.
My lady
is the Commandery Princess Rong'an
coronated by His Majesty.
If anything happens,
is Su Family going to be responsible
or you?
Well...
I'll be responsible for my own actions.
I started the fight,
but Lady Shen
incidentally stepped on the pearls,
fell on the floor and got hurt.
Am I also responsible for that?
At most,
I'll let you hit me back.
Su Wei,
all you need to do is apologize.
Shut up.
Minggu is my sister.
My sister did wrong,
so I'll apologize to you on her behalf.
Xiaoman.
All the medicine and
nourishment from now on
will be borne by Su Family.
Xiaoman.
Lady Shen.
Xiaoman,
we...
Go out for a while.
What are you trying to do?
I have something to say to her.
Go out for a while.
Hanchen,
it's all right.
Are you responsible for
stealing the Helu?
What?
The Helu was lost once?
Why would Xu Shu take the Helu
for no reason?
Only people from
the Commandery Prince's Mansion.
knew it's with me.
In there,
doesn't everyone
hope you and Zhao Xiaoqian
will get married?
Yes,
so what?
It's too bad.
Those from
the Commandery Prince's Mansion
want you and Zhao Xiaoqian
to get married,
but Zhao Xiaoqian
himself doesn't want to.
Xie Xiaoman!
You're trying to blame the matter on me
because you want him to dislike me.
You want to marry him, am I right?
Whether I'm marrying him or not
has nothing to do with you, a concubine.
You're so full of yourself.
Xie Xiaoman,
do you think my feelings for Hanchen
are only one-sided?
What do you mean?
Right now,
a memorial about my marriage
with Hanchen
is being prepared in the capital.
Hanchen knew about it long ago
yet he didn't tell you.
I'm afraid
you don't matter much to him.
Am I right?
After I get married to him,
it'll be easy to get rid of you.
I am in no rush to
get rid of you for now.
Why don't you
leave Hanchen right now?
You seem to be a studious one.
If you leave now,
at least it's better than entering
the ancestral temple later on
as a nun.
Don't you think so?
Lady,
you sure take your time to apologize
and disturb my lady's rest.
My sister accidentally injured you.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Just tell her to be more
careful from now on.
These few days,
do a background check on Xie Xiaoman.
While you're at it,
prompt Princess Consort Pu again
who's in the capital
to quickly get the decree.
Yes.
Two ladies got into a fight
and one of them suffered
a serious head injury.
Both the jade bottle and temple block
were smashed into pieces.
Everything's fine now.
Director Xu,
what happened earlier was all our fault.
Now that Lady Shen's forgiven Minggu,
we also seek your understanding.
Xiaoman!
What's wrong?
You and Shen Zhaowen are engaged.
Is it true?
She told you that?
Answer me.
Yes,
but I definitely won't
agree to it.
Believe me, okay?
I can solve this.
- You have to...
- How are you going to solve it?
An imperial order from the capital
cannot be defied.
Tell me. How are you going to solve it?
Why won't you
believe me?
Why did you keep it from me then?
Why did you lie to me?
You want to know why?
You want to know ever since
the moment I married you,
I've been worried that
this day will come.
You want to know,
as the Commandery Prince of Julu
why I could only think about you
and even defy an imperial order?
You want to know why I lied to you,
but at this moment
I'm pleading with you?
It's because I don't want you to worry.
I don't want you to overthink
or leave me.
I really like you, Xiaoman.
You like me?
Imperial order...
None of us could defy
the imperial order.
You have to marry Shen Zhaowen.
And me?
I'm just a small object
in your relationship.
When you like me, you'll coax me.
When you don't,
I'll be discarded right away.
That's not the case, Xiaoman.
Zhao Xiaoqian,
that's not how you like someone.
That's just possession.
Tell me. How am I
supposed to believe you?
Xiaoman!
Xiaoman.
Human beings are insignificant.
In Buddhism context,
to the universe,
a person is so small in comparison.
However, mankind is also noble.
A single thought forms
within a person's mind.
And that thought
is the most precious thing
in the universe.
Everyone has someone they
miss throughout their life.
During one's life in this world,
it always has to do with entanglement.
Master.
Amitabha.
What if this feeling
is wrong?
Feeling itself isn't wrong,
but you asked the wrong question.
No matter what our feelings are,
we shouldn't be obsessed with returns.
What we should seek
is when the feeling matures,
demand nothing, and without pain.
Let it be when the time comes.
Whether you let it go or not
is up to you.
Don't panic, everyone! Calm down!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Let me do a head count.
Wang Weicheng!
Is Wang Weicheng around?
I'm here.
I'm still alive.
Ying!
Where are Zhao Xiaoqian and Yan Boyang?
Director Xu,
His Highness hasn't returned.
I'll send people to look
for him right away.
I'll do that right now.
I'll go look for him myself.
No way.
We have guards.
How can we let a lady go?
No, you can't go.
Director Xu,
I'm the Commandery Princess Rong'an
on His Majesty's order.
If I say that
I'm going,
who dare stop me?
Hurry up!
Go after her!
Hurry!
Make sure you'll protect her!
You go look for Yan Boyang.
I sneak outside with them
to look for Zhao Xiaoqian.
Don't go, Xiaoman.
You can't go outside.
Director,
she also wants to go outside.
Director Xu,
Zhao Xiaoqian is my husband.
I must go and look for him.
A Commandery Princess is
enough of a headache.
Now, you're also causing trouble.
Don't worry.
If they can't find him,
so can't you.
Come back here!
Director Xu!
Come back!
Xiaoman.
I'll go with Xiaoman.
Don't worry, Director Xu.
We'll be fine.
You...
Ridiculous!
You people are too ridiculous!
Yan Boyang.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I'm glad to hear that.
Can you stand up?
Yes.
Yan Boyang!
Yan Boyang, where are you?
- I...
- Yan...
I'm here.
What are you doing, bending over there?
Stop making noise.
If you keep making noise,
there will be another earthquake.
There's no more earthquake.
Come out now.
Come out quickly.
Come out!
I don't want to.
- No.
- It's fine now.
Out! Now!
Where did you go?
I was so worried.
You're worried about me?
Of course.
Xiaoman went to look for Zhao Xiaoqian.
Who's going to worry
about you other than me?
My mother once told me,
when there's an earthquake
hiding under the table is the safest.
That's why I dare not move at all.
Why did you go to the main hall alone?
I went...
Didn't you say that
this is your family heirloom
given by your mother.
Make sure such a precious item
won't go missing again.
Who knows in the future,
you may give it to your daughter?
So,
you don't blame me for scolding you.
You even went to help me find
the pearls at the main hall?
Did you scold me?
When was it?
I can't remember.
No...
Why are you crying?
You...
Yan Boyang,
you're an idiot.
Xiaoman,
do you want to take a rest?
No need.
I'm fine.
What if he's waiting for me somewhere
and couldn't see me?
Congwen, take a rest first
if you're tired.
I'm fine.
Hanchen!
Lingniang.
Are you okay?
What are you doing here?
I was worried about you.
Just now, after the earthquake,
I was worried something might
happen since you're alone.
I'm fine.
Where's Xiaoman?
Seems like she's with the rest of them
in the temple.
What's wrong?
You sprained your ankle?
Let's go back quickly.
I'll carry you on my back.
Come on.
Hanchen,
I've always liked you.
I've been thinking every day
when we'll get married.
Who would've thought
he's actually liked by someone?
I was wrong about him.
Let's go back.
Xiaoman.
(Lonely Boat At Night, volume three)
(I don't understand a word.
It's full of gibberish talk.)
(Look at the name of the author.)
(Lunatic from Wild Dreams Hall.)
(He himself admitted to be a lunatic.)
(All the people mentioned
so far were talking gibberish.)
(As what the author had said,)
(unusual people make other
plans in difficult situations)
(whereas ordinary people are bound
in the sea of tribulations.)
(This kind of article with
higher understanding)
(is not meant for)
(you common people.)
(It's fine if you don't understand,)
(but you shouldn't criticize it either.)
(If you're able to see these messages,)
(I hope, in the next volume,)
(you'll talk more about)
(what you've mentioned before)
(the stories of viewing
Queen of the Night at the burial mound.)
(I wonder if there's really)
(such lustrous and magical flower
in this world.)
(I really yearn for it.)
Xiaoman.
Let me bring you to a place.
Let's go.
Each year, Queen of the Night
only blooms for a few hours
on the nights between
summer and fall.
You're lucky
that I've stayed here for a while
and figured out the entire
mountain's geographical features.
Xiaoman,
there are really
Queen of the Night here.
Queen of the Night?
It's blooming.
Isn't it beautiful?
Yes.
Xiaoman.
(Brothel)
Mr. Zhong, you're here.
Is there any new business today?
Yes,
of course there is.
Come on.
(Theory of Punishment)
Go and tell them
I accepted the money.
He can come and get it after three days.
Sure.
Mr. Zhong.
Thank you, Mr. Zhong.
Take care.
I suddenly realized that I was wrong.
I suddenly felt that
even if there's only one
person who understands me,
I should probably carry on.
Principal,
I'll stay
instead of going for
the imperial examination.
Are you sure?
I've made my decision.
I won't be swayed by
others' opinion anymore.
Lunatic of Wild Dreams Hall
is indeed a lunatic.
That's right!
Catch it!
Okay!
Come on.
All right, you can go and play.
Don't wander off.
Maoya,
look.
I prepared a rooster
for His Highness last time,
His Highness really liked it.
This time,
I've prepared a plumpest hen
for His Highness.
How is it?
No need.
The Commandery Prince's Mansion
has become a chicken coop.
When are you two
planning to have a son?
Mother, what nonsense
are you talking about?
What about this?
We'll tell His Highness
to give you 1000 strings of 1000 cash
just to be safe.
Mother.
You silly girl.
Why don't you understand?
I'm doing this for your own good.
Think about your identity
and the situation you're in.
You're just a concubine.
In the entire
Commandery Prince's Mansion,
such a huge and rich family,
the only person we can depend on now
is His Highness.
You're still young in this matter,
so you won't think it through.
As your mother,
I have to consider thoroughly for you.
Are you selling your daughter
or in fact she's married?
It's for your own good.
For my own good?
If it's for my own good,
you shouldn't have
brought me to Wujiang Prefecture.
Maoya!
Hen.
You forgot the hen.
Look at her.
(Grocery store)
Sir,
you've tossed ten times
and didn't hit even once.
That'll be ten cash in total.
Something's wrong with your bottle.
What do you mean by that?
Are you here to cause trouble?
Take care.
Did you see that?
A jar full of black beans.
It's nothing but trickery.
How dare you deceive us?
Someone's here to cause trouble!
Who is it?
How dare you deny it?
Move aside!
Who is it?
Brother,
it's him!
(Hooligan, Zheng Hai)
It's him!
Who are you?
Do you know who I am?
I don't care who you are.
This is my territory.
If you want to set a stall here,
You have to get my permit.
If you want to cause trouble,
you have to first go through me.
Well.
Go through you?
I'm afraid
it won't do you any good.
You've overestimated yourself.
Huang Liu.
You...
Brother!
Look at you.
How dare you call for backup?
You're a deserter.
How dare you cause trouble here.
A deserter?
Do you know who he is?
Stop it!
(Deserter, Huang Liu)
Zheng Hai,
I'm done for.
Pardon me for being late.
Let's go!
Move it!
Why are you here, Arms Instructor Qin?
I entered the city
to report the army supplies
to the magistrate.
That hooligan just now
was from the army camp.
Bring him to the magistrate office.
Yes.
Then I'll take my leave first.
Let's go.
Hanchen,
usually when you fight,
you'd just go easy on them.
Why...
Desertion is a capital offense.
Ask your father when you go home
Yes.
Well, it's for your own good.
Hanchen,
you're acting strangely today.
What exactly is going on?
I agree.
You seem to be in a bad mood today.
Xiaoman found out
about my engagement with Shen Zhaowen.
What do you plan to do?
After all, when it comes
to your marriage,
those in the capital
will intervene for sure.
I'd better go talk to Yang Chidao.
Let's go.
(Jingnv Pavilion)
Music, good food, literature and words.
The right timing, and joyful events.
Look far up in the sky
and enjoy during holidays.
The sky is high and
the land stretches on,
making one realize
the endlessness of the universe.
After pleasure comes sadness.
Xiaoman,
why are you unhappy today?
The dynamics of matter
and nothingness.
What's there to be happy about?
Looking in the direction of
Chang'an city at dusk
and Wu county while being
surrounded by clouds.
At the end of southern land
is the bottomless ocean.
Heavenly pillars are unreachable while
the Big Dipper hangs far up in the sky.
Border mountains are difficult to cross.
Who'll feel sorry for
those who were lost?
Like the floating plants,
by chance, they all meet.
They're travellers from
far-off places, indeed.
I had missed the imperial court
yet I'm not summoned.
When will I serve His Majesty again?
I've received the homework
I assigned to you last time.
Only Lady Xie hasn't handed in.
Is there any problem?
Teacher Liu,
the question is about our
future ambitions,
but I haven't found a direction.
Can you give me a few more days?
I'll make sure to think over properly.
Lady Xie, from your words,
you seem to be undecided
as to what you want to do.
However, being cautious for
you writing isn't a bad thing.
It's fine.
There's no hurry.
All right, class dismissed.
Thank you, teacher.
Congwen has returned.
Congwen's back.
Congwen.
After I come back this time,
I'll stay for good.
That's good.
Everyone's hoping you'll be around.
I heard that Teacher Liu
is going to compile and
write Admonitions of Women.
She thinks highly of you.
Pay more attention to yourself.
Recently, when I was reading Liezi,
I came across
a story called
Jiufang Gao and the Horse.
Its purpose is to illustrate
how one shouldn't judge
a book by its cover.
Similarly,
sometimes,
one shouldn't hear only
one side of the story.
It's better to ask clearly.
Tomorrow afternoon,
will you go with me to the suburbs?
Why?
You'll know when we're there.
I need your help, Principal Yang.
Did you cause trouble again?
I'm an old man.
I'm unable to go through such torment.
I want to help Xie Xiaoman
get a conferment of title.
Aren't you
engaged with Lady Shen?
Take a look at this.
This was written
by my student in the capital
for my entertainment.
Now, it's known across
the entire capital
the Prince Pu's Mansion who
broke off the engagement
is again connecting with Shen Family
through marriage.
Moreover, an order has been
issued at the imperial palace.
♪Ask the moon whether it has seen♪
♪The other end of the earth♪
♪Your feelings fluctuate
like the moon's wane and wax♪
♪Have they ever been the same?♪
♪Carried by misty clouds,
the moon came into your eyes♪
♪As a substitute for me, it appeared♪
♪Cast our eyes over the bustling street♪
♪Don't shed tears when we part♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪