♪Memories of the past are always vivid♪
♪They accompanied me to take every step♪
♪On the road♪
♪Going through heat and cold♪
♪The bumpy journey
has rendered my longing♪
♪Rock solid♪
♪The same moonlight
shines on our shoulders♪
♪Even if we are far away separated♪
♪We are close in our hearts♪
♪The wind blew away the past♪
♪I look for your distant location
on the starry night♪
♪In the ocean of faces♪
♪For you, my heart burns and races♪
♪Despite its turns and twists,
fate is in my hands♪
♪May waiting convert regrets
into a happy ending♪
♪May solitary figures
find right companions♪
♪And become a pair♪
=Time Flies and You Are Here=
=Episode 16=
(I have no appetite with a bad mood,
neither am I happy playing with a sword)
Were you waiting for me?
I need to talk to you.
What's the matter?
Minggu told me the academy is
hosting the ritual, Dance of Nuo.
I was wondering...
Minggu said the Dance of Nuo requires
us to wear a mask and hold a sword.
The prayers will be
heard by dead spirits.
I was wondering if I could use the Helu
to speak to brother-in-law.
What?
Brother-in-law?
Will you allow me?
Brother-in-law.
Sure.
What's the matter?
Didn't you hear?
She called my brother
her brother-in-law.
(Jingnv Pavilion)
The teacher is here.
Teacher Liu is here.
Here comes Teacher Liu.
Greetings, teacher.
From today onwards, Lady Shen
shall join the Jingnv Pavilion
as a student.
I've heard
Jingnv Pavilion of Bailu Academy
gathers the best female scholars.
I've finally seen it for myself.
It's indeed like they said.
I'm Shen Zhaowen.
My courtesy name is Lingniang.
You may all call me Lingniang.
It's my pleasure
to be able to learn
with you, fellow classmates.
I hope for your help and support
in the days to come.
You may settle down there.
Please be seated.
The civil examinations
are approaching.
This time,
the ladies of Jingnv Pavilion
are supposed to prepare
for the Dance of Nuo.
During the last examination,
the prayers of Dance of Nuo
were prepared by the seniors
of Jingnv Pavilion.
Most of them have left Jingnv Pavilion.
For the civil examinations this year,
Director Xu
has yet to hold classes
of etiquette this year.
He intends to request all ladies
to master the Dance of Nuo
with the coach
while learning customs and etiquette.
During the preceding ritual
of Dance of Nuo,
as I recall, a lady
led the dance in the centre.
Would it be the same this year?
Yes.
Since we're performing
the Dance of Prince of Lanling,
among fellow ladies,
is there anyone who would like to
volunteer yourself?
Xiaoman, you should do it.
You can do it.
I'd like to volunteer.
Xie Xiaoman.
All right.
Are there any other volunteers?
I would like to volunteer as well.
The goddess can only
be played by one person.
Since two ladies have
volunteered themselves...
She did it on purpose.
You should both
participate in the practice.
Then, we will select the best one
from the both of you.
Lady Shen should be chosen.
Apparently, Lady Shen
grew up in the palace.
It's a given for her to
be good in everything.
How do you know that?
She's the younger sister of Shen Yan.
About her visit to Wujiang Prefecture,
the capital
informed my father beforehand.
All right.
Both of you shall
proceed to the practice.
We shall resume class.
If you find a rook in
your game of chess,
you must let it go.
Otherwise,
you will not be able to win.
If I use the chess pieces
of the counterpart
to allow my rook to escape,
this method is known as a distraction.
After shifting the piece,
it could turn into an opening
as another way to victory.
If you do not let go of your obsession,
in the game of chess,
it will be difficult to move forward.
Look.
I won.
Impressive moves.
Let's play a game.
Let's go.
You lost.
It's fine to lose a game.
I went easy on him.
By the way,
where has Boyang been?
He comes and goes recently.
He's hardly seen around.
What could he be up to?
Anyway,
before Mr. Liangji was
assigned to work for me,
did he serve the Minister of Rites
previously?
I understand.
I'll have it arranged.
I guarantee you will be able to
perform the Dance of Nuo with Xiaoman.
You made it seem like
I'm desperate to do so.
What did I tell you?
See?
She does not bear kind intentions.
Haven't you heard?
The drunkard bears ulterior motives.
Did you think she truly
seeks to pray for the scholars?
She's just trying to suppress you.
Listen to me.
You need to beware.
She shared a past with Zhao Xiaoqian.
Do not provoke their past feelings.
Do you understand?
The first love is always
passionate and easily rekindled.
Mind your words.
Lady Xiaoman.
Speak of the devil.
I heard of you back at the capital.
I met Hanchen urgently that night.
I wasn't able to greet you properly.
Where's Hanchen?
Is he not with you?
Classes for the students of
Luming Pavilion have ended.
Are you on your way back to the
Commandery Prince's Mansion?
I came to Wujiang Prefecture
to visit my brother,
but I also came to
get to know the friends
of Hanchen.
If you do not mind,
may I tag along?
We...
We're performing
the Dance of Prince of Lanling.
Hanchen and I
were playing when we were kids.
I performed this dance before him.
His knowledge in etiquette and customs
surpasses mine.
I would like to consult him.
At the same time,
I could learn it with you.
Nuo Opera
originated from
the ancient Nuo Sacrifice.
Back then,
it was a religious ceremony to
coronate the Emperor.
There are many types.
There are types to pray for blessings
and types to repel evil spirits.
The most common one at the north
is Fangxiangshi's Dance of Nuo.
In the south, Prince of Lanling
is the most common.
Over the years, Bailu Academy
has been performing
the Dance of Prince of Lanling.
This is it.
Prince of Lanling of the Northern Qi
possessed a delicate
and graceful figure.
He fought the enemies wearing a mask
and achieved countless victories.
Your form is hideous.
Your Highness.
They were meant for ladies.
I'm just demonstrating.
Your Highness.
Lady Xie's carriage has arrived.
The Helu is a remnant
of Duke of Yongguo.
Get back to work.
Hanchen.
Lingniang?
What are you doing here?
You're sure cocky.
Why can't I be here?
I'm a student of Jingnv Pavilion now.
I'm Xiaoman's classmate.
You knew this.
I've always wanted to be
a student of Teacher Liu.
It's a pity that she refuses
to go to the capital.
Now that I'm here,
I'm going to learn from her.
Were you chosen as Prince of Lanling?
I volunteered,
but practice is required.
The teacher said that
the best would be selected.
I volunteered, too.
Hanchen,
do you remember
that back at the palace,
the Empress taught me the Dance of Nuo.
You guided me a lot then.
That's why
I came to learn from you.
You...
I don't care.
You're my brother.
During the shooting ceremony on July,
I was the one who drew your mask.
Besides, we're performing
the Dance of Prince of Lanling.
Do you remember
the story of the general
Xiaojie told us?
You weren't like this back then.
You're pulling a long face.
Back then, you said you
wanted to marry...
Isn't this Xiaojie's sword?
This is for Xiaoman.
Thank you.
I'll head home and practise alone.
I'll leave you both alone.
Xiaoman.
Xiaoman is rather irascible.
(Commandery Prince's Mansion)
Hanchen gave the Helu to that lady.
It seems like their bond
can't be broken by me easily.
Xie Xiaoman
is more trouble than we expected.
The Empress
has never earned the protection
of His Majesty to this extent for years.
What kind of enticement
did Xie Xiaoman pull
in order for
Hanchen to fall heads over heels?
I'm sure you've heard, Lady Shen.
The lower one's origins are,
the more licentious they'd behave.
Licentious sounds really crude.
However, no men could resist that.
I was told,
on the day I arrived at the city,
my brother's lackey, Xu Shu
won a hefty sum from
Hanchen's learning partner.
While drinking with my brother,
I overheard their conversation.
Xu Shu?
(Yan's Mansion)
Master,
we spent the day loitering around.
We didn't go to the academy.
If Old Master Yan finds out, he would...
Why would I go?
They are all going to laugh at me.
Unbelievable.
You unfilial son!
Father.
You macaque.
How dare you lie?
The teacher from your academy dropped by
and told us
that you haven't been attending
the academy for the past few days.
Your mother said
you've been frequenting filthy places
like the brothel!
What's wrong?
You can't learn anything
from the academy,
but you could learn from the brothel?
Boyang is aware of his mistake.
He will not repeat that anymore.
Don't be too harsh on the son.
Is he even sorry?
He doesn't look sorry to me!
He's bold enough to frequent
the brothel!
If we leave him be,
he will end up a useless lecher!
He's going to spend
the wealth I accumulated!
Loving mothers spoil their sons!
That's who you are!
Reprimand me as you please.
Do not involve my mother in this.
Shut up!
Reprimand you?
I was going easy on you.
You shouldn't even
step foot in a brothel.
Right now,
the Personnel Commissioner has
arrived at Wujiang Prefecture
to eliminate corrupted officials.
Are you treating me
as a joke?
The son of a bureaucrat
frequenting the red-light district.
You may not care,
but I have a reputation to keep!
Yes.
I brought dishonour to the family.
I'm nothing like my brother.
When my brother was 20,
he passed the civil examination.
Every year on his birthday,
you'd throw him a huge
birthday celebration.
As for me,
it's my birthday tomorrow.
Does any of you remember?
I want to eat
my mother's longevity noodles, too.
You called me a failure.
Fine.
That's who I am.
I'm no longer
the second son of Yan Family!
Boyang.
Master.
Is tomorrow
Boyang's birthday?
(Yan's Mansion)
Mr. Yan,
you're pretty slick.
Are you trying to escape?
What are you talking about?
I'm telling you.
This is my house.
I'm not afraid of you.
I'm not evil.
Isn't that right?
There's no need to fear.
We're not committing a crime.
Let's have a cup of tea.
Come here.
Move it.
Get out of the way.
- Hurry up.
Get out.
(Pledge)
Speak.
What do you want?
Division of Personnel
are inspecting the whole
of Wujiang Prefecture.
You're the son of a bureaucrat.
You gambled and failed
to pay your debts.
Will
your father be implicated?
It's my problem.
It has nothing to do with my father.
If the Personnel Commissioner
happens to find this receipt,
no matter how capable Lord Yan is,
he will not be able to
avoid the complete liquidation.
No matter how honest Lord Yan is,
tell me,
which official is completely clean?
If this minor impurity
was discovered by the commissioner,
do you think
Zhao Xiaoqian,
a Commandery Prince
uninvolved in politics,
an abandoned prince
exiled from the capital,
would be able to help
resolve this for your father?
Quit threatening me.
What's it that you want?
I want the Helu.
Zhao Xiaoqian's Helu?
Good morning.
Xiaoman.
What's this?
Is this your new polo mallet?
Let me take a look.
This is Zhao Xiaoqian's Helu.
I need it for
the Dance of Prince of Lanling.
Does the practice begin today?
Let me have a look.
How petty.
In my opinion,
with your abilities,
you'd definitely emerge
as the main dancer.
You're way better than she is.
Don't be ridiculous.
It's true.
I heard that
Xie Xiaoman will be bringing
the Helu to the academy tomorrow.
You know what to do.
Boyang.
Where have you been
for the past few days?
You're nowhere to be found.
I...
Hanchen,
do you know what day it is today?
Xiaoman is learning
the Dance of Nuo today.
Should we
watch her in secret?
She came to ask for my help yesterday.
I didn't manage to.
Peeping
would make you a lecher.
It doesn't matter.
I have to make sure she gets selected.
Boyang.
Fine.
Another one who avoids me for no reason.
Your Highness.
Mr. Zhong.
My Old Master
has a message for the both of you.
It's Master Boyang's
18th birthday today.
Old Master Yan's slipped his mind.
Master Boyang is rather unhappy.
Hence, he
would like to invite both
of you to the mansion
after class
to celebrate Master Boyang's birthday.
It's Boyang's birthday today.
Raise your hand higher.
How do I do this?
Like this.
Just lift it slightly higher.
That's right.
Since
both of you would like
to play the role of Prince of Lanling,
I discussed the situation
with Teacher Liu.
The date of performance is near.
I hope that both of you
will practise diligently.
Once you master the moves,
we shall hold an appraisal
tomorrow afternoon.
What do you say?
- Yes, teacher.
Lady Shen is holding a sword.
You're using a wicker instead.
If you'd like to win,
you should place more effort
and equip yourself with the right prop.
Yes, teacher.
After the practice,
I'll retrieve the sword.
After becoming a concubine
of a distinguished household,
some people have
forgotten their place.
A village peasant
intends to compete with Lingniang.
Yes.
My sister is married to
the Commandery Prince.
She's eligible to compete
with Lady Shen.
On the other hand,
you're of no prominence
yet you'd insult others shamelessly.
Everyone knows
you have feelings for Congwen.
What did you say?
What's wrong?
I'm saying, someone
bears ulterior motives
towards Congwen.
Am I wrong?
Repeat it.
Ruying.
Did you just push me?
Minggu,
don't get in a fight.
We're in a wrong if we do.
Let's retrieve the sword.
I've learned to avoid her.
You shouldn't argue with her.
It's a waste of time.
I did it to defend you.
Xie Ruying of your household
has a disgraceful mouth.
If it wasn't for our close ties
with Xie Family,
I would have disciplined her
on behalf of Uncle Xie.
By the way,
why didn't you bring
the sword with you?
The Helu is Zhao Xiaoqian's
prized possession.
I dare not bring it out casually.
I don't want to damage or lose it.
You're so concerned about him.
His childhood friend
is about to trample on you.
What's wrong, Xiaoman?
What happened?
The Helu is gone.
It's gone?
How is that possible?
Maoya.
What are you up to?
If you have time,
let's head to Yan's Mansion
after class today.
We're going to celebrate Yan Boyang...
Forget it.
We need to practise the Dance of Nuo.
There's practice?
You should skip the afternoon classes.
I'll take you home to practise.
Mr. Liangji
would be able to teach
you better than the coach.
It's fine.
The coach is pretty great.
There's no need to concern us.
Both of you...
Why is everyone avoiding me?
Xiaoman.
How did I lose the Helu?
He cherishes the Helu the most.
Xiaoman.
Do not panic.
I'm not
leaving after class.
I'll look for it with you.
Even if we were to
search all corners
of Jingnv Pavilion,
I'll find it, all right?
Do not worry.
Master Yan,
His Highness and Mr. Zhong
are here to see you.
Forget it.
Master Yan.
I said I'm not seeing anyone today.
Tell them I'm asleep.
Hold it right there.
Boyang,
what a friend you are.
You didn't even invite us
over for your birthday celebration.
Look at you.
Look.
Why are you here?
I don't like your tone of voice.
Can't we show up to
celebrate your birthday?
Yan Boyang,
you've gotten really brazen.
You didn't even invite us
over for your birthday.
I...
You forgot about my birthday anyway.
My memory is horrible.
You knew that.
Besides,
both of us are right here.
Listen to me.
Close friends are
more likely to miss important dates.
Did you know that?
That's enough.
It's my fault.
I
offer my sincerest apology.
Here, Boyang.
Happy birthday.
Lord Yan.
My son.
Your father realised he was wrong.
He spent all night on this.
Let's hear it.
Go on.
My...
My son...
Let me do it.
My son, Zhanzhi,
I forgot your birthday.
It's my fault.
I've done nothing
to deserve acclamation
yet by the grace of the heavens,
I was blessed with you and your brother.
My son, Zhanzhi,
you should understand,
as a member of nobility,
no matter how exceptional
or virtuous you are,
the public may still doubt you.
However, one minor mistake
will invite the denunciation
of them all.
Besides devoting yourself
into rectification
and studies,
there's no other way.
A man should bear great ambitions.
Respect your elders,
sever lust and desires,
abandon idleness,
pursue the virtues of the saint,
portray the qualities of a sage,
keep the enlightenment
engraved in your heart,
submit and assert as required,
discard trivial troubles,
always ready to learn,
and eliminate immorality.
Your father,
Yan Nengfu.
Here comes the longevity noodles.
Master Boyang,
enjoy it while it's hot.
Dig in.
Boyang,
I selected this fine stallion
from the mansion.
It might not be Zhao Mao,
but it came from Dayuan.
You must cherish it.
There you go.
I never said I wanted a horse.
Boyang is shy.
Come on.
Bottoms up.
Cheers to Boyang's birthday.
All right. Happy birthday.
Happy birthday.
I'm sorry.
Come on.
Let's eat.
Lord Yan, cheers.
Both of you.
Xiaoman,
we can't find it anywhere.
What should we do?
I have to inform him.
Xiaoman.
Mr. Liangji.
Has she returned to Lotus Garden?
Yes.
Why do you think
Xie Xiaoman is always
giving me an attitude?
I did not offend her in any way,
but she's always mad at me.
In my humble opinion,
I think Lady Xie is jealous.
Your Highness,
look.
Ever since Lady Shen's
arrival at Wujiang Prefecture,
Lady Xie hasn't been at ease.
Back at the courtyard,
she wanted to practise
the Dance of Nuo.
However,
because Lady Shen was around,
Lady Xie was dispirited.
If that's true,
she's mad at me
because she cares for me.
Certainly.
That's what
majority of the ladies think.
I see.
Your Highness.
(Sleeping Room)
Xiaoman,
what's the matter?
I lost the Helu.
Please punish me.
What are you talking about?
Stop kneeling.
Get up first.
I lost the Helu.
Please punish me.
I know
the Helu is the most important thing
to you.
I failed to take care of it.
It was my negligence.
Go ahead and punish me.
I would receive them willingly.
I would atone for my mistake.
Atone?
You can't afford to do so.
You lost the remnant
of the late Duke of Yongguo.
How dare you quibble shamelessly?
This is the Commandery Prince's Mansion.
It's not the residence of a commoner.
Servants.
Seize her.
- Yes.
May I speak to you?
Your Highness,
say something.
Zhao Xiaoqian,
can I please talk to you?
Speak.
I...
You begged me for the Helu.
You lost it as well.
Since you do not treasure it,
you shouldn't have asked me
in the first place.
What I'm trying to say is that
I lost the Helu.
It's my fault, not yours.
I deserve all forms of punishment.
Punish me however you like
because I know
how important the Helu is to you.
I know I've committed
an unforgivable mistake.
However, Zhao Xiaoqian,
you've done nothing wrong.
You cannot be shackled by the sword.
You cannot be shackled
by the ruthless palace.
Liangji said that
ever since your brother passed away,
you never took the Helu out again.
You often jolt awake from your dreams.
Your Highness.
This wench
lost the remnant of
the late Duke of Yongguo.
Please leave her to me.
Stay out of this!
Who do
you think you all are?
Quit meddling in my matters.
Take her away.
- Yes.
Zhao Xiaoqian.
Cast her out.
Did you hear that, Lady Xie?
His Highness wants you to leave.
(Kunning Palace)
If Hanchen is able to marry Lingniang,
I'll definitely bring him back
to the capital.
I'll not allow him to
cause any more troubles.
If your son
was to live
completely under the surveillance
of Shen Family,
will you agree to that?
I dare not oppose.
I understand.
Their marriage
will be decided by me.
(Residence of the Su Family)
That can't be.
We searched everywhere,
but we cannot find it.
Jingnv Pavilion is
the only possible place.
This is strange.
Lady Su.
Lady Xie is here to see you.
What's wrong?
Why are you here?
Where's Zhao Xiaoqian?
What's wrong?
Stop crying, Xiaoman.
Tell me.
What's going on?
Send for Arms Instructor Qin.
Order him to search everywhere.
Even if he has to flip
Wujiang Prefecture around,
find me the Helu.
Yes, Your Highness.
How did it go?
Unfortunately,
it's a little prince.
The figure is already formed.
A kite came out of nowhere
and landed on Her Highness.
Her Highness had a shock
and suffered a miscarriage.
Yes.
Your Highness,
Imperial Household Department
treats us with contempt.
They wouldn't provide me with charcoal.
They even cast me out.
Apparently, the Empress
intends to hold a religious
ceremony for the late prince.
All palaces are
experiencing budget cuts.
What should we do?
They are clearly tormenting us.
Brother is still ill.
I'm going to reason with them.
Your Highness.
Xiaoqian.
The Empress just suffered
from a traumatic incident.
We should avoid troubles at all cost.
Fetch some charcoal from the kitchen.
Boil some water
and fill the heating bags.
We can warm ourselves up the same.
Your Highness,
the charcoal ran out a few days ago.
If there is any left,
there's no need to
beg them for charcoal.
There should be some
firewood left in the backyard.
Let's burn them to warm ourselves up.
Without charcoal,
the nights will still be freezing.
I'll cover you up with my
fur mantel.
You don't have to sleep
in the cold at night.
I don't want you to be
exposed to the cold.
I'm not cold.
I'll head out to find some charcoal.
Your Highness.
Her Highness has arrived.
Your Highness,
you mustn't enter.
Wasn't Her Highness ill?
Why is she here?
Her Highness is speaking
to His Highness.
You may enter after they are done.
(Wude Palace)
Brother,
are you feeling warmer?
Where did you find the charcoal?
I guessed
they'd never restrict
His Majesty's supply.
I took some from
the side chamber of Ruisi Palace.
Taking without permission is theft.
Did you forget what I've taught you?
Xiaoqian.
In the future,
I may no longer be able
to keep you company.
Don't say that.
You're lying.
Xiaoqian.
Remember.
No matter what happens,
no matter who asks for your return,
do not listen to them.
Do you understand?
No, I don't.
Don't say that.
Stop messing around.
I'm not listening to you anymore.
You do not belong here.
Go.
Go to where you belong.
Did you say
you wanted to lead an army into war
and eliminate all the enemies?
Go.
Do not come back.
That's where you belong.
You will find freedom there.
It's the winter solstice.
Brother.
Wake up, brother.
Wake up.
Brother, wake up.
Brother.
Wake up.
Brother, wake up.
Wake up, brother.
Brother.
How long will you remain
hiding in Wujiang Prefecture?
Do you really want Xiaojie
to watch as the sheathed sword
goes to waste?
In three months,
I'm leaving this place
for Zhending Prefecture.
Don't worry about the capital.
Chancellor Qin has everything prepared.
He obtained His Majesty's approval.
His Majesty has plans
to conquer Baichuankou.
War is about to break out.
Although Baichuankou
is a fortress difficult to attain,
in order to accumulate merits,
this is your only opportunity.
Hanchen!
Do not forsake the dignity
and ambition you once had.
♪Ask the moon whether it has seen♪
♪The other end of the earth♪
♪Your feelings fluctuate
like the moon's wane and wax♪
♪Have they ever been the same?♪
♪Carried by misty clouds,
the moon came into your eyes♪
♪As a substitute for me, it appeared♪
♪Cast our eyes over the bustling street♪
♪Don't shed tears when we part♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪