Unforgettable Love
EP14
Ruowei.
Why are you here?
It's the time
to pick up Xiaobao with me.
What's happening?
What is it?
Your love rival now is
the director of Heshi promotion department
who takes full responsibility
to promote He Qiaoyan's precious bracelet
to the European and American market.
You mean
Lin Wei went to work at Heshi.
Didn't He Qiaoyan talk to you
about it?
Does it matter?
Of course it matters.
If he did,
it means the problem
is not that serious.
But if he didn't talk about that,
it's probably 80 percent that
he is guilty of it.
Do you think it's important or not?
Why didn't you say it?
Why not?
Sit down.
Fine.
I see.
You are playing dead, aren't you?
Since you play dead,
I'll wake you up.
Hit, hit, hit
Presumptuous.
You don't say, but I will make you say.
Tell me.
I tell you
my fist is very hard.
Tell me.
Tell me now.
You haven't been asleep yet?
Do you think I can be asleep?
You didn't hear anything, did you?
What do you think?
What did you hear?
I heard about 60 decibels
man-made noises
for 27 minutes.
which seriously affected my cerebral
cortex's nerves to rest.
I'm sorry.
I just shouldn't have been in the room
practicing for the kid
the story I'm going to tell tomorrow.
If that bothers you,
I'll shut up right now.
That's good.
Have an early rest.
Good night.
No.
Don't think blindly.
And don't imagine something strange.
I swear.
I definitely didn't sleep on it
and snore.
I think I get it.
You think
I have your cartoon pillow
whilst you don't have one.
You don't think it's fair,
so you are angry.
Right?
Who wants your cartoon pillow?
I have nightmares with it.
Ok.
I'll make one for you
with the same size as mine.
What do you want me to wear?
I don't want
the same size one as yours.
No, No
I, I mean
I don't want your pillow.
Got it.
Tomorrow, I'll give you one
cartoon pillow the same size as me.
Rest early.
I'll arrange it.
What a mess!
Qin Yiyue.
You tell me,
why don't you ask him?
Lady,
What should I ask?
Of course you should ask
why Lin Wei
is going to work for Heshi?
So what?
Right!
So annoying.
I was misunderstood by him
that I'm crazy about his body.
It's weekend today.
You don't have to go to the company,
so I made breakfast
After breakfast,
let's take Xiaobao to the horse-riding yard.
Xiaobao said that
he wants to learn to ride a horse.
I also made for him
his favorite eggs.
Let me wake him up now.
Wait.
I have to work overtime at the company today.
I don't have breakfast today.
See you!
He doesn't have breakfast
for the first time.
Who is he going to eat with?
Breakfast is gold.
Lunch is silver.
Dinner is copper.
Who allows you cheat?
Why is Mommy unhappy?
Because your Mommy's love rival
went to work at your Dad's company.
What is love rival?
A love rival is someone who with your Mommy
snatches your Dad.
Xiaobao.
Today is the weekend.
What do you want
to do with Mommy?
What about going to the amusement park?
What about the museum?
Go to Dad's company.
You miss Dad?
Ok.
Xiaobao misses Dad,
then Mommy takes you to meet Daddy.
OK?
Xiaobao.
Is Mommy beautiful?
Good boy!
If your Dad is half as sweet as you,
it's wonderful.
Mr. He.
So careful?
Why did you come to the company?
Xiaobao said he missed you,
so I bring him to see you.
I also bring you something to eat by the way.
Didn't you have breakfast?
I forgot to tell you that
today's noon...
I know you're in a hurry at noon
so as to eat something simple.
so I made for you
your favorite...
Qiaoyan,
Let's have sandwiches for lunch.
Mr. He.
Minister Lin.
Designer Lucas
will be here in five minutes.
When they arrive,
bring them directly.
Ok.
You'd better eat this.
I have made your favorite
tuna sandwich.
I added the amount of tuna.
Help yourself.
I remember Lucas
dislikes tuna the most.
You'd better not eat it,
or it will leave a bad smell.
Put things down first.
I'll have a meeting later.
It will take about an hour
to finish.
We should have a good lunch.
When I finish the meeting,
I will bring you and Xiaobao
to go for a lunch together.
Ok.
You are working,
and finish work first.
I won't disturb you.
I'll wait for you outside with Xiaobao.
Ok.
Let's go, Xiaobao.
Pay attention to safety.
The designer will come here soon.
Let's take a look at
his plan.
Ok.
Take a seat.
I'm just thinking about it.
Devices of immersive virtual reality
and the matching degree of the bracelet
Mommy is going to the bathroom.
You wait for me here
Don't go away,
okay?
Lucas is disgusted the most with
the smell of tuna.
Why doesn't he dislike the smell of air?
Because now there are a lot of
new features,
so the comfort of wearing
is very important.
Besides, I think
the battery sensor module,
and in the stand-alone module,
the advantage of low power
need to be further strengthened.
If its functionality
makes a breakthrough,
I believe our bracelet
will make a better benefit.
Except for the battery,
the...
Xiaobao.
What are you doing here?
Hello!
Xiaobao.
You are coming to play with Dad, right?
Your Dad will play with you after the meeting,
okay?
I'll go to the bathroom.
He Weifei.
I know why you're here.
Stop pretending.
We are all female.
I know what you're thinking about.
But you
are not  at the same level.
Barely climbing up
while no one supports you,
you will just fall down more seriously.
Mumbo jumbo.
Come down.
What's wrong?
Calm down.
Xiaobao.
You tell Mommy
why you did that?
You must have a reason for that,
right?
What reason can he have?
What he did
can't be forgiven.
He Weifei, I tell you
you can do whatever you want at home.
But at the company,
this kind of behavior is absolutely not allowed.
Is it your attitude of admitting your mistakes?
Is it?
Now, go home
You are not allowed to have yogurt within three days.
No cartoons.
No games.
Don't worry about him.
Mr. He
I know you're the boss.
You get used to educating your employees seriously.
But Xiaobao is just a kid.
Can you pay a little attention to
the way you speak.
Whether he's a kid
or an adult,
as long as he did something wrong,
he should have a lesson.
Yes.
You can teach him.
But should you
figure out the reason first?
There's only one reason for it.
He's just too naughty.
Do you know
how to educate children?
Do I know how to teach children?
You think you know it well, right?
It is because
you have spoiled him too much recently
that he did not behave himself.
Yes.
I don't know.
You know.
You all know.
At least I know that we need to spend more time with the family.
Today is the weekend.
But you come to work early in the morning.
Xiaobao said he missed you,
and let me bring him to meet you.
In the end, you blew him up.
Is that what you should do as a parent?
Do you understand
what I told you?
Understand.
She's coming. She's coming. She's coming.
Come on, everyone!
After work,
I'll treat you to dinner.
Well.
Ruowei.
The activity of last quarter is over.
When are you going to give the report?
But this project,
I'm only responsible for contacting suppliers.
The major planning and implementation
are in the charge of Lin Sheng.
Lin Sheng is your predecessor.
You'd better give him a hand.
Ok.
No problem.
Please pack up the materials for me.
I'll follow up as soon as possible.
And
the
preliminary market research of new products
and data analysis,
I think you can also have a try.
This part I before have
never dealt with.
But I can get to know about it.
Give me some time.
I'll go off work ahead of time.
For the data,
please check it again.
Data service
is not in my field of expertise.
Asking the project team to take over it
will be more suitable.
Only the confirmed forms
need to be checked again.
Robots are capable of doing this.
You are so smart.
I'm sure you can be adept at it in five minutes.
Bye!
Are you done?
Just tell me if you can't do that.
Don't delay the working progress.
Send me the report as you finish it.
I have to go to the 16th floor at two o'clock in the afternoon
to give a report.
Weiwei.
I'm sorry.
Can you give the check
result to me now?
I'm in a hurry.
Stop.
I told you to stop.
Mr. Wen.
What are you doing?
Demonstrate your job responsibilities
and work authority.
Senior administrative assistant
deals with personnel related issues
in daily life,
and coordinates daily schedules.
So checking the report
is your job?
In principle, no.
What about market research and data summary?
And what about business check?
In principle, no.
So who are you responsible for?
The management layer represented by you.
You guys hear it.
Yang Ruowei in here
is only at my service.
Even if you joined the company earlier,
you are equal to her.
Besides,
don't always
shirk your responsibilities to someone else.
Finish your work on your own.
To reiterate,
Yang Ruowei is just for me.
Every word she says,
and everything she does
are guaranteed by me.
Do you remember?
Yes. Yes.
These jobs
are what I am willing to undertake.
And I've already finished them.
I have sent them to
your mailboxes.
As for the technical problems of data,
I have consulted the technical team.
There are indeed some mistakes.
But it's not a big deal.
I've solved it.
My ability is limited,
and I'm a freshman.
Thank all the predecessors for
giving me tasks
to make me know about how each department works,
and to serve you better in the future.
What's so funny?
Go back to your seat.
Ok.
Tell me the truth,
when in front of everyone, I was just
supporting you,
Am I masculine?
A piece of cake.
Totally unnecessary.
The workload when I worked in the hospital
is several times as much as here.
In the first week,
I must keep in mind quickly
with the basic components of 20 departments
and information of more than 100 doctors.
But I was helping you.
You left me embarrassed.
What you did would harm me.
The most important thing about administration
is to get on well with people.
I know those jobs
are not mine.
I can choose not to do them.
I can make mistakes.
They are not my responsibility.
But if I shirk the responsibilities
to let them be scolded by you,
How will I work in the future?
It's not your duty to please others.
I didn't.
I just like learning and challenging.
Fortunately.
I am confident of my ability.
If there's nothing wrong with you,
I got to go now.
This is balloon flower.
And this is morning glory.
Here.
This is little daisy.
Come on, come on.
Watermelon.
Mom.
Here.
Xiaobao.
Open your mouth to have a piece of watermelon.
Don't eat?
Come and sit here.
I'll do it, mom.
You don't eat what Grandma feeds,
do you?
Come and have another one.
What a dirty mouth!
Slowly!
You have one, too.
When she was a child
in kindergarten,
I prepared it for her.
Even though we use paper towels now,
she's always with it.
Does it taste good?
Xiaobao.
Call me Grandma.
Mom.
Don't force him.
Yes, yes.
I forgot again.
Ok.
No need to call me.
Xiaobao must be hungry.
Grandma is going to make delicious food for you.
Let me help you.
All right, come here.
Here.
You eat here by yourself
Mom is going to help Grandma cook.
Ok?
Careless!
Carry it in your pocket.
Is my Dad still sleeping?
He has taken anti-fever medicine,
so he got sleepy.
Why does he still have fever?
It's been almost a week.
Five days.
I'll take Dad to hospital tomorrow.
It's not good to have a fever all the time.
Tell me.
Why did you come back all of a sudden?
I come back to see you.
What's wrong with that?
And it's the weekend.
I bring Xiaobao back
to acquaint himself with his grandparents.
Then why are you two alone?
Where's Qiaoyan?
Nobody cares.
You must have had a quarrel.
No.
You give us a sudden phone call,
saying you would come back for a night,
and show us the kid.
But you didn't bring any luggage.
There's no reason except for quarrel.
If a young married woman quarrels and goes back to her parents' home
without anything,
she's waiting for
her husband to take her back.
Actually,
That's how the couple quarreled
When quarreling, the wife
takes the kid back to her parents' home,
and leaves the husband at home.
When he can't bear that without wife's care,
he will come to his mother-in-law's house
to apologize
and takes his wife back.
Right?
But only bringing the kid back
is not heartless enough.
You should take
all the money with you.
Only in this way,
the husband will realize
the importance of wife.
Do you take his pay card with you?
For a person like him,
bank cards
are numerous.
Ms. Luo Mingmei,
please go to cook.
I am hungry.
Ok. Wait a moment.
Hi, long time no see.
How are you recently?
Not bad.
Hello.
Are you miss Lin?
I'm Alex's friend, Ning Fang.
Here's your medicine.
Thank you!
I truly appreciate your coming.
My pleasure.
International students don't have medical insurance.
It's not easy to take this medicine.
If you are in need next time,
contact me directly.
I have friends in Switzerland.
Ok.
Thank you.
Can I have your WeChat?
It's more convenient to contact.
But what a coincidence!
In fact,
we are from
the same place.
I didn't expect to be here
meeting a fellow-townswoman.
You are also from Qincheng City?
Right!
Are you still taking medicine?
If you need a doctor specializing in this,
I can recommend one to you.
No, I don't.
Thank you for your concern.
I am good.
All right.
The world is so small.
I didn't expect that besides being fellow townsmen,
we can meet here.
How about having a meal next time?
My house is nearby.
No, thanks.
If you don't mind,
I hope you can keep it a secret for me.
What you know in France,
please don't tell anyone.
I got to go.
Bye!
The one that you want to see,
I have made an appointment for you.
See you at eight o'clock in the afternoon. I'll send you the address.
Mr. He, you're back.
By the way, Mrs. Liu
Where is Mrs. He?
Mrs. He said that
she would take Xiaobao back to see her parents.
Are Mrs. He's parents
getting in trouble?
It seems not.
Ok.
Well.
Tonight,
I won't  have dinner at home.
You don't need to prepare the dinner.
Go ahead with your stuff.
Ok.
Well, Mr. He.
Mrs. He forgot to take away her luggage.
Miss Qin.
What you are doing
is controlling the baby and commanding Mr. He, right?
What are you talking about?
I just don't want to see
He Qiaoyan.
It must be Qiaoyan.
You open the door first.
I'm going to fetch the clothes.
Then I'll give him a hot meal.
I have to make him a new one.
How can he have leftovers?
Mrs. He.
Mr. He
asked me to send them to you
What about He Qiaoyan?
Mr. He and Minister Lin have been to meet
a very important partner.
Mr. He said
he allows you stay at home with your parents.
He grants you days off.
All right.
Thank you.
Secretary Zhong.
What about staying for dinner?
No, thanks.
If there's nothing wrong with Mrs. He,
I got to go.
I'm fine.
I am ok.
Goodbye!
Lao Qin!
Meeting Song Yuan tonight
is a right choice.
Because of Song Yuan's recommendation,
Mr. Jia is so agreeable
to meet us.
By the way,
when we get back tonight,
Let's get ready in details.
At ten o'clock tomorrow morning,
when we meet Mr. Jia,
try to get the deal done.
Don 't worry.
Doctor,
how's my dad?
Infective endocarditis.
He's in critical condition.
And the patient is old.
All the body functions decline.
Besides,
He also had mitral regurgitation,
and carotid artery occlusion.
So the risk of surgery is relatively high.
Is there another way?
For now,
there is no better way.
There are certain risks in the operation.
But the more you delay, the greater the risk.
I hope the family members can make a decision as soon as possible.
Mom.
Doctor.
Go and call someone.
Mom.
Lao Qin.
You are breaking your words.
You once said that
no matter what happens,
you're always with me.
Please wake up.
Mom.
Don't do that.
The doctor says your blood pressure is too high.
What about your father?
What do we do?
Yue’er.
Aunt.
Don't be panic.
Uncle will be fine.
Xiaobao.
Let's go.
Xiaobao, everything is ok.
You've been in hospital because of getting a cold before,
haven't you?
Grandpa
didn't eat healthily
and didn't sleep well,
so he had a cold.
But the cold he has this time
is more serious.
He needs to be hospitalized.
Don't worry, Xiaobao.
Ok?
Mom needs to be here
with grandparents.
You go home with Aunt Yang first
to meet Dad, ok?
Xiaobao is so good.
Ruowei.
I'd like to trouble you for another trip.
Don 't worry.
I'll be here as soon as I send Xiaobao home.
Come on.
Say goodbye to Mom.
Bye.
Xiaobao.
Mrs. Liu, here.
Aunt has something else to do.
I have to go first.
You listen to what Mom has said.
Go to bed,
okay?
I got to go.
Mrs. Liu.
Thank you, Miss Yang.
Xiaobao.
Isn't there a holiday for you two?
Why did you come back alone?
It was Miss Yang who sent Xiaobao back.
Yang Ruowei?
Yes.
Get on with what you are doing.
Ok.
Xiaobao.
Why mommy
didn't come back with you?
Grandpa is sick.
Serious?
He needs to have an operation.
Your father's condition
is developing rapidly.
If it goes on like this,
the risk will be higher.
You need to make a decision quickly.
Mom.
The risk of the operation is very high.
What did the doctor say?
If not,
it will only continue to deteriorate.
I don't know what to do.
Dad is ill.
Mom's down, too.
I, alone,
don't know what to do.
It's all my fault. It's all my fault.
Because I don't have time
to take care of them.
It's all my fault. It's all my fault.
You did a good job.
Believe me.
Everything will be ok.
Yiyue.
You take Xiaobao in first.
Secretary Zhong,
please contact me with
the GMN Medical Center's
Professor Xu.
I just got in touch with
the well-known experts and teams in China.
They'll come here as fast as they can
with the best team
to assist the operation.
Will he be fine?
Don't worry.
They've just made
a remote preliminary diagnosis.
Although the condition is serious,
there is still room to recover.
Hello, Dr. Liu.
I am a family member of the patient.
The thing is,
may I ask you can we
directly transfer the patient to ICU
to do monitoring?
In addition,
I have the best
medical team.
They're on their way
to assist you.
As for this matter,
the Dean has told me.
For your family's condition,
we're also working through the night.
As for your request,
we will try our best to cooperate.
If the operation is confirmed,
please sign it.
And we can arrange
the operating room and medical personnel.
Ok.
Thank you.
Not at all.
Mom.
Trust me.
Thank you a lot.
Qiaoyan.
Thank you.
Without you,
Yueyue and I
wouldn't know what to do.
Mom.
You don't have to say that.
Just let
me and Yiyue do that.
What you need the most now
is to take care of your body,
and have a good rest.
Ruowei,
I have to trouble you
to stay with Yiyue for a while.
I'll send Xiaobao to school first,
and then take mom back to have a rest.
When it's ready,
I'll come back.
No.
I'm not going back.
I want to be with her Dad.
Mom.
Listen to Qiaoyan.
Xiaobao.
Go to school as a good boy.
Ok?
As Mr. He is here,
everything will be fine.
You wake up?
I brought you wonton.
You have ever said
it's unhealthy to have midnight snack, haven't you?
You remember it so clearly.
Today is an exception.
Your strength and energy
are both draining.
You need a nutritional supplement.
Thank you for today.
Why did you help me so much?
Because you are my wife.
Actually, you don't have to
help me so much.
We're just hiring partners.
It's unnecessary for you to fulfill any obligation.
Have it when it's still hot.
Or the wonton will be cold in a moment.
He Qiaoyan.
You haven't been at the company all day.
I heard about that
You and Miss Lin Wei
have ever been engaged.
Been engaged?
I just heard about it.
Lin family and He family have been friends for generations.
More than 20 years ago,
it did say that.
But it was just a joke.
I didn't take it seriously.
To be exact,
We've only known each other since childhood.
Why do you suddenly want to ask this?
This wonton is really delicious.
Would you like one, too?
It's too hot.
It's not hot anymore.
Is it delicious?
Not bad.
You eat more.