Unforgettable Love
EP13
Xiaowei.
Auntie, long time no see.
More and more beautiful.
Thank you, auntie.
Qiaoyan, look who's here.
Excuse me for a moment.
Long time no see, Qiaoyan.
Long time no see.
Qiaoyan
you brief Xiaowei to the situation.
Who is she?
She is
Miss Lin.
I heard that she is the founder
of the niche luxury brand
emerged two years ago
Vivi Lin.
Many celebrities
have recommended this brand.
What a good match!
They look like
a perfect couple.
They really are a perfect match.
Finally.
Good to see you, Uncle Wang.
So, she is the bride
arranged to He Qiaoyan?
Lin and He are family friends,
when the He family was in trouble
the Lin family provided their
unwavering supports
and offered much help.
They're still a major shareholder of the He family.
Mr. Lin's daughter,
do you remember her?
Of course.
Much taller.
Thank you, uncle.
I'll wait for him outside.
OK.
Why are you so careless?
What did I say?
She just can't make it.
Anniversaries of Heshi Group,
before she showed up,
have never gone wrong.
Please don't be mad, auntie.
She's just fallen down
by accident.
Other than that, she did well.
It was Lin Wei.
It was not someone else.
I haven't seen her for years,
and she barely asks for anything.
You have to be considerate.
I know what you mean.
We owes to the Lin family,
but it doesn't mean that
we have to
make compromises for everything.
Making our share price rise
does good for both He family and Lin family.
I know,
you're still investigating the car accident.
After so many years,
the wound has already healed
why tear it open?
We're unaware of the truth.
That's not healing.
It's only self-paralysis.
My advice for you,
stop the investigation.
Right now,
you must put all your energy
into our business.
That's what your brother wants.
It is no longer
your own career,
but the hard work of our whole family.
Don't let us down,
I understand.
Rest early,
Good night.
A heart-stopping dance.
An exciting night.
heart-stopping?
Palpitation?
What about myocardial infarction?
Excited?
by whom?
He Qiaoyan?
He's my husband.
How dare him?
When I'm with him,
he dare not even move.
It's not that I'm completely unmoved.
Let me have a look.
It's better to be careful.
That fall on the dinner party,
it might cause
a slight sprain.
It's alright.
What did you just say?
I said, it might cause
a slight sprain.
Not that,
the first sentence.
You said that,
you're not completely unmoved.
I knew it.
After all, you've done so much for me.
Wait, you mean touched?
Don't you mean touched?
I'm going to sleep,
Good night. Goodbye.
You might smother yourself.
It's OK. I'm cold.
Good night.
Hey.
Hello? Are you asleep?
Let's have a chat.
For no reason?
I'm ready to go to sleep.
Wait!
What do you think of Miss Lin?
What do you mean?
Is she excellent?
She's always been excellent.
The Lin family is very strict
with their children.
Well,
do you two get along well?
Back when we were kids,
we all like math very much,
so we both attended the math club.
So do you think she's pretty?
Well
She's so beautiful
and talented,
so she must get many admirers .
You two
were arranged for marriage?
Have an early rest.
Save the power and net flow
for your cellphone.
It's charging
and there's WiFi.
I wander,
why
you two are arranged for marriage,
yet you haven't married her?
I'm going to turn off my phone and go to sleep.
Good night.
No!
He hang up on me...
She's rich,
talented,
and beautiful.
I am no worse than her.
It's just first love.
I don't believe it.
Is first love
so important for men?
Qin Yiyue
What the hell are you doing?
So?
What happened last night?
Did Mr. He
got cross-examined?
Cross-examine?
In what capacity
and on which side can I cross-examine him?
So you're going to hold on like this?
Until you fall apart?
She's right.
I can't fall apart.
Why don't you text me back?
Come on, quarrel with me.
Don't you love to pick up quarrels?
Still no response.
I warn you, He Qiaoyan,
On three,
if you still don't text me back,
I'll get angry!
And it's not a good one!
One two three.
Why can't you just text me back?
Didn't you usually text me back immediately.
I'm so sad.
Sis,
no matter what happens,
you'll always be my goddess.
You are the best match for Mr. He.
What's going on?
Didn't you know?
Check the microblog.
The beautiful fiancée of He Qiaoyan
completely defeated Qin Yiyue.
Lin Wei
I've already said that,
Qin Yiyue and he Qiaoyan
are no match.
To be honest,
Lin Wei is so elegant.
Top designer and overbearing president,
standard configuration of romantic fiction.
Qin Yiyue?
just an unexpected calculating girl.
My god,
they really are good at making stories.
How about becoming an online novel writer?
They are just jealous.
Also,
you spent your spare time here
voluntarily
for a part-time job,
not for gossip.
So you don't care about what they said?
It's just gossips,
Why should I give a rap?
Where are you going?
To pick up Xiaobao.
There're too many online posts,
I'm afraid that
he might hear about this.
Whenever anything comes up,
he's always been
your first concern.
Things like these,
we know black from white,
yet children can't.
Still,
How about yourself?
Don't you worry?
These posts
are generally hostile to you.
Some even slander you.
Think about it for yourself,
ever since I met He Qiaoyan,
my name has become a popular search term.
So I couldn't care less about
the rumors they post.
Alright,
you take care here.
I have to go now.
Where is Dr. Qin going?
Dr. Ning, look.
People all say that Lin Wei and Mr. He
are arranged to get marry.
and Dr. Qin is a mistress.
Right, I see.
You go to work.
Next week's work schedules
are all set.
Please take a look.
Also
about the posts of Dr. Qin on the Internet…
Should we take action?
What kind of posts?
Look.
Inform the legal department,
let them deal with it.
I want to see the solution after work.
Ok.
I've brought Xiaobao home.
Don't worry.
Are you ok?
Why?
About those posts on the Internet.
With you by my side,
Nothing could ever go wrong.
Besides,
You must have told the powerful legal team
of the Heshi group to deal with this.
Xiaobao and I
just need one night off the Internet,
and everything will be alright.
The legal team are already working on it.
Later today
there should be results.
I've got another meeting.
I have to go.
Tonight,
I won't come home for dinner.
OK.
Bye.
An unknown doctor and the pretty rich girl
Qin is so ugly.
Mr. He is just playing around
Cinderella will be dumped sooner or later.
What a crap!
forget it,
I won't be angry,
that's exactly what they want.
Xiaobao, mommy's here to play with you.
So strange,
Screensaver with sound.
What a mess.
Don't be scared, Ruowei,
I'm coming.
Don't do that.
I'm just kidding.
I just want to play the hero.
It's just a game.
I didn't mean to provoke you guys.
Help!
Zhang, Xu
You're wearing trousers and shoes.
The toilet is so bright,
I saw it all at once, okay?
And Zhang,
the hand he put on my shoulder
is wearing the wedding ring.
Director Wen,
your script is such a cliché.
But at least,
costumes and props
should be more careful.
All right, you guys go home.
Boss
our task is finished.
Bye bye.
Go, go, go
Boss, is this overtime working?
Right, does it count?
It was supposed to count.
Now, it doesn't.
Go, go, go.
Hurry.
Having fun?
You're too bold, aren't you?
I'm an extreme fan of horror movies
and have participated in
every popular room escapes game.
For all your
shoddy little tricks.
Just a piece of cake.
Boring.
It's you that's boring, isn't it?
Such an old-fashioned story.
So boring.
Want to stimulate hormones with horror.
And play the hero?
You're just boring.
If I show up
when you're in danger
and save your life,
will you be moved?
well
I might
cry.
Really?
Why?
Because the last person I see
before my death
is you.
I will never rest in peace.
All right.
Turn off the lights.
Go home.
No, no, no, No.
Don't leave me here alone.
Have you been waiting long?
No I just arrived.
I didn't know that
aunt also invited you.
I didn't know she invited you either.
Xiaowei.
Auntie.
Excuse me,
I need to use the lady's room.
OK.
Congratulations.
Your bracelet
got the support of the board of directors.
Did you do it, Aunt?
Do what?
Is it you that
promote media to
let those posts
emerge in an endless stream?
Yes.
Why?
Those posts
are the best way for Qin Yiyue
to get a clear understanding of herself.
I want her to know clearly that
you two are not a well-matched couple.
Qin Yiyue is my wife
I say we make a good couple.
She's the perfect match for me.
Even if she is,
however,
she's not suitable to be the daughter-in-law of our family.
So she has to be gone.
Let me remind you now,
your responsibility
lies on the Heshi group.
It's the work of your father and your brother.
If…
All right, all right.
Eat first.
I have something else to do.
Take your time.
Qiaoyan got busy with company stuffs.
He's always like that,
a workaholic
Got nothing but work, work, work.
It's OK, auntie.
I understand.
I'm just like him.
Sometimes when I get busy
I can stay up for two whole days.
You two are the same,
both so sensible
and stick to your own mission.
I Know,
the marriage of Lin family and He family
is a win-win for both of us.
Those posts on the Internet…
I've taken care of them.
Don't worry, auntie.
Of course,
I was right about you.
So…
You don't mind
what's going with Qiaoyan and that girl?
Didn't you just say that
they're just contractual.
It's not real marriage.
However,
Qiaoyan seems to be…
attracted to her.
Well, young people
all like to
dream unrealistically.
People like me and Qiaoyan
we are bond to go back to
our own tracks.
This is Miss Qin
I believe soon
will leave Qiaoyan.
Here, here.
Don't you have anything to ask me?
Wait a moment.
What did you just say?
Here's your water.
Thank you.
About the posts…
Right, about those.
Why are they keeping emerging?
What's going on?
There're some problems.
Is it because of Auntie?
I guess so.
I'm sorry.
What do you mean you're sorry?
Not sincerely at all.
We have an agreement in the contract,
situations like this,
I need to compensate you for your mental loss.
One hundred thousand is transferred to your account.
Check it.
Come on, this
will get you beaten up.
Ok?
If you do
feel sorry.
How about…
shorten our contract
by one month?
No way.
What about half a month?
What about a week?
No way.
You're so stingy!
Bully He.
Are you in such a hurry to leave?
You can't understand
how much I yearn for freedom.
Fine, you['ll have your freedom.
Really?
Wait.
You call this freedom?
From now on,
you have 24 hours.
Enjoy your freedom.
You really are so stingy.
What's the matter, He Weifei?
Daddy told you,
no way.
Xiaobao, mommy will get it for you.
I'm free today,
nobody can stop me.
Come on.
A marshmallow please.
Thank you.
How much is it?
Twenty-five.
My treat.
But don't do this again.
Wait, don't move.
I think someone's taking a photograph.
It must be about me.
Let me teach them a lesson!
What are you doing?
I told them to do so.
Since we can't stop
the villainous posts.
Why don't we create
some sweet and positive posts
to cover them all.
Smart move.
Let's show them
a happy family
of three.
Come on.
let's go.
Let me see your smile.
Let mommy have a look.
Go ahead.
Wave with me.
Start from today,
every morning
I'll come with you
to bring Xiaobao to school,
and then I'll drive you to work.
Actually, Mr. He,
since we went shopping
yesterday,
there have been many positive posts on the Internet.
More than enough.
More than enough?
Far from enough.
I'll drive you to work.
A real gentleman.
Please.
Well,
you do know how to impress women.
A little too obvious,
don't you think?
Sit tight.
Sit tight?
I'm not up yet.
Wait! I'm not ready.
Good morning, Dr. Qin.
Morning.
Dr. Qin,
news about your love life
has become a hot search topic.
Mr. He was never
on any SNS.
Now he actually registered microblog.
And all his posts are about you.
What is this?
Your husband's on microblog.
Key points
His profile
is not the CEO of He['s group
but husband of doctor Qin's.
Oh my God, that's sweet.
Look! Look!
His own microblog,
you're in the profile,
you picture is used as profile photo.
Even the first post
is about you.
So, all those
rumors and gossips can stop.
That overseas returned designer
and perfect ex-girlfriend?
she can never compare with you,
the official wife.
It was posted at 6:07.
He got up so early.
June 7th
is my birthday.
Oh my God,
save me please.
This is so sweet!
Work hard.
I'm leaving.
Auntie.
Qiaoyan
The person I told you about is here.
Will you greet her?
She's the best person
to promote our bracelet
in Europe and America.
I see.
Hello, I'm He Qiaoyan.
Hello, I'm Lin Wei.
The person my aunt mentioned
is you.
Was it a surprise?
Don't forget
I studied business in college,
the designer work
is just a hobby.
The smart bracelet project
is very important for He's group.
It's not something for you to practice.
I know how much you rely on data.
I'll use data to convince you that
I am qualified for the job.
For the past few days,
I've been doing my work.
This is the data of the bracelet user group.
Users from 25 to 30 years old
take up the largest proportion,
30 percent.
And among those
people,
65 percent of them
share a common feature.
All of them have been using
modern science and technology creative products
for over five years.
What does this mean?
It means the current market demand
for your smart bracelet
is very high.
Each age group
has different amount of market demand.
Users over 35 years old
only take up nine percent.
And user group under 20 years old
is also relatively small,
only takes up 13 percent.
And your smart Bracelet
is getting more and more attention.
From 2014
to 2019,
attention has increased dramatically.
Besides,
people are paying more and more attention to health.
I don't want to go to work.
Why?
I am the CEO.
Why do I need to work?
I don't want to go to work.
You do?
Then I'll tell Mr. Wen that
you decide to
choose your bed
over your freedom of
finance and love life
for the rest of your life.
How did you got in?
I've changed the room code.
You change the code from your first girlfriend's birthday
to
your second girlfriend's birthday.
Is that a change?
Every thought in your head
is all under my control.
Take a rest, bro.
I have a secret tunnel.
Don't you  know?
What?
It is newly built.
A tunnel to your heart.
The tunnel collapse ahead
please take a detour.
Actually, have a look.
This one is more detailed.
Excuse me. I need to take this call.
Could you whisper to me,
is there any bugs of
your second generation Bracelet?
From chip to system
and then to the sensor,
everything uses cutting edge technology.
There are no bugs.
Well,
is it possible
to deliberately
insert any bugs in it?
Are you going to seek out
some trade secrets?
Of course not.
I took a bet with Yang Ruowei
for my freedom.
I have to make her moved,
but I can't be moved.
Just tell me,
is there any way
to reprogram the bracelet?
Our company don't provide
after-sale services that involve
fraud and falsification.
I'm too busy to play with you.
Technology
maybe it's the ladder of human progress,
but it definitely
is the stumbling block for me.
I knew you didn't eat breakfast.
So I made you a
simple sandwich.
Very tempting.
However,
I'm not hungry.
Nobody can resist such temptation.
Are you stuck?
Show me the bracelet.
The breakfast I made for you
left the cooking smell all over me.
Therefore
I
need to take a bath, too.
Don't do that!
Go to the bathroom!
Goblin.
She's definitely a goblin
It's so sweet
I'm so jealous.
This is the clinic.
What are you gossiping about?
Look at the composition and the angle.
It's full of love.
Look.
I forwarded it with my spare account.
What's your spare account.
I won't tell you.
Qin Yiyue Global Fans Support Association
Super talk host of  "the captured He"
Shush
Do you want everyone hear you?
"the captured He". How did you get the idea?
You are a real genius.
I almost laugh my ass off.
You're so miserable.
The wife personally advertises her love life
No one else has done it.
It's almost two o'clock,
I'll have patients later.
Have to go now.
Bye,
The captured He.
Mr. He is in a meeting.
You can wait in his office
for a while.
There's no need.
I'm here to get the wine for Mr. Wen.
He said you knew where it is.
Right, the bottle given to Mr. He
by the partner last week.
Mr. Gu has been thinking about it.
He told me to give it to you when you're here.
This way.
They are all in English, can you read them?
Why is Miss Lin here?
Miss Lin is the director
of our third marketing department.
She's in full charge of
entering the European and American markets.