LAW SCHOOL
ALL NAMES, ORGANIZATIONS, CASES
AND INCIDENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIOUS
PUBLICATION OF SUSPECTED CRIME
MADE BY AUTHORITIES BEFORE…
FIVE DAYS BEFORE THE CONSTITUTIONAL REVIEW
"Once the media begins to report
on one's charges,
it will plant presupposition and bias
on the judges.
This damages
the defendant's right to a fair trial."
"The defendant may be innocent,
but the damage cannot be restored."
We should assert…
What's wrong? You don't like that?
APPLICANT: JIN HYEONG-U
Why? It's well-written.
This seems good enough
to be up against Prof. Kang Ju-man.
I get that you'd rather have
Prof. Yang write this,
but he said he can't do that.
So why can't he do it?
JIN HYEONG-U
APPLICANT'S TESTIFIER: YANG JONG-HOON
CONCERNED PARTY: KANG SOL
PRINT
TESTIFIER STATEMENT
How can you be Prosecutor Jin's testifier?
My opinion is that it's unconstitutional.
Then why were you so keen
on having Jin indicted?
I needed to get him in court.
You did what I couldn't do.
You weren't helping me.
You used me to get what you wanted.
"Used"?
You knew if Jin gets indicted,
he'd request a constitutional review,
and used me, right?
-If you shared your intention--
-My intention?
What's my intention?
My father passed away
due to his publication of my dad's
suspected crime, but you--
It's yours to prove on the trial.
It must be found constitutional
for the trial--
Then you shouldn't be here now.
Prosecutor Jin and I
won't be an easy fight.
THIS ARTICLE CONTRADICTS
THE PRINCIPLE OF PROPORTIONALITY
AND MUST BE ABOLISHED
Is that enough to convince the judges?
If publication of suspected crime
is allowed,
they say it contradicts
the presumption of innocence.
It's not to break
The people commissioned us
as investigative authorities,
so it's only natural for us to disclose
the suspected crime
after an investigation.
Especially when…
a key presidential candidate
such as Ko Hyeong-su
or other high officials
are investigated
for crimes and corruption…
the people should absolutely have
the right to know.
Now that's a good argument.
Is this why you made me
the first prosecutor in Korea
to be indicted for violating
Article 126 of the Criminal Code?
A constitutional review
can be requested only with a trial.
How did you know
I'd request a constitutional review?
I would've done the same.
OFFICER CHO YE-BUM
If you have questions, ask me.
His internship is over.
Don't contact my student in secret
and make him rat on them.
POWER OFF
What was that? Did he hang up?
He needs to know that we know.
Squeak, squeak.
Not everyone can be a spy,
and you aren't cut out for that.
What do you mean?
I bet everyone thinks it's you.
You wrote Seung-jae's complaint, too.
It was a part of my internship.
I had to do as he asked.
I get that you want to be a prosecutor
and made a mistake
trying to be on his good side.
But still, Prosecutor Jin?
Sol.
I don't know why I did that.
I'll take care of this, so--
You can leave the study group.
Then he'll have no reason to use you.
Joon-hwi.
How can you say that to me?
You of all people can't say that to me.
Why do you think I did that?
During the internship,
the guy who passed the second round
got all the attention.
I was practically invisible next to you.
I'm not the type who doesn't get noticed,
but next to you, I was just…
I get how you feel.
I've also suffered enough
with smarties at home and at school.
Only you get me.
Stop talking, and take care of this.
You said only I get you, right?
Then do me a favor.
Okay, shoot away.
It's about that absurd vlog you film.
My vlog?
Yes.
What would've happened had the facts
about Lee Man-ho's sexual assault case
been published
through the proper channels?
He would not have been ruled
"feeble-minded" so easily,
and we could've prevented the verdict
which the public at large deemed unjust.
He oddly has a point.
Politicians who applaud publication
of allegations involving their opponents
and lash out when it happens to them
should no longer be allowed
to take advantage of the provision.
When did Ji-ho find out
Prof. Yang is his testifier?
He didn't say anything to us?
Article 126 of the Criminal Code
could not keep your father safe.
Who do you think benefits the most
from this law?
No other countries
have such a general and broad provision
against publication of suspected crime.
Regarding similar cases
in other countries,
Ms. Erica Shin, a lawyer
and comparative law expert at Harvard
who was also selected as a witness,
will virtually join us.
Are we ready for this video call?
He betrayed us to help Prosecutor Jin.
And what's all this fuss about?
They won't win anyway.
CONSTITUTION
Hello, I'm Erica Shin.
I'd like to thank Prof. Yang Jong-hoon
and the Constitutional Court
for this chance to share my opinion.
CONSTITUTIONAL COURT
Look at the view count.
She totally made me do this.
Hey, doesn't this mean it's a huge hit?
I'm frightened.
CONSTITUTIONAL COURT
Why didn't you tell me?
She asked me not to.
She said she'd call you in time
and asked me to stay quiet.
"In time"?
When is that time?
I believe it's now.
Hello?
It's me.
"It's me"?
Have you been well?
Have I been well?
How's Mom?
Is Byeol also--
Criminal Code Article 126
on publication of suspected crime
only exists in the Republic of Korea.
Before we take a look at other precedents
in other countries,
we must first consider
the biggest beneficiaries
of this clause in the law.
Erica Shin?
I was about to call you right now.
Do you have any money?
Money?
What makes you think I have any money?
I'm living off a line of credit.
Can you take out some cash
from that account then?
My landlord wants to raise the rent.
What can I do?
Otherwise, we'll have to move out.
Who knew Sol had a twin sister?
They look the same.
Hey.
They only look the same.
She went to Harvard Law.
She's not in her league with that career.
Anyway, why is she named Erica Shin?
Sol looked surprised, too.
Did you know?
Don't get curious. You'll get hurt.
Hold your horses.
I'm starting to get scared.
If you're that scared, take it down.
No, he's about to get the silver medal.
You're at 100,000 subscribers?
He had a good reason
when he uploaded that video
as if he was forced.
What I'm really curious about
is Ko's response.
The video blew up like this,
but why is he as quiet as a mouse?
He was in the media,
so he probably put an embargo on this.
And he won't take a legal measure.
He can't sue him for spreading falsehood,
but I thought he'd threaten him.
Did you see the bulletin?
Someone raised an issue
on how Yeong-chang came to the dorm.
What? No way.
They're saying we should kick her out
and have her punished.
They're furious.
Hey, don't look.
They want all of you,
from Ye-seul, who gave him a key,
to Sol and Joon-hwi, who let him go
although you knew.
But why did this suddenly resurface…
He wasn't staying quiet.
MOM
I sent you some tonic.
You'll compete
in the Justice Mock Trial, right?
This was delivered.
HERBAL TONIC
I'm throwing it out.
Why? It must be expensive.
You can have it then.
Again?
While you were busy
stabbing the kids in the back,
they also caused huge trouble.
Take a look.
RELAY VIDEO:
EXPOSING ASSEMBLYMAN KO HYEONG-SU
If they want to make a case
against Ko Hyeong-su,
they should at least buckle up.
You can be their help,
just as you saved me
by making Ko abandon Lee Man-ho.
That happened by chance.
Assemblyman Ko was the one
who sent Lee's son to the U.S.
I gave him the Lee Man-ho Act
in exchange for the life of Lee's son
as James.
He's living a good life as James now.
If Ko Hyeong-su didn't ask James
to send them his recent photo…
Your photo?
Okay. Let me call you back.
I wouldn't have known that Lee Man-ho
had been in contact with Ko.
I had no idea why he broke his promise
to never talk about his son again
and wanted to make a deal
with a man like Lee Man-ho.
What if the world finds out
you made a deal with Lee Man-ho
after you enacted the Lee Man-ho Act?
You threatened him? That's unlike you.
To get Ko to abandon Lee Man-ho?
Threaten him?
I gave him a warning
disguised as a piece of advice.
So he got scared Lee Man-ho will talk
and took the bait.
How could he do anything like this
as a human?
-Darn it!
-I wish to have…
Assemblyman Ko Hyeong-su,
you can't do this to me!
He was suffocated by him,
then the news was all over the media.
At that point,
it doesn't matter what Lee says.
Ko Hyeong-su can easily say
he's talking nonsense
due to his grudge against him.
And who would the people believe?
Lee Man-ho knew that.
That's why he kept quiet,
trying to make a deal with Ko.
But I pried for his connection
and tried to make a deal on his sentence.
So in the end,
Ko Hyeong-su got rid of him.
That jerk…
Then we took part in Lee Man-ho's death.
And I took part in saving you.
Ye-seul must be insane.
She sued me?
I'll get you an attorney.
Just go get questioned.
I have a phobia against lawsuits!
Dad, you need to stop this.
It'll hurt you, too.
Stopping the lawsuit
isn't the solution to this.
I have a plan in my mind. Okay?
ASSEMBLYMAN KO HYEONG-SU
Hey, get started on your task.
I found this photo while looking
for the reason of the disclosure.
It's Assemblyman Ko Hyeong-su,
the prosecutor's acquaintance,
and Cho Tae-yeong,
the CEO of TOYGOODTOY's competitor,
who's also Assemblyman Ko's
head supporter.
If Seo Gi-yeol's son brings up my name
into this matter…
Will you sue him?
I can only stop the reporters for a while.
We should do that
to make people stop assuming, so…
You want to say it's not true?
That's what they're after.
They want to investigate
and see if this is true or false.
They're law students.
And Yang Jong-hoon is behind them,
waiting for a chance to get me.
Then are you going to do that again?
I should use that method.
What? What do you mean?
Our policy changed to differentiate
the credit line level for law students.
Our previous policy was established
back when over 80 percent of law students
passed the bar exam.
But at this point,
the percentage dropped
to 50 percent and less,
so many candidates
never make it in the law.
So the level depends on my grades?
Yes, that's the change in our policy.
If you have bad grades,
your credit line will be adjusted, too.
We need your report card.
How does this make any sense?
Why did the policy suddenly change?
What if I barely managed to pass the year?
Your current loan already exceeds
the credit limit of our changed policy,
so we can't give you any more loans.
You must pay back the amount
exceeding the limit by next month.
So loans are decided on grades, too?
HANJU BANK
ADJUSTMENTS FOR GPA 2.3 AND UNDER
Students who win an award
in the Justice Mock Trial Competition
are exempt?
Are you competing
in the Justice Mock Trial?
No.
-I'll do a civil case. Join me.
-No.
What?
Ji-ho, this says your dad took his life
after embezzling the company fund.
What is this?
There's a comment from this guy
who claimed to have been a manager…
No way. Did Sol serve time in juvie?
And for school violence?
Someone posted photos, too.
YANG WAS SOL'S PROSECUTOR
AND NOW TEACHES HER
KANG SOL GOT IN THANKS TO YANG?
I knew people would expose our info,
but now that they have,
I'm worried about the others.
So you got in trouble without a plan?
We had to cause trouble to find a plan.
We won't sit around and get bullied.
What about the guest book from the funeral
Seo and Ko went to together?
If they didn't lose it…
She had three children.
I'm sure one of them
may tell us the truth.
PROFESSOR KANG JU-MAN
PROFESSOR JUNG DAE-HYEON
Are you here to see me?
No, sir.
Come in for a moment.
I have to talk to you.
I won't go inside.
Your father could've been
the dean of this school.
You know that
he quit because of you, right?
Then you should lie low.
You shouldn't associate with troublemakers
who attack Assemblyman Ko
who works hard for our law school.
Think of your father and--
If you're concerned about me,
I'd like to turn it down.
That cheeky brat.
Professor.
Did you send for me?
Hey.
Have you seen Kang Sol B? My roomie.
Hey, you know,
if you win the Justice Mock Trial,
it'll help you become
a judicial researcher, right?
You saw the photo in the comments?
What? The photo? What photo?
HEY, SOL, DID YOU FORGET YOUR JUVIE DAYS?
Darn it.
Take the photo down now
before I file a criminal charge
over portrait rights.
What are you doing?
UNLESS YOU WANT TO PAY ME FOR THE DAMAGE
There are no clauses
in the Criminal Code for this.
You didn't know it's a civil case?
Of course I knew.
I got angry and confused.
Go with defamation
and make it a criminal case.
I can't. It's true.
I agree that we should abolish
defamation for stating facts.
The comment isn't the problem.
You didn't make it as the court's intern,
so you should win that competition.
Even for me,
it's tough to win an award there.
Then Joon-hwi, too. Two plus one.
I won't be a freeloader
or become a nuisance.
The three of us should compete.
I have a dire reason
to win an award in that competition.
If you want to win, it can't be you.
Maybe your twin sister.
I wasn't going to say this to you, but…
It's a matter of survival.
LAW OFFICER LOAN
ADJUSTMENTS FOR GPA 2.3 AND UNDER
Come on, say something.
Well, you should at least consider.
How much do you need?
If you need money, I'll lend you some.
Hey, we lived together for a while
as roommates.
How can you be so harsh?
She was shaken.
What?
GET OUT, IF YOU WON'T LEAVE, I WILL
CONSIDERING A CLASS ACTION
STOP PLAYING THE VICTIM
YOU'LL CRIPPLE YOUR NEXT BOYFRIEND
SO WHEN? GET OUT!
I apologize for having caused trouble.
I will…
move out of the dorm.
And I also apologize
for damaging the reputation…
of my fellow female students.
But please remember this.
As a woman,
I was tormented by his violence.
I was scared of his threats
and conciliation,
but as a law student,
although it wasn't enough,
I did the best I could to stay honorable.
And thanks to all of you
who study the law with me here,
I was able to return.
How superficial.
Hey.
Superficial?
You of all people can't say that.
What?
You got the court internship
Sol B couldn't and saw her trial.
So what if I saw it?
If you did, you couldn't say
it was superficial as a woman.
No, you should not.
It was finalized after the first trial.
Haven't you read it?
What do you mean? I read everything--
Don't even try to lie to me.
You should give it a read.
If you think she's superficial
after you read that,
you're the one who should move out.
Whatever, ex-convict.
Right, that?
Isn't that amazing?
A juvenile delinquent
becomes a student at Hankuk Law.
Doesn't that seem amazing?
She overcame her dark history
and became an officer in law.
People love these stories, no?
What is it?
She says she'll make it big in law
because she's an ex-convict.
My gosh.
If you interned at the court,
you should know
getting sent to a juvenile hall
isn't a part of criminal punishment.
It doesn't leave a record,
so if you call her an ex-convict,
shouldn't you be ashamed as a law student?
LAW SCHOOL LIBRARY, LECTURE ROOM
SELECT
If you told them off for me,
does it mean you'll compete?
If you need money--
I don't want money to come between us.
What I need isn't your money
but your generous heart to help me.
Be honest.
You are thinking about it, right?
Get away from me.
I wasn't going to be this patronizing,
but I let people think
I was Prof. Kang's daughter
to help you get less stressed out.
Did I ever rub that in your face
despite all the misunderstanding
and hatred?
How's the trial going?
It's all right.
I'm doing it without an attorney.
Then it'll get rough.
Not as rough as the time
I got questioned by you.
And I deserve it anyway.
Anyway,
the comments on that video
are really malicious.
Is everyone okay?
How would they be okay?
It's just that they can hold out.
Seung-jae, I have a favor to ask.
Isn't that why you came?
Everything but hacking.
I looked into the students
from your med school…
What? The president?
Do you know how agitated the president is
because of that malicious video
on Assemblyman Ko?
Well, it's not that I wanted to upload it.
If you get on his bad side,
your life at school will be hard.
And I'll be teaching practical classes
on the prosecution next year.
You know that you need good grades
on that subject to be a prosecutor, right?
Of course I do.
What can I do?
Yes, president.
Yes, I understand.
PROFESSOR JUNG DAE-HYEON
Professor, what should I do?
Drop that video
before the president asks to see you,
and upload a public apology
to Assemblyman Ko…
An apology video?
Embezzlement?
They're killing my dad twice.
My dad wouldn't embezzle money--
You're right. He wouldn't.
The prosecution found nothing
on his embezzlement
when they investigated his suicide.
So defamation of the deceased--
Let's wait and see.
It can't be just an individual.
He wanted to wait and see.
Prof. Yang looked into this?
Let's see.
Is your back okay
after you got stabbed by him?
No.
But I don't think he betrayed me.
Jin Hyeong-u leaked it out,
but Ko Hyeong-su instigated it.
In the end,
my target is the same as Prof. Yang.
And it's true that Ko is playing around
with Article 126.
But I'll fight to the end.
I believe it's constitutional.
Jin Hyeong-u should've turned him down.
If he had,
my dad wouldn't have become a victim.
I'll make sure
I win and make Jin Hyeong-u pay.
I'm on your side.
Okay. Let's fight to the end
and win this case.
We couldn't show our mock court properly
after a man died in there,
so I was disheartened.
But Assemblyman Ko Hyeong-su said
he'll do his best to hold
the Justice Mock Trial Competition here.
Did you call me out here
just to share that with me?
How can they slander a man like him
who always does his best
to help out his alma mater?
The students who were in that video
damaged our school's reputation--
You shouldn't punish them rashly.
You put me out of office
for damaging our school's reputation,
but you did it for nothing, correct?
It was a shameful moment
for a school that teaches the law.
That's because the police didn't conduct
a proper initial investigation--
Did you listen to what they said
on the video?
-If it's true--
-It's not true!
They're slandering him!
It's true. Everything is factual.
You should cut Ko Hyeong-su off
while you have a chance, President Lee.
And you're the one who should be
doing his best for the school.
DATE AND TIME
QUALIFICATIONS
You are interested.
You want to,
but not after your mom's suggestion?
It seems like you want to do it.
Let's do it together then.
Why do you try so hard to persuade me?
Why do you care so much about my roomie?
I'm grateful for her.
Are you sure it'll be okay
for you to record a video?
I won't be okay.
I'll be shattered into pieces.
If it hadn't been for Ko Hyeong-su,
your uncle may not have been involved
in that hit-and-run incident.
And if so, he probably wouldn't have taken
the free land.
Then your uncle wouldn't have been killed,
and you wouldn't have been framed
for killing your uncle whom you adored.
If it hadn't been for Ko,
Dan…
wouldn't have left in such a hurry.
Ji-ho's dad
also wouldn't have passed away,
and Ye-seul…
I feel like I owe her,
and I hate owing people.
THE 9TH JUSTICE MOCK TRIAL
COMPETITION APPLICATION
PROFESSOR YANG JONG-HOON
Hello?
Right now?
Yes, sir.
What--
THE 9TH JUSTICE MOCK TRIAL
NAME: HAN JOON-HWI, KANG SOL
KANG SOL A
Hello?
Hey, our professor wants us
at the hideout.
Prof. Yang?
Prof. Yang asked us to come.
Right now?
What time does he think it is now?
I lost my world since I lost you.
I have no reason to live.
I feel like my entire body is paralyzed,
not just the lower half.
I'd like to take this chance
to share my sincere apology to her.
I loved her so much
that I dreamed of marrying her.
When she got into law school,
I felt belittled
as we had prepared together.
I deeply regret and want to apologize
for causing an irrevocable wound
in her heart.
Now that I am crippled,
I finally realized what I have done.
I sincerely apologize
to Ms. Jeon and our people
whom my foolish son
have hurt deeply.
Please put the blame
on this father
who didn't bring him up properly.
And law students of Hankuk University,
please do not get abused
as a vessel in political slandering
against me.
Political slandering?
It's like him.
I can't watch him. Makes me feel sick.
As a politician,
I will pay the price…
FREE LAND
…for not bringing up my son properly
through legislations,
starting with reinforcing punishment
for dating abuse cases.
I will repay you
by working as hard as I can.
Where was this uploaded?
KO HYEONG-SU'S APOLOGY
What?
Wait, hey.
Why is this…
I received support and help
for all the laws
-Well, I…
-I put into motion
-Wait.
-from a professor
of Hankuk Law School, Prof. Kim Eun-suk.
-Together, we will do our best
-What?
to amend the laws regarding dating abuse.
Why is Prof. Kim with that man?
To make a law, he said.
Also, I'd like to use this chance
to suggest Ms. Jeon, who is also a student
of Prof. Kim Eun-suk,
-to join us in this process.
-Crazy…
What's he asking her to do with him?
My gosh. Why are we watching this?
Why don't you accept it?
Assemblyman Ko's offer.
-Prof. Kim!
You'll be doing it with me,
so give it a thought.
Goodness, why does my face look so big?
How did you film this video?
I have a bigger face than him?
You do.
I need to talk to you.
Is my face really bigger than his?
I must've been clenching my teeth.
Okay, fine.
I'll tell you. I'll talk.
President Lee told Prof. Jung
to make Ye-bum upload an apology video.
The great Yangcrates looks like
he has no idea what I'm up to.
I love it.
It was Prof. Kim?
I just did as she told me.
She's the mastermind behind this?
The press conference where he proposed
the abolishment of defamation by facts
was also her idea.
She did that to have an upper hand
for the trial of Bad FaMa.
But what's this one for?
How did Prof. Kim come up with an idea
to put on this show?
I'm so disappointed.
I didn't think of her like this.
She even gave him a big hand
during Ko Hyeong-su's lecture.
Maybe she wants to go into politics.
I don't think so.
People love the Ko family's video,
but our video is covered
with malicious comments.
I'll say what they're doing is nothing
but a B-grade show.
I'm going to accept his offer.
Gosh, is someone talking behind my back?
What's this?
BILL TO PREVENT DATING ABUSE
When did you…
The Sunglasses is considering too.
Thank you, professor,
for becoming my special attorney.
I quit defending you
in the middle of the trial.
He didn't appeal, but be on guard.
If you're still thankful,
you can read it over.
BILL TO PREVENT DATING ABUSE
You already saw through my plan?
A public apology?
I can't believe I'm doing this
because of my foolish son.
I want to propose an act
which strengthens punishment
for dating abuse to atone for this.
Proposing laws won't get you exempt.
Exempt? No, it's to atone for what he did.
Only someone like me
could pass the laws I propose.
I'm a key presidential candidate
for a reason.
But I can't just press a button
to pop a legislation out.
And it'll get too old
if you hold another press conference.
That's what concerns me.
You should counter them.
Instead of making him take it down,
you should have him upload your video too.
I can't have you see through me yet.
I don't know the details,
but I only did as Prof. Kim said.
She said
I wouldn't have to delete your video
or upload an apology.
I didn't want to be on Mr. Lee's bad side.
What's wrong is that
he got us on his bad side.
When he finds out what he's like,
he'll regret it bitterly.
Yes, we should reveal his true nature.
I thought you were done defending me.
Hyeongseol is taking Lee's case.
Exactly.
If I did you good,
why didn't you continue to hire me?
If you gave me this,
I can bail you out on self-defense.
Prosecutor Jin Hyeong-u is a tough man.
But I, Park Geun-tae,
made him cancel the indictment.
On top of that, he was recently shot down
in a self-defense case,
so he's completely pissed,
it won't be easy.
Prosecutor Jin has his eyes
on these two photos.
If the way Lee Man-ho was stabbed
looks similar to this one,
could your case really be ruled
as self-defense?
I defended Lee Man-ho up until his death,
so I'll appear as a testifier too.
I plan on making a strong case
that it wasn't self-defense.
My case
will be ruled self-defense for sure.
Gosh, you seem amazingly confident.
Who's your connection?
Someone who can consider
Prosecutor Jin Hyeong-u as his minion?
If that's the case, then I'll get lost.
Get lost, then.
Okay.
HAPPY CORRECTION, HAPPY PEOPLE
It's me.
Ki Du-seong is 100 percent sure
it'll be ruled as self-defense.
His connection thinks of Prosecutor Jin
as a minion,
so I think it's definitely
Assemblyman Ko Hyeong-su.
It looks like Assemblyman Ko Hyeong-su
got him
Attorney Song Ki-joon of Hyeongseol.
Anyway, I'll share the details in person.
I'm sure Ko Hyeong-su made you rule
Ki Du-seong's case as self-defense.
You're a prosecutor,
so you shouldn't be treated as his minion.
The guest book from the funeral
on that day
where Ko and my uncle went.
They hadn't lost it.
It was with Mr. Shin Woo-seop's daughter.
His son-in-law went to med school
with Seung-jae.
It's the evidence that Seo and Ko
were at the funeral
on the day of the hit-and-run.
VISITORS REGISTER
SEO BYUNG-JU, KO…
SEO BYUNG-JU, KO HYEONG-SU
But were they in the same car--
It can't prove that.
But why did Ko Hyeong-su fool you
and said he went the day before?
He may be your biggest connection
and the key presidential candidate.
SEO BYUNG-JU MURDER CASE
DID HE INSTIGATE HIS MURDER?
HAD JIN LEAK SUSPECTED CRIME
KANG DAN ACCUSED KO
CHO TAE-YEONG OF I-BIT
KO HYEONG-SU
Let's go with self-defense.
If that's what Assemblyman Ko wants.
Gosh, you should've said so sooner.
I don't usually do everything
as people say.
I mean, it's Assemblyman Ko.
It was Assemblyman Ko…
so you did as he said?
JIN HYEONG-U
HEAD PROSECUTOR JIN HYEONG-U
AUNT
You should know by now
that your connection is finished.
AUNT
Do you have anything to tell me?
What did you want to hear from me
to call me out this late?
Nothing?
Hey, Prosecutor Jin.
I'm sure you won't dare to interrogate me.
What more do I have to say between us?
We're in the same boat.
Just as you were in the same car with Seo
when he got drunk and hit someone and ran?
I don't know why you're doing this,
but you just have to trust me.
The rope I'm holding on to
should not be a rotten one, you know.
No, of course, it isn't!
What are you so worried about?
I have the law and the media
all in my hands.
Yang Jong-hoon, you lunatic.
How dare you shake Jin Hyeong-u
and get on my nerves?
Hey, that Kang Dan
or Erica Shin or whatever.
-Did you find her number?
-Yes, sir.
This is her number.
STAFF ONLY
Please head that way.
What's the prelim case?
CRIMINAL TRIAL
FEBRUARY 2021
CHARGED WITH DEFAMATION…
All right! A defamation case.
It's the only thing I'm good at.
This is freaking hard.
That's why I wanted to go
with a criminal case.
I want to be a prosecutor.
Why did I take up a civil case?
If we went with the criminal case,
we'd be against Joon-hwi.
Hey, so, what if we're against him?
I can win without you.
-Is that all you can say?
-Yes, it is.
Well, I'm scared of speaking
into microphones.
Why can't the main competition
be on paper like the prelims?
How will you stand in court
when you become a lawyer?
Overcome it with this.
Can we really do this in a week?
More time doesn't necessarily mean
a better performance,
but we need an award.
Then the president won't be as harsh.
You're right.
I put my faith in you, Ji-ho.
Anyway, why did Prof. Yang bring us here?
It's not a crime scene.
I have nothing else to say.
How were you bailed out?
The land value is high here,
so this café must have cost you a lot.
Something happened to a friend,
so he handed it over
at a very cheap price.
Was your friend a driver to Cho Tae-yeong?
Cho Tae-yeong,
the CEO of a toy company called I-bit.
I have to do something.
The day I came here…
you were at Lee Man-ho's place
with his anklet.
Where did Lee Man-ho go?
I have no idea, okay?
How the heck would I know
where he went and what he did?
Then how did you end up
giving me all these?
He was doing all kinds
of suspicious and weird stuff, so…
I already told the police
and the prosecution.
I'm grateful.
I was cleared of my false charge
thanks to you.
Then you shouldn't be here
obstructing my duty--
Your duty?
Don't people usually say
it's obstruction of business at a café?
What exactly is this duty
that we took you away from?
One more question.
The day we failed to see Ki Du-seong.
I don't know who it is.
BUKBU DETENTION CENTER
Oh, I know who it is.
Around 11 a.m. on December 15th,
who were you talking to?
December 15th at 11 a.m.
Check Choi Jae-cheol's call history.
INVESTIGATOR JUNG TAE-HUN
Did you find
Choi Jae-cheol's call history?
Send it to me.
DECEMBER 15TH, 2020,
11:00:13, SEOUL, 010-765-3395
3395.
AUNT
Darn it!
FIRELOL: THIS IS SLANDER!
FIRELOL: I MUST EXPOSE HIM
HOT PINK CHILI: HIS SON IS A VICTIM
HOT PINK CHILI: NO WAY, KANG SOL
People with these IDs
are very friendly only for Ko and his son.
They must be his avid followers.
These politicians have fans.
He could be the next president.
What if it's manipulated,
disguised as fans?
Organized fake comments?
Ye-bum, can you upload that video?
KO APOLOGIZES IN TEARS,
BUT WITH FAKE TEARS?
My client, Prof. Kim Eun-suk,
decided to take her hands off
of the legislation
of the dating abuse law
with Assemblyman Ko.
She found out
Assemblyman Ko faked his tears
on the video of his public apology.
Darn it. Get it into my eyes, will you?
Get it in there.
Hey, put in some more.
-That's way too much.
-Some more.
I'll put this up.
You need to get here.
-Put it on the floor.
-Yes.
-What's with your handwriting?
-Stay still.
That's way too long.
When my client found out
he shed crocodile tears,
she felt shocked in betrayal
and decided to take her hands off
of the entire legislation process.
This is what Prof. Kim wanted.
PARK GEUN-TAE
Ko Hyeong-su and his son
have put on a huge act together.
Look at these comments.
You're right. These do seem suspicious.
Hey, look at the comments.
This one.
Look at how these IDs swarm in
as if they'd been waiting.
It's suspicious.
BUT HE WORKED SO HARD
They all show support for Ko and his son
but are criticizing us.
They're manipulating these comments.
Prof. Kim wanted to confirm this.
But this phenomenon
can't be used as direct evidence
to prove that Ko Hyeong-su is behind this.
And I think Prof. Yang came here
to find a lead.
Right here?
If you won't pick up, hang up.
If you won't hang up, pick it up.
MISSED CALL
STAFF ONLY
RESTRICTED AREA
RECENT CALLS
CALLING
Don't provoke him.
Ko Hyeong-su isn't your fight.
What?
It's a piece of cake to destroy you.
Only you will get hurt.
So what? Did you--
What was that?
-Look at where you are.
-What?
It's staff only.
Can't you read?
It's not like I went in there.
What's in here?
Get away.
STAFF ONLY
FREE LAND
832-12 YEONSEO-RO, EUNPYEONG-GU, SEOUL
PARK JUNG-GIL
MOLESTS HIS ADOPTED DAUGHTER
These are the fake news and comments
that drove Ko Hyeong-su's opponent
to death three years ago.
The IDs here are the same as the ones
who made comments on these videos.
Support for Ko,
but criticism for the opponent.
FIRELOL
His specialty
was in manipulating fake news.
CAFÉ RITA COFFEE
FREE LAND, 832-12 YEONSEO-RO
Wow, there's a high chance
that this is their hideout.
CAFÉ RITA COFFEE: 832-12 YEONSEO-RO
That café was built on the free land
my uncle got from Ko Hyeong-su.
He sold the land
to Cho Tae-yeong's driver,
but Cho actually owns it.
Why didn't you stay in the police academy?
Hey, Attorney Park.
What did you say?
Attorney Song of Hyeongseol sued me?
HOT PINK CHILI: NO WAY, KANG SOL
HER MOM WAS AN ESCORT TOO, LOL
WHO'S YOUR MAMA, YE-SEUL?
LET'S SPREAD THIS VIDEO
I WANT TO SHARE THE TRUTH
SEO GI-YEOL'S WIFE KILLED HIM
AND HE SAYS HE STUDIES LAW?
Damn it, these evil jerks!
How can they go on a witch hunt
for everyone?
This is an act of terrorism.
This is considered murder, not defamation.
Stop reading those.
Forget about it.
We have no time to lose our mind
over some malicious comments.
We might end up dead first
before catching Ko.
The public is against us.
This is how he has maintained his power.
And my dad was one of his victims.
We must annihilate this manipulation.
Darn it!
We have to turn in our summary
of arguments in two days!
Close your ears for a second.
Darn it!
ERICA SHIN'S US LAW LECTURE
She's Kang Sol A's twin sister.
They look exactly alike,
but they're on two different levels.
A sexual scandal with Yangcrates?
I can't believe her.
Why would you come here?
Your sister will only lose her spirit.
ERICA SHIN'S US LAW LECTURE
She won't lose her spirit so easily.
BILL TO PREVENT DATING ABUSE
INTENTION OF THE PROPOSAL
Come on in.
Everyone.
Hello.
Is Kang Sol here?
Are you Erica Shin?
Where's my sister?
She went to the library
to find some materials.
JUSTICE MOCK TRIAL IN 5 DAYS!
I'm Han Joon-hwi.
Did you make the statement
on the constitutionality?
Yes, I did that.
I enjoyed it.
I enjoyed your take
on how it's unconstitutional.
So you're my sister's roommate.
I heard
you two are teammates for a mock trial.
Yes. Your sister wrote it. Take a look.
I'm Prof. Kim's attorney, Park Geun-tae.
You filed a suit against my client,
Prof. Kim,
for slandering you in court
during the Bad FaMa trial.
Right, have you been paying
your child support?
Sorry. I just get very curious.
Aren't you?
I'll let you sue me all you want.
You wanted to tell me that?
No.
I wanted to tell you
not to drop your suit.
Write a note that you won't drop it,
then we'll have it notarized.
You seem a bit worn out.
That figures.
You were framed for murder,
then you got involved
in a sex scandal with a student.
My gosh, Professor Yang.
I mean, I've gotten used to dealing
with absurd rumors like that.
Why did you want to see me?
It's not that I wanted to see you.
POWER OFF
It has been so long.
I wondered why you're Erica Shin
then found out you went to the U.S.,
to your birth father.
He's barely a father.
That married man had an affair with my mom
then emigrated before he found out
he got her pregnant.
But he still gave you a different life.
He's better than that scumbag stepdad.
Just cut to the chase
and tell me why the three of us are here.
Let me tell you that.
I asked for you, prosecutor…
I mean, professor,
I asked him to have you here.
You must have another phone.
I think someone's calling you.
Darn it.
I just need to check the CCTV.
Why can't I see it?
Well.
Hey, well.
If you won't let me see it,
I'll have to call the police.
It's a really important flash drive.
It's not that I don't want to.
It'll get more hectic with the police,
so just show us!
Gosh.
STAFF ONLY
What do we do now?
LOCKER ROOM
STAFF ONLY
Goodness.
FOR LEASE
Stop shaking my sister around.
Let her focus on her studies
and graduate law school.
I don't want her to be involved with you
only to become a nuisance
for Assemblyman Ko.
Please ask Sol
to delete the video yourself.
What if I say no?
Then I'll upload a video myself
that my accusation of Mr. Ko
was a misunderstanding and a mistake,
that the letter was all fake.
Now that she lives in a bigger world,
she finally got a grasp
on how the world works.
There was no violation
of the Election Act.
Why are you taking it this far?
She went to a juvenile hall because of me.
And that led to her involvement
in a scandal with you.
I can't let her get hurt because of me.
There's no reason for me to stay here.
Delete her photos from the juvenile hall.
Delete all malicious comments
on my sister as you promised.
And the sex scandal.
Bring everything back to its place.
ASSEMBLYMAN KO HYEONG-SU
Do it.
No way. We can't do that.
If we only delete her comments,
it'll be obvious.
Hey, do as you're told.
Do you want to end up like Lee?
Fine, I'll do as I'm told.
Okay, we've been told what to do.
So let's do it.
Okay.
DELETE, EDIT
DELETE
EXPOSING ASSEMBLYMAN KO
THERE'S EVIDENCE! IT GOT COVERED?
How amazing.
What are you all doing?
You're all under arrest
for manipulating online comments.
-Cuff them.
-Yes, sir.
-Hey, don't move.
-Freeze.
-Stop everything.
-Hands.
-Keep your hands there.
-What's going on?
-Freeze.
-Okay.
-Be gentle.
-Don't make a move.
I'll walk myself. Let go.
We should consider fake news
as a part of our free speech.
Kang Dan,
you became a success as Erica Shin
all thanks to me, right?
I hope Yang Jong-hoon remembers that.
I will remember that.
KO HYEONG-SU
ASSEMBLYMAN KO HYEONG-SU
-We'll begin our search and seizure.
-What is this?
All right, now.
I'm Park Geun-tae, an attorney.
Give me a call if this seems unfair.
Call me, okay? Goodness.
Here, take one.
You know me. I'm Park Geun-tae.
RECENT CALLS
Here you are.
Park Geun-tae, an attorney.
INCOMING CALL
-Hello?
-Detective Jang?
Kang Dan, you.
You'll have to pay for this!
Right.
Ms. Kang Dan's appendix burst,
so she never got on the plane.
What?
Subtitle translation by Eun Sook Youn
We're in the same boat, you know?
Are you telling me to destroy evidence?
Do you think I'll crumble down like this?
What?
These are all circumstantial evidence.
We need his confession.
There is a way.
Ko Hyeong-su doesn't trust anyone easily.
People like Ko may have allies,
but they have many enemies, too.
I'll represent you, as you wanted.
Are you sure though?
The law…
It'll punish Ko Hyeong-su
for what he did, right?
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs