Ms. Choi.
(Episode 15)
Yes, she just went in.
She heard the recording file.
And I told her everything.
Let's wait.
It will be hard
to make a decision right away.
Great work.
Should I get you some food
on my way back?
How about the macarons
I got you last time?
Forget it.
King-sized mandu.
Both meat and kimchi flavors.
You've reached Daebak Realty.
This is Hong Ji A.
Ms. Hong?
I'll testify.
But the secret ledger is somewhere else,
not here.
That ledger is the record
of all of Dohak's corruption.
That'll be...
more than enough evidence.
Ms. Choi.
Thank you for mustering up the courage.
He's that guy.
At 10:30 p.m. tonight, at Sky Building
in Haengun-dong, Seoul,
- Oh In Bum.
- A fire incident...
that is suspected to be
a gas explosion took place.
In Bum!
In Bum.
Mom!
What are you doing?
In Bum.
Are you okay?
What happened?
There was an explosion.
An explosion?
Scruffy.
He's one of Do Hak Sung's henchmen
who lied about wanting...
to sell the cold storage.
Right after Ms. Choi had entered
Sky Building,
I saw him leaving.
The police found this footage
of Sky Building before the explosion.
They're going to make a composite
based on the information we have...
and put out an APB by tonight.
Do Hak Sung is more terrifying
than ghosts.
How could he kill his secretary
of 20 years?
We must find him before the police do.
Last time, he headed toward
the intersection in Haengun-dong.
Okay. I'm sure we'll find a lead
once we look into the CCTV...
and his call records.
Give me a list of her real estate.
Include ones that are
under other people's names.
Why do you want to see that?
During my last call with her,
she agreed to testify
and mentioned a secret ledger.
But the secret ledger is somewhere else,
not here.
That ledger is the record
of all of Dohak's corruption.
That'll be...
more than enough evidence.
I'll look into it right away.
Will we be able to bring him down
with that secret ledger?
We must.
That scumbag is garbage.
How many innocent lives did he take...
just to murder Ms. Choi?
Didn't I tell you...
that you wouldn't be able
to catch me?
You just wait.
I'll make sure you get sacked
at all costs.
Go home safely, sir.
We'll meet again soon.
(Kind, Present, and Swift Police)
- Here he comes.
- Move aside.
- Is it true that you instigated...
the Yongnam Village fire
20 years ago?
Please tell us!
Please comment regarding
the death of your secretary!
- Please share a word or two!
- Is it true?
Please tell us your thoughts!
Please comment!
Do you admit to your offenses?
Sir, it's very difficult to reach you.
But then again,
I could still get out without your help.
Okay. Sure.
Have you reached Assemblyman Han?
Not yet, sir.
Those darn scumbags.
How dare they treat me
like a spent force?
What about the guy
who rigged Ms. Choi's house?
He'll be stowing away on a ship
early tomorrow morning.
I've located Scruffy.
(Daebak Realty)
He had turned on his phone
for a brief moment,
and it was around Haesung Port, Incheon.
(Daebak Realty)
I'll call the police for help.
Be careful, guys.
Even if we get him,
he won't tell us right away
that Do Hak Sung had ordered him.
When he had been detained last time,
he feigned ignorance
until he was let go.
This time, he'll spill.
Why are you so certain?
Because I won't hand him over
to the police.
Hello, sir.
Wait. Over there.
Scruffy was on that motorcycle.
So I heard you handled it nicely.
Well done.
You should leave Korea for a while.
Thank you.
No. This can't be.
A man is passed out here and bleeding.
Please hurry to the warehouse
at Haesung Port.
Stop it.
It's too late.
(Yoo Young Jae)
Get the necklace ready.
Now.
I'm inside.
She just left.
So she'll be there in ten minutes.
Take care of it.
Okay.
Ten minutes?
That will be more than enough time.
Let's see.
Oh, my.
You will burn anyway.
So why don't you come with me?
What's this?
Is that a key to a safe?
So I heard you handled it nicely.
Well done.
You should leave Korea for a while.
Thank you.
Thank you, sir!
Sir...
These days, people can get arrested
outside Korea.
- The key.
- What?
He left Secretary Choi's house
with a key.
Ms. Choi Sun Mi had a townhouse
under a borrowed name.
And there's a private safe
for the residents at the townhouse.
What's the name of the townhouse?
Happy Townhouse.
Okay. I got it.
Scruffy stole the key when he broke
into Secretary Choi's house.
You'll find a secret ledger there.
Did you find this out
from the spirit's memories again?
(Dohak Construction)
(Chairman Do Hak Sung)
Put an APB out on Do Hak Sung now.
Yes, sir.
Push ahead with the safety test
of Sky Building.
If you don't get it going
and things go south,
it will be the end for all of us.
What if people move back into
the building and there's a problem?
There was a fire and an explosion
in the building.
Buildings won't collapse that easily.
Gosh. That chairman. I mean,
Do Hak Sung caused all of this mess.
Please take care of it.
I'll help you if you need anything.
Okay.
Mr. Jung.
You...
Did you enjoy your meal?
What do you think you're doing?
How rude!
(Arrest Warrant)
I'm arresting you
on suspicion of taking bribes.
What are you doing?
- Let go of me!
- Let go!
- Hey.
- Mr. Jung. Hey!
How could you do this to me?
- Let go.
- Hey! You're unbelievable!
Let go of me!
Okay. Thank you for your help.
With the evidence he got
from Secretary Choi's storage,
he will be able to prove
he's guilty of embezzlement,
professional negligence, bribery,
and instigation to murder.
Even Do Hak Sung won't
be able to get away with this.
So what? He already got away.
There's an APB on him,
and he's on the No-Fly List.
He'll be apprehended soon.
In the end, Secretary Choi died...
to get back at Do Hak Sung.
That scumbag ought to be crushed.
He took away so many lives.
Even at this moment,
more injured people...
are dying at the hospital.
Is that why?
A strange rumor is going around online.
A strange rumor?
A lot of people are saying
they saw a ghost at Sky Building.
But what's odd is that
the ghost is faceless.
And when they see the ghost,
they will end up dying.
What is it?
Did I say something wrong?
(Jinsung University Hospital)
It can't be, right?
The doctor said it was
something like mass hysteria.
He'll be fine
once he's stable and gets treated.
We're all going to die.
It's going to kill all of us.
You'll be okay, honey. Calm down.
Goodness.
Gosh, that sound...
That's the sound
of a faceless ghost coming.
Spare me.
- Spare me.
- Honey.
Spare me.
All right, calm down.
- Someone help us, please.
- We need someone here!
That's the second person.
He also died after he said
he saw a faceless ghost.
What if something bad happens to us?
Tell me about it.
What's going on here?
I'm too frightened to stay here.
The faceless ghost...
he told us about...
is the egg ghost, right?
The same one
that possessed me 20 years ago.
Yes.
Like that time,
people who died in the fire at once
became the egg ghost.
That means Do Hak Sung...
made the egg ghost again
just like that time.
That egg ghost appeared
at the hospital and killed people?
The egg ghost is
at Sky Building right now.
People who died in the hospital were...
probably bewitched by it
back at the Sky Building.
Egg ghost.
Is there no way of doing
an exorcism ritual on that one?
There's only one way.
By stabbing someone
who's possessed...
with a nameless needle
and killing it.
Someone who's possessed
by the egg ghost?
Like a psychic?
Are you saying In Bum has to die?
An egg ghost can possess
an exorcist's body as well.
Does this mean
either one of you has to die?
You're kidding, right?
Let's not do this exorcism ritual.
If we let it go on,
it'll continue to kill more people.
It doesn't go around
killing people forever.
It vanishes once it kills
enough people to vent its spite.
How many people must die
before it loses its spite?
One hundred? Two hundred?
What if it's 1,000 people?
Can we sacrifice one person...
to save 1,000 people?
If I don't perform the exorcism,
more people will die.
To stop that disaster,
we must sacrifice the boy.
What are you talking about?
I don't care about that disaster.
You cannot kill In Bum!
An egg ghost is...
an evil spirit
that cannot be controlled by humans.
It's like a natural disaster.
How is this a natural disaster?
People who died a wrongful death
because of Do Hak Sung...
became that egg ghost.
And that egg ghost is
about to kill more people.
How can we turn a blind eye to this?
What if we don't?
Do you have a plan?
What now?
Will you sacrifice yourself?
No, he can't do that!
I'm saying I'll find a way.
That's enough, all of you.
In Bum.
Do whatever you want.
Go find a way
or help those unfortunate people.
Do whatever you like.
But I'm not taking part in this.
Don't ever bring up...
the word "egg ghost" when you're with me.
I've been...
looking into the possibility
of revoking...
the building completion certificate
for Sky Building.
The permit
shouldn't have been granted...
due to faulty construction
to begin with.
Do Hak Sung lobbied some people...
and completed the building
out of the ordinary.
Once I have the certification revoked,
it'll only last for a while,
but we'll be able to stop
any huge disasters.
(Daebak Realty)
Mi Jin.
Mom...
You can't do the ritual alone.
Ms. Hong is out too. What's with you?
Stop thinking.
Okay. We'll find a way.
Yes.
Let's go to sleep.
Okay.
- Goodnight.
- Night.
I'm not like you, Mom.
I can ignore this.
I can ignore it.
Hello, may I have a word with you?
Sure, go ahead.
You were on the scene of the fire
at Sky Building, right?
Yes.
I wanted to ask you something.
(List of deaths in the Sky Building fire)
I never even saw the fire
because of the thick smoke.
There were sprinklers,
but they never went off.
(Lee Jae Pil, 49, male, Unit 903,
suffocation, death on the scene)
(Death on the scene)
There were lots of smoke
due to the cheap interior material,
and the sprinklers didn't go off,
so the damage became greater.
I see.
(Choi Mi Hoon, 17, male, Unit 701,
suffocation, died in the ambulance)
It was a huge fire.
What's worse was that
the sprinklers didn't work either.
I think that's why they all asphyxiated.
(Daebak Realty)
Delivery.
Here's your food.
Gosh, you're so generous.
Thank you for the meal.
Where's In Bum?
He had plans, so he left.
Are you done already?
I don't have an appetite.
I'll be back later.
She didn't finish her food.
She's seriously ill, isn't she?
How may I help you?
You can't go in there right now.
Are you sure no one has entered
the building?
Yes. Until they finish
the safety inspection,
even the residents can't enter.
- Hello.
Didn't you just say that
no one was allowed in?
Sorry?
(Safety Inspection)
They're here to do the safety inspection.
If they can't enter,
who will do the inspection?
You could die
if you go in there right now.
- What?
- Who is she?
Beats me. Who are you?
Where are you from?
You look completely normal,
but you must be insane.
Move aside before I call the police!
Is this the police?
Why did you do that?
She's crazy.
Otherwise, why did she throw my keys?
Ms. Hong, say something, will you?
Sir.
Take a look at this.
("Fatal Accident at Sky Building")
Once again, people have died.
(Daebak Realty)
What? What do you want?
Why did you go there?
I was just passing by.
You were just passing by,
but then you caused a scene
and damaged their property?
Had you gone there on purpose,
it would've been horrendous.
You couldn't help...
but feel concerned, could you?
I knew it.
The Ms. Hong I know...
acts coldly toward others
but is actually warmhearted.
Give me the paper
you've been jotting down on.
You knew?
How could I not
when we live under the same roof?
It's a list of individuals
from Sky Building who have died.
In order to perform an exorcism,
we need to identify the unrested spirit.
That's where I began.
We should identify the unrested spirits...
if we want to do anything.
I've visited the police, hospital,
fire station,
and the bereaved families.
If an egg ghost is created
by several unrested spirits...
who have died at the same time
in the same place,
then those eight individuals
are the names.
Since there are eight of them,
maybe you should stab me eight times.
Or...
stab me once with eight needles?
Has it ever crossed your mind
that you could die?
Right.
Hold on. You're a skillful exorcist,
and I'm a special psychic.
What's there to worry about?
All right. Let's think this through.
Have you gone crazy?
How dare you come here?
Please help me this once, sir.
I refuse to go down like this.
If you help me,
I will get back on my feet.
Think about the hefty amount
of money I've given you!
You darn thug.
Are you threatening me?
Do you not get it?
You're done for.
You've ruined my appetite.
After leeching off of me,
how dare he call me a thug?
That darn scumbag.
How did it go?
The police have blocked
all your secret accounts.
Darn it.
How in the world did the police get...
the secret ledger Ms. Choi had?
Ms. Hong.
It was Ms. Hong from Daebak Realty.
And she was the last person
to speak with Ms. Choi.
What?
Hong Ji A, that wench.
Find out her whereabouts
and report back to me.
(Republic of Korea, Passport)
- What is this?
- It's your fake passport...
and stowaway ticket.
The ship will head for Vladivostok
tomorrow evening.
This is as far...
as I can help you, sir.
You scumbag.
Don't you know
how much I've paid you?
That's why...
I'm doing this much.
All right, then.
Goodbye.
Take this with you, you scumbag!
Hong Ji A...
They passed the safety inspection
of Sky Building?
What do you mean?
They were even debating whether
to cancel the construction or not,
so how did it pass?
It's not that easy to shut down
a construction.
Not only did Do Hak Sung bribe
his way into getting the approval,
but there's faulty construction too.
So why did it pass?
Did the higher-ups pressure you?
It's not like that.
Then what is it?
Sir.
We can't let people move
into that dangerous building.
The safety inspection was done
by a reliable company,
and no one's moving in just yet.
They will thoroughly reinforce
the construction...
before letting anyone move in,
so don't worry.
(Choi An Na, Died at the scene
Kim Sung Gu, Died at the scene)
(Lee Jae Pil, Died at the scene
Hwang Ho Sun, Died at the scene)
If an egg ghost is created
by several unrested spirits...
who have died at the same time
in the same place,
then those eight individuals
are the names.
(Choi Sun Mi)
(Daebak Realty)
Yes?
Why are you out here?
No.
So many people will die
once people start moving back in.
They won't move back
into the building right now.
It's only going to get delayed.
As long as the egg ghost is in there,
a disaster is bound to happen.
It hasn't happened yet.
But you know that it will.
What then?
Will you kill Oh In Bum?
Hong Ji A.
- Are you thinking of...
- No one will die.
How?
To dissipate an evil spirit like
an egg ghost, someone must die.
What if I seal it instead of killing it?
What are you talking about?
Oh In Bum got a list of the victims
who died from the incident.
Sealing them might work.
It's only your speculation.
Don't worry.
I'm sealing the spirit, not killing it.
So no one will die.
And if anything goes wrong,
I'll pull myself out right away.
Have I ever failed you?
I'm sure you know better than anyone
that I can't die...
before I send off my mother.
Seal it?
It's a curse that looks up
a very strong evil spirit.
It's only temporary
since it's not an exorcism.
Let's think about...
the perfect solution with some time.
Then, no one has to sacrifice their lives.
The exorcist will experience
a side effect.
That's why we don't usually seal spirits.
A side effect?
Wouldn't that put you in danger?
It's better than people dying.
When will we do it?
We should do it right away.
If we delay it even for a day,
there could be more victims.
(Daebak Realty)
Seal the spirit? What is this?
What's this earthen jar?
You guys don't have to risk
your lives, right?
Don't worry.
How could I not worry?
She's never done this before.
You're not sure if this will work or not.
I can hear you.
Be safe.
Okay.
I'll bring your boyfriend back
in one piece.
He's not my boyfriend.
Please bring him back in one piece.
(Daebak Realty)
Call me as soon as you're done.
If something goes wrong,
we'll leave right away.
For what? And you think you can help
once you get there?
Don't be rash.
The egg ghost might attack you.
Well, we're more like backup.
I'm just giving you moral support.
Okay, I understand. Bye.
Mi Jin.
(Daebak Realty)
You have to keep...
Ji A safe.
If anything goes wrong,
I'm going to stop.
Get out of the building right away.
Why are you saying stuff like that?
You're scaring me.
I knew it wouldn't be easy.
But...
I believe in you.
I know you will make it work.
Thank you for not giving up.
We're partners.
That's what partners do.
(Lee Jae Pil, Choi An Na)
(Kim Sung Gu)
(Gu Ji Young, Gu Ji Woong)
(Lee Jae Pil, Choi An Na)
(Jo Yong Jin, Hwang Ho Sun)
Get out, In Bum!
This is good. It's always good!
Your food is the best.
Just the food?
No.
Everything you do is perfect,
Ms. Hong Mi Jin.
Hey, Ji A.
Why are you standing there?
Come and eat breakfast.
Ji A, come and take a seat.
Come and sit already.
Mom.
Nice, fried eggs.
Is it good?
Mom.
I had a dream.
What was it about?
I was an exorcist in the dream.
An exorcist? What is that?
Someone who lets unrested spirits
leave this world.
You were a psychic.
A psychic?
What's that?
No idea, but it sounds like
a perfect job for you.
What an interesting dream.
It was sad.
You were an unrested spirit
in my dream.
You're still a little girl, aren't you?
It was just a dream.
Don't be sad. I'm right here.
I'm not sad anymore.
Hey, Ji A.
What's that necklace?
You're right.
I've never seen it before.
My necklace?
It'll get in your way as you eat.
You should take it off.
Take off your necklace.
- Yes, Ji A. Take it off.
- Yes.
Just take it off.
Take off that necklace.
I've been bewitched.
What?
This isn't real.
You aren't my mom.
In Bum.
You cannot leave this room.
Never.
If I don't perform the exorcism,
more people will die.
To stop that disaster,
we must sacrifice the boy.
This was it.
This was how she felt back then.
She couldn't let
this horrible disaster...
go out into the world.
Because she's an exorcist.
Stabbing a spirit...
without writing down its name
could cause physical damage.
Stabbing a possessed psychic's heart...
is the only way to exorcize them.
Once the psychic dies,
the egg ghost also vanishes.
Ms. Hong.
No!
No.
We did it.
I'm glad.
Secretary Ju.
We're done with the exorcism.
We did it.
(Secretary Ju Hwa Jeong)
I told you to look forward...
to the kind of interesting things
that will happen...
once you turn me into your enemy.