♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 34=
Back then,
I was the cold-hearted Lonely Star,
one of the 36 Heavenly Generals.
That day, I was ordered to hunt down
the Evil Spirit who sneaked into
the heavenly realm.
Who are you that dare to molest me?!
You darn lothario!
I was kind enough to help you
clean up the sludge.
How could you slander me?
You were kind?
It was you who knocked me out!
Sorry.
I only focused
on killing the Evil Spirit.
It was my mistake
to make you fall into the puddle.
I’m the most beautiful Blue Swallow
in the Heavenly Realm.
But you made me fall into a puddle!
Look…
Why am I clean?
Then…
You washed my whole body?
It’s my fault.
It’s what I should do. You’re welcome.
What do you mean?
Then…
You’ve touched me all over?
I’m not a flirtatious bird!
No. No.
I mean, I did touch…
No, no!
I mean I did wash you.
No…
Sorry, I didn’t think about this.
Sorry for my rudeness.
I’ll stand here still so you can
vent your anger at will.
You said you’d
stand still here.
Don’t move.
Don’t blame me for being rude
if you don’t stop.
This was the first time in 3,000 years
that I smiled.
It was because of Blue Swallow.
The Lonely Star had a lonely destiny,
but she made me feel that
my heart was not lonely.
She loved to travel in the three realms,
and loved to fight for justice
even though her power was not strong.
In case that she got into troubles,
I made Three-call Spell with her.
But one day…
It’s evil energy!
The Evil Spirit will cause trouble
in human world.
It’s the Ugly Evil Spirit!
He should be trapped in the Sky Net
of Luofeng Pavilion.
How did he get out?
I have to ask someone to take him back.
Lonely Star, Lonely Star…
Wait.
Now he must be guarding
the Terrace of Goddess Nuwa.
I can follow this ugly monster first
to see where his lair is.
Where are you going?
Don’t come close!
Or I will call someone here!
Lonely Star!
Lonely Star! Lonely Star!
Qing?
Lonely Star…
Lonely Star… Lonely Star!
Qing?
Qing! Qing!
Lonely Star,
I’m fine.
Don’t cry.
You look better when you smile.
But, don’t
forget me in the future.
I… Why am I back alive?
In my body…
It’s your Inner Star?
Are you stupid?
Why did you use it to save me?
I’m destined to be alone.
For the past thousand years,
I’ve never felt terrible for
being alone at all.
But just now,
I knew
I couldn’t bear to lose you.
But, you shouldn’t have used
your Inner Star.
I just need to rest for a few days.
You can keep it.
Next time if I don’t arrive in time,
it can protect you.
As long as we don’t be apart,
I’ll be fine.
You look good when you smile.
After we went back,
we thought everything would be fine.
Stone of Goddess Nuwa!
What’s wrong?
It’s gone!
Lonely Star,
are you on duty today?
Yes.
Lonely Star!
Because of your absence,
dragon demon Yuchi Longyan stole the
Stone of Goddess Nuwa!
Do you plead guilty?
Take the Lonely Star and the
Blue Swallow into custody together!
Why are you arresting her as well?
This is my dereliction of duty,
all the consequences are borne
by me alone.
This is the Emperor of Heaven’s order.
You want to disobey it?
I advise you to accept it.
Maybe the Emperor will show mercy
and you can be punished lightly.
That day, I let go of your hand.
But I never thought that
I’d never be able to hold it again.
Lonely Star, do you plead guilty?
It’s my dereliction of duty.
I’m willing to be punished.
According to the Heavenly Rules,
Lonely Star should be punished with
the Heavenly Thunders.
Blue Swallow, you seduced
the Heavenly General.
Do you plead guilty?
We’re just in love with each other.
Why are we guilty?
You’re still impenitent.
From now on,
you and Lonely Star can’t
get together again!
Lonely Star!
Emperor,
please!
Please spare Lonely Star!
He has suffered eight thunders
and is already at his last gasp.
The last one…
Lonely Star…
Please let me withstand it for him!
We have no relationship now.
You should go.
No.
No!
Qing!
Qing! Qing!
I…
am…
sorry…
How ignorant.
The Nine Heavenly Thunders
are not something that a lower-ranked
half-immortal like you can withstand.
How incorrigible.
Open the Evil Spirit Portal.
No!
I used my last power
to send her to the mortal world.
My memory was removed.
I was renamed Xue Qianxun,
and became the Lord of Luofeng Pavilion,
who sends souls
to go through tribulations
for a term of 3,000 years.
Blue Swallow fell into the mortal world,
and after a thousand years
of cultivation,
she became my Qingqing.
Emperor, the one who stole
the Stone of Goddess Nuwa is
this bold dragon demon.
Then, I wonder
why the Heavenly General was not there.
Emperor, we should find out if any
Heavenly General left the position.
That absent Heavenly General
turns out to be Xue Qianxun?
(Punishment of the Lonely Star)
The Lonely Star got his memory removed
and Blue Swallow reentered
the mortal world.
What a fate.
Deep love will be broken.
The Star against the Heaven
will be lonely.
Is Xue Qianxun
doomed to be lonely forever?
I was about to go to see you.
Do you remember
the Punishment of the Lonely Star
2,000 years ago?
You remember it now?
Qingqing passed out suddenly
and her power is weak.
This is also related to you.
I want to know
besides the punishment
of Heavenly Thunders,
and removal of my memory,
is there anything I don’t know?
(Chronology)
Why do you have this book?
Immortal of Fate gave it to me.
Why didn’t he give me that directly?
He doesn’t know how to tell you.
So he wants me to tell you.
(Punishment of the Lonely Star)
Deep love will be broken.
Fate can’t be decided by himself.
The Star against the Heaven
will be lonely with a cursed kiss.
Why is this page
complete in your hand?
You mean
you have read this book
but there was no this page?
Deep love will be broken.
That’s to say,
once Qingqing and I are deep in love,
her soul will be broken.
Once I kiss her,
that will get her cursed.
Maybe that’s the meaning.
I’ll ask you for one last time.
Why do you have this page?
Are you doubting me?
Yes.
I was the cause of this
incident that year.
So, you’re afraid to tell me
and hiding everything from me?
I just got to know that you were
the Lonely Star who was guarding
the Terrace of Goddess Nuwa then.
What else haven’t you told me?
Nothing.
Say it!
I have been waiting for you.
I was about to go to you.
But you come to me yourself.
That curse is really strong.
But, what a pity.
A thousand years ago,
you should have been a happy couple.
But the arrogant Yuchi Longyan
made you be far apart from each other.
Is there any way to break it?
I’m asking you!
Are you angry now?
Answer me!
If you hadn’t had the great joy
and great anger,
this ancient spell couldn’t
have been finished!
What ancient spell?
Because the poison you got
needs anger as its guiding drug.
What are you talking about?
At this last moment,
I’ll let you know it clearly.
Smell the fragrance.
This fragrance
is not the fragrance of Datura Flower.
I’ve replaced the Datura Weaver Ribbon
with the Sorrow of Hell Maid.
Alright.
Take it.
And, the tea you drink often
is not Three Pearl Leaf Tea.
It’s
Heavenly Break.
This is Three Pearl Leaf Tea
made by God Gou Mang
with leaves like pearls.
It has a miraculous effect on
meridian injuries.
Remember to let him drink it regularly.
Don’t tell anyone
you exchanged it with me.
Alright.
Let me give you some more jars
of Three Pearl Leaf Tea.
Why?
What are you going to do?
The Sorrow of Hell Maid and
the Heavenly Break.
If you take the two poisons of
heaven and hell every day,
your mind and body won’t be
under your own control.
To finish this ancient spell,
great joy and great anger
are needed as the guiding drugs.
The great joy is every time you think
about the Blue Swallow.
The great anger is you thought
Dragon King lied to you.
Say it!
The ancient spell is finished.
From today on,
you should obey my orders.
Yes.
Emperor, today I have compiled
the events of the immortal world
in the past year,
and found that someone has taken
away the Fire Protection Shield
and stolen the Rain Wand.
That’s an important matter.
Please decide the way to deal with it.
Who is it?
It’s the last dragon demon of
the Candle Dragon Clan,
Yuchi Longyan.
Immortal Ziyang, take that
dragon demon here to me.
Yes.
That dragon demon is cunning.
I suggest to let
Lord of Luofeng Pavilion
to go together to help.
Xue Qianxun, you go with him.
Yes.
Xue Qianxun,
what’s wrong with you?
Seven Deadly Spell?
You want his soul to be annihilated?
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪