♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 33=
It’s an ancient spell,
the Nightmare Spell.
One year in the dream is one day
in the real world.
In seven days, her soul
will be slowly absorbed by the one
who cast the spell.
We have to find the spell caster
within seven days
and kill him.
You can enter the dream world
through your spiritual awareness.
The caster presents the dream
as if it were real,
but there will inevitably be flaws.
You can find out
who the caster is from the flaws.
But…
But I can’t wake up
from the dream either.
You can only tell us who the caster is
and we go kill him.
What if
we fail to kill the caster
within seven days?
You’ll be trapped in her dream.
Your soul will fall into the nightmare.
Let’s do it.
It’s Liuying’s room.
The spell caster knows
the things of Qingyan’s past life?
This place looks so real.
He must have used hair
or skin of people familiar with
Xiahou’s Mansion
to make this.
What’s going on?
He is fake.
How dare you pretend to be me!
Come with me.
So lively here!
Kunlun Hall?
What kind of awful place is this?
I want you to carry me home.
Yuchi took me here before!
You’re the real one!
Darn it!
It was not a dream that day?
Star Halo!
This place
is where I came with Liuying.
What’s going on?
Yuchi! Look!
Star Halo!
It’s so amazing!
Yuchi,
I want to see fireflies. May I?
So many fireflies!
Yuchi.
Yuchi, thank you.
Let’s stay here
and don’t leave, alright?
Alright.
Let’s stay here.
Looks like
he is also reluctant to leave
this dream now.
Dragon King! You can’t stay there!
You have to find the spell caster!
Hurry up!
Qingqing,
the one who can
make Yuchi Longyan obsessed
must also know him well.
Why do I feel like
this dream is a trap
specially made for them both?
Yes.
Let me think about who
they both offended at the same time.
Who did they offend together?
Who can it be?
Yuchi,
let me take you to some good places.
It tastes good!
The Durian Cake tastes good?
Liuying and I actually
know that we don’t like durian.
But others don’t know.
The kitten was also
present at the time.
Cat demon Marble.
But, how does she know about
Xiahou’s Mansion?
We can have a good talk next time!
About the past 200 years ago.
200 years ago?
She must have got to know the story
of Xiahou’s Mansion from Qingqing.
Yuchi,
among all these places,
this place is my favorite.
Do you like it?
Of course.
But, we have been
to so many places today
and you must be tired.
How about we have a rest here?
We can go buy chestnuts
after you wake up,
alright?
Sure!
He is about to control his body.
Then,
now he can hear us?
He really heard us!
Did you find the caster?
I see.
These are two buns!
They can move?
Fairy! Right?
Two idiots.
Scratch?
Grab?
Paw!
Bear demon!
I see!
Water snake demon!
Immortal of Wine!
No! No!
Monkey demon!
Lick himself?
Ears.
Cat’s whiskers.
Catwalk.
Cat demon!
It’s really the cat demon!
This evil demon!
I even wanted to make good
friends with her!
How could she be so vicious?
But, where can we find her now?
Your hair.
Let me comb your hair.
I got it!
She combed my hair
just to get my hair and make the dream!
So insidious! What a bad demon!
My hair can be used to trace?
Every single hair of yours is mine.
You bad demon!
Liuying saved you. Qingyan let you go.
How could you bite her hand
that feeds you?
Bite her hand?
I’m not!
I just want to avenge my sister.
But, I never hurt Qingyan.
You never hurt her? But…
Why do you want her soul?
Soul?
The Nightmare Spell will only
make her sleep for days.
Looks like you don’t know it.
Who taught you that spell?
I…
Xue Qianxun!
What… What’s wrong with her?
Qianji Heart Thunder.
What’s that?
The person behind this is so cruel.
Her soul has been scattered.
We lost the clue again.
My head hurts.
It’s good that you’re awake.
Yuchi.
I had a really long dream.
That dream
was like reality.
It had Fallen-flower Valley,
Star Halo,
and those fireflies.
Qingyan.
You had been in a coma for six days.
Your master must be worrying about you.
Six days?
Oh, no!
No. No. No.
Master will scold me!
No hurry. I’ll send you back.
Yuchi, is there
really a Fallen-flower Valley?
Can we go find it together later?
If you want to go,
I can take you there at any time.
But now you have to
think about
how to explain to your master.
There will be a way.
Anyway, I’ll just do
what Master tells me to.
I have experience in it.
Alright.
I’ll stop here.
That’s so soon.
Go back and have a good rest now.
Then, Yuchi,
I’ll go now.
Yuchi.
♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if the moon shone for you♪
I made this spell myself.
Isn’t this beautiful?
You gave me the Dragon Pendant.
I give you a sky full of fireflies.
♪Withering in the sentimental world♪
Thank you.
♪In a flash I picked your teardrop♪
♪Does my heart ripple with memories♪
♪Only to remember you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
Yuchi,
see you.
Take good care of yourself
when I’m not by your side.
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
Qingyan.
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
Nothing.
Be careful on your way back.
Don’t worry.
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
I’ll tell you everything
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
on your birthday.
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
Although the cat demon is dead,
you can’t escape from the punishment
for leaving here without permission.
For the sake of your good attitude,
go to the Introspection Wall
to reflect on your mistake for 20 days.
Yes, Master.
Master, 20 days
are too long.
This time,
no one can intercede for her.
I’ll make sure she learns her lessons.
Qingyan,
don’t be sad.
20 days will be over soon.
Thank you, Qingfeng.
There is no barrier back
in the mountain.
I can call Qingqing there to
play with me.
This Golden Eagle Dagger
may hurt Qingqing.
What’s on your mind?
Qingfeng, there is no point
of taking this dagger with me
while reflecting on myself.
It’s so heavy and useless.
How about you keep it for me
and give it back to me
after I leave there?
Look at you. It’s just a dagger.
How heavy could it be?
Thank you. I gotta go now.
Dragon King.
Immortal, what’s the matter?
Xue Qianxun asked me about
his punishment for many times.
I searched through all the records
and found it.
(Chronology)
Qingqing and Xue Qianxun
are destined to meet
but they can’t be together.
Why?
Xue Qianxun’s punishment
is related to Blue Swallow’s punishment.
(Punishment of the Lonely Star)
(Punishment of the Blue Swallow)
Turns out that
Xue Qianxun is the Lonely Star
and Qingqing is the Blue Swallow.
It’s not proper
for me to tell this.
Xue Qianxun is your friend.
And it has something to do with you.
You’re the better one to tell him.
I have told you about this.
(Chronology)
It’s up to you whether to tell him.
You bold demon!
How dare you come to our place!
Xue Qianxun! Xue Qianxun!
Xue Qian…
Xue Qianxun.
Xue Qianxun, Xue Qianxun!
They want to kill me without any reason.
I didn’t do anything bad!
(Back Mountain)
Guys, this girl is my friend.
Could you please spare her life
for my sake?
What girl? She is just a demon!
You…!
You have an immortal aura,
and speak politely.
You should be a heavenly immortal.
Why are you protecting this demon?
She is a demon, but she’s cultivating
with her sincerity.
In time, she can become an immortal.
Don’t think that you are an immortal,
so you can do whatever you want!
Kunlun Sect is enforcing justice
for heaven
by eliminating demons!
If you interfere with this,
it’s also against the heavenly rules!
You…!
Did you see that?
People from Kunlun are always like this!
So unreasonable!
This demon sneaked into our place
with a suspicious manner.
If we don’t eliminate her now,
it will be too late when she causes
a trouble.
If I use my power in human world,
it will break the heavenly rules.
But I can still deal with you
without using my power.
Today, I must take her away.
Watch out!
No!
Qing!
So, this scar
was left by the Heavenly Thunder.
You also recalled it?
I just had those
flashes in my head.
Did we
know each other a thousand years ago?
Yes.
The Blue Swallow lured the Lonely Star
to leave his position.
Do you two plead guilty?
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪