Why are you hiding here alone and crying?
(Because you lost the game?)
(I was already very unhappy
to lose the game.)
(I'm even more upset to see
how harsh the comments are on)
(E-sports Industry Farm.)
(I want to grab everyone to tell him.)
(I really had no choice at that time.)
The next time will be better
if we are prepared.
(But I don't have a chance anymore.)
You know what those people are like.
Why do you still care so much?
Because I used to say
I can lead the team to win.
(This feeling is quite familiar.)
(No team can easily)
(win another team.)
(Before others seem to beat you easily,)
(who knows how much effort
has been done in private?)
(We're all humans.)
(How could there be one person)
(who's as strong as an alien?)
(So,)
(never underestimate your opponent.)
(Don't fight unprepared battles.)
Cheng,
I want to ask Tai to confront again.
You're not afraid of him anymore?
=Falling Into Your Smile=
=Episode 14=
I'll head to the restroom.
Weren't you just there?
Scared?
What are you talking about?
Tong Yao, don't feel stressed.
We all know how hard you've worked.
I should be the one who's feeling stressed.
It's okay Tong Yao, fight on!
I'll handle the pressure from the top.
She's obviously panicking,
and you're asking her not to stress out.
You guys really don't know
how to put yourself in other's shoes.
I'm not nervous.
Really.
My heart rate is completely normal.
You're not very good with stress management.
Yep,
you should learn from Lu Yue
when you get a chance.
Calm and steady like he's so experienced,
looking more like the defense turret
than the turret itself.
He knows how to rest assured,
let the teammates do the job,
just sit and wait for victory.
Avoid taking the lead as much as possible.
Come back.
The game is starting.
Where's my cursor?
My cursor is gone.
Where did it go?
Here.
You see it?
It shows up again.
Why are your hands so cold?
I just washed my hands with cold water.
If you lose, you lose. What's the big deal?
What are you nervous about?
You were so fierce
when being asked to battle with him
looking all hyped.
You're trying to comfort me?
Close your eyes.
Take a deep breath.
Relax.
It doesn't matter if you can't beat him,
I'll lead you to victory.
Did you hear that?
Cheng said,
"If you can't beat him,
I'll lead you to victory."
Sounds like something a normal man
would say to a beauty.
I have to say
I'm a little touched hearing this.
To hear him say something like this
in my lifetime,
my life is complete.
You guys are two-faced.
Why didn't you guys say he's not normal
when you held on to him
and begged him to help you win
during the monthly assessment?
Let's start.
Tong Yao, we're picking shikigami first
in this round.
Do you want to take Tamamo-no-Mae?
I'm still going to pick Higanbana.
Okay.
Let's go.
The line is about to enter the turret.
K just ganked for you
while you still backed off.
So you don't even dare to
get out of the turret if Tai is here?
Five minutes, 0-0-0,
and you're lagging behind 300 gold
than the opponent.
Are you offline, midsolo?
You are over the top today,
stop talking.
The Orochi is about to refresh.
The gold on both sides is about the same,
once it gets the Orochi,
the gap should be obvious.
K, go give them a vision.
Okay.
What are they doing ambushing here
and not going for the Orochi?
Who are they trying to scare?
Wait for me.
Tai's coming.
What's with the flash,
did you even see him yet?
You run faster than western reporters.
I will die if I don't run.
What are you talking about?
Come here,
after it's done with the Orochi,
look for a chance to attack.
It's okay if we can't win.
I'll revenge for your death.
Chubby.
(Successfully Sealed)
Is he my support or yours?
If you keep backing off,
(Demon Parade)
will Cat have to protect you as well?
(Double Kill)
(Demon Parade)
(Defeat)
You're really playing Lu Yue style
with Higanbana.
I'm on.
Why are you hiding?
The jungler already got on
and you're still hiding.
(Legendary)
(Destroyed)
Come back.
What are you afraid of? I'm here.
Chubby is dead.
Not in a good state, let's retreat first.
Cat's coming to support, don't panic.
Hide in the back and continue the attack.
Go go go.
If we win the team fight,
we can push it all the way.
No need to hide when you see Tamamo-no-Mae.
-Hold on, Cat.
-Cat, hold a bit longer.
(Defeat)
Tong Yao, come on and take it.
(Perfect Power)
No, no, I'm being controlled.
(Triple Kill)
(Ubume, Yuki Onna)
This can be done.
Tai has to go back and clean the line.
(Double Kill)
(Shuten Douji
Tamamo-no-Mae)
(Higanbana)
(Defeat)
I'll head back to the base
and wait for your resurrections.
Push it through.
One-on-one. Have a good show.
(Legendary)
Don't panic.
Even if you lose, it's okay.
Yeah, Tong Yao,
we can try again in the next battle.
(Before others seem to)
(beat you easily,)
(who knows how much effort
has been done in private?)
(We're all humans.)
(How could there be one person)
(who's as strong as an alien?)
(Never underestimate your opponent.)
Nice, Tong Yao!
(Victory)
Well played.
Seems easier than imagined,
right?
That's right.
Not as invincible as the legend has it.
It was never about you anyway.
Nice job.
Your recent training paid off.
I should thank everyone.
I won because of you guys.
You are too humble.
This is not reliance,
we're a team.
Hey, you.
You guys were never this kind to me!
You're so thick-skinned,
why do we need to be kind to you?
I'll have to work harder in the future,
and strive to kill him by solo
as soon as possible.
You are so proud.
But it's acceptable.
Today's training game
marks a milestone victory for Tong Yao.
So I propose
we should go have something nice today!
Great!
Good! Excellent idea!
- The club will pay for it. Let's go!
- Yes!
Who says the club will pay?
Works well!
Rui is paying.
If it is inevitable
for every professional player
to go through a darkest moment,
then,
from the moment I defeated Tai,
this experience
has become a part of my armor.
I'll always remember
the belief of a professional player.
This will never fade.
How about building a new belief
with the determination to win?
Come on.
Chubby, how about this pair of shoes?
So ugly.
Show me.
("Onmyoji: The Card Game"
Official release of full version CG)
(ZGDX post-game interview)
But she is strong
and has a very serious attitude.
As the captain, I'm delighted
to have such a teammate.
ZGDX will become more powerful than ever
with her joining our team
this summer.
(The Cowherd and The Girl Weaver?)
(That's the Cowherd and The Girl Weaver.)
(Cheng's smile is obvious.)
(He said they don't know each other well.)
(Cheng, give me some compliments as well!)
(That's the Cheng I love.)
Poof, boring.
(I will always support you!)
(Cheng is such a wonderful man.)
ZGDX will become more powerful than ever.
He's really smiling.
Rui, Rui.
What?
You need to go to the toilet?
Can't hold it anymore?
- Excuse me.
-No, no.
Look at this, Rui.
What? Are people bashing you online again?
(But she is strong)
(and has a very serious attitude.)
(As the captain,
I am delighted to have such a teammate)
(joining in.)
Give it back to me.
Isn't this an old interview?
This was happened from long ago.
You guys are too noisy.
Rui and I were just watching a video.
You were complimenting me.
What's wrong with that?
The staff wrote the interview outline,
I just read the script.
Ask Rui if you don't believe me.
Is that true, Rui?
No.
The piece of paper
had only the interview questions on it.
Who'd dare to teach Lu Sicheng
how to answer the reporters' questions?
Give me my phone.
No.
Give it to me.
Nope. No.
Nope.
What are you doing?
Cheating for you.
What?
What's going on?
Yeah, what's going on?
Delete it.
Got to have long hands
to play the hero
who saves a damsel in distress.
Caring for small animals is a virtue.
Who's the small animal?
Lu Yue,
who are you sending the photo to?
Is it posted online?
How can it be?
I'm not that low.
You are lower than you think.
(Ms. Wang)
This is the same girl
who got complimented by Cheng
in the interview.
This should be turned over.
God, is my food ready yet?
I'm so hungry.
Me, too!
Stop rushing!
All you know is eating every day.
I'll bring it over.
Okay, go.
I said I'd do it. You're so slow.
Thank you.
Is it good?
(Mrs. Lu)
Told you not to mess around.
Our sister-in-law is calling.
What sister-in-law?
Oh, this.
You pick it up.
You just want to see
a war break out, horrible kid.
Give me some, too.
Cheng, the phone was ringing
for a long time.
Who was it?
Looks like your girlfriend.
Mrs. Lu.
I saw it by accident.
Shut up.
Not that, Mrs. Lu.
Hello.
What are you doing?
I called you so many times
and you didn't pick up.
What important thing that kept you so busy?
Speak slowly. What's the hurry?
You're not even speaking clearly.
Also, aren't you in a meeting?
Why did you sneak out?
If you keep messing around like this,
your company's going to go bankrupt.
Intimate tone.
Sounds like a complaint but not really.
Sounds like he's indulging her.
So it is his girlfriend.
She is my teammate, why did I compliment her?
She played well in the game,
so I complimented her, what's the matter?
I'm going to the bathroom.
You guys can eat first.
Cheng.
What?
Although I don't know
who's going to be lucky enough
to become your Mrs. Lu,
but I'm already
feeling envious of her.
Because she will be well protected by you,
invulnerable and undefeatable.
Cheng,
do you have a girlfriend already?
What's wrong with you?
Looking all upset, are you jealous?
Don't be crazy, girl.
He is out of your league.
All right.
It'll definitely look good.
What?
You're coming to Shenzhen?
What are you going to do in Shenzhen?
My national league has started.
I don't have time to mess around with you.
Mess around? Didn't Lu Yue tell you?
When did Lu Yue tell me?
If you want to see him
and wants him to go back,
call him yourself.
Don't always try to scare me
by telling me
you're going to run away from home.
Is everything alright?
My mom.
Okay, I got it.
Let me do it. What do you guys want?
Do you know how?
Of course.
Okay then, let her do it. Let's go.
All yours.
It's good.
Looking so upbeat, did you win the lottery?
- Go go go.
- Let's go.
You want some?
- Is it done?
- Want some?
Here.
Thank you.
Why aren't you eating?
I'll get fat if I eat too much.
It's so good.
(Mrs. Lu)
Lu Yue,
you seem to have stirred up a hornet's nest.
If this affects Cheng's performance,
you're going to pay with your salary.
You will never understand
the feeling of a mother
who has a handsome son
that's of marriage age,
but doesn't even have a girlfriend.
But if she suddenly
sees hope one day,
then that hope ceases quickly,
that'll be a big problem.
(Ms. Wang)
Hello.
Cheng, it's for you.
Blind date?
What blind date?
Don't you think
you are a little crazy to say this?
I will have a game next week.
I have training games every day.
How do I have time for a blind date?
I don't care if she's good looking.
A fair lady?
How do you define a fair lady?
Someone who's not going to disturb me
when I play training games,
and when I'm in competitions,
who won't say stupid things on the Internet,
who won't ask to see me on every holiday,
and who's so quiet that
she doesn't seem to exist?
If that's what the fair lady is like,
I'm okay with that.
Cheng.
Fair lady,
I like that.
You haven't gotten your games straighten out,
stop that fantasy.
So what?
That's not very nice.
Even electronic pets will vibrate
when they are hungry.
Yeah, I'm a male chauvinist.
Isn't that good?
You won't have to worry about
my sexuality anymore.
A male chauvinist who doesn't like women
is even more terrifying.
Why do you…
Why don't you just admit that
you've got something going on
with the shorty?
It's not like she'd know.
It's okay.
I'll take care of
Ms. Wang.
Hello, mom.
It's me.
Mom, don't mess around.
For someone so high-class like my brother,
a bunch of girls
will fall for him in an instant.
You won't need to arrange
a blind date for him.
This is a very important year for our team,
we're really busy.
This is the year that determines
whether we'll get the championship.
You're right.
It's time for my brother
to go on a blind date.
I'll help you persuade him.
Mom says if I dare to say another word,
she'll arrange a blind date
for me too.
I'm only 23 years old,
so I won't sacrifice my youth
for our grand brotherly love.
Happy blind date.
I heard she's a pretty girl.
She's the same age as you,
and her name is Su Luo.
She just came back
from her studies in Britain.
Her family
is also in a business relationship
with our family.
I'm sure it'll be
a match made in heaven.
Cheng, don't look at me like this.
It's not my first time
having betrayed you, right?
Cheng, don't be mad.
Hi, mom.
Here.
Just eat this, and he'll cool down.
So,
is your brother really going on a blind date?
Probably just a formality.
If that's something Ms. Wang has decided on,
then no one can persuade her.
But if the girl
is truly a sensible and pretty fair lady,
isn't it at least better for him
to go on a date
than acting like a robot all day?
Maybe
he'll become a kinder person.
You hung the phone faster than anyone
when you were asked to go on a blind date.
I am different.
I have Onmyoji Arena.
Oitsukigami is my girlfriend.
Girlfriend?
Can't even play Oitsukigami's skills well.
Jerk.
Take some notes with that free time
instead of bickering.
The next game is not easy.
LAN is one of the old
and traditional noble teams.
Even though they haven't been
very good in recent years,
they haven't yet fallen into
the relegation match,
and they're still hovering in the mid
to upper reaches of the league.
FNC is trickier.
Theoretically,
it's the only team
that can challenge us in this set.
We can't underestimate them.
You guys should be clear on that.
I remember.
Cat was quite miserable
ganked by them in the last training match.
We had to rely on Tong Yao of
middle lane to get back on track,
drag it to middle and late stages
with a strong duo ADC,
and had Cheng take over the game
to win.
So we have to be prepared.
Hear that?
Do your homework.
Mom,
can you stop introducing girls to me
without my consent?
I really don't have time now.
I don't have to
introduce FNC any more, right?
We've all had a few games with them.
I believe we have a sense of
what they're capable of.
- Nice.
- Come on.
If they are assigned to the red side,
Kun will definitely go for Dharma
on the bottom lane.
If Dharma
sees the jungler's movement
on the other side,
he'll find a chance to ambush
or invade the jungle.
He'll have a high success rate.
Look,
(Parasite)
Here.
(Xiaolingkun)
Here
(Red Imp)
and here.
We've all been ambushed by them.
On the contrary,
if we don't allow him
to take Dharma in the beginning,
and we occupy the vision of
the river course on the other side,
then he will lose his tempo.
See?
In the match against CK,
the jungle almost got destroyed by Yang
because he lost our tempo in the beginning.
That's right.
Ming,
those mixed nuts are working on you.
Big moves come continuously.
Come on, have one more.
Why do I feel like the team took in
another data analyst all of a sudden?
I like that.
Not like we have to
pay another person's salary.
If you guys can learn from Tong Yao,
I'd thank the Lord.
Laziness is something
that can be cultivated slowly.
No rush.
Nonsense.
It's good, satisfying.
Look,
when Lu Yue first came,
he was also hardworking.
But see,
now he's just another dummy who
plays with someone else's account
and lose points.
Damn you Chubby, shut up.
Okay.
Got it.
See you there.
Lu Yue, where's my car key?
I don't know.
Tong Yao,
pay attention to this, too.
Are you going out?
Yeah.
My mom asked that girl out
and only told me
after the girl left the house.
Which girl?
Blind date?
What blind date?
You are running about bare footed again.
Next time you have your period,
no one will have sympathy for you
even if you have to crawl due to the cramp.
Put them on.
Tong Yao.
Come take a look at this habit of Kun's.
Coming.
Also, pay more attention to this.
Miss Su.
Hello, I'm Su Luo.
Lu Sicheng.
Someone entrusted me to take you home.
You're not going to have a cup of coffee?
No, I've got something else to do later.
Okay.
Give me a few minutes.
I need to use the restroom.
Please.
(Mother)
Hello dear.
How is it today?
Is the blind date going well?
Mom,
those matchmakers you found
didn't take their jobs seriously.
You don't like him?
We've all seen his photos before.
No.
He looks better
in person.
But I didn't have any hopes,
so I wasn't prepared.
My daughter is beautiful
just the way you are.
What else do you need to prepare?
Anyway, I'm very satisfied
with this one.
Okay, he's waiting for me outside.
I'll talk to you later.
Let's talk about it at home. Bye.
Okay.
(Lu Sicheng)
(Rabbit Tightly Holds the Carrot)
On the blind date?
(Sent to Rabbit Tightly Holds the Carrot)
Just met.
Is she pretty?
I didn't look closely.
Where are you?
The coffee shop
on the first floor of Star Building.
You went so far for the blind date.
But I know that place.
Go out and walk 300 meters to the right,
there is the best shop of Takoyaki.
Add some seaweed and bonito flakes,
you'll capture
the heart of any girl in an instant.
What else do you know besides eating?
You're not being appreciative.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Fifteen minutes, you have bad digestion?
You guys don't know a thing.
I went to freshen up,
not to the toilet.
Excuse me.
Hello there.
Check, please.
Here you go, please.
Okay.
Let's go.
I heard you are
a professional e-sports player.
Yes.
Quite different from what I expected.
I thought that e-sports players
are internet addicts.
I've never thought someone like you
will be a part of them.
What about me?
I have a pretty good feeling about you now.
What do you think?
I have a good feeling about e-sports as well.
Is this your first blind date?
Is it not for you?
Where are we going now?
Do you want to have that?
(Takoyaki)
I'm not used to eating those kinds of stuff.
Looks very greasy
and... not very hygienic...
Hello, a large one, please.
More bonito flakes and more seaweed, to-go.
OK, one minute.
So cute.
So handsome.
You're a fan of this?
Buying it for my pet.
You have a pet?
Is it a dog?
Pretty nice food for it, then.
A rabbit.
Rabbit?
Can rabbits eat such greasy things?
She's a trash can
and she can take in everything.
Thank you.
How can you say this about your rabbit?
It is raining all of a sudden.
The weather forecast didn't even tell us.
Wait for me here.
I'm going to take my car.
So jealous.
So hot.
I want a car like this
on a rainy day as well.
Not the same for me.
I want the man in that car.
In your dreams.
Look at his girlfriend and look at you.
So unfortunate.
Didn't even get to sit down
and have a good chat with you
due to the heavy rain.
Are you free this weekend? We can…
I have a game to play this weekend.
I'll go and watch your game then,
I've never seen
an e-sports game before either.
As your friend,
can I go to the backstage?
Miss Su,
you're pretty good.
You are, too.
But I don't think
we're right for each other.
Look, the rain came so suddenly.
It's God's arrangement.
How about this?
Tell me where you live,
and I'll give you a ride back.
Okay.
Tong Yao.
You've seen this video
three times already, right?
I'm just looking at the details.
I wonder if Cheng brought
an umbrella with him
since it's raining heavily.
My brother's still out.
It must be a pretty smooth blind date.
We will have a sister-in-law soon.
What are you going to do?
Want to go for a double-queue?
I'm tired and going to lie down.
What's wrong with her?
Take a guess.
♪Whose reasoning and expectations♪
♪Don't seem to be my inner monologue♪
♪To be myself or to run away♪
♪Should I just sway with the wind?♪
♪You're the one
who came through the sea of stars♪
♪Those corners open unexpectedly♪
♪It seems someone will really understand♪
♪My helplessness♪
♪The loneliness that
comes with the gradual leave♪
♪I'm beginning to believe♪
♪The existence of a tacit understanding♪
♪That fate can be changed♪
♪Because persistence♪
♪Has never been pale♪
♪The successes and failures
we have gone through♪
♪The crowd of people cheering tomorrow♪
♪Your look fuels my passion♪
♪Welcome the sunshine♪
♪Let's welcome the sunshine♪
♪Do you still remember♪
♪That I watched the shooting stars
pass by with you♪
♪How many times I seem to have heard♪
♪The wish I made that night♪
♪We all made a promise♪
♪Youth is about no regrets♪
♪If I have a dream in my heart♪
♪I'll follow the light♪
♪The moment we ignite with passion♪
♪Will light up the night♪
♪How foolish the stubbornness
that no one understands♪
♪How strong the desire to return to glory♪
♪Remember that moment at the top♪
♪Let's welcome the sunshine together♪