Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ No longer panicking on the night of the blackout ♫
♫ You're by my side, illuminating a beam of light for me ♫
♫ Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet ♫
♫ Your breath brushes up against my cheek ♫
♫ With you warming up the stage,
happiness never comes to a close ♫
♫ Boring jokes add some sweetness to the dinner ♫
♫ Daily life is even more like a comic than comics themselves ♫
♫ Happiness and sadness ♫
♫ Make up the moments of life ♫
♫ Rainy days become very special because of you ♫
♫ Picked up a pitiful youngster off the street ♫
♫ No matter when and where, you always appear ♫
♫ Holding me tightly and spinning in circles ♫
♫ Rainy days make me so nostalgic because of you ♫
♫ Becoming some part of the memories ♫
♫ Walking down a street with lights lighting up
one after another ♫
♫ Warming up the whole world ♫
[Please Feel at Ease Mr. Ling]
[Episode 9]
I've prepared a gift for you. It represents my kind regards.
President Ling, giving a good review doesn't mean that we can be good friends.
You understand that, right?
I'm just giving you a gift to express my apologies.
If you don't want it then throw it out.
Sorry, it wasn't on—
My heart is going to burst.
I'm going to puke. You're disgusting.
Let go of her.
Brother.
Does it hurt here? Is it here?
- Wait, wait.
- Does it still hurt?
Wait, wait, wait, wait-
No, it doesn't hurt.
Then I'll be leaving.
What?
Why are you so close to my big brother?
How am I close to him?
You even stroked his chest in front of my eyes.
Stroked his chest? I only touched it.
Why do I sound like a pervert from your mouth?
You haven't even stroked—
In short, don't have contact with him. Otherwise he will stick to you like a fly.
Didn't you say you liked flies?
When did I—
He's your big brother.
How can you say that about your own brother?
If he's a fly then you're a little fly.
Why are you always speaking for him?
- Do you care for him?
- I'm not speaking for him.
I'm just saying the truth.
- Don't bring him up again.
- You were the one who brought him up.
Are you jealous?
- No.
- That's good then.
If you're not then we're just talking. Right?
I think Ling Fang isn't that bad as a person.
But, he's pretty cute.
If there's nothing else then I'll head back.
You can't.
Can't you move in with me?
Why would a man and woman live alone together?
- Is Gu Ansheng not a man?
- He's my brother.
You and I just have a creditor and debtee relationship.
You're my creditor. Plus, I already owe you a lot of money.
I don't want to owe you even more.
- You're allowed to not pay it back.
- No, I have to.
I can't always owe you.
- But isn't having a fate that lasts a lifetime a good thing?
- That's not necessary.
I'm leaving.
President Ling, how much was the car fare? I'll transfer it to you.
Talking about money hurts relationships.
Talking about relationships also hurts money. I only carpooled with you.
I still have to pay.
Cheesy.
Brother Yue.
Miss Gu.
I didn't think you would be here too.
I have saw their advertisement and saw that the design was good so I came to take a look.
You probably understand lipsticks well.
Since your girlfriend likes to use it.
Girlfriend?
My sister Gu Anxin.
-Last time at the party-
-She's not my girlfriend.
Really?
I am still pursuing her. She hasn't agreeded yet.
Oh, then you should work a bit harder.
It sure is hard.
What kind of gifts do girls like?
To me as long as it's from someone that I like,
I would like it no matter what.
But, girl's
usually like a special perfume.
Ai Li, what kind of perfume do you use?
Gu Long Perfume.
Can't really use that as reference.
Apologizes.
Anxin is cheerful.
A heavier perfume scent probably doesn't suit her.
She is more suited with a sweet fruit scent.
Miss Gu seems to know perfumes well.
It's nothing, I just know Anxin well.
Especially since she's my sister.
Do you need any suggestions?
-Please do.
-No worries.
[Chocolate Box]
This is our work area.
Don't be too nervous about meeting your coworkers.
Hi, Chief Inspector.
Anxin, from today on you are a formal editor of Zhao Shi Culture.
I'm your group leader.
-Manager Zhao.
-No need to be so polite.
Here we are. If you need anything come and find me.
If you want to get food then don't look for me.
-I have a lot to do everyday and am quite busy after all.
-Ok, Manager Zhao.
You can look for Xiao Zhang or Xiao Wang too. It's all the same.
-Then I'm going to go back to work.
-Okay.
Here is your seat.
Hi! You're Anxin?
I'm little fox, Mu Mu!
Your more cute than me.
Hello! I'm He Shuhuan.
This is a new comedy routine?
Hello! I'm Lu Yiping.
Anxin, you are so funny.
-Isn't she, Huan Huan?
-You're right.
But you aren't laughing.
I've laughed haven't I?
W-What are you guys laughing about?
Her He Shuhuan's He, Shu Qi's Shu and Zhen Huan's Huan.*(The characters of her name are taken from well-known drama character's names)
It's not from Romance in the Rain.*(Famous chinese drama)
I'm so sorry. I thought-
-I'm sorry.
-It's alright!
She's just like that. Even though she doesn't look it,
she's actually super happy inside.
After all, our studio
is missing young, beautiful women.
How? Everyone's young and beautiful!
In the future, everyone will be working together.
If you don't understand something, feel free to ask!
-I'll take care of you!
-Ok!
Thank you！
Didn't the internet say it's impossible to get in line? Why is there no one here?
Let me tell you. All the stuff on the net are fake.
Not necessarily. What if it's because it's not lunch time yet?
Who knows? We're celebrating Anxin's start at a new company today!
Thank you.
Hey what-what is this?
Scared me!
Thank you...
Brother, we didn't order hotpot and this stuff right?
We didn't...
I'm sorry. We didn't order red wine and...these
These are all gifts from our store's VIP, Mr.Ling.
-Mr.Ling?
-It couldn't be Xiao Ba?
He wouldn't do something so exaggerated, right?
I've reserved this entire place!
I'm the one who ordered the meat and wine. If it's not enough, there's more!
Call for anything you want to eat. Order anything and don't hold back.
How is it?
Are you moved?
Afraid to move.
Then I'll move more.
I'm sorry. I have to drive in a bit, and my sister doesn't drink.
We accept your kindness.
That's unfortunate. It's Lafite from '82.
Who's this Mr.Ling? He does some cheesy things, but looks quite good.
It's the cheesy rich man I told you about before.
He looks quite good. What a waste of his good looks.
-He looks good?
-It's alright.
I can hear your little whispers.
So what if you hear?
This meal
isn't tasty all of a sudden.
Big brother, this air conditioner's leaking water.
It's just because you're my little brother.
I go easy on you.
Let's all eat first.
Eat!
What horrible pot is this? It burns the meat.
Can it be anything other than burnt the way you're doing it?
You do it then!
Who knew you actually know how to do things.
Because I have a good teacher.
This is called...the disciple is better than the master.
Did you get burned?
I told you to be careful! Where?
I'm alright.
Brother, I'll go buy some medicine. I'll be back soon.
Wait here.
Anxin, let's go together.
How disgusting.
What are you doing? Aren't we going to buy medicine?
Ling Yue, I'm talking to you. Hey-hey!
Those annoying people aren't here anymore.
I can finally do what I want boldly.
Do? D-Do what?
Help me apply medication.
If you had medicine in your car, you should've said so earlier. What a waste of time.
Then if I told you earlier, would you have come down with me?
So you did it on purpose?
Isn't that because of you? Always pushing me away.
If you're putting it like that, then it's my fault.
No. It's my fault.
Anxin, forgive me.
No matter what happens, I won't leave you again.
I can forgive you.
However...
I promise you my everything.
I-I wasn't talking about that.
What do you want to say?
I was saying...
Have you forgiven me?
Alright, I give up! You're too good, alright?
Then come with me tomorrow to meet my family.
Meet your parents?
This fast?
I-I haven't agreed to be your girlfriend.
-Then aren't you right now?
-I'm not!
I just agreed to forgive you, but I didn't agree to be your girlfriend.
Then if you aren't willing, then forget it!
What do you mean forget it? You're regretting it already?
Then you're truly my girlfriend.
It's not too much to eat a meal together, right?
It's fine.
Then where are we going?
We're switching places to eat barbeque.
Then I have to tell my brother and You You.
Send a message.
Why hasn't Anxin come back? Taking so long just to buy medicine.
Alright!
You two continue eating. I don't think those two will be coming back.
You're leaving?
I still have business and will be leaving. Hey!
The meat's burnt. Hurry up you two.
It's fine though?
Brother, I'll be leaving first. You have to send You You back home safely.
Come home early.
My beloved concubine, I will be leaving first.
Make sure to take advantage of your alone time with my brother!
Understood! I will try my best to give you a nephew soon.
Ansheng, try this.
-It's delicious.
-Thank you.
Don't drink red wine. If you're eating barbeque, you have to drink spirit.
We aren't leaving sober. Waiter! Give us a bottle of spirit!
Toast?
You You?
Are you...ok?
I'm alright...
Why...am I a little dizzy?
Can you...send me back in a bit?
Ok...
You You.
Here, I'll go drive the car over.
Wait for me here. Are you ok by yourself?
Don't worry. Go drive the car.
I'll wait for you here...
Ok, I'll be quick.
Why did you push me?
Are you trying to take advantage of me?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I didn't do it on purpose.
I think you did it on purpose.
Elder sister, who would take advantage of you?
Elder sister?
Who are you calling elder sister?
Are you blind?
-You're the elder sister! You're whole family's an elder sister!
-I didn't mean it like that-
I'm sorry! I didn't-
Wait, don't hit me!
-How could you call me elder sister?
-Don't hit me!
-What's wrong? What's wrong?
-Ansheng...
He bullied me.
-Who's bullying who here?
-You're bullying me!
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. My friend drank too much.
Uh...should I take you to the hospital?
-No need!
-No need. No need.
Hurry and take her back. Stop making trouble outside!
-I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
-Don't let me see you again!
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
You You.
Let's go home, alright? I'll send you back.
I'm tired. I want to rest for awhile.
I'll take you to the car.
Why don't you have battery?
Don't be in a hurry. I'll charge you up, alright?
You You, there's no where to charge your phone here. We can in my car.
Let's go to my car.
There is. How is there not?
Don't worry. It doesn't matter where we charge it.
See.
You You.
It's about to rain. Let me take you back to the car.
Alright?
You keep trying to make me go to your car.
Do you want to do some embarrassing things to me?
No, no. You've misunderstood. I don't mean it like that.
It's alright.
I-I've always wanted to give birth to
little monkeys for you.
Perfume?
Wow, who knew you were into perfume?
Does that give me some points?
Keep trying!
Oh, right. I'm downstairs. We can leave now.
Alright, I'll be down after changing.
Wait. Something's missing.
Don't worry. I'm here.
Is that a family portrait? Which one of them is you?
I really don't know you well enough. You like him instead of me.
Why is there a fly in your house?
Why are you here?
You two are really...
Mom.
- This is Anxin.
- You're Anxin?
Come sit down.
Sorry, Auntie. There was some traffic on the way here.
It's fine. It's good that you're here.
Brother, the two of you planned to come together?
Future sister in law, I've finally met you.
Hello.
You guys are finally here.
-Hello Auntie.
-Hello.
She played the piano well today.
When Anxin was in college, she was a lot better than me at playing piano.
-Anxin also graduated from Yale University right?
-Auntie, you might not know
Before I studied overseas, I studied my undergraduate degree at Seijoh University.
Anxin was my classmate in my undergraduate course.
That's not right.
If I remember correctly, Anxin didn't graduate from university.
Brother.
Brother Ling Fang, you can't say it like that.
-Anxin is actually—
It's true that I'm not university graduate.
However, President Ling Fang.
At least I know how to respect people. Unlike you
who graduated from college and still didn't learn how to. It's a pity.
Anxin, Brother Ling Fang didn't have any bad intentions.
-There's no need to be so nitpicky.
-That's right.
If you want the listener to think that way, the speaker must have the right intentions.
Right?
Mom.
Mom. Just listen.
I knew it. Anxin has such a bad temper, I don't know if Brother will be able to handle it.
-Alright, alright, don't say too much.
-Coincidently
I like her bad temper.
Listen to that.
What are you all talking about?
You guys are having a good time talking.
-Dad.
-Hello, Uncle.
Dad.
Hello, Uncle.
Hello, Anxin.
You look exactly like your mom.
Sit.
Uncle.
It's our first time meeting, so I brought you a small gift.
You are such a thoughtful child.
- What is it?
- Open it and take a look.
A brush.
How valuable.
Uncle. This was my mom's favorite calligraphy brush.
I brought it to gift it to you for remembrance.
Thank you.
Speaking of gifts, I also prepared a small gift for Uncle.
Xin'er is so thoughtful.
Miss Gu always impresses.
I accidentally stumbled upon this piece of artwork from the Baroque period.
Since Uncle likes it, I'm glad it found it's owner.
Anxin, is there something you want to say?
This painting is not from the Baroque period.
But from the Late Renaissance period.
It's also known as the Mannerism period.
Like it's name, it likes the form it takes.
This painting is exciting and strange.
It's also hard to understand what it expresses.
These are all aspects expressed during the Mannerism period.
What you said is true. As expected from the daughter of Xiao Wan.
Alright, put this painting up in the bathroom upstairs.
Aren't you deliberately embarrassing her?
It was intentional.
You sure do hold grudges.
So don't provoke me in the future.
Dad.
Out of these two presents, which one do you like more?
Brother, don't try to start anything.
Anxin,
ever since your mom gave birth to you, I never received
any news about you and your mother.
How have the two of you lived these past years?
Why did your mom suddenly-
Sorry, Uncle.
After my mom passed away, I fell ill.
There was a lot I couldn't remember after I woke up.
Child.
You have suffered so much.
I'm your mother's best friend. If you are willing to,
I hope you can feel like Uncle Ling
is a family member of yours.
Thank you, Uncle.
I also have a gift I want to give you.
Open it and take a look.
Uncle.
I can't accept this gift.
You haven't even looked at it. How do you know if you can accept it or not?
You were close friends with my mom.
I'm sure that when my mom helped you, she wasn't expecting to get anything in return,
so I can't accept this valuable gift.
You might already know what the gift is.
Anxin, I respect your decision.
If you change your mind, you can always come find me.
You should know that Uncle Ling is also your family member.
The Ling family will always welcome you. Okay?
Okay.
Everyone is hungry right? Let's eat.
Eat. Eat. Eat.
Let's eat.
Here. Eat some fish.
He's allergic to parsley.
Look at how forgetful I am. Xin'er is so thoughtful.
That's to be expected. They were so close in high school.
You could say they were childhood sweethearts.
And, a match perfect looks wise.
The two of you know each other?
We were in the same school.
Here.
Second brother, if I'm not mistaken. Is your watch and Anxin's watch
a customized couple model?
That's right.
Dad. It's looks like you will be seeing Sister Anxin often.
Ling Yue, you must treat Anxin well.
If she's mistreated, I won't forgive you.
Dad, don't worry.
Anxin, eat.
Okay.
I picked out the parsley for you.
Ever since my second brother came back, you have never stopped looking at him.
I know. The only reason why you promised me to come back to eat,
was because you knew he would be here.
Since you know, why did you still bring me back?
Because this is the first time you said yes to my invitation.
Even if it is because of my brother, at least it is a good start.
My feelings for him won't change that easily.
I know. But that's okay.
Don't forget, you still owe me a date.
It's up to you.
Where are we going?
Hey!
I wish you guys a wonderful night.
Have fun.
Are they?
President Ling.
-Ai Li!
-Hi
Director Ling Fang...he...
It's going to rain, let me take you back.
Are you teasing a kid? You're telling me it's going to rain when the weather is so nice.
Can it be that you prepared a surprise for me?
No, I really didn't!
I really didn't.
It's really going to rain. Let's go.
Okay. Let's go.
I finally understand why you hate your brother.
He doesn't use money as it should be. All he knows is how to make trouble.
I originally wanted to give you a surprise.
I understand the effort!
Wait a second.
What is this?
Stupid, your face is dirty.
Anxin.
Let's restart?
Then you have to promise, you will tell me everything.
I promise you.
What are you doing now?
During the Gu company banquet, you owe me a dance.
♫ Walking those dark streets with you ♫
♫ Watching streetlights flash on and off ♫
♫ How far is the future? We see it with a turn of our head ♫
♫ We've yet to part but longing has already begun ♫
♫ Hugging you is like holding the entire world ♫
♫ So beautiful that I fear a time limit ♫
You are my girlfriend now, so you can't leave.
Say yes!
Okay.
Let's forget all the bad things from the past, and create new memories in the future.
♫ Learning warmth to heat up those cold and lonely memories ♫
♫ The passing scenery start and stop ♫
♫ The story continues under camera lenses ♫
Old Ling, our child says she doesn't want it and you really aren't giving it to her?
She...She is afraid that after she accepts my gift
it'll confirm the rumors between her mom and I.
This kid, is a good kid.
Xiao Wan would rest easy knowing this.
Boss, are we going to leave now? What about the shares?
What can we do? Didn't you see how those two were like Siamese twins?
Are you sure that Gu Anxin
is interested in him?
But that is not my goal.
As long as the stocks don't fall in number two's hands, anything's fine.
You...
Your home.
Are you drunk or are you losing your mind? Why did you bring me here?
You will know in a few minutes.
♫ Meeting unexpectedly, those lost memories ♫
♫ Illogical, too much like comedy ♫
♫ That day of bad weather ♫
♫ was good fortune that brought you into my life ♫
♫ The flirtatious atmosphere spreads around us ♫
♫ Unbelievably stimulates telepathy ♫
♫ The you who appears aloof ♫
♫ finally starts to reveal your childish self ♫
♫ The hint of fate was already present ♫
♫ Destiny has already foreshadowed our path ♫
♫ Resting against each other in sleep that dark night ♫
♫ Steady happiness is you by my side ♫
[At noon, you can make ramen to eat.]
[The fridge has your favorite bottled water, ramen and cake.]
Breakfast is on the table. There's bottled water for you in the fridge.
♫ Steady happiness is you by my side ♫
♫ Are we destined to be together? ♫
Do you want a drink? This is your favorite flavor.
♫ The future gives us both courage ♫
♫ So don't suspect anymore, this must be love ♫
♫ It's love ♫
What happened?
I bought this house back.
I'm this house's landlord now and you're the tenant.
However, the rent period is everlasting.
You're not joking?
This is our contract.
But I added a line behind it.
I, Ling Yue
promise to rent the house, and will only rent it to Ms.Gu Anxin.
I will never raise rent nor sell the house.
If I ever go against the contract, it can be seen as purposefully relinquishing ownership on the house.
The house will belong to Ms.Anxin.
This contract is too unfair for you, right?
No, I think it's quite fair.
I'm the landlord. You need to pay me rent.
It's very equal. Just like this contract,
last time I took advantage of it. Now it's your turn.
Thank you.
This was where our relationship started, and now our relationship is continuing.
We will hug each other tightly and not let go anymore.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Memories are soaked in rain ♫
♫ Fate works bizarrely ♫
♫ The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly beats abnormally ♫
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Obviously, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness, for it has always been you ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Yet the longing has never been able to stop ♫
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Using all of my most beautiful adjectives ♫
♫ Is still not enough to describe your name ♫
♫ Our story is exclusively ours ♫
♫ Our palms hold onto the key to the future ♫
♫ Using love to slowly open up a lifetime ♫