(All characters, locations, organizations, religions,)
(and incidents in this drama are fictional.)
(Episode 14)
I'm sorry.
Which one are you apologizing for?
For deciding to erase our memories?
Or for falling for my looks again?
Both.
I'm sorry for everything.
No, I'm sorry...
for looking so handsome.
Come to think of it, that's what I was doing.
I think...
everything I did this whole time was to go back to you.
I wanted to face the consequence by myself.
I thought I would be able to get away.
But look where I ended up.
What do we do?
What should we do now?
We finally realized...
that whatever we try, we can't escape this.
So we should...
acknowledge it.
- What? - Our fate.
Let's accept it.
Okay?
That's your plan, right?
You're planning...
to dissipate for me, right?
It doesn't matter what I say.
It won't change anything.
Whatever we try,
we won't be able to...
escape our fate, right?
Right.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing? You didn't do anything wrong.
It's all my fault.
If I didn't make such a stupid wish that day...
Then, we wouldn't have met.
And I can't have that.
If we never met,
I would still be nothing.
I want to mean something to you.
Experiencing that once will be enough for me.
So you didn't do anything wrong.
It's always been my fault.
So let me have my way.
Okay?
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
I looked for you everywhere.
What did you need from home?
Me.
Doctor?
Aunt, you remember him?
Goodness, Dong Kyung. Of course, I remember him.
What's that supposed to mean?
Do you think I've become forgetful due to my age?
No, that's not what I meant.
It's been a while, so I was worried you might not remember me.
That's probably why she asked.
Actually, come to think of it, I really haven't...
seen you around recently.
What were you so busy with?
I was busy getting things done.
What do you mean?
There's a lot to prepare before a wedding.
Dong Kyung and I...
are going to get married.
What?
You're getting married?
Let's close the cafe early today.
What? Already?
It's not time to close yet.
Mr. Lee.
When you run a business,
it's crucial to keep the promise we make to our customers.
Mr. Lee, is there something wrong?
- Does it look like it? - Yes, very much.
I feel like you're about to cry.
You look like a man walking in the rain all by himself.
The rain...
I heard it rained that day.
That day? When?
It didn't rain yesterday.
That day,
when she kissed some other guy.
What? Who? Ji...
I mean, you mean the lady from yesterday?
But it doesn't matter.
It's all in the past.
So that doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter?
You must really love her.
Yes, it doesn't matter.
The real problem is...
I got dumped yesterday.
Just stay as you were. Go on.
I'll do everything.
Get some rest.
Ji Na is unbelievable.
Hello. Oh, hey.
Come back home.
They know each other.
They even live together, but he didn't tell me.
He was totally toying with me, right?
Number... Number two?
Ji Na.
You startled me. You're here early. Did work finish early?
What?
Did you dump Mr. Lee?
That got around pretty quickly.
You really dumped him?
- I wouldn't say I dumped him. - And whom did you kiss?
How do you know about that?
That only happened recently. I can't believe he told you already.
It happened recently?
Which one are you talking about?
From what I heard, it was ages ago.
What?
You kissed him again recently?
Do you go around kissing people?
What is it that makes guys fall for you?
Whom did you kiss and when?
It was with number two, right?
I guess it was. It was with number two.
Dong Kyung, Ji Na recently...
No, don't listen to him.
They're getting married.
No, we're not exactly getting married.
That's the news.
No, it's not.
It is.
Yes, I think it's going to happen.
Can we talk in private?
I need to talk to you too.
My gosh. But...
Is that why you haven't been around lately?
It's not that I wasn't around.
It's more so you didn't know.
Well, I obviously didn't know you wanted to marry her.
Brother.
You're a very magnanimous guy.
I'm far from becoming like you.
Let's be honest. It's not an easy decision to make.
I don't exactly feel comfortable about it.
Oh, here.
I always kept it with me thinking this was bound to come.
It's the money I saved up ever since I turned 20.
Why are you giving me this?
I always carried this around wondering when and how...
I should give this to my sister.
And I think this is the right time.
You can use it for the wedding.
(Savings account)
To be honest, I thought you were a real bum.
You were handsome and seemed rich,
so I didn't get why you liked my penniless sister.
I bet you had no idea I thought that about you.
You're right. I had no idea.
But now I can't stop thinking that Dong Kyung got really lucky.
Maybe it's because she lived such a kind life.
You must've been really kind too...
seeing that you ended up meeting my sister.
I hope you'll continue...
to stay by my sister's side.
You'll do that, right?
Yes.
Seriously? You're getting married?
I guess that's what he wants.
What about you?
Do you not feel the same way?
I want to do everything he wants.
Listen. Marriage isn't...
something you do out of loyalty.
No matter how much you love him...
Ji Na.
Hey.
I have no choice but to be picky about your marriage.
What am I going to do?
Are you crying?
No matter how hard I try to end it...
No matter how hard I try to run away,
I always come back to ground zero.
I try to abandon him, but I can't.
And I can't seem to get him out of my mind either.
What am I going to do?
I'm running out of time, but I don't know what to do.
What am I going to do, Ji Na?
- Dong Kyung. - It's all my fault.
Everything's my fault.
No, it's not your fault.
You did nothing wrong.
So just do everything you want.
I don't care.
Just forget everything I said earlier.
I'm fine as long as you're happy.
So don't say you're running out of time.
Don't ever say that again.
What am I going to do, Ji Na? What can I do?
Ji Na...
Leave them. I'll do the dishes.
I get it now.
- What? - This is how you waited for me.
I always wondered what you did while you sat here.
You always waited for me to finish.
I did not.
You don't have to let me have my way anymore.
You don't have to wait for me anymore.
You've raised me well.
- Hyun Kyu. - I want to stop bothering you.
I need to grow up now.
If you keep watching my back,
I keep wanting to depend on you.
Look at me now. I'm still blaming you.
- Are you saying you'll move out? - Yes.
I'll enter the real world now.
When will I pack all this up?
Still...
it's time to go.
So...
- Doctor. - I heard.
- You're getting married? - What?
How did you...
Gosh. There are eyes and ears all over the hospital.
Congrats.
Well...
That's why I'm saying this,
- but... - You don't want to do...
the biopsy, right?
You said it was in a dangerous location.
Then let's do this.
Until the wedding. Let's wait until after the wedding.
Okay.
To be honest, you're right.
It's very dangerous.
Once we go in,
we may have to close it right up.
That was why...
I wanted to do a biopsy and treatment rather than surgery.
But...
Let's live a little longer.
Let's live a little longer and become a little happier...
since you've decided on the treatment.
Yes.
But have the wedding as soon as possible.
Come to the hospital right away if you don't feel well.
Can you promise me that?
Thank you.
Don't be too afraid though.
You're doing well already.
I'll be there at your wedding.
Did you set a date yet?
Not yet...
Well...
Dong Kyung is going home.
What did your aunt say?
She's worried.
Tell her not to worry.
I'll take full responsibility.
I will drive her to and from every time.
So tell her not to worry...
and that we should do everything for Dong Kyung that she wants.
What has gotten into you?
I thought you'd be adamantly against it.
She clung onto me and cried.
She doesn't show it, but it must be hard.
And nervous.
I don't want to even think about it,
but just in case...
Let's give her what she wants...
so there are no regrets.
Okay.
(Lee Hyun Kyu)
- Hey. - Let's meet up.
Okay. Where?
Okay.
I have to go.
- Wait. Ji Na. - Yes?
Make sure you don't regret it either.
Worry about yourself.
Later.
Is it marriage blues?
Are you that depressed about marrying me?
I'm hurt.
You used to say I was handsome and all that.
You should be grateful that I'm marrying you.
Not everyone gets to marry a guy...
they thought was good-looking when they first saw him.
You don't even respond anymore.
You'll have to respond when you see this.
(Savings account)
Sun Kyung gave it to me.
He said to use it for the wedding.
You've raised him well.
Why are you staring at me like that?
Are you marveling at my good looks?
It's been so long since I came here.
Back then, the field looked so big.
That just means that we grew up.
I told you that my friend was sick the other day. Do you remember?
Yes.
She has glioblastomas.
She could die from them.
I never thought...
she would get sick like that...
because never in my life have I thought...
that I would lose her like that.
That just shows how foolish I am.
And yesterday, she told me that she wanted to get married...
when she was sobbing.
That made me think a lot.
Like what?
"If today was my last day, what would I do?"
"Would I..."
"be in love like her?"
When I first saw you,
you were really cute.
When our eyes met in the hallway,
I could hear...
what you wanted to tell me from your gaze.
I could see what you were thinking. I like that about you.
There was honesty in your eyes.
But did you know?
That hasn't changed.
There's still honesty in your eyes unlike mine.
I got indigestion after eating rice cake and bombed the CSAT.
So I was being transported to the hospital in the morning.
This crossed my mind.
"What a relief."
I talked a big game of going to the same college as you...
and attending the same school in Seoul.
But you knew that my grades were never good enough.
But I didn't admit that in front of you.
I was so humiliated...
because I really liked you.
So I wanted to always look cool in your eyes.
But when I went abroad to study, I dodged your calls and texts.
But on my social media, I kept...
posting pretentious photos.
To tell you the truth, I cried every night before going to sleep.
I didn't speak the language.
I didn't know anyone.
I was falling behind with the training.
My life was a total mess.
I wanted to go back home every day.
I missed you every day.
But...
I thought I would cry if I heard your voice...
and that you would sense it.
So I never called you back.
But after that, I came back to Korea.
I was so embarrassed that I had to come back home...
after leaving you like that.
So I couldn't call you.
Why?
I'd rather be a bad guy,
not a pathetic guy.
But that's what made me pathetic.
I was so childish.
I didn't know any better.
I'm sorry.
You should have told me.
You should have.
This school field...
still looks big to me.
I guess I didn't grow up at all.
Hyun Kyu.
You didn't ask me to see me. I asked you out today.
So we still have one more date.
And you can ask me out for the last date...
when you really want to see me.
When you really want to see me.
Don't force yourself.
I won't beg.
Before I go,
let's shake hands to celebrate our graduation.
Goodbye.
I didn't give up yet.
I'm not running away.
I know.
You'd better not mess up.
I'll run to her and take your spot.
Don't lower your guard.
Never lower your guard.
I won't.
Ji Na told me only then, she felt...
as she was no longer 18, 19, or 20...
and that she finally felt like she was where she belonged.
And no matter when she faced it, in the end,
the result wouldn't have changed.
"The result wouldn't have changed."
That's another way of expressing fate.
I was also...
heading toward my fate that wouldn't change.
Hello.
You must be getting discharged.
Did I startle you?
That wasn't my intention.
You look so gaunt.
I wanted to help.
I'm sorry.
Help me. Help me just one more time.
It's out of my hands now.
Then what am I supposed to do now?
What are we supposed to do?
Just accept it.
- No. - Then what?
Will you destroy the world?
Yes.
You can't do that.
You also know you're incapable of doing something like that.
No.
I'll do anything for him.
My life perished countless times.
So I know better than anyone about perishment.
You cry and try to fight it.
But in the end, you just accept it.
Because that's his choice.
And that choice...
is his fate.
So just modestly accept it.
Accept doom.
There's nothing we can do about it.
I'm sorry.
But that's the ending he wants.
That's his happy ending.
Neither of us is happy.
So how is that a happy ending?
As you live life, you'll realize one day...
that there was a reason behind everything you went through.
You'll find out that it was a happy ending.
You can only find out if you stay alive.
If everyone dies, no one will know.
So live.
He wants you to live.
He wants you to live a very happy life.
[VIU Ver] tvN E14 'Doom at Your Service'
"Cold Heartless Fate"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
You sold a lot today.
You can go home now.
I'm your last customer.
You're going to leave it all here?
I don't need them anymore.
So I should leave them behind.
They're a burden.
I've always felt burdened throughout my entire life.
Now it's time to leave it all behind and go.
Goodbye.
You lived a great life.
My gosh.
Gosh.
Hello.
You could've just come inside.
What's with the joke?
Will you marry me?
Hey, you smiled. I'm going to take that as a "yes".
The flowers are pretty.
We only said that so I could get discharged from the hospital.
You didn't have to get me flowers.
Who says I didn't mean it?
So you actually bought these to propose to me?
No, someone gave them to me.
Who gave them to you?
A person whose life was going to end today.
She gave them to me before she left.
A person who was about to disappear...
gave them to another person who's going to disappear soon.
I should put them in a vase...
so I can enjoy them for a long time.
Let's always stay together.
- Okay. - Let's never be apart.
Okay.
Forever.
What is it?
I guess it wasn't the last time.
Flowers might blossom again.
On that tree?
Yes.
Let's come see it together.
You and I...
should come see it together.
Just a little bit.
Days like this will continue.
After you're gone, spring will arrive.
After you disappear, the morning will come.
And after your life ends, my life will begin.
Okay.
So every year when spring comes,
and every time morning is here,
I will think of you throughout my entire life.
Will I be able to endure that?
How would that kind of life...
be any different from doom?
A fountain pen?
What's wrong with her?
To the most sane author I've ever worked with...
and the most insane friend.
Insane?
Let me make myself clear.
I'm not trying to make you cry, so don't.
This is water-based ink.
So don't cry. Become strong.
That is your goal, Ji Na.
(Savings account)
I can't take your money, Sun Kyung.
It isn't even half of what I've spent on you.
Don't try to call it even with this.
You seriously have no shame.
But thanks always.
I'm always proud of you, my little brother. You grew up well.
Auntie.
My life was filled with a lot of love.
Thinking back, it was love...
that saved me.
Your love, Sun Kyung, Ji Na...
and him too.
That's why I'm scared.
Because I don't want to lose anything.
I had asked...
if it'll hurt a lot...
when I die.
Mom.
Dad.
I'm so scared.
I have no idea what I'll choose.
(Tak Jong Won, Kang Soo Ah)
But...
whatever I choose,
it'll probably hurt a lot.
That terrifies me.
I'm so scared.
(House of Love)
What are you doing here?
I followed you.
How long were you following me?
From the moment you were born.
Why are you following me?
Because I like you.
Because it's a waste.
Because I don't want to miss a single moment.
- Go with me. - Where?
To work.
Why are we here? Will this library disappear?
No. Words disappear.
I hear them.
Even now, hundreds of words...
are disappearing every second in that corner.
Collogue. Disport.
Indite. Malapert. Peregrinate.
Even words are forgotten.
If they aren't used,
they die.
This is a secret.
There are words that never disappear.
Like a dozen of them.
The meaning of your name is among them.
Dong Kyung. Admiration.
What about "human"?
That's on the list as well.
I'm annoyed.
Why?
I want to stay awake, but I'm sleepy.
Go to sleep. You're human, so you need to sleep.
I'll sleep for a few minutes. Just for a few minutes.
Okay.
Don't go anywhere.
Stay right next to me.
Okay.
Don't disappear.
Is this the end?
I came to say bye.
I'm the one who came to say bye.
You knew, didn't you?
That I'd make this decision.
Since a deity knows everything.
Everything is uncertain.
Even if she wishes for doom,
it's impossible to know whether or not it's possible.
So why don't you bet on that?
No. I'll bet on the sure thing.
On the sure way to save her.
Why did you make such a stupid promise?
I guess it was something I had to do.
- What? - Keep my promise, protect her,
and protect this world.
You have more to protect than I do.
I plan to live a little longer.
I plan to rely on the human heart...
and extend this life a little.
That's the first time, isn't it?
You never thought of doing that before.
Yes.
That heart will stop again eventually,
but there's still a lot that I want to see in this body.
I really like this life in many ways.
What do you want to see?
Flowers.
A flower in full bloom.
Where did you go?
I was...
Where were you?
I'm sorry.
I thought you had left.
I thought you were gone.
When I woke up, I didn't see you.
So I was...
I'm sorry. Sorry.
I just closed my eyes for a bit and opened them.
I thought if a day had gone by.
Or two days.
I thought if it was over.
I don't have much time left.
I really don't have much time left.
It's okay. We still have time.
We still have one more day.
I don't think I can do it.
I really didn't want to do this.
I really don't want to do this.
Do what?
Make me not love anyone.
No one.
That's my wish.
I can't do that.
I said that was my wish.
That was the term of our contract.
Why can't you do it?
Because I must save you.
If you're not in my life,
my life would be worthless to me.
No, it will be worth it to me.
I might have to...
live in an empty world...
to the end of time after losing you and everyone you love.
Dong Kyung.
Humans...
can fall in love again.
No.
You're human.
You can overcome it, but I can't.
You know that, right?
I don't eat, sleep, or cry.
I don't have compassion or fall in love.
But you're human.
So you can do it.
No. I can't.
I can't... I cannot live without you.
Don't do this. Don't say things like that.
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
It's my fault.
I want to make a wish for real now.
Take me...
to the world of doom.
It's not possible.
I'm not asking you to take me there for real.
I don't care...
even if it's fake.
It can be in a dream or a figment of my imagination.
Let me...
stay there with you on my last day.
Grant me this wish.
I'm serious.
- Is this... - The world of doom.
Seriously. There's no one...
My voice is too loud.
Because no one is here to make any sounds.
This is weird.
I'll be lonely.
In the world of doom, I will have lost my purpose.
I will be nothing.
Being responsible for everything that disappears...
means that I exist...
for the things that disappear.
As there's nothing that needs to disappear here,
I will be...
a particle of dust, floating around.
So it will be pointless...
if I exist without you.
You're lonely.
When you look at the things that disappear,
you still...
look lonesome.
You too.
You always look lonesome...
when you look at me.
There's a place I want to visit.
Why did you want to come here?
I wanted to pray.
There's no deity in the world of doom.
Because there are no humans?
Right.
I'm here.
I'm a human being. And I'm right here in this world.
The sun also sets in the world of doom.
What did you pray for in the church earlier?
It's a secret between the deity and me.
You said there was no deity.
The deity would have been born at the moment you wanted.
What did you pray for?
I...
I just...
For the last time, I prayed that I won't ever love anyone again.
I know.
I know it won't come true.
But I still prayed for it anyway.
Dong Kyung.
I love you.
You're what I love the most.
I'm sorry I fell in love with you.
I'm sorry I love you the most.
Thank you...
for loving me.
It's going to be midnight soon.
It's okay.
Everything will be all right.
I wanted to be with you until the very last moment.
I know.
I love you.
I'm so scared.
- Dong Kyung... - Don't say anything.
Don't say a word.
This contract is invalid.
No.
- No. - I will take with me...
your sadness and pain.
Don't worry. I'll take everything with me.
No.
I don't want that.
I was created for you.
So don't worry.
Live a happy life.
That's why I was born.
I was born to make you happy.
Can't you stay?
Please?
Earlier at that church,
I prayed for your happiness.
I need you to be happy.
I need you by my side.
Do you remember what I told you last time?
Even if it rains,
and you're the only one without an umbrella, it's okay.
If you run just a little bit, you'll soon be home.
I want you to run once I'm gone.
Don't look back and just run.
Then you'll soon be...
(Doom At Your Service)
I wonder if it all actually happened.
I wonder if you were really once...
a part of my life.
No, it's not that.
Joo Ik.
Ji Na, don't you keep in touch with Cha Joo Ik?
We all gathered together for a meal today.
And everyone told me they miss you.
If I ever walk past you, will you grab my hand...
just like you always did?
You're happy, right?