♪Waking up in a nightmare♪
♪Facing this cruel world♪
♪Whose heart is flipped♪
♪Missed farewell to lover♪
♪If the ending is tragic♪
♪Fearlessness is born in adversity♪
♪Even if the wings are torn♪
♪And fall back to the abyss♪
♪Hold your hands and move forward♪
♪Never stopping day or night♪
♪Transcending time and distance♪
♪I may be hurt and heartbroken♪
♪Yet be brave to fight on♪
♪As a hero♪
♪Looking beyond, conflicts and war never stops♪
♪Turning behind, you are always there♪
♪Lash out the curse in life♪
♪Let the story be eternal♪
♪Martial Soul surges aggressively♪
♪To embrace your lone wolf braveness♪
♪Even if the future is harsh♪
♪I will never give up♪
♪When there is no way out in reality♪
♪Hope is vexed by desolation♪
♪Yet smiling freely♪
♪Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant♪
♪The power of twin souls illuminates♪
♪Surviving in every plight♪
♪I will never give up♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
It's Haishen Island!
We're finally here!
Passing my challenge with your third skill
and at such a young age.
Alright.
You are qualified to accept
the God of the Ocean's challenge.
Even though it's weak,
why is the God of the Ocean's energy
coming from him?
Black level six test.
You definitely won't pass
with your current power.
You will die for sure.
Even if we die, we won't give up.
God of the Ocean, please give us our challenge!
[Episode 169]
Yellow level one test is not hard
and your life won't be in danger.
This is a good thing for you.
Xiang, don't worry.
[Black Level Five Test]
[Black Level Six Test]
Four black level tests were given in one day.
This only happens once in a lifetime!
My talent and potential are so much
weaker than the others.
Zhu Qing got the black level five test,
and Ao and Fatty got black level six.
This is...
The top-tier level seven test!
[Top-tier Level Seven Test]
Welcome, heir to Haishen Island's Head Flamen!
Senior, this...
The red top-tier test
is for the heir of Haishen Island's Head Flamen.
Once it appears,
the challenger will always be successful.
That means you are destined to be
Haishen Island's future leader.
Rong Rong already got
the top-tier level seven test.
I can't imagine
what kind of test San will get.
Senior, please!
The young one with the energy
of the God of the Ocean,
let me see your power.
What... what...
What...
What happened?
Top-tier level one test!
God of the Ocean, God of the Ocean...
After 100 years of waiting,
I'm finally about to meet you.
Senior, what test is the gold color?
It seems as if I need to complete
nine challenges to pass.
I don't know.
Then what about her?
Why did she get the top-tier level one test?
I don't know either.
No need to question him.
You will not receive the top-tier level nine test,
but the God of the Ocean's nine challenges.
As for her, her top-tier level one test
is to finish your nine challenges with you.
[Soul Land]
Greetings, Head Flamen!
Greetings, Head Flamen.
I was unable to complete
the God of the Ocean's orders.
Please give me my punishment.
She is the Grand Ocean Master, Bo Sai Xi!
This isn't your fault.
It is also my first time
seeing an heir to the God of the Ocean.
The God of the Ocean's heir!
No wonder the God of the Ocean's energy
is apparent in him.
Young man.
Can you tell me about yourself?
My name is Tang San
and my great-grandfather's name is Tang Chen.
You are
Tang Chen's great-grandson?
Yes.
Who would've thought
that the person I was waiting for
is his great-grandson.
Tang San, from now on,
you do not
need to bow down to anyone on Haishen Island,
including me.
Ou Ya.
Send my orders.
Before their tests are completed,
all eight of them
are important guests on the island.
No one shall be impolite to them.
Except for helping them complete the test,
everyone should try to satisfy their asks.
Yes.
Remember,
you must complete at least
one of your nine challenges every year.
Or else,
all your effort will be in vain.
If I fail,
will I also die?
Tang San, your test
affects the existence of Haishen Island.
If you fail,
the outcome will be much worse than death.
Tang San, remember.
You must never think about giving up.
Why is my test related
to the entire island?
So strong.
Her presence just now
made me feel like I was about to be crushed.
Distinguished guests.
It's getting late.
I'll take you to your lodging in Haima City.
We will begin the tests tomorrow.
Thank you, Senior.
We're here.
This is Haima City.
Haishen Island has Seven Sacred Totems
and seven cities.
Each city has about 1,000 residents,
all dedicated followers of the God of the Ocean.
I heard
that Haishen Island has about
3,000 ocean soul masters total.
If there are already 1,000 in Haima City,
then what about the others?
That's not quite true.
Those 3,000 or so ocean soul masters
are the 3,500 ocean warriors
who passed their tests and were chosen
to protect the God of the Ocean.
My guests, please follow me into the city.
Look at this.
It's so mean but still allowed
to bask in the sunlight out here?
That's because you pissed it off,
Xiang.
The building up there is my mansion.
My guests, please.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 169 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1564 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2555]
[Total scene: 62170]
[Total CGI: 28465]
[Total plan of action scene: 12678]
[Total scene model: nearly 577]
[Total character model: nearly 1055]
[Total props model: 13410]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪We still have to part from each other♪
♪I'm faint-hearted to stop you from leaving♪
♪Amidst the grieving woods♪
♪Who is crying out there♪
♪I still relentlessly hold on♪
♪I refuse to accept this destiny♪
♪Desperately searching♪
♪Any signs of you♪
♪The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight♪
♪In your eyes, the world never changes♪
♪Yearning grows and interweaves with the past♪
♪Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven't told you♪
♪You are the memory I refuse to let go♪
♪And the craziness of my desperation♪
♪Can you hear♪
♪My calls♪
♪Breaking through extreme dolors♪
♪Rushing towards your embrace♪
♪You are the only one I dreamt to comb my hair♪
♪And the wish I made upon a star♪
♪One day♪
♪You will turn up gorgeously♪
♪And hold my hands♪
♪To envisage our future♪
[Next episode]
We successfully entered Haishen Island,
but this is just the beginning.
This is the forbidden area?
The surroundings feel very serious and solemn.
The depressing feeling gets stronger
with every step closer.
Don't try to force it.
Also, be careful of the Round Ocean.
Where is Xiang? Has anyone seen Xiang?
Xiang's missing.
Missing?
I'm ready.
Let's get started then.