(Final Episode)
We did it.
I'm glad.
- Hello?
- Did it go well?
Secretary Ju.
We're done with the exorcism.
We did it.
- Thank you.
- All right.
Great work. Great work, really.
Ms. Hong.
(Secretary Ju Hwa Jeong)
Ms. Hong, say something.
Ji A. Ji A?
I told you to look forward...
to the kind of interesting things
that will happen...
once you turn me into your enemy.
Did you think you could do
a number on me...
and get away with it? Did you?
You scumbag.
How dare you?
- Hey!
- You scumbag!
Darn it.
Ji A!
Oh, no!
In Bum!
- Hey, I'm going to pee.
- Where are you going?
- Okay.
- Gosh.
You scumbag.
Wait. Hey.
You should apologize for hitting me.
Let me go, you punk!
- Are you okay?
- What's your problem?
- Get him.
- Wait.
Let go!
Hey. He hit me!
- Hey!
- Get him!
- Hey! Come here!
Let go!
Are you looking down on us
for being poor?
Let go, you scumbag!
Ms. Hong! What do I do?
In Bum's still inside!
- See you at the hospital.
- Okay!
Hurry up! Hurry!
In Bum!
Please save him!
Please prepare an OR
for immediate surgery.
Thank you.
Don't die.
- Sir, are you awake?
- In Bum.
Are you okay?
What?
- What?
- What's going on?
What's going on?
(Operating Room, Restricted Access)
(Operating Room)
Mom.
Are you finally awake?
Had he stabbed 1cm deeper,
it could've been life-threatening.
How's In Bum doing?
Don't tell me he's still unconscious.
According to the ambulance driver,
the car suddenly malfunctioned,
and they crashed.
When he had regained consciousness,
In Bum had disappeared.
Did you say Do Hak Sung died
at the scene?
Correct.
His body was found in an underpass
near Sky Building.
We believe he fell down the stairs.
It was a freak accident,
but I think karma got to him.
I think his unrested spirit entered
In Bum.
But In Bum was wearing his necklace.
It broke during the exorcism.
I've analyzed all CCTV...
in a 20km radius from the car accident.
Electronic devices malfunction
when a ghost appears.
So I connected all CCTV cameras
that temporarily disconnected...
for no apparent reason.
I think he's headed to our realty.
You're right.
Do Hak Sung wants to kill me.
He failed to do so the day he died.
This is infuriating.
How dare he turn
into an unrested spirit...
after all the evil deeds he had committed?
First,
let's ask the police for help.
He's an evil spirit who's out to get you.
We don't know what he's capable of.
No, not the police.
What if the unrested spirit
gets caught red-handed?
Then In Bum will go to prison.
That won't happen.
Don't worry.
(Daebak Realty)
Ms. Hong.
It's not too late to back out.
You can't hold your own
when you haven't fully recovered.
First, let's leave this up
to the police.
After that, we'll think
about how to save In Bum.
I'll get help from everyone I know.
I made a promise to him
during our first exorcism.
You'll never wake up
with bloody hands again.
I won't let that happen.
I must keep my promise.
Where is he?
He's almost there.
Okay.
I think he'll arrive at the realty
in five minutes.
Okay. You should get out of there first.
Okay. I got it.
Hey! You...
Why are you walking on the road?
Have you gone mad? Are you crazy?
No, In Bum. No!
In Bum...
What...
In Bum.
(Daebak Realty)
Oh In Bum.
Are you in there?
No.
I got you.
Did you think
I would let you go that easily?
(Do Hak Sung)
Don't ever forget all the crimes...
you committed...
as your bones burn
in this blazing fire...
forever.
Come out!
Oh In Bum. Are you in there?
No.
Ms. Hong.
Are you awake? Are you all right?
I heard.
When I was possessed
by Do Hak Sung's spirit,
I tried to kill you.
I almost...
killed you.
No.
You saved me.
Pardon?
Even when you were possessed,
your will...
dominated the evil spirit.
So I was able to finish the ritual.
Thanks.
Thank you...
for staying alive.
Ms. Ju.
- Did you have lunch?
- Yes. I just did.
I heard that there's a great
makguksu restaurant nearby.
I just had my lunch there.
That sounds delicious, right?
By the way,
how did you hurt your hand?
It looks like it got burned.
What happened?
The side effect of sealing the spirit.
Sealing the spirit?
The method you were going to use
on the egg ghost?
I didn't want Do Hak Sung
to dissipate without any pain.
He'll feel burning pain
all over his body for eternity.
That's a glorious injury, then.
You're here.
How's Ms. Hong?
She'll be discharged in a week.
Goodness,
it must be a lot of work for you.
It's not bad.
- Ji Chul.
- Yes?
Thanks.
What? For what?
I heard you hurt your arm...
because of me.
No, I slipped in the bathroom.
Ms. Ju told me.
She said you stopped me
from hurting other people...
while I was possessed.
Come on, Ms. Ju.
I knew you'd feel bad,
so I asked her not to tell you.
- Ji Chul.
- Yes?
Did I ever tell you that I love you?
All of a sudden? You're scaring me.
Someone said...
I should say thanks when I'm grateful...
and say sorry when I feel bad.
And if I love someone,
I need to tell them that I do.
That's how we won't turn
into unrested spirits.
Ji Chul.
Thank you, and I love you. Lots.
My gosh!
Hey, I just got goosebumps.
Look. Look at this.
You really startled me. My gosh.
- Man.
- My gosh.
Hey, I'm feeling great. Take these.
Aren't these from Soo Jung?
No, I bought those.
I wouldn't give you something
my sweetheart gave me.
You bought a lot of these.
Ever since I got these as gifts,
I've only been wearing these.
- I can't wear anything else now.
- Really?
It's a lot of work to travel
back and forth from the hospital,
so you can make use of those.
I got a lot, so don't worry.
- Thanks.
- Me too.
Thank you, and I love you.
Lots.
Don't you feel like the time is flying?
It was freezing when we first met,
but it's summer now.
What's on your mind?
Once I get discharged tomorrow,
I'd like to give another shot
at letting my mom go.
Will you help me?
Of course.
It won't be easy...
because I hurt her.
She hasn't shown herself since that day.
She must be furious at me.
I don't think she's furious.
She must be heartbroken.
I'm sure she knows how you feel.
She's your mom.
What's wrong?
Is there...
an unrested spirit around here?
No. No, I don't know.
I don't see anything.
Is something going on?
You're back!
Congratulations on your...
Did something happen to her?
Let her be alone for a moment.
Then, no one has to sacrifice their lives.
The exorcist will experience
a side effect.
That's why we don't usually seal spirits.
What do I do now?
What do I do now, Mom?
I have to send you away.
She was...
just getting better
physically and emotionally.
What if she breaks down like last time?
I'm worried.
I'm sure she'll overcome this.
Ji A is...
much stronger
than you think she is, Hwa Jeong.
How is she?
Let's give her some time.
I'm sure she's sorting things out.
Gosh, how can this happen?
I can't believe
her exorcism powers are lost.
Gosh! Do Hak Sung,
that disgusting scumbag.
Not only was he a problem
when alive or dead,
but he's also a problem
after being exorcized.
What? Wait a minute. Hey.
You still have your psychic skills.
Can't you let yourself
get possessed by her...
and then get stabbed?
Wouldn't that help her mother find peace?
If someone who has
no exorcism powers stabs a psychic,
the psychic will die.
Are you going somewhere?
Let's go eat.
This looks delicious.
Eat up.
It's my fault for thinking lightly
about the side effect...
of sealing a spirit.
But I don't regret it.
Do Hak Sung deserved a cruel punishment.
Even if I could turn back time,
I'd make the same decision.
You're right.
And come to think of it,
no one has ever said
that the side effect was permanent.
Does that mean you'll regain
your power?
There's no guarantee.
But I can't just sit back and wait.
I'm going to look for a way.
We'll do the same.
What is this?
Gosh, that's hot!
This is something martial artists do.
It's called the Iron Palm.
It's something they do
when they lack strength.
I've replaced the sand with salt.
You want me to put my hand in this?
- Have you gone insane?
- Give it a try.
Who knows?
She didn't buy it.
Strengthening your vigor could solve it.
This proves
that your vigor isn't the problem.
I'll be counting down from ten.
And you...
will time travel to the past.
Go back...
and retrieve your power.
Ten,
nine... Go back to the past.
- Eight...
- There's a tunnel.
On the other side
of the tunnel is...
a big flower bed.
It's pretty.
I didn't know there was a flower bed
in his heart.
How fragrant.
Are you okay?
What do you mean?
You seem to be straining yourself.
When I was young,
I'd pray every single day...
that I'd stop seeing unrested spirits.
I didn't want my exorcism power.
I wanted to get rid of it.
I hated myself for being different
from others.
I wanted to be normal.
But now that I've lost it all,
I think I'm nothing without it.
Ms. Hong.
Don't worry.
I won't blame myself
or be depressed anymore.
I haven't found a way yet.
But I will retrieve my power...
and help my mom find peace.
I know you will.
Goodness. You brought so much.
We left in such a hurry...
and couldn't even say our goodbyes.
I couldn't thank you either.
You did that day.
Did I?
Thanks to you,
I was able to feed my boy one last time.
That had always been something
I regretted.
I'm truly grateful.
Chang Hwa.
I'm sorry.
This is the last meal I'm making for you.
I hope you enjoy it...
and find peace.
- Ms. Ju.
- Yes?
I think I can help my mom find peace.
Did you get your power back?
No. I'm going to perform
the exorcism without the stick...
like I did with Chang Hwa.
The moment she let go
of her obsession over her son,
the unrested spirit left on its own.
Are you saying her obsession
hindered his spirit from leaving?
I hindered my mom from leaving as well.
My reluctance to let her go,
my resentment toward her
for leaving me behind,
and my guilt for killing her.
It wasn't your fault.
I know.
Nevertheless,
I couldn't let go
of the reluctance and resentment.
After exorcizing the egg ghost,
I finally understood
why my mom made that decision.
Although I can't agree
with her decision,
I can now at least understand her.
That's why I think
I can finally let her go.
It took too long.
That's natural.
Letting go of a beloved...
is always painful.
(Chinese Character Dictionary)
What are you doing?
I'm trying to find a way
to retrieve your power,
but your ancestors aren't helpful.
Why is everything in Chinese characters?
There are too many characters
that aren't even in the dictionary.
In Bum.
Help me perform an exorcism.
(Daebak Realty)
(Hong Mi Jin)
Take off your necklace.
Ji A.
Mom.
It's me.
Mom...
My dear Ji A.
My beautiful daughter.
Mom.
Mom...
I'm sorry, Mom.
I made you stay here.
I made you suffer in cold...
and stopped you from leaving me.
I'm sorry, Mom.
No. I was so happy...
that I got to see you grow up.
Thank you...
for growing up into a fine lady
without me.
I was proud of you every single day.
I should...
go now.
Can you tell that boy that I'm sorry?
He had done nothing wrong,
but I almost took away his life.
Mom. No, don't go.
No. Please don't go. Please stay.
I must go.
I'm sure you know
that I can't stay here...
like this anymore.
I don't care about that. Mom...
Ji A.
Then, let me go with you.
Please take me with you.
Take me with you.
When I come home,
you won't be here now.
I won't be able to see you
ever again.
Mom. Mom...
Don't leave me alone here.
Ji A.
You're not alone.
You have so many people who love
and cherish you by your side.
You were a much better exorcist
than me 20 years ago.
And you still are.
You achieved what I couldn't.
And you saved a lot of people.
I'm sure you will...
continue to be great.
Mom.
You're not cold now, right?
Take care,
my dear daughter.
Mi Jin.
Hwa Jeong.
I left behind such great responsibility.
I'm sorry.
Mi Jin.
I really...
wanted to keep Ji A safe.
You did a great job.
Thank you for keeping Ji A safe.
(Daebak Realty)
(Psychic, Special)
Get ready and come out.
Let me buy you a meal.
(Daebak Realty)
- Hop in.
- What is this?
Just get in.
We're going somewhere nice.
Let's go.
Gosh, don't you feel a little refreshed?
Close the roof.
Why would we be in a convertible
if we're going to close the roof?
The weather is nice
and this road is nice too.
Everything is looking nice.
(Happiness Hall)
Ms. Ju told me...
you've never been here...
ever since your mother passed.
I knew her spirit wasn't here.
I had no reason to come.
It's your first time
at your mother's resting place,
so it's bad manners
to show up empty-handed.
Let's go inside.
(Hong Mi Jin rests here.)
When you miss her,
you can come here.
Forget it.
She's not here.
Why would I come here?
That's how ordinary people live.
Not because they believe
their spirits actually rest here,
but because they can be comforted
when they miss them so much...
and want to see them again.
(Hong Mi Jin rests here.)
Long ago, you asked me...
if I ever wanted to do
anything else other than this.
I've never thought
of doing anything else...
than living as an exorcist.
It's not that I wanted to do this.
I had to.
I couldn't avoid it.
I thought I didn't have a choice.
But now you do.
You can start thinking now.
Think about what you want to do.
I'm done thinking.
Already?
I want to be an exorcist.
I think I'd do an excellent job.
This is great. You have a dream.
Actually,
I also have something I want to do.
What is it?
It's a secret.
Fine. I was never curious anyway.
- But you are.
- I'm not.
- Do you want to know?
- I'm not curious at all.
You won't be able to sleep.
All right.
How was your visit to your mother?
Since when did you
and In Bum become so close?
Are we not allowed to?
You must be jealous.
Jealous, my foot.
Did you say goodbye to him?
You didn't.
My gosh.
Think about how sad he'll be
if you leave without a word.
It's not like I'm leaving for good.
I don't want to make a big scene
over going on some trip.
Traveling to find your lost power
isn't considered a trip.
You don't even know when you'll return.
You have the weirdest personality.
And you have a knack
for breaking people's hearts.
- What are you doing?
- I've been seeing...
awful lines on my neck recently.
I began to take care of it.
You're looking happy.
- Are you going on a date?
- No.
I've been meaning to ask.
Have you been dating Mr. Jung?
- No?
- No.
You should start going on dates.
It doesn't have to be him.
You barely had any personal time...
because of me until this day.
I don't think you realize this,
but I've enjoyed
a fair share of personal time.
Those years weren't
a devastating sacrifice,
so don't make me sound nice.
Take this.
Use it on your trip.
This is a good time for you
to start preventing wrinkles.
Preventing what?
Thanks, anyway.
Have fun on your date.
It's not a date!
It's not!
(Daebak Realty)
(Temporarily closed)
Why do I feel like crying?
I had fun.
Ms. Hong is awful.
How can she leave without saying goodbye?
She'll be back soon.
She said goodbye to you?
What? You've been
keeping in touch with her?
No, it's not that. But this is...
Ms. Hong.
Take care.
And stay out of trouble.
What are you saying?
Don't talk like you won't ever see us.
I'm going to text you every day.
Don't leave me hanging
after you've read it.
Okay, then.
Go ahead.
I'm really leaving now.
(Daebak Realty)
We should go too.
(1 year later)
As per your request, I've deleted...
all of your daughter's traces
on the Internet.
Including her social media accounts,
web portals, other websites,
as well as records
of her financial transactions.
You have nothing to worry about, ma'am.
Thank you.
If you come across any records
related to your daughter,
please give me a call.
I'll consider this my duty
until everything is gone.
Thank you so much.
Don't mention it, ma'am.
I'm only doing my job.
Goodbye.
(My Soo Jung)
Hey, Soo Jung.
Has the result been announced?
You got in?
Congratulations!
You worked so hard for it.
Tomorrow?
Of course, I'm free.
Okay. I'll see you tomorrow.
Yes!
(Thank you for helping shut down
the redevelopment plan!)
(Temporarily closed)
(Changhwa Restaurant)
(We're open once again.)
This looks scrumptious.
Here's your rice soup.
Are you their son?
Sorry?
Yes.
Hey. I said I'll go.
It's okay. It's not far.
Okay, but let me go.
Someone as old as you
shouldn't be carrying heavy things.
I'll go.
I'll be back. Enjoy your food.
I'm off then.
It must feel great to have
such a reliable son.
What?
He's not reliable at all.
He's still a kid.
Congratulations, Mr. Director.
Congratulations!
- Let me pour you a drink.
- Sure.
Thank you.
Tonight's on me, so drink up.
Why would you treat us?
Because I'll be needing
your help often in the future.
Excuse me.
Please give us your raw tuna special
and sprinkle some gold dust on top.
- Sure.
- I just need kimchi.
Gosh, I hate him.
Congratulations!
Bottoms up!
What about Ji A? Has she called yet?
I'm sure she's doing well.
Thanks to her,
I get to hang out with you. It's great.
I'm happy to spend some time
with you as well.
(Redevelopment Plan Canceled)
(Daebak Realty)
- Hi.
- Why are you here?
You meant "hi," right?
Yes.
Did you get it back?
(Daebak Realty)
Is it true that you guys exorcize
and sell haunted houses?
Yes. I'm glad you're here.
This way, please.
We have coffee,
Solomon's seal tea, and green tea.
Which one would you like?
We'll be asking you a few questions.
It's just a formality that we have.
Have any of your electronic devices
malfunctioned for no reason...
or have there been
repetitive power failures?
Has anyone died
in your building recently...
or has a murder taken place there?
I've secured the area,
and there will be no one nearby.
Good luck tonight.
Like I've said before, this place is full
of historical artifacts.
Please don't break anything.
During our last exorcism,
you broke all kinds of objects.
Compensating for everything
was such a pain.
(Thank you for supporting and watching
Sell Your Haunted House.)
(Sell Your Haunted House)
(Yang Woo Jin played by Jung Soon Won)
(Nam Young Do played by Choi Seung Yoon)
(Cho Hyun Seo played by Seo Jin Won)
(Lee Eun Hye played by Baek Ji Won)
(Kim Byung Ho played by Im Ji Kyu)
(Joo Kyung Hee played by Nam Ki Ae)
(Lee Sung Sil played by Park Ye Young)
(Kim So Min played by Kim Jung Young)
(Yoo Chul Gu played by Yeo Moo Young)
(Yoo Young Soon played by Lee Ju Sil)
(Eun Byeol played by Park Ye Rin)
(Eun Byeol's mom played by Lee Jin Hee)
(Bae Soo Jung played Ji Woo)
(Lee Hyun Ju played by Lee Seo An)
(Ma Kwang Tae played by Park Sung Il)
(Oh Sung Sik played by Kim Dae Gon)
(Chang Hwa's mom played by Baek Hyun Ju)
(Yang Chang Hwa played by Oh Kyung Ju)
(Do Hak Sung played by Ahn Gil Kang)
(Hong Mi Jin played by Baek Eun Hye)
(Heo Ji Chul played by Kang Hong Suk)
(Ju Hwa Jeong played by Kang Mal Geum)
(Oh In Bum played by Jung Yong Hwa)
(Hong Ji A played by Jang Na Ra)