=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 16=
I wish I could be with you not as a god
in the next life.
My birthday banquets
have always been
high-level and high-profile.
You can’t attend the banquet
without precious treasures.
As True God Bai Jue,
this gift from you
might be too trifling.
I won’t have you die.
As long as the Three Realms exist,
you exist.
You are the Chief God of Chaos.
I won’t have you die.
♪Ask for the love of this life♪
♪She turned into ashes♪
♪Life and death♪
♪He protects the Three Realms for her♪
♪Perseverance♪
♪It’s still echoing in ears♪
♪Repeat it again♪
Your Grace...
♪This love is boundless
and will never extinguish♪
Master…
Not as a god in the next life...!
Shanggu!
No!
What time is it? Bai Jue.
Get up quickly!
Didn’t you say
you would teach me magic arts?
How shameless of you saying
that I’m lazy all day.
No!
Unexpectedly, Master Bai Jue
is the real lazy one.
If you still didn’t wake up,
I would spread this news
to the whole God Realm!
Shanggu!
No!
Across the Three Realms!
What do you want to do?
From now on,
I will always stay with you.
I will accompany you to practice,
read,
and drink.
When the weather is clear,
we can go out to fly a kite.
From now on,
I won’t leave you alone anymore.
♪Countless twists and turns
Drifting away for many times♪
♪I can’t help missing you
But I can only hug your back♪
Bai Jue, come here!
♪Write down our whispers♪
What are you doing there?
Play on the swing with me.
Come here!
You promised me to play
on the swing with me today.
How did you teach me?
Walk it like you talk it.
Don’t go back on your word.
Come here!
♪Wait until we meet again♪
♪Exchange a one-second encounter
for a lifetime♪
♪It’s not a pity
if we can meet each other♪
♪I do♪
♪Looking for you at thousands
of days and nights♪
♪Wait until we meet again♪
♪Exchange a one-second encounter
for a lifetime♪
It’s flying! It’s flying!
Look! It’s flying very high!
Look!
♪I am willing to indulge in the past♪
As the Chief God of Chaos,
I was born to
protect the Three Realms.
No matter how much responsibility I have
on my shoulders,
I’m willing to take it.
I will do anything I can
to help you take over the God Realm
as soon as possible.
Someday,
the place you shine,
will be in the name of Shanggu,
the Chief God of Chaos.
♪Pursue you♪
♪For millions of miles♪
Master!
Master, you are finally awake!
It’s windy outside.
The Original Being of you
was badly injured.
Please go back to the hall and rest.
We have been waiting for you
for a long time!
Congratulations on the coming
of the Devil God!
It has been seventy thousand years.
I planned everything.
Finally, I got what I wanted.
Overlord, you’re really wise.
If that day you weren’t able to
tell the secret of the Tribulation
of Chaos earlier than all gods,
today
the one who had sacrificed
for the God Realm would be you.
For the God Realm?
Ridiculous!
I don’t even care about
the Ancestral God.
Why should I die for the God Realm?
Although I was bound and trapped
in the Nether World.
But this is just my plan.
My enemies are not them.
It’s destiny.
As long as the Tribulation of Chaos
is not eliminated,
whoever is the Chief God
will just cage himself.
I don’t know if my old acquaintances
from the God Realm
still remember me.
(Endure the Hardship)
Master Zhiyang.
Is Bai Jue awake?
My master…
wouldn’t allow anyone in or out.
He also said that
he would close the Changyuan Hall.
Alright.
I’ll talk to him.
The looks
are quite similar to Shanggu’s.
Everyone in the God Realm
feels heartbroken about
the death of Shanggu.
But we are True Gods.
We shoulder the responsibility
of the world.
I know that
since you taught Shanggu,
the only things you cared about
are hers.
But now you have watched her
disappear in front of your eyes.
Let alone you,
it’s also hard for me to let it go.
It still hurts when I’m thinking of it.
What I want most is to protect her.
But I pushed her into
everlasting perdition.
Recently,
I’ve often thought of something
in the past.
Tianqi,
you and me.
We were still young at that time.
We did what the Ancestral God
let us do.
Although we couldn’t understand
the meaning behind,
and couldn’t understand
the truth within,
we were confused but very happy.
If you insist on escaping the world,
I won’t persuade you anymore.
I have found out something.
It was Moyu who gave
the Destruction Pestle to Xueying.
Presumably, the Devils had known
the Tribulation of Chaos in advance.
The soldiers of the God Realm
hadn’t recovered
from the Destruction War,
and then we encountered
the Tribulation of Chaos.
If Xuanyi comes here to attack,
all beings of the world
will be in mire and fire.
And the death of Shanggu
will be in vain.
Xuanyi?
Do you still remember the guess
I told you at Mount Lookout?
If Xuanyi knew that
the fate of being the Chief God of Chaos
was to sacrifice for the world,
would he obey the destiny?
This is why Xuanyi fell into the Devils.
He wanted Shanggu to sacrifice
in the Tribulation of Chaos for him.
For that, he was willing to endure
70,000 years of hardships.
Bai Jue.
You are not able to teach
the Chief God you are obsessed with.
Why don’t you give her to me?
Within a thousand years,
I will definitely return you
a Chief God of Chaos.
My proposal
has benefits
to you, to me,
and to all beings in the Three Realms.
If it is really like
what you and I have guessed,
then Shanggu’s death
definitely has something to do
with Xuanyi.
Master!
What happened
that made you so badly injured?
Report to Master.
Xuanyi has led the Devils to break
the barrier of the Nether World.
The guards all died
except for me.
It’s the Bronze Bridge.
The Devils are attacking here.
Master ordered us to leave the God Realm
and go to the Heavenly Realm
to stabilize the situation
in case of contingencies.
In case of contingencies?
Master’s words are very pessimistic.
I’m afraid the battle with the Devils
will have the most hopeless outlook.
If Tianqi hadn’t attempted to
destruct the world,
and the Demons hadn’t counterattacked,
how could our God Realm
have ended up like this?
Sooner or later,
I’ll bring fair back from the Demons.
Master sacrificed herself
in exchange for the stability
of the God Realm.
I will never allow the Devils
to destroy it.
(The Pilgrimage Hall)
Don’t go!
Gu Jun.
Master must have his reason
to give us this order.
We can’t be impulsive.
But the God Realm…
I know.
We are all not afraid to die.
But in case...
Gu Jun,
we must listen to Master’s orders.
Xuanyi chose to attack at this time.
He must have detected
our poor situation.
Your spirit is badly injured.
My cultivation has degenerated.
So what?
I will let him pay for it today.
I have waited for 70,000 years.
Today finally comes!
You two are really righteous.
In order to preserve this God Realm,
you didn’t even take a god
with great spiritual power.
Stop talking rubbish!
You have been planning for 70,000 years
and have known the Tribulation of Chaos
for a long time.
And you deliberately let Shanggu
die for you.
I will never let you go!
So what?
I have cultivated the God power
day and night.
Why should I die
instead of the entire God Realm?
Is it my life
inferior to that of other gods?
Both as the Chief God of Chaos,
you are like a piece of trash
compared with Shanggu.
You are like dried dung!
If we were defeated in this battle,
the God Realm would be overthrown.
All gods and soldiers.
Yes!
Guard the God Realm!
Oh no!
There must be a war in the God Realm.
That God light is like Master Bai Jue’s.
And that black power…
Report to gods.
Please go to the Barrier Gate
to resist quickly.
The Devils are attacking.
The Devils?
No.
After tens of thousands of years,
you still only have this ability.
Listen to my advice.
You two should stop guarding
the God Realm.
How about
delivering the Three Realms
all to me?
I have endured for 70,000 years.
Today I’ll let you see
how poor a god is
and how capable a devil is!
All gods, follow the order
and leave quickly!
The God Realm has difficulties now.
We won’t stand idly by.
All gods were sad and touched
after Shanggu’s death.
If there really is
a Tribulation of Chaos,
it should also be all gods’ tribulation!
For the same reason,
let’s fight together
against the invasion of the Devils.
We won’t leave this time!
All gods, listen! Set the formation!
Oh, no! Overlord!
You froze me
with the Power of the Original Being.
Your spirit will be destroyed
as the end!
I have no regrets
since I met Master Bai Jue in this life.
It’s impossible!
I have survived
the Tribulation of Chaos.
I have already broken the Rules.
I will never lose!
You gathered the power of the gods,
but only to fight like this.
Today I will show you
how they disappear one by one.
I will make this world
without any Master or Hall!
Master is here.
I am in charge of the thunder
and lightning in the Three Realms.
Today I will not allow this devil
to make trouble in the Three Realms!
I am in charge of all disasters
in the Three Realms.
Today I will use my spirit
to help Master in this battle.
Master Bai Jue.
I am in charge of the rain
in the three realms.
I would also like to use my spirit
to help Master in this battle.
A life for a life!
Master!
Hongri has been a Divine Beast for you
for over a hundred thousand years.
Now you want to destroy the Devils.
How can I not help you?
In the future,
I hope Master take good care
of your health...
Hongri!
And take good care of all beings!
God of Four Seasons, together with Gods
of Wind, Rain, Thunder and Lightning,
congratulate Chief God on the succession
of Chief God of Chaos.
God of Stars congratulates Chief God on
the succession of Chief God of Chaos.
I thought
teaching a group of little kids
could make you more gentle.
I didn’t expect you to be the same
after ten thousand years of absence.
Bai Jue?
It’s been over 100,000 years…
This is the first time
you joked with me!
The lives of common people
are too important and I have no choice.
Bai Jue,
I’ll leave
the Three Realms to you.
I promised Shanggu
to protect the God Realm for her.
I made it.
Master said that
the stars in the sky are all gods.
Look.
There are so many stars tonight.
Could it be that the gods are fighting?
Will you and I become stars
in the future?
Master said that
if we practiced hard,
we could become immortals.
Master also said to take us
to the Human Realm to play.
When did it count?
Look, how bright that star is!
(Sixty thousand years later)
I heard from Heavenly Father that
there once was the God Realm
above the Immortal Realm,
named the Shanggu Realm.
It’s a pity that in the Tribulation
of Chaos 60,000 years ago,
the gods of Shanggu Realm
almost all died.
And the Power of Chaos
left by the Chief God
brought the Human Realm here
replacing the exterminated Devil Realm,
the Immortal Realm and the Demon Realm,
and becoming the new Three Realms.
The new Three Realms
should have coexisted amicably.
But because of the Demon God’s
Destruction in the past,
the immortals and demons
quarreled endlessly.
It lasted for 60,000 years.
Now it’s not clear to judge
the right from wrong
and the good from evil.
There is only one Demigod in the
Demon Realm, Sen Jian, the Demon King.
And in the Immortal Realm today,
there are four Gods.
The first three are Gods
left from the Shanggu Realm.
But the origin of the fourth God
started with a famous marriage
in the Heavenly Realm.
How can the Heavenly Palace
be so extravagant?
How many Sacred Beads will it cost?
The King of Heaven is
God Muguang who inherited
the blood of the Gold Dragons.
The Queen of Heaven is the patriarch
of the Phoenix Clan, Goddess Wu Huan.
Extravagance is reasonable.
Have they invited God Gu Jun
from the Qingchi Palace?
When True God Zhiyang
handed over the Immortal Realm
to the Three Gods,
he did not specify who’s in charge.
Qingchi Palace and Heavenly Palace
are separate.
Not to mention
the marriage and divorce
have their destiny.
Just with the temper of God Gun Jun,
can this be held successfully?
Let’s go.
Do you think he will come?
I spoke sincerely in the invitation.
I hope that Gu Jun
can disregard the past grudges.
Hope so.
Today is our wedding day.
Don’t mention him anymore.
Heaven and earth as evidence,
all immortals as witnesses,
the King and Queen
will marry each other.
The Three Realms will be peaceful.
Greetings to God Gu Jun.
Stand up.
Gu Jun.
You are here.
Ling Juan.
Yes.
What can I do for you?
This is the daughter
of the Queen and me.
Her name is Houchi.
How come the Queen…
Even the Gods can’t escape love affairs.
The poorest
is the child in that egg.
You are in charge of every being’s fate.
You do me a favor. Please let me know
what destiny my daughter will have.
Well…
I don’t think it is necessary.
What?
My daughter is not worthy of you
to tell?
I dare not.
Report to Your Majesty.
Report to Master.
The Little Master…
The Little Master will be a God.
This…
How could it be God’s fate?
How come there’s another God?
This…
Ling Juan.
As we all know,
after the God Realm was closed,
there are only three Gods in the world.
You should watch your words.
Report to Your Majesty.
I dare not tell lies.
The Little Master will indeed be a God.
Have you got any objection to this,
Your Highness?
I…
How about Your Majesty?
Okay.
Today all immortals witness this.
My daughter Houchi will be
another God in the future,
with the sun and moon as evidence,
as well as heaven and earth
as witnesses.
Congratulations to God Houchi.
(Houchi)
It took me 40,000 years
to break my shell.
It has been 20,000 years
since my foundation was built.
I have practiced for 60,000 years.
Why am I still a lower immortal?
Your Grace, you’re back from practicing!
You must’ve worked hard, Your Grace.
(Claim No Credit)
Lord Boxuan often said that
it wouldn’t matter if the cultivation
didn’t go well.
As long as Your Grace is happy.
Everything depends on fate.
Today is the same as yesterday.
I have no improvement.
When will my fate come?
Look at you!
You always say the wrong thing.
How about I ask Lord Fengran
not to test your spiritual power today?
No need.
I asked Fengran
to supervise my practice.
Isn’t it just punishment?
I’ve long been used to it.
It’s all my business.
I’m going to find Fengran now.
The sooner I finish the test,
the sooner I’ll be scolded.
Then I can go to bed earlier.
Wu Xu,
look at that!
The barrier of Qilian Mountains
has been opened unexpectedly.
What a rich Spiritual Spring!
The Qingchi Palace’s Spiritual Spring is
said to be the best in the Three Realms.
The rumors are true.
I... I think it’s getting late.
We’d better go back quickly.
Don’t delay the important event of Lord.
What’s the hurry?
There are still a few days
before Lord Donghua’s birthday banquet.
If we drink such rich spring,
our cultivation will definitely increase
by a thousand years.
You’re not tempted at all?
What are you afraid of?
The Qingchi Palace
has long been dilapidated.
Let’s go in quietly
and take it out quickly.
Who can find us out?
But now Lord Fengran is
in charge of the Qingchi Palace.
She has old grudges
with our Zijin Mansion.
So what?
Our Lord Ziyuan
is the most popular person
in the Heavenly Palace.
Even if Fengran meets us,
she has to step back.
Houchi.
I’ll put the harsh words in front today.
You should have taken the exam
a few days ago.
But you told me
that you hadn’t mastered the spells.
You delayed it for three days.
(Fengran)
If you failed again today,
I wouldn’t be soft on you.
Sure. Sure.
I’ll be scolded by you anyway.
I’ve long been used to it.
Houchi.
Still Spell.
- She made it. She made it!
- She made it!
Great!
Your Grace, you made it!
Your Grace, you finally made it!
Not bad.
Another one.
Control Spell.
No, no, no.
I haven’t tried that spell.
You’ll know if you try it.
Gather your spiritual power
and use it on this thing.
Her Grace is so great!
- It’s great!
Not bad.
Your Grace, you finally made it!
Yes.
Your hard work hasn’t been in vain
over the past ten thousand years.
I’ll teach you more powerful spells
tomorrow.
Your Grace.
Did you hear that?
Fengran never lied!
Even she praised you
for practicing well.
Your spiritual power
has really improved!
Yeah, that’s right!
Unbelievable! I made it!
I have practiced for so many years.
Why did I make it only this time?
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪