=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 15=
The Tribulation of Chaos comes,
and the God Realm will collapse.
Only when the Chief God of Chaos
sacrifices her life to the tribulation
can you solve the difficulties
of all beings.
Bastard!
Old man!
You let Shanggu work hard
to learn the Power of Chaos
and inherit the position of Chief God,
is it
just to make her
die for your people?
In your eyes,
is she just a sacrifice?
Master, watch your mouth.
Purple Jade Whip!
Master!
I am not afraid.
Qingtian,
if you have the ability,
pass the God’s punishment on me
and kill me!
Get out!
Master!
I must stop it.
No matter what price I will take,
I will never let Shanggu
inherit the position of Chief God.
I couldn’t protect her
thousands of years ago.
This time,
I won’t let her get hurt at any cost.
Even if it’s you,
I won’t let it happen.
After inheriting the throne of God,
she is going to die
for the common people.
Tianqi.
So this is your difficulty.
So this is why
you’d rather let the common people die
than tell out the secret.
Tianqi.
I said that
one day you would regret it
if you knew about the truth.
If it weren’t you who let her
become the Chief God so soon,
how could she
have a great God power of Chaos
and become a pawn
to save the common people?
How could I be forced
to be of destruction?
You thought you protected her.
But what about the truth?
The truth is that you
forced her into her destiny
step by step
and let her fall into perdition.
It’s you.
You killed her by yourself!
No way.
There must be a way
to resolve the Tribulation of Chaos.
Her life must not
be the only way.
I have already found
the way, haven’t I?
It will be solvable
at the expense of the death
of all beings from Three Realms.
But you!
You ruined her with your own hands!
It’s not the right way.
It definitely won’t be Shanggu’s wish
if we save her by billions of lives.
What else can you do?
There must be another way.
Give me some time.
A hundred years. No.
Ten years.
I must find a way.
I will definitely find a way
to save her.
That’s too late.
The Tribulation of Chaos
will come in two days.
All this is doomed already.
When the Tribulation of Chaos comes
and spiritual power
of the world disappear,
it’ll be the Gods’ end.
Except for her death,
nothing could help.
It turned out that I hurt her
by my own hands.
What’s up?
Just now,
I was watching the stars
at Changyuan Hall.
It suddenly reminded me that
Chief God still owes me
an appointment.
What appointment?
Let’s talk about it after I cultivate
the instruction feather of Chief God.
Haven’t you forgotten
your appointment with me
at the Taoyuan Forest that day?
After you take over
the instruction feather of Chief God,
can you go to Taoyuan Forest with me?
I have something
hiding in my heart for a long time.
I want to tell you there.
Haven’t you forgotten it?
I never forgot the appointment
with you.
But this appointment has long passed.
I come to the Pilgrimage Hall today
to invite Chief God to
our appointment of that day.
No way.
Tomorrow I will become
the Chief God of Chaos,
and give an explanation to the Gods.
Just because you will be
the Chief God of Chaos tomorrow,
I come here today.
I have never wanted anything
in my life.
But my only wish
is that Shanggu who practiced with me
in my Changyuan Hall back then
can accompany me
to the appointment today.
Not tomorrow’s Chief God of Chaos.
Can you?
No.
No way.
What’s wrong with you today?
The Gods have felt stirred by
the cultivation today.
If I stopped abruptly,
it would be too improper.
Wait till I end all this.
I never asked anyone in my life.
I have only one wish.
Just this one wish.
Shanggu,
leave with me.
OK?
(The Tribulation of Chaos comes,
and the God Realm will collapse.)
(Only when the Chief God of Chaos
sacrifices her life to the tribulation)
(can you solve the difficulties
of all beings.)
The Tribulation of Chaos is coming!
Hurry up and report to Master!
Yes!
Master!
Everyone knows that
between heaven and earth,
there will be a tribulation
every 180,000 years.
Only the Chief God can resolve it.
And now the stele means that
Shanggu must sacrifice her spirit
to save the world.
Nonsense!
It’s impossible.
Block the Heaven and Earth Platform
immediately.
No one is allowed in or out.
Master can block
the Heaven and Earth Platform,
but you can’t keep all Gods’ mouths
of the God Realm shut.
The instructions from the Ancestral God
are nothing but the truth.
It is already said
that there is a tribulation.
There must be a tribulation.
If Master Shanggu still
hasn’t shown up yet,
would she want to wait
until the God Realm collapses?
Even if the God Realm were collapsed,
there would still have
my Master and two True Gods.
When is it your turn to talk that much?
Ridiculous!
The God Realm is the God Realm
of all the Gods.
How could your Pilgrimage Hall
have the final say?
Master Zhiyang.
Since all Gods are here,
I thought that
as the tribulation has not come yet,
all Gods should perform our duties
and keep our responsibilities
at the moment.
As for the matter of the resolution,
we still have the True Gods to decide.
We can’t be messed up here
because of this warning.
Report.
Report to Master Zhiyang.
The Tribulation of Chaos
at the Bronze Barrier Gate is spreading!
The Bronze Bridge is collapsing!
I’m afraid the entire God Realm
would collapse
within twenty-four hours!
The Power of Chaos is disintegrating?
Could it be…
This is the Tribulation of Chaos!
The Tribulation of Chaos.
My Master is the Chief God of Chaos.
If her spirit were sacrificed,
who can protect the common people?
The Tribulation of Chaos is coming.
Our God Realm is about
to encounter a catastrophe.
Master Zhiyang, please ask the Chief God
to come out of the Hall
and decide for the common people!
Please ask the Chief God
to come out of the Hall
and decide for the common people!
You guys…
You see.
The God Light is off!
Shanggu is not cultivating
the instruction feather of Chief God!
What can we do now?
What to do?
God of Thunder, what can we do now?
Shanggu must know
that she should be sacrificed
so she escaped from the God Realm.
Nonsense!
How can my Master be such a person?
Then where is she?
She descended the imperial order
to inherit the throne.
But she stops cultivating the instruction feather
of Chief God just at this moment.
If not to escape…
Shut up!
I will definitely bring Shanggu back
and give an explanation to you.
But before everything is found out,
I don’t want to hear any
slanderous words against
the Chief God of Chaos.
Otherwise, remove his Title of God
and banish him from the God Realm.
Master Zhiyang, please forgive me.
I was also in a hurry.
That’s why I dared to speak falsely.
Muguang.
Yes.
You hold my Twin Spear
and fight against the Tribulation of Chaos
with all Gods.
If there is a traitor,
punish him with the crime of treason!
Within twenty-four hours,
I will give an explanation to you all.
Yes.
Master.
I thought
you would take me to Taoyuan Forest.
Since it’s a late appointment,
I can decide where the appointment is.
Be serious!
(Endure the Hardship)
Why should I learn this
primer of babies?
Bai Jue, come here!
Today,
you and I have fun for a day.
I’ll accompany you
to do everything you want.
Master, please.
I remember that
when you were in Changyuan Hall,
I even scolded you.
Zhiyang has burnt
many gadgets of mine when I was little.
Fortunately, Yuemi and Tianqi
prepared a warehouse of them for me.
Now they can feel relieved.
Since then,
they don’t have to worry about me
anymore.
That’s it. I won’t mention these.
If Master Bai Jue loses,
will there be any reward?
To the best of my ability.
I have played in the God Realm
for so many years.
It’s the first time for me to see
a person speaks
with such great assurance.
Come on.
Whoever has more points wins.
Let’s make a deal first.
No cheating with God power.
Come on.
Open it.
Oh, there really are things
that Master Bai Jue is not good at!
Master Bai Jue lost this, right?
I admit the defeat.
What reward do you want?
It’s not difficult.
Do you remember that
when I first entered Changyuan Hall,
you let me do three things.
Yes.
Today,
if you can make me laugh three times,
I will be satisfied
with this appointment
at the Mount Lookout.
What’s the problem?
I said
I’ll do it to the best of my ability.
You silly.
How can you make girls happy
by giving a mountain of pears?
♪Goes with memories♪
How about this?
♪My thoughts in eyes are now
blocked between my eyebrows♪
We will come here next year.
Sure.
♪Dreams are imperfect♪
♪I can’t help missing the past♪
♪What’s in my hand is
what I can’t get over♪
♪How are we destined to meet♪
♪Tide rushes and the moon rises♪
♪The trip takes a thousand years♪
♪Wake up the clouds♪
♪But can’t wake up the helpless love♪
♪It’s dreamlike♪
♪And it’s also aimless♪
♪For one single glance at you♪
♪I don’t regret cultivating myself♪
♪Dreams are imperfect♪
You already knew
that Shanggu should sacrifice her life?
Yes.
What about Tianqi?
Tianqi was the first to know
the warning from
the Tribulation of Chaos.
Everything he did was
for Shanggu.
Just now,
an inscription from the Ancestral God
appeared on the Heaven and Earth Platform.
All Gods knew that
only Shanggu
could resolve the Tribulation of Chaos.
Bai Jue.
She must come back.
Go back?
And sacrifice her life?
Zhiyang.
It shouldn’t be her.
No one knows that the fate
of the Chief God of Chaos
is to sacrifice in exchange for peace.
But no matter how the tribulation
will be resolved,
now the God Realm is in turmoil.
As the Chief God of Chaos,
she must return to the God Realm
to control the overall situation.
What are you doing?
Even if it is God’s will,
I have to go against it.
Zhiyang.
I never beg you for anything.
Only today.
I’m asking it at expense of my life.
I can’t let Shanggu return
to the God Realm.
Once she knows the truth
of the Tribulation of Chaos,
she will definitely inherit the throne
and sacrifice her spirit.
I don’t want to see her in ashes.
What do you want?
I’ll do it for her.
The Tribulation of Chaos
can only be resolved
by the God power of Chaos.
Even if your spirit were destroyed,
and you sacrificed it for Shanggu,
you could just seal it temporarily.
You set stars in the God Realm
day by day.
Here we come to the Heavenly Realm,
and you still take me to see the stars.
Aren’t you tired?
I thought that
as long as you watch the stars with me,
no matter where,
you would like it.
Do you remember
these stars?
Are these…
Back then at Heaven and Earth Platform,
we were looking at the same stars.
Then why
we have to see these stars today?
I thought
you would miss that night.
♪Hold tightly with your warm hand♪
What happened?
Why are you so sweet today?
Are you
miraculously transformed by others?
It’s possible.
Try it out
if you want to know the truth.
How to?
Mount Lookout. Restaurant at Southsea.
You never mentioned them.
And I never asked about them.
♪To have the next life♪
♪When we meet again♪
♪I’ll travel around with you
without hesitation♪
Just do it like this.
♪Listen♪
Do you remember that
set of actions just now?
♪We feel each other♪
♪And get close♪
♪For a little talk♪
♪If it’s such a good time
and such a beautiful scenery♪
♪Hope♪
♪Go with me♪
What are you doing?
There must be something I don’t know!
I can’t inexplicably
lose anyone anymore!
The Tribulation of Chaos comes,
and the God Realm will collapse.
Only when the Chief God of Chaos
sacrifices her life to the tribulation
can you solve the difficulties
of all beings.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods♪
♪And memories last♪
No!
I beg you, Shanggu!
♪No matter what♪
♪Years have passed♪
I have never wanted anything
in my life.
But my only wish
is that Shanggu who practiced with me
in my Changyuan Hall back then
can accompany me
to the appointment today.
♪Staying away♪
Not tomorrow’s Chief God of Chaos.
This is my responsibility
as the Chief God.
I have to protect the world.
This is what you taught me.
I don’t want you to do this.
Do not go.
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
As long as the Three Realms are here
and the mountains and rivers are here,
I will be here,
OK?
You should say that we are a good match.
We should buy a pair
of mandarin duck lamps.
Shanggu,
what are you going to do?
Do what I wanted to do.
♪Maybe we part because
we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds♪
♪And rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪In the future♪
It’s been half a day.
Why doesn’t Master Zhiyang come back?
I just went to Changyuan Hall
to invite Master Bai Jue.
He was also missing.
Seeing the situation so bad,
could these Masters leave us
and run away?
Nonsense!
Our God Realm was almost destroyed
at the Great War
between God Realm and Devils.
Master Zhiyang and Master Bai Jue
led the charge.
Whenever did they abandon our God Realm?
If you, disaster god,
spoke arrogantly again,
don’t blame me for being impolite!
I’m just talking.
The tribulation is so powerful
just at the beginning.
The God Realm is going to be ruined.
What could we do?
The Master has not come back yet.
What should we do now?
Set the array!
Everyone, work together.
Resist it together!
Master.
Muguang.
You did very well.
Master.
Is there any news
about the Chief God and Master Bai Jue?
Do not worry.
They will be back.
Master Zhiyang.
When will Her Grace and Master Bai Jue
come back?
The God Realm would be gone
if they didn’t return.
Shut up!
Shanggu.
Why are you here? Where’s Bai Jue?
Thousands of years ago,
you protected me.
Thousands of years later,
you still did it.
Zhiyang.
I am no longer that Shanggu back then.
Since the Ancestral God made the epoch,
the God Realm has been stable
for hundreds of thousands of years.
The catastrophes we had been through
were a lot more than this.
I never participated in your past.
But right now,
we have to face it together.
Just take it as God’s
first trial for me
after inheriting the Chief God of Chaos.
Master is going to cultivate
the instruction feather of Chief God.
Shanggu!
Master!
We have always been together
to fight against the catastrophe
of our God Realm.
We never assign responsibility
to one person!
Please don’t be instructed by one warning
from the Ancestral God!
You don’t have to sacrifice your life!
Gu Jun is right!
Now the God Realm
suffers this catastrophe.
We should work together
and bridge over
the Tribulation of Chaos.
Thank you all.
My life is a life.
The lives of all common people
are also lives.
This is the destiny,
though I really don’t agree with it.
But if today,
we must sacrifice one person’s life
in exchange for
all common people’s peace,
no one would be more suitable than me.
I will cultivate the instruction feather
of Chief God again
and eliminate the Tribulation of Chaos.
Master, do not!
Didn’t you just say
that we should face it together?
I am the Chief God of Chaos.
Saving the common people
is my duty.
If you
stood in my position here,
how would you choose?
Shanggu.
You really grew up.
All Gods. Follow her orders.
Protect the Chief God!
The position of Heaven.
Come on, Gods of Seasons!
The position of Earth.
Come on, Gods of Weather!
Overlord.
Shanggu is in
the Heaven and Earth Platform
cultivating
the instruction feather of Chief God.
I believe it will be completed soon.
I have waited for 70,000 years.
Today finally comes!
Back then Qingtian
told me about the good news
that Tribulation of Chaos
would come.
But he wanted me to sacrifice to
save the entire God Realm.
Looking at the entire God Realm,
why should I die for them?
However, because of this, Qingtian
thought that
I wasn’t suitable for the position
of the Chief God of the Three Realms.
Today I’ll take a good look at
how those hypocrites
will choose.
No!
I beg you, Shanggu!
This is my responsibility
as the Chief God.
I have to protect the world.
Bai Jue.
Don’t worry.
I will be a qualified Chief God
and bring peace and tranquility
to the God Realm.
Master!
Shanggu!
Master Bai Jue!
Bai Jue.
You can’t die for her!
No way!
Destruction Pestle?!
How dare you collude with the Devils!
I’ll settle accounts with you later!
Master!
Shanggu.
Don’t!
Bai Jue.
Just go.
I don’t want to look at you
die for my own fate innocently
one by one.
I know.
I know it better than anyone.
You can be responsible
for the lives of common people,
and you’re able to take the responsibility
of being the Chief God.
I have never made any mistake
in my life.
I regret only one thing
so far.
It was me who forced you
to become the Chief God.
I pushed you
into this perdition.
♪Ten thousand years of ups and downs
are just in a moment♪
Actually, I just want to ask you if
that mountain of pears
and the sky full of stars
you gave me yesterday
are true?
I gave them to you with my whole heart.
You also said that
you wanted to listen to music with me,
read books with me,
ride horse with me,
and be with me day by day
forever.
Did you lie to me?
They are all true.
Come back now.
It would be all good
if I was born a few years earlier.
If I met you 70,000 years ago,
grew up with you,
then
we would have 70,000 years
get along with each other.
I…
♪Perseverance♪
Unfortunately,
God’s life is too long.
I never cherished it.
Don’t…
The lives of common people
are too important.
I have no choice.
Shanggu.
Bai Jue.
I’ll leave the Three Realms
to you.
No!
No way!
Shanggu!
Shanggu, come back!
I’m begging you!
♪Snow and smoke are in the dusk♪
♪Ask for the love of this life♪
Shanggu!
♪She turned into ashes♪
♪Life and death♪
Shanggu.
♪He protects the Three Realms for her♪
I wish I could be with you
not as a god
in the next life.
♪Repeat it again♪
♪This love is boundless
and never extinguished♪
I won’t let you die!
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪