♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
From today onward, Tang San will be recognized
as the crown prince's teacher,
with the title Lan Hao.
Greetings, King of Lan Hao!
From now on, this is the symbol of your status.
If the Peerless Flexible Armor is a magical item,
then this Vast Sea and Universe Shield
is the most magical of them all.
After this departure,
who knows when we'll see them again?
They will go towards the west
to Tian Dou Empire's western-most sea,
then switch into boats
to get to Haishen Island.
[Episode 156]
Chief Tang.
We are five li away from the next village.
Shall we crash in this village tonight?
Something's wrong.
There's no one in the field at all.
Maybe they all went home?
They even left their farming tools in the field.
That is strange.
Brother San.
I'll go take a look.
Be careful.
It was brightly lit the entire way
but there wasn't any sound.
Help me!
What happened? What's wrong?
Don't worry, I will protect you.
Stop!
Xiang!
Rong Rong.
Zhu Qing.
You guys stay
and help me take care of Wu.
Okay.
The first skill of Vast Sea and Universe Shield,
Vast Sea Protection.
Ao.
Protect them.
Be careful.
Brother Dai.
Let's go.
Wolf thieves.
It's surprising there should be wolf thieves
in Tian Dou Empire too!
Wolf thieves?
Are they human?
They are a mix of humans
and the soul beast Gale Devil Wolf,
a kind of monster that is half wolf and half human.
Feng Xiao Tian's martial soul,
Double-headed Gale Devil Wolf,
is the mutant and stronger version of the Gale Devil Wolf.
That means
wolf thieves have
both the physique and talent of Gale Devil Wolf
and part of the intelligence of humans.
That's right.
They are born blood-thirsty
and enjoy hunting humans as food.
Once attacked, they'll be relentless till death,
making them extremely hard to deal with.
500 wolf thieves
can defeat an army of over ten thousand soldiers.
It's difficult for us to confront
this many wolf thieves.
What should we do?
Do it!
Your opponent is over here!
Fourth Soul Skill,
White Tiger Meteor Strike!
Brother San!
Xiang.
Are you hurt?
I'm alright.
Xiang.
You take the villagers and escape.
We will take care of the rest.
Everyone, follow me!
These wolf thieves are only some followers.
There has to be a leader in this group.
As long as we catch the leader,
the rest of them will disperse.
The wolf leader isn't here.
I need to trust them.
Brother Dai, be careful!
Fatty.
Attack from mid-air!
Okay!
First Soul Skill,
Phoenix Firing Line!
Darn it!
Is it gonna stop or what?!
We're surrounded.
What should we do, San?
[Soul Land]
You go first.
I will stall them!
Do you still not gonna stop?
Xiang!
Darn it.
He is the leader of the wolf thieves.
We need to take care of him first.
No way.
He still has Xiang.
If you want this woman to live,
come get her with your lives.
No!
San.
What should we do?
We agree to your conditions.
No!
Fatty.
Take care of Xiang.
Soul bone skill of Soft Bone Rabbit,
Invincible Golden Shield!
Act according to the plan.
What?
Tiger Wiping Skill!
Purple God Light!
Xiang.
I will protect you!
You're asking for your death!
This state is...
Fanatic!
What should we do?
Leave it to me.
You guys step back now.
You destroyed them all in an instant.
Brother San, you're so powerful!
San.
What move did you use?
Brother San.
Look. What is that?
It's a soul bone.
Brother Dai.
This soul bone is yours.
Amongst us Seven Devils,
you're the only one without one.
But
Wu doesn't have one either.
Wu doesn't need one right now.
Brother Dai.
Don't reject it.
If I guessed correctly,
the skill that this soul bone gives
is possibly Berserker.
It will be very useful for you.
Brother San.
I should check on the villagers.
I'll go with you.
Go ahead.
I'll stay here.
This way.
What are you doing?
Please help us here.
I'm coming.
Xiang.
Anything else?
Goodbye.
Thank you! Have a safe trip!
Ma Hong Jun.
If you weren't here,
I would probably be dead by now.
Thank you.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 160 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1501 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2418]
[Total scene: 59574]
[Total CGI: 27799]
[Total plan of action scene: 12408]
[Total scene model: nearly 557]
[Total character model: nearly 1011]
[Total props model: 13384]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
♪ I'm faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods ♪
♪ Who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching ♪
♪ Any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven't told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
Brother San!
Ma Hong Jun, he is...!
[Soul Land]
[10 AM every Saturday]