♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
=The Eternal Love S3=
=Episode 19=
For what reason was Prince Consort
on forbidden grounds?
I'm not sure.
Perhaps my Prince Consort
got lost.
You…
Where did you get this dagger from?
Why? Prince Consort
must've accidentally dropped this dagger.
I'm sure Second Princess
knows what the characters on this dagger mean.
I don't.
No worries if you don't.
Your Highness, just hurry up and make a decision.
What should I do?
Every minute that I waste could result in
Cheng Cheng being in a more dangerous situation.
But I don't even know
if this weirdo is bluffing or not.
Please take your time, Second Princess.
Either way,
we're not in a hurry.
I'm not in a hurry.
No.
I can't gamble with Cheng Cheng's life.
I'll marry him
for Cheng Cheng's sake.
This is not infidelity.
I'll marry him.
And the lost item goes back to its rightful owner.
Congratulations, Second Princess.
You now have a main prince consort.
Xuan Ling.
Who is exactly is Empress?
If I hadn't lost my memories,
maybe I could find out more.
Got to find a way out first.
If the embers move,
that means there's wind from that direction,
where there is wind, there is a way out.
There's wind.
This way.
Why are your hands shaking?
I've been copying writings for too long.
No need to worry,
Your Majesty.
Your hands were fine when you were making tea,
but they're shaking now.
Perhaps, you cannot
bend over?
I've been sitting for too long due to praying.
It's no big deal.
Recently,
there has been a lot of commotion in the palace.
Should I perhaps give those
with ulterior motives a warning?
What do you think?
I'm merely a man.
I'd never dare to postulate
what Your Majesty is thinking of.
If I let you speak, you should just speak!
Official Xiao is a highly proficient fighter,
so regular assassins pose no threat.
I was very impressed
by your martial arts
and combat skills
at the training grounds before.
Your Majesty, you think too highly of me.
How about you
stand guard for me tonight?
Such great responsibility...
You don't want to do it?
Such great responsibility,
I'm afraid that I might make mistakes
and disappoint Your Majesty.
I'm not even afraid.
What are you afraid of?
I humbly accept the order.
Where are you going?
It is inappropriate
for a man and a woman to be
in a room together, alone.
I will guard the doors.
Your Majesty.
As soon as Second Princess heard
that Eighth Young Master has been injured,
she agreed to the peace-making marriage.
Your Majesty, if you want someone,
there is no need to do it in such roundabout ways.
Couldn't you just find some reason
and take him in as part of your harem?
Power cannot bring me true love.
Even then,
if the heart is not broken,
no new love can heal it.
But Your Majesty,
you mustn't forget about the taboos of your illness.
Having too affectionate feelings can hurt you.
Besides, he went to investigate
Altar of Souls in the middle of the night.
He seems to have some ulterior motive.
We must be wary.
Say,
why did he do so?
Altar of Souls is a forbidden place in the palace.
Since he already coveted power above all,
it is not strange that he went to investigate it.
The point is
who is he investigating it for?
Now that he has turned his back against Mo Yuan Long.
Do you mean it's Second Princess?
Second Princess's odd actions
have been going on for quite some time now.
I've also found
that there's a strange connection
between Second Princess
and the Soul-guarding Bead.
Yesterday, I saw
that Her Highness approached
the Soul-guarding Bead.
I felt a commotion from the Soul-guarding Bead
and Her Highness was covered
by a sudden white light.
Why did you only tell me now?
I felt that it was very strange indeed,
but I had no concrete evidence.
It was only a feeling.
If what you speak of is true,
then perhaps
it will be of great help to our grand plan.
Today is the day
she marries her new prince consort.
You know what to do, right?
Understood, Your Majesty.
Tan.
You can't avoid
going to the newlywed chamber forever...
You have to talk to Prince Consort.
If Prince Consort
were to speak poorly of you in front of Her Majesty,
more punishments will come your way.
I'm busy.
Second Princess!
Fourteenth!
Fourteenth.
How's your Eighth Brother?
Is he alright?
Did Her Majesty
force him to do things he didn't want to?
Hurry, speak up.
Don't you talk a lot normally?
Eighth Brother...
What?
Eighth Brother went to
Her Majesty's bedchamber last night
and hasn't come back yet.
I heard Her Majesty
gifted Eighth Brother with lots of
new clothing and gifts.
Is that true?
Was it against his will?
It probably...
wasn't...
Mo Lian Cheng, you bastard!
I had to marry another man to protect you
and you went off to the palace
to be all lovey-dovey with Her Majesty.
You freaking bastard!
The head of the palace guards, Official Xiao,
has come to congratulate you.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
Her Majesty hereby gifts you a pair of golden locks,
a pair of jade ware,
wishing Your Highness
and Prince Consort a happy marriage.
I do thank Her Majesty.
Jing Xin,
let's go out for a walk.
Second Princess, please wait.
By Her Majesty's order,
to ensure the continuation of the royal bloodline,
Second Princess,
please remain in Prince Consort's chamber tonight.
The newlywed chamber is this way.
Well, you are quite familiar
with the layout of my residence, aren't you?
I want to go change into sexier clothing,
can I not?
I will wait for Your Highness quietly
outside the room.
Who designed this room?
So red, so out of style.
Take everything down!
Nothing is going right today.
Although Cheng Cheng is safe for now,
Her Majesty,
despite knowing he entered forbidden grounds,
did not punish him
after she called him to her bedchamber.
She even gifted him gifts.
Tan.
Prince Consort is very intelligent.
He will for sure find a way out of the situation.
Jing Xin,
everyone knows what Her Majesty
is thinking about.
It's not something one can
get out of with persuasion alone.
Then even if so...
Even if so,
Prince Consort was forced.
That's right.
He was forced.
I'm not mad at him.
I'm not mad at him at all.
That's right.
If I get upset, I lose.
Even if
Her Majesty kept him in her bedchamber
and gifted him gifts,
can't he just reject her for once?
I'm so mad right now.
Just wait till he comes back.
Don't get angry. Don't get angry.
Second Princess.
All of you, get out!
I'm here diligently keeping my chastity
and he's there flirting with others.
An eye for an eye
and a tooth for...
Well, I can't.
Not all men are like him.
You barging in like that
is against proper etiquette, isn't it?
When I thought
that perhaps I can help
solve Your Highness's problem,
I couldn't care about any etiquette.
Don't go.
Jing Xin.
Don't you dare...
You...
Come back.
You must've heard me wrong.
I'm absolutely fine.
There are no problems for you to solve.
That's good then.
You should be enjoying yourself
on your wedding night.
Even though you've saved me before,
I only think of you as a comrade.
What are you doing?
Don't come any closer!
Tonight,
I'm staying for sure.
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
Let go!
Official Xiao.
Her Majesty knows that standing guard at night
must've been hard work for Eighth Young Master,
so Her Majesty has gifted you some tonic
that will be delivered to your residence later.
How can standing guard at night
for Her Majesty be called hard work?
I heard
that heavy rain has suddenly hit the south,
alleviating the drought.
It would seem that the praying has worked,
Her Majesty's grace has touched the heavens.
And recently,
the situation in the palace has become tense,
Second Princess's Residence
must require managing.
Eighth Young Master, would you like to return?
I am afraid
that the residence will be a mess,
which would damage the royal family's reputation.
Her Majesty has agreed.
I
thank Her Majesty.
Actually, these days,
Her Majesty has been keeping you
at the palace for another reason.
Things at Second Princess's Residence
have been a little complicated.
Last night,
a new prince consort married into the residence.
Prince consort?
Hurry back to greet Prince Consort.
This way, Second Princess can stop worrying.
There's no need to worry, Official Xiao.
If it was Princess's decision,
I
will certainly respect it.
(Mo Residence)
Father.
Have you heard
that Second Princess married for
peace-making last night?
I have faced the one who came
for peace-making marriage, Yun Xiu, in battle.
He is quite cunning.
This peace-marriage
may not be as simple as it seems.
The peace-making marriage was sudden,
Her Majesty may have other reasons.
It would be best to just wait and see.
But if something is really off with Yun Xiu,
not only Eighth Brother
and the Mo family will be implicated,
the entire Dongyue may be threatened.
The situation is still unclear,
we must not act rashly.
I must investigate.
I will only act
after I find evidence.
At a time like this,
you must be even more careful.
Don't worry, Father. I understand.
Her Majesty's move this time,
is it to balance the power
or does she have other intentions?
To congratulate Your Highness on
marrying a new prince consort,
I have prepared a small gift
as a token of my congratulations.
General, you are too kind.
It seems Prince Consort is too used to
fighting on the battlefield.
Since you have come to Dongyue,
you must abide by Dongyue's rules,
as to not implicate Princess in the future.
He had just arrived,
so he is unfamiliar with everything.
But
men who do not bother with trifle details
are the most charismatic.
As such,
how about let my subordinates bring these gifts
into Prince Consort's chambers
according to Dongyue's rules,
as to not have mistakes happen?
General, do you care about rules
or are you suspicious of me?
I am just trying to be considerate,
how did it turn into suspicion?
General, you mean to be considerate.
However,
if those who like to gossip
turn this into that you lust after Prince Consort,
making excuses to barge into his boudoir,
wouldn't that be terrible?
I do not lust after men,
how is it possible that...
So rumours like that must not exist.
Prince Consort is indeed
striking
and easy to fall for.
I also believe
that you just misspoke.
It is impossible that you
have any improper intentions.
Second Princess, you repeatedly spoke up for him,
it seems that you do like him.
I must remind Your Highness,
time will reveal a person's heart,
be careful to not trust the wrong man.
This is not the borders,
why are you still so aggressive towards Yun Xiu?
You know the reason better than I do.
Your Highness, please allow me
to bring the gifts inside.
But
barging into a man's boudoir
is indeed improper.
General, if you
are really suspicious of Yun Xiu,
why don't you stay over
at my residence for a while?
If you
really do find something,
I'm certain neither Her Majesty nor I
will be lenient.
Your Highness, since you say so,
I will do as you say.
Of course.
Jing Xin,
please arrange for General's stay.
Okay.
General Mo,
please come with me.
(Princess's Residence)
What happened?
The new prince consort,
with a thud,
pushed the door open,
picked Her Highness up
and headed towards the bed.
Who wouldn't love such a man?
No wonder
Princess likes him more
compared to the previous two.
Bold of you to gossip about the master of this house.
Are you seeking death?
Forgive us, Prince Consort. We have made a mistake.
Where is Princess?
Her Highness is
in the new prince consort's chamber.
Prince Consort.
What is it?
Princess said
no one is to disturb her
when she's in Main Prince Consort's chamber.
Young Master,
do you think
Princess may have run into
some unspeakable difficulties?
Check it out for me.
If you hear anything,
report to me anytime.
Understood.
You look so beautiful today.
Since when did Princess
learn to be shy?
You're not giving me an explanation on
why you stayed over at your ex-girlfriend's
and you still appear so righteous?
Which girl wouldn't be shy
when they're together with the person they like?
Is that all
you wanted to tell me?
I should be the one
asking Your Highness that.
Still so stubborn.
You've already been back for a while.
Why haven't you greeted Main Prince Consort?
Greetings
should be done in the morning.
Now that the morning has passed,
it would be disrespectful to do my greetings.
A load of rubbish, all excuses!
Why,
Your Highness, do you want me to show disrespect
to Main Prince Consort
on my first day?
Your Highness,
don't get angry.
In any case,
we'll have more opportunities in the future.
You're right, Prince Consort.
Next time, once it reaches the morning,
you will need to go and greet Yun Xiu.
Let's go.
Princess, Prince Consort.
Young Master, Young Master.
Previously,
General Feng Yang and Prince Consort
had a confrontation.
General thinks that he's suspicious.
In order to calm things down,
Princess arranged for her to stay
in the guest room of our residence.
Let's go take a look.
Feng Yang.
Eighth Brother.
Our situation now
is what you get for trying to oust Eldest Brother.
Since you're willing to stay at the residence,
I'm sure you have the same thoughts as me.
There has been foul play
in this peace-making marriage.
That's what I want to investigate,
as long as you don't cause trouble.
As a woman,
it'll be difficult for you to enter a man's boudoir.
But I
can help you.
Under what conditions?
Tell me
what kind of person Yun Xiu is.
How will men be able to understand
what happens on the battlefield?
Why don't you try?
Although Yun Xiu is a man,
he was awarded the rank of a general
because he is of noble descent.
He has been guarding the border
between Dongyue and West Yue.
The situation suddenly got tense last year,
and he deliberately ordered
for the troops to draw back.
Tell me,
why do you think he did that?
The Empty City stratagem.
When the situation escalated,
the armies of both sides were in a deadlock,
he deliberately sent soldiers to negotiate.
Why was that?
A fake surrender.
Yun Xiu is full of tricks.
He even tried to launch sneak attacks at night.
Thankfully my army was well-prepared
and we were victorious.
Therefore,
this peace-making marriage
is definitely not simple.
I'll find an opportunity
to search his room
and find some leads.
Be careful.
Where is she?
Prince Consort.
Where's Second Princess?
She should be
in Main Prince Consort's chamber.
I will take my leave.
Spending the night in the imperial bedchamber...
I'll give you a taste of how I felt.
Upsetting you like this
isn't considered going overboard, right?
♪The sound of the waves are ever so gentle♪
♪The blurry images hidden
in my memory become clear♪
♪Why did you give me all the unhappiness there is♪
♪Standing by the wind alone♪
♪The sky is getting dark,
my memories are going crazy♪
♪Who did the moonlight become gentle for♪
♪Tossing and turning at night,
my eyes are hazy when dawn breaks♪
♪Who did I give my all to♪
I just need an explanation,
and I'll believe you a billion times.
But you won't even say a word.
And it seems like
you're intentionally out to upset me.
♪That's your truest and most hidden nature♪
♪Let me escape your relentless control♪
(Princess's Residence)
Secondary Prince Consort, why are you
barging into my room?
Attacking me without first
seeking an explanation,
is that how Xiyue taught you to behave?
Is sneaking around
a habit of Dongyue's men?
Why are you fighting so early in the morning?
Yun Xiu's skills
are pretty awesome though.
Princess,
ask him
what he was trying to do,
breaking into my room early in the morning.
I felt apologetic for offending
Prince Consort yesterday.
I came to clean Prince Consort's room
to make up for it.
But Prince Consort attacked me
without first figuring out the situation.
So I ended up fighting with Prince Consort.
I see.
So you wanted to give expiation.
I have a good idea.
Don't you have some nice things from your dowry
that you can give to Prince Consort
to prepare?
Let Yun Xiu teach you how to prepare lunch
and make
Xiyue nut cake
to make up
for your mistake.
Okay.
Speed things up.
Put those
walnuts, dates
raisins and Chinese wolfberries all in.
Move faster.
Princess.
Have a taste.
This aroma
is just soul-stirring.
This Xiyue nut cake
looks sweet, soft, glutinous,
smells and tastes delicious.
It is worthy to be
on "A Bite of Xiyue".
["A Bite of China" is a documentary on Chinese cuisine]
Can "soul-stirring" be used
to describe aroma?
Look at you.
Your actions are chaotic,
you're unfamiliar with the procedures,
and your service is terrible.
I think you are
on the verge of being repudiated.
Yun Xiu.
Feed me.
You...
What?
I'm afraid Your Highness will choke to death.
Are you feeding a cow?
Princess.
It's time for me to bring General Mo her lunch.
Great timing.
Yun Xiu,
bring her the nut cake
that you made yourself.
Okay.
Didn't I make it?
Princess and I taught you how.
You...
He seems
very satisfied with the way you're doing things.
Yun Xiu and I are of one mind,
of course he's satisfied.
I'm saying
that compared to staying here,
he wants to go find Feng Yang more.
Stop trying to change the topic.
Jing Xin. Jing Xin.
What are you doing?
Comparing sizes.
I wouldn't want you and Prince Consort
to both choke to death.
Lord of Jealousy
turned green-eyed all of a sudden.
You...
I just made these. Have a taste.
Prince Consort, you are very skilled at cooking,
but I'm not hungry right now.
General, you needn't be so impatient.
I just didn't want to trouble you,
I had no other intentions.
Use the cloth.
This is to tell me that he didn't
put poison in them.
Innocent on the outside,
he must have ulterior motives.
He's coming, he's coming.
Here.
How is it? Does it taste good?
Don't move.
You got something on your face,
let me get it for you.
Your Highness, when do you start liking
hairy men?
I've completely forgotten about that.
Love can really
change a person quietly.
Stand by.
Serve us tea.
Here, Yun Xiu,
have some more.
Have an orange.
- I'll peel it for you. I'll peel it.
- I'll do it.
- Let me.
When did the rules change?
The concubine shouldn't eat
at the same table as us to begin with.
Before,
I spoiled you too much.
Issuing an order in the morning
and rescinding it in the evening,
it's unconvincing.
Fine.
What do you think, Main Prince Consort?
What do you think?
Excellent.
This way,
no one disagrees.
Yun Xiu.
What Yun Xiu feeds me
tastes so good.
Are you not hungry?
If you're not,
practice your swordsmanship outside.
Okay.
I'll practice with you.
When you have an opponent,
you can test your true powers.
That depends on whether
you're worthy of being my opponent.
Why aren't you attacking?
I don't want to hurt you.
No need to worry.
You think too much.
Did you let him
train with Mo Feng Yang on purpose?
No.
Aren't you staying over at Yun Xiu's?
What are you doing in Snow Court?
No hurry.
Regardless of what happens,
Yun Xiu will wait for me.
Why do you keep
trying to upset me?
You're allowed to be unwilling to leave
the imperial bedchamber,
but I'm not allowed to do PDA?
I was trapped in the palace,
I couldn't decide my own actions.
Where did the "unwilling to leave" come from?
Not being able to decide your own actions
allows you to stay over at Her Majesty's
bedchamber for the entire night?
Why did Her Majesty gift you so many things
while you did nothing?
So this is the reason
you've been trying to upset me on purpose.
Then everything with Yun Xiu
has all been an act?
That's not why.
Yun Xiu and I have a bond as strong as gold.
It's not because of this?
Then it's because
I didn't give you half
of what Her Majesty gifted me.
Who cares about your shitty gifts?
Jing Xin's idea is terrible.
Not telling her the truth isn't a bad idea.
This way, I won't wake a sleeping wolf.
I'll explain everything
once I find out all
about Yun Xiu's secrets.
Also,
she looks quite cute
when she's jealous.
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪A flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part,
no matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part,
no matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪