=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 41=
Thank you for coming
for old times’ sake.
Just leave.
I won’t.
I’ll get you out.
No one can harm you.
Not even my mother!
Go now!
Being able to see you before I die,
I have no more regrets.
Fengran,
I found out who you are
back in the Parasol Forest.
I thought
as long as I stayed away from you,
you’d be safe from my mother.
But I was wrong.
I should’ve told everything to Father.
That way,
Mother wouldn’t do anything to you.
It was all my fault!
Fengran!
Go…
Fengran! Fengran!
Fengran!
I lied to you back in Dibei Town.
I love you,
and only you.
I already knew that.
Fengran,
could you give me one more chance?
Fengran! Fengran! Fengran!
Only a True God
deserves such a grand wedding.
It’s beyond splendid!
In the year 63421
of post ancient calendar,
on June 5th,
True God Bai Jue and
Princess Jingzhao are getting married.
Please welcome them.
Master,
this is our big day.
Aren’t you happy?
We both know the truth.
Why bother putting on a show?
Look, how beautiful that is!
What a perfect couple!
Get Houchi out.
You went there regardless.
Houchi.
Goddess Houchi!
Qingmu,
how could you marry her?
Have you forgotten about
our promise?
I’ll say this one more time.
I’m not Qingmu.
Liar!
These fireflies
recognize Qingmu’s scent.
His spiritual sense
must still be in your body.
Also, I know for a fact
that you still remember me.
I’ve learned everything.
That you and Boxuan...
Enough!
You can deny all you want,
but I know you’re him.
Nothing can change that.
I’ve made it clear
that no one
in the Three Realms
shall bring up
my previous identity again.
I’ve left
the past behind.
That’s not up to you.
Here’s something you should know.
I’m pregnant...
Goddess Houchi,
honestly,
what you had with Qingmu
is as weeny as those fireflies.
Life and death
are predestined.
You can’t change anything.
All I want to hear from you
is that Qingmu is still alive.
He didn’t die,
did he?
He’s just become another man
who doesn’t
love me
but...
My Spiritual Strength
doesn’t belong to anyone else.
Stop pestering me!
You’re so eager to get rid of me
that you’re crushing the past
between Qingmu and me.
Is Master Shanggu
aware of what you’re doing?
So this is a True God.
All patronizing
and heartless.
Whatever.
Anyway,
I’m marrying Jingzhao.
You’d better leave
with dignity.
He doesn’t love you at all.
He’s using you.
Are you sure
that you’re going to marry him?
Houchi,
you’re jealous, aren’t you?
Finally,
you’re tasting what I once tasted.
This time, I’m marrying my love
while you’re abandoned.
You love him?
Because he has Qingmu’s face
or he’s powerful?
Or neither?
You simply hate to lose,
especially
to someone you’ll never win.
How dare you!
That’s fierce!
I still think something is missing.
What is it?
Let me.
Qingmu.
Stop.
Master,
Houchi is disrespectful and impertinent.
Shouldn’t she be punished?
Do not push the envelope!
Why do you seem outraged?
Did I do anything unforgivable?
No one was as impartial as you
in the God Realm.
Father.
Sorry, I’m late.
Or none of this would’ve happened.
My daughter
is of noble birth.
What did she do wrong
that you tortured her like that?
That was far from torture.
Disrespecting a True God
is a capital crime.
Who are you
to interrupt me?
Enough, Gu Jun!
How dare you
sabotage Master’s wedding!
100 years ago,
Houchi and Qingmu were a couple.
But it seems
that my awakening
did set them apart.
So
what Houchi said and did just now
are understandable.
Take her back
and talk to her nicely.
Don’t let her come to me
because of Qingmu again.
Houchi,
let’s go home.
Since Qingmu has become part of you,
you should take care of
his unfinished business.
What is that?
Divorce me in public
in presence of the immortals.
In the name of Qingmu?
Do it,
or I won’t leave.
Then you and Jingzhao
can’t proceed with your wedding.
That’s...
Houchi,
Master has been lenient enough.
Don’t push it.
If there’s one thing
I learned from True God Shanggu
60,000 years ago,
that is,
justice must be upheld
in the world.
Master Bai Jue,
Houchi’s request is fair.
It’s only right to put an end
to everything between you two.
Will you let me go
if I give you the divorce letter?
Yes.
I’m officially cutting all ties
with Houchi right here and now
witnessed by all the immortals present.
♪Write down our whispers♪
We won’t see each other
ever again
in this life or the next
in all Three Realms.
♪I will be the shadow in your eyes♪
♪I’m willing to♪
♪Look for you at thousands of
days and nights♪
(Divorce Letter)
♪Wait until we meet again♪
I’ll let go of
what happened earlier.
From now on,
if anyone dares to hurt or insult her,
whoever that is,
even if it’s a True God,
I’ll fight back for her
at the cost of my life!
♪Dizzy the smile♪
♪How much luck do I need
to get myself♪
♪Be always stuck in your heart♪
♪In your heart♪
♪Pursue you♪
♪For millions of miles♪
Wu Huan,
Master has let us go.
How dare you stop us!
Houchi not only offended him,
but also the Heavenly Palace.
He’s tolerant enough
to forgive her
but the Heavenly Palace has rules
that can’t be disregarded.
Houchi must be severely punished.
Or if others follow suit,
how should we lead immortals
and discipline the lower realm?
The Heavenly Palace
is never my concern!
I’ve never seen anyone
more shameless than you.
Tianqi,
shouldn’t you be in the Demon Realm?
What are you doing here?
Bai Jue,
we’ve known each other
for hundreds of thousands of years.
How could I
skip your wedding?
Oh, and,
stop calling me Tianqi.
Right now,
my name is Jingyuan.
You haven’t regained your power.
You aren’t my match.
I’m not in the mood for a fight.
You’d better leave.
I will
after I stop your wedding.
Are you here to stop me?
Of course.
Cancel it,
and I won’t interfere
in any of your business again.
What if I don’t?
If not,
then you’re a liar
and a jerk.
Demon God,
you’ve helped Houchi
and the Qingchi Palace more than once.
Does that mean they’re indeed
in cahoots with you demons?
So what if we’re demons?
An immortal
with a rotten heart
is as filthy as dirt.
Wu Huan,
don’t forget how Yuemi died.
I’ll make you pay.
Just wait for it.
Demon God,
enough of your nonsense!
What is he talking about?
You don’t know?
Muguang,
don’t listen to him.
Bai Jue,
if Shanggu finds out
that you’re marrying Jingzhao
and betrayed Houchi,
she’ll never forgive you.
Why are you bringing her up?
She sacrificed herself
for the Three Realms 60,000 years ago.
You know she...
Tianqi,
zip it,
or I won’t be easy on you.
Bring it on.
I’m not afraid.
Enough is enough.
Just stop.
We have divorced.
I want nothing else from him.
Houchi,
you’re on top of the Three Realms.
You can’t afford to lose.
Purple Moon!
Half of the Power of the Original Being
has been used to make the Purple Moon
to support the Demon Realm.
Tianqi,
don’t you know that without it,
demon lords whose cultivation
depends on it
will suffer and die?
Tianqi!
(Something is happening in the Dome.)
(Your safety matters the most.
Stay away from my mother.)
(Go back to the Qingchi Palace.
Jingjian)
Houchi.
Mother won’t let them go
for the sake of the Heavenly Palace.
But going inside is of no help.
That’s the only way
to put a stop to it.
Immortals are beyond salvation.
I’ll fill in for Shanggu to be the judge
and execute them all.
You can’t
as long as I’m here.
Tianqi,
leave now.
Bai Jue,
do you know what Houchi said to me
in the Hidden Mountain when she knew
you woke up in Qingmu’s body?
She said Qingmu’s life and death,
love and hatred
were never up to someone else.
Bai Jue,
if you were him,
how could you see her
wait for 100 years for nothing?
Don’t stop me, or you’ll regret it.
I won’t.
Bai Jue,
you’ll regret it.
You’ll regret it
someday.
Stop! Enough of the fight!
Houchi!
How could you be so stupid?
How could you?
My baby!
My baby, my baby!
♪Year after year time goes by♪
It’s useless.
My spiritual vein is cut off.
You dirty bird!
What evil trick did you play?
How is Houchi injured so badly?
♪And memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you♪
Master,
♪No matter what♪
could you do something to her?
I wish I could.
Her spiritual vein is ruined.
Even the Ancestral God
couldn’t save her.
But I promise
that I’ll do everything in my power
to keep her alive.
Wu Huan,
if anything happens to Houchi,
I’ll paint your Palace with blood
and tear down the Dome
to avenge her death!
Sweetie,
it’s my fault.
Over the past 60,000 years,
I’ve only taught you
to be honest and upright
but forgotten
that without the matching power,
you’d be on the chopping block.
Father,
I’m giving everything up.
Could you beg Master
to let us go home, please?
I won’t let you die.
No one can kill you.
Father...
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds♪
♪And rain drops♪
Houchi,
I’m not your Father.
♪I’ll♪
A humble flood dragon like me
doesn’t deserve you.
It’s not that your name
isn’t on the Skyreach Pillar,
but your awakening is yet to happen.
I, Gu Jun,
pay respects to Master Shanggu.
I pay respects to Master Shanggu.
On the day of the Tribulation of Chaos,
I was so lucky
that I received a shred of
your Power of the Original Being.
Master!
It’s taken me thousands of years
to nourish it.
Shanggu’s Power of the Original Being!
You’ve kept that from me for so long.
Gu Jun
has the Original Being of Chaos.
She’s really...
Now, I’m giving your power
and supremacy
back altogether.
I only hope
you’ll take good care of my daughter
and her baby once you wake up.
Father...
What are you doing?
Father!
Don’t!
Father, I’ve lost Qingmu.
I can’t lose you.
♪He turned into ashes♪
♪Life and death♪
Gu Jun!
♪He protects the Three Realms for her♪
♪Perseverance♪
♪It’s still echoing in ears♪
♪Repeat it again♪
♪This love is boundless
and will never extinguish♪
No, Houchi!
Houchi,
your body is too weak to support
Shanggu’s Original Being of Chaos.
Listen,
get it out.
Now!
Houchi,
let it out!
Do it!
Bai Jue,
you selfishly
neutralized Qingmu and Boxuan.
You did nothing
when my spiritual vein was cut.
I also lost my Father because of you.
You’re my mortal enemy.
I will avenge their deaths.
I wished
I could be a daughter
to live an easy life.
I wished
I could be a wife
to grow old with my husband.
I wished
I could be a mother
to raise my children.
But
they called me dirty.
They called me cheap.
They called me evil.
Since there’s no justice
or room for me in all Three Realms,
I’ll have to accept that
and fight back.
Shanggu…
Houchi.
♪I’m willing to♪
Bai Jue!
Master!
♪Look for you at thousands of
days and nights♪
♪Wait until we meet again♪
♪Exchange a one-second encounter
for a lifetime♪
♪It’s not a pity
if we can meet each other♪
♪I am willing to indulge in the past♪
♪When tears dizzy the smile♪
♪How much luck do I need♪
♪To get myself♪
♪Be always stuck♪
♪In your heart♪
Get out of my sight.
I don’t want to see you ever again.
Bai Jue,
after this,
we’re even.
From this moment on,
you and I are over.
♪In the name of the world
protect a heart♪
♪If love finally♪
♪Becomes ashes♪
♪I will be the shadow in your eyes♪
♪I’m willing to look for you
at thousands of days and nights♪
Master!
♪When tears dizzy the smile♪
♪How much luck do I need♪
♪To get myself♪
♪Be always stuck♪
♪In your heart♪
Houchi!
♪Pursue you♪
♪For millions of miles♪
Houchi, you will be fine.
Let’s go.
Once this drum is beat,
they’ll know
our border at the Demon Region
is in danger.
Father,
fellow guards and soldiers,
this is my only option.
Please forgive me
for sending the false signal.
That demon killed True God Bai Jue.
Go
and kill her!
Stop right there!
Wu Huan,
are you crazy?
She’s Master Shanggu!
Master Shanggu died
in the Tribulation of Chaos.
The Qingchi Palace and Demon God lied.
They cannot get out alive!
How could you have Demon God attacked?
Like the situation isn’t bad enough!
Drumbeat from the Demon Region.
Demon God must’ve launched attacks on us
when the Dome is in chaos.
Without the Purple Moon,
demons are much weaker.
Why would they
start a war now?
What do you think is going on?
Whatever it is,
we can’t lose the Demon Region.
Jingyang,
your punishment can wait.
Lead the troops to the Demon Region
to guard the border.
Yes, Father.
Jingyang, come back.
All of you may leave.
Yes.
Demon God has barely regained his power.
He might not be our match.
We must get rid of him now,
or he’ll pose a bigger threat.
Wu Huan,
since when did you become like this?
You really think
your secret will be safe
by killing Demon God and Houchi?
What’s that supposed to mean?
I’m not that stupid.
Three-head Fire Dragon already confessed
in the secret chamber to the Twin Spear
and Bi Xi’s death.
Be honest with me.
Demon God brought up
my master Yuemi in front of you.
What exactly happened?
Demon God is a threat to the world.
You’d rather believe him than me?
We’re a couple.
I demand the whole truth!
I’m done talking to you.
Gu Jun,
am I wrong about her all these years?
Master,
you’re finally back.
The loss of the Purple Moon
has left the Demon Realm in chaos.
Demon King is dying.
What...?
What happened to young Goddess?
Is Master Shanggu about to come back?
Go find Fengran
and take her here.
Yes.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪