=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 42=
Master.
You are finally back.
Since the Purple Moon disappeared,
the demon realm has got in chaos.
The Demon King was incurably hurt.
It...
What happened
to the young Goddess?
Is Master Shanggu going to awaken?
Go get Fengran.
Let her come right now.
Yes.
Houchi.
Your child is gifted with God vein.
Your energy will be drained.
If he survives,
you’ll lose your Spiritual Strength.
I can feel he’s about to be born.
Promise me.
If I die,
you’ll keep this child for me.
No! I can’t, Houchi!
Please.
You must keep this child for me.
He...
He’s innocent.
Okay.
I promise.
No matter what happens,
I’ll protect him well.
Houchi.
You’re the closest person to me.
No matter what,
I won’t let anything happen
to you and your baby.
♪He protects the Three Realms for her♪
♪Perseverance♪
♪It’s still echoing in ears♪
♪Repeat it again♪
♪This love is boundless
and will never extinguish♪
Shanggu.
Master.
Master, what can I do for you?
Please tell me.
Shanggu.
Leave.
Yes.
Sen Yu.
Is Demon God crazy?
Purple Moon is withdrawn.
How will our demons
fight against immortals?
The demon lords of Third Heaven
mostly rely on Purple Moon
for cultivation.
Let’s go back to see His Majesty.
Okay.
Soldiers, guard the camp!
Let’s go.
The two sides are holding peace talks.
Jingyang.
What do you mean by this?
Demon God attacked the Dome
and hurt True God Bai Jue.
I’m ordered to kill all of you.
Soldiers, listen to my order.
Eradicate the demon soldiers.
End it once and for all!
Aye!
Qin.
Sen Yu!
Go!
Go back and tell Father
it’s Master Tianqi
who got us into this.
Go!
No!
Why?
Why didn’t you leave?
Without Purple Moon,
you can’t defeat him
even exploding your demon core.
The demon clan is behind me.
I must fight.
Okay.
We won’t leave.
Let’s fight them to the end.
Stop!
Brother.
I stroke the drum.
The demons didn’t invade
the Demon Region.
Sorry.
I did it to save someone.
Jingjian!
Are you out of your mind?
Are you helping the demons?
Brother.
Withdraw your troops.
Don’t push me.
Demon God attacked the Dome today.
There’s no turning back
for the two sides.
Eradicate the demons,
and the threat to our immortals.
Brother.
Don’t make another mistake.
Demons are also living creatures.
Why should they be eradicated?
Go away!
It’s Mother’s order.
But the peace talk is Father’s order.
You...!
You’re as soft-hearted
as Father.
Calm down, Your Highness.
If it weren’t for Muguang,
I should’ve caught both of them.
There are soldiers guarding outside.
If they find it...
Why do you fear while I fear nothing?
You said we must act with caution.
What... What’s wrong with me?
I can’t even control my demon power.
We’ve been a couple
for 60 thousand years.
I don’t wanna anger Muguang.
But I can’t bear with his temper.
He’s soft and indecisive,
claiming to be kindhearted.
With him,
how should I deal with the True Gods?
What if Tianqi takes advantage of it
and Bai Jue knows
Yuemi was harmed
because of me?
I meant to kill Tianqi and Houchi
on the wedding.
Unexpectedly,
Shanggu was revived.
What a miscalculation.
That said,
Tianqi’s strength hasn’t yet recovered.
Nor Houchi has awakened to be Shanggu.
The time has come.
I can’t miss such a good chance.
Fengnyu.
Your Highness.
But...
Just do as you were told.
I will bear the consequence.
If Heavenly Emperor blames...
As a matter of fact,
Yuemi’s death was just an accident.
Given a couple
of 60 thousand years,
Muguang won’t severely punish me.
Even if he knows
I’m descended to a demon,
I have a way to deal with it.
Yes.
Are you alright?
I’m fine.
Master Jingyuan has taken Houchi
back to Xuanjing Palace.
Master ordered me to take you to her.
What is it?
Master withdrew
the power of Purple Moon.
These people must mean no good.
You go inside first.
I’ll guard here.
(Purple Moon Spring)
Your hair!
What on earth happened in the Dome?
Gu Jun is dead.
Was it Wu Huan’s doing?
I’m going to kill her.
Fengran.
Come back.
Houchi just awakened to Shanggu.
But she’s too weak
to bear the power of
Original Being of Chaos.
And she just gave birth.
Now she needs your care.
Whose baby is it?
It’s Qingmu’s.
Be careful.
Your Highness.
You came back in time.
His Majesty...
He passed away.
Father.
I’m back.
Look at me!
Please talk to me!
Father.
You said you’d punish me
for my mistake.
Now I’m back.
Please punish me! Please scold me!
Father!
Come back to me!
With that Demon God,
how could the demons not win?
His Majesty’s lifelong cultivation
was inseparable from the Purple Moon.
Demon God withdrew it.
So His Majesty’s power was all taken.
I should’ve repelled him.
Sen Yu.
Calm down.
Whatever he has done,
he’s the foundation of the demons.
If we fight each other
at this time of crisis,
the immortals will attack us off-guard.
Chang Qin, you’re so cruel.
His Majesty sees you as his daughter.
Now he’s dead.
You even ignored the blood feud.
A disaster is imminent.
Are you still inciting him?
If you really mean it,
why don’t you try to help His Highness?
My father
ended up like this.
I can’t bear this.
Where are the elders of Xuanjing Palace?
Irritated by Demon King’s death,
they’ve gone to the Purple Moon Spring.
Sen Yu.
Are you going to kill Demon God?
As his son,
I must avenge my father.
As the young chief of the demons,
I must protect the demon clan.
If Demon God is dead,
no one else can protect the demon clan!
Sen Yu!
(Purple Moon Spring)
Everyone.
What do you mean by this?
Purple Moon Spring is
where the Master lives.
No trespassing.
If Demon God is guiltless,
why doesn’t he show himself?
He withdrew the Purple Moon
and ruined all our cultivation.
Shouldn’t he give us an explanation?
If not the Purple Moon,
you wouldn’t have had your cultivation.
Master took back what belongs to him.
What should he explain?
Leave now.
Or I’ll show no mercy.
Does it belong to him?
Zihan.
The demons did benefit from Jingyuan.
For 60 thousand years,
we’ve been against all beings for him.
The whole clan protects him alone.
As the Demon God,
shouldn’t he protect the demon clan?
But what did he do?
For his personal affair,
he withdrew the Purple Moon
and got the demon clan into this.
We follow his lead.
What about him?
What are we in his eyes?
A bunch of animals he keeps?
I’m warning you.
Get out of the way.
Your Highness.
Watch your tongue.
Watch my tongue?
My father has died in the palace.
That’s what he gains
for his loyalty of 60 thousand years.
You let me watch my tongue?
As his son,
I shall avenge him
or never be an immortal!
Demon King died?
Even if he lost power,
he could just be a mortal.
How could he die?
If Demon God can’t bring my father
back to life,
he’ll pay with his blood!
Sen Yu!
About Demon King,
I know you’re angry.
But don’t jump to conclusion.
Everyone.
Since Master is back,
he’ll try to recover your power.
For Demon King’s sake,
I won’t argue with you.
Leave now
and I’ll pretend nothing happened.
Your Highness, don’t believe him.
Demon God won’t care about our lives.
Purple Moon is in Demon God’s body.
Kill him
and take back the Purple Moon.
Shut up!
Xiaoli!
Xiaoli! Xiaoli!
Demons, take my order!
Kill Demon God for the Purple Moon!
Houchi.
Look.
It’s a boy.
He’s so cute
and so small.
He takes after Qingmu.
Houchi.
Give him a name.
His father has gone.
I’m dying soon.
I’ll name him
“Qi (abandonment)”.
Qi?
Qi.
Little one.
Your name is like
your uncle’s name Tianqi.
You’ll have the name Yuanqi.
Good name.
He’ll achieve something big.
Yuanqi.
I have nothing to give you.
In Qingchi Palace, there are some toys
your grandfather bought for me.
They’re all for boys.
You will like them.
Now they are yours.
Your grandfather had a good eye.
You’ll certainly like them.
Houchi.
In the future,
if he asks about his parents,
please tell him
his father is North Sea Lord Qingmu,
a true hero
who curbed the violent
and assisted the weak,
upholding justice and love.
His mother Houchi
had a happy life,
was accompanied by good friends
and spoiled by her father and husband.
She led a carefree life.
Houchi, stop talking.
Take a rest
and you will be fine.
Yeah.
When he grows up,
tell him yourself.
Houchi.
You don’t have to comfort me.
True God Shanggu sacrificed herself
for the Three Realms.
Now
let me pay for her kindness instead.
If Chief Goddess Shanggu wakes up
and remembers me,
the couple
of Qingmu and Houchi,
as well as their love,
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
please tell her this.
As the body for her to awaken,
I have resentment,
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
but I’m greatly honored.
♪Waiting for returned birds♪
I achieve little all my life.
In the end, I can
make this great contribution.
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
I don’t fail the title of God
my father struggled for me.
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
Don’t feel sorry for me.
Actually,
it’s a relief for me.
Since Qingmu’s death,
I’ve wanted to go to him.
What do you think
the world would be
when the Spiritual Strength disappears?
I will
reunite with Qingmu, right?
I can certainly meet him again.
♪When we wake up♪
Houchi.
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
Don’t forget it, everyone,
I’m a God.
You are not my match.
I won’t hurt you
for we are all demons.
You are a God.
How could you bear to see us suffer?
Your Highness.
God Zihan is blindly loyal.
He has no sympathy for us.
You fox!
Are you stirring up troubles?
Do you want me to beat you
to your true form?
Demon King’s death is fishy.
After this is ended,
I’ll look into you.
Calm down, everyone.
Don’t panic.
Before withdrawing the Purple Moon,
Master said
he’d give back your cultivation
that he had taken,
though it would take some time.
Some time?
How long will it be?
Yes. How long?
- How long?
- Make it clear!
A hundred years.
Just a hundred years.
I swear with
the Power of the Original Being.
Only a hundred years.
Is it true?
If your power isn’t recovered
in a hundred years,
you can come and confront me.
I will surrender myself
and never resist.
What about my father?
He owned the cultivation
of thousands of years.
Dream on!
Today you’ll all die!
Why bother a hundred years?
You again!
Are you done?
A low Lord
dares to be so rude in my realm!
Do you think no one can stop you?
Deicide Flower!
How did you get the demon’s item?
It’s toxic.
Protect yourself.
Fengran.
Take Houchi and Yuanqi
back to Qingchi Palace right now.
Activate the protection barrier
left by Gu Jun.
No matter what happens outside,
do not open the barrier.
Keep it in mind.
Why back to Qingchi Palace?
Isn’t this the safest place?
Not any more,
I guess.
When she wakes up,
she’ll be no longer Houchi
but Shanggu.
Will you look after her and protect her
as you did to Houchi?
Shanggu or Houchi,
she’s the same.
Master.
Master, where are you going?
Jingyang.
You rat
take advantage of this!
How shameless!
Don’t irritate him!
Xiaoli!
Are you alright?
Your Highness.
I won’t let you die.
Ignorant!
I’m gonna kill you all!
I have a way.
Don’t!
Xiaoli! Xiaoli!
Master, be careful!
Other than me, no one else
shall fail the demon clan!
Demon God.
When you attacked the Dome,
you should’ve thought of this.
As the Demon God,
your power is so weak.
My mother even gave me this.
Demon God is just average.
Bai Jue!
Aren’t you in a coma?
Brother.
Don’t be rude
to Master.
You dare to use the demon’s item.
Tie yourself up and go to Xuantian Hall.
Wait for your punishment
from your father.
Where is Houchi?
I’ll protect her.
None of your business.
You’d better protect her all your life.
She hurt True God.
She can’t pay the price
even if she dies.
Zihan.
I...
Master.
I’m deeply poisoned.
I won’t live long.
Don’t talk nonsense.
I have the divine power.
I can definitely save you!
Yes.
Master is powerful.
But Master,
Purple Moon is gone.
Sen Jian is dead.
I’m also dying.
Who will protect you in the future?
Master.
I privately made a decision for you,
to restore the demon clan
in a hundred years.
Please be sure to do it.
I... I don’t wanna be cursed by them.
I don’t want you to live in stigma.
Yes.
I promise.
I will never forget
your words.
I used to listen to you.
You can finally listen to me once.
Master.
In this world,
I envy you so much.
You live freely,
doing whatever you want to do.
It was Yuemi first. Now it’s you.
Zihan.
I promise.
From now on,
I will never be willful.
I promise.
Lord Fengran.
Where are you taking Houchi?
Fengnyu.
The time has changed.
Houchi has awakened
as the Chief Goddess Shanggu.
If you hurt her,
you’ll be guilty
of murdering the Goddess.
It’s unforgivable.
So what?
The God Realm is long gone.
The immortals will soon
eliminate the demons.
Bai Jue and my master
are paramount.
Without Bai Jue’s order,
she’s nothing but a commoner.
Soldiers.
Get them.
Get lost!
What are you doing here?
Don’t get me wrong.
Master Bai Jue
asked me to save you.
Did Bai Jue send you here?
What does he mean?
He harmed us.
Now is he helping us?
I don’t know the grudge between you.
Just be aware that
I’ll only serve Master Bai Jue
in the future.
You wicked manner
makes me sick.
I didn’t mean it
to offend Qingchi Palace before.
It was stirred up by that witch Wu Huan.
Please pardon me.
Don't lower yourself to my level.
Ungrateful
and vicious.
You are so mean,
having no principle at all.
I work for the most powerful person.
That’s exactly my principle.
No need.
I can do it.
Master.
Muguang.
From today on,
the demons will join the Dome.
I order you to recover
the demons’ strength in a century.
Any problem?
The demons are also living creatures.
It’s up to you, Master.
I wonder what Jingyang has done
that you let him kneel here.
He released the Deicide Flower
and slaughtered the demons.
Shouldn’t I punish him?
You bastard!
How did you get the Deicide Flower?
I have the doubt, too.
Heavenly Empress asked me
to give you this.
Your Highness.
She said it’s the Deicide Flower.
Its poison can kill God.
Isn’t Mother too careful?
We have Master Bai Jue.
Why bother doing this?
I don’t know.
She just let me tell you.
Do not open it
unless it’s necessary.
Father.
It’s not me.
It... It’s Mother...
Master.
My son is unruly.
He must’ve played
with the Deicide Flower
and made the mistake
when Wu Huan was out
of the Nether World.
I...
I didn’t teach him well.
Please spare his life.
Please spare his life, Master!
Really?
Jingyang is just a Lord.
How could he control the Deicide Flower?
Master.
For the sake that
he’s been guarding
the border for years,
please spare his life.
I’ll be lenient,
but he must be punished.
Yes. Yes.
Punish him with 20 thunder strikes
and 100-year detention.
You bastard!
Thank Master for sparing your life!
Master, thanks for sparing my life.
Only a truce of two sides
can bring peace to the world.
If anyone dares to attempt it again,
he shall not be spared.
Yes, Master.
How long will she sleep like this?
I don’t know.
Maybe one month.
Or a century.
It all
depends on herself.
Chang Que.
Is there any medicine to wake her up?
Sixty thousand years is
just a blink of an eye.
We could wait for a longer time.
Demon God.
What did Bai Jue mean by that?
He was so ruthless to Houchi
in the Dome.
Why did he save her today?
For Shanggu, maybe.
Today,
thank you
for covering me for my power loss.
I should thank you
for sparing my brother.
You should hate me.
I dare not.
I’d like to ask you a question.
Go ahead.
You don’t like me,
yet you agreed to marry me.
Is it to let Houchi give up
or for Master Shanggu?
You know I don’t like you.
Why do you stay here?
In terms of love,
I’ve given up hope for it.
Now I only
care about honor.
It’s best for me to stay in the Dome.
At least, in the eyes of others,
I’m still the closest person to you.
You’re now
frank and sincere, not pretentious.
At the wedding,
I’ve lost face.
Please have mercy on me.
Don’t expel me out of the Dome.
I hate
to be an ingrate.
As long as you behave,
you’ll have the honor as you wish.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪