♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
=The Eternal Love S3=
=Episode 12=
To celebrate our anniversary,
cheers.
Cheers.
I even prepared presents for you.
(Have you decided yet?)
"Have you decided yet?"
To decide on what?
This is one way to display affection.
Have you...
decided yet?
(She is using the repudiation paper)
(as leverage.)
Have you decided, Prince Consort?
Have you decided yet?
In her dream!
(Have you decided yet, Prince Consort?)
What?
Nothing.
No.
Have some tea.
Have some tea, Young Master.
(Does she think I'm like other men, that I would)
(give in as long as I'm threatened)
(with my reputation?)
Eighth Brother.
Why do you look so absent-minded?
He's been spaced out recently.
Nosy.
The thing you said you need to do yesterday.
You didn't do it after all, did you?
Yu Hao!
You're being nosy again.
I'm not.
So you've already asked for
the repudiation paper?
But you didn't pack your belongings
or leave Princess' Residence.
Her Highness must haven't agreed, right?
Not really.
What is it then?
Eighth Brother, what is it?
Her Highness asked,
"Have you decided yet?"
I keep hearing that line in the manor.
I'm curious too.
What is it that you should decide?
Don't you have better things to do?
Curiosity killed the cat.
Fourteenth.
Why are you here every day?
I'm definitely not here for Jing Xin.
I...
I'm here because I care about you.
What exactly is going on with
your repudiation paper?
It is a test.
If I pass, I can get the paper.
Is it hard?
So you can't pass it.
Of course not!
It's so easy that I can pass in an instant.
You never wanted to get that paper,
which is why you're so frustrated.
In this world we live in,
no man would voluntarily give up
their happiness.
Who says marriage means happiness
and being disowned means misery?
Everyone knows that
being disowned means misery.
Not to mention Her Highness thinks
so highly of you.
This isn't right.
Her Highness set a test that is easy to pass
as a condition to disown you.
I think
Her Highness doesn't think highly of you.
(She keeps urging me to make a decision.)
(It does seem like she's in a hurry to chase me out.)
(In that case, I shall fulfill her wish.)
Jing Xin.
Tell Her Highness that
I've made up my mind.
Really?
He agreed?
Who would have thought?
We're married for so long,
but I'm still so touched by his action.
Jing Xin, get the bathwater ready for me.
Put some petals into it.
Light some incenses too.
I should get sexy pajamas for the night too.
Should I get a new hairstyle as well?
Tan. Before bedtime,
only the man should dress up
and clean his body.
Why are you the one who's worried?
You're right.
It's not every day
Mo Lian Cheng would take the initiative.
I should act cold.
I'll stay put and wait.
I'll be ready for him once he's all set.
But...
are you really going to disown him
after the night together?
You'll find out soon enough.
I have no idea
what kind of challenge Second Princess
is asking you to have,
but the way I see it,
you will never falter.
Falter?
If it were you, you would have lost.
If I were you,
I would face the same predicament.
The world is too harsh for men.
If you want to give up now,
I will never look down on you.
Never.
Her Highness keeps pushing me now
only to make me give up.
But I will never surrender.
What exactly is this challenge
that makes you so worried?
It's a long struggle of mind and strength.
It requires your strength?
So that's what the swordplay training for.
I have faith in you.
Go.
No eavesdropping!
But...
I said, no eavesdropping!
What is this challenge?
Just tell me.
That is not possible.
All you need to know
is that all men fear it.
That's all.
Is it so terrifying?
Are you scared already?
Scaredy cat.
I'm not afraid!
If you use it to challenge me,
I'll definitely not be nervous.
I'm not challenging you!
Why do you keep coming here?
It's late and you should leave.
Otherwise, you'll get a lecture.
Go.
But...
Just go.
Go on.
It's such a beautiful night.
What is taking him so long?
Curse that Mo Lian Cheng.
Is he backing out?
You'll pay dearly for this.
Princess.
Princess?
The candle just went out.
How can you fall asleep so quickly?
Could it be...
that Your Highness is nervous?
Who is this nuisance?
Why are you hitting me?
Open your eyes and look at me.
Don't run away.
(My goodness. How bossy.)
(He's finally come around after
drinking some wines?)
Perhaps...
Your Highness is shy.
There is no need to punish yourself.
Eighth Young Master was reckless.
It wasn't your fault.
I understand the purpose.
Yet, I chose to do nothing.
I even hope for his plan to succeed.
I deserve this punishment.
You and Her Highness were childhood friends.
People in love are selfish.
It's normal for anyone.
Once,
I mocked those men who had become
calculating and shallow because of love.
But now,
I'm just like them.
(The slightest negligence of kindness
makes way for the darkness.)
(Is it all over now?)
(I shouldn't have drunk so much.)
(This is the last time we share this bed.)
(But you're sleeping as if you don't know any of it.)
(That's good anyway.)
(Since you're oblivious to it,)
(it's easier for me to let go.)
(You're so reluctant to part ways.)
(My charm must be overwhelming.)
(I should mess with him a little.)
Did you have enough fun?
I fulfilled the agreement.
It's your turn now.
Help me get changed.
We are no longer husband and wife.
You have no right over me.
Very well.
Suit yourself.
Where is the repudiation paper?
I wasn't satisfied.
You...
She wasn't satisfied?
Young Master, it's time for your meal.
Eighth Brother!
Eighth Brother, there are rumors everywhere!
Aren't you going to do anything?
What rumors?
Well...
The Mo family knows
you've left Her Highness unsatisfied.
Even the Mo family knows it.
Judging by your look...
The rumors are true?
This is bad.
The son-in-law of the Minister of War
was considered a letdown.
He lost the slightest respect in the family
within three days.
Not to mention the concubine of
Princess of Qian Yue
was considered a letdown
and got...
I have a goal
and there is no shortcut to it.
Prince Consort.
This is the tonic soup I was asked
to send to you.
Get rid of these!
Check out this beautiful bracelet!
Have a look around!
Check out our fabrics!
Check out our fabrics.
Your Highness!
Look at this fabric.
Lady.
This is too bright.
Check out ours.
- How about this?
- Have a look.
It's too plain.
Lady, what about this?
We have the finest goods.
These are all quality goods from Jiangnan.
Please have another look!
This lady matches that of a goddess.
Your elegance and grace are enchanting.
Your beauty is beyond any words.
At least you're not blind.
- Don't you know she is...
- Mi Xue.
This is an anonymous trip.
Be discreet.
Yes, Eldest Princess.
Pardon my ignorance.
The rumors about your beauty are true.
Your Highness's charm
outshines even the most radiant gems!
How about a handkerchief?
Your Highness.
Colorful fabrics!
(Fragrance sachet)
Feel free to browse our merchandise!
Young Master, you have great taste.
With the fragrance sachet,
the couple will thrive in harmony!
Here, have a look.
Very well. I'll have one.
I hope this fragrance sachet will remind
Tan Er of the past.
Eldest Princess.
Remembering the past?
Is it worth it to stoop so low for her?
Please be mindful of your words.
She is your sister and my wife.
The whole city knows
her attitude towards Mo Lian Cheng.
Do you also want dissatisfaction?
Please don't believe the rumors.
It's a fact.
I'm reminding you out of pity.
Since you only slander her name,
I won't argue with you.
Why can't you open your eyes?
She doesn't care about you.
Otherwise,
she wouldn't ignore your pain
or make you suffer in silence.
Yes.
I'm blinded by the pain.
I can't see the truth.
But Your Highness,
are you any different?
I'll take my leave.
Serve me in my chamber.
(Have you decided yet?)
(Have you...)
(decided yet?)
(Would the outcome be any different
if I had not been drunk?)
Who would have thought?
The word "unsatisfied" would be this powerful.
I should have made the word our family motto.
Jing Xin, grind the ink.
(Keep working)
Tan.
Is this calligraphy for Prince Consort again?
I want him to frame it
and hang it above his bedhead.
Where there is a will, there is a way.
But he already went through a lot today.
At this rate...
You don't get it.
He loves going against me.
But he's a man.
He has a delicate heart.
If he really takes it to heart,
it will be a great loss!
He's a tough one.
He's no ordinary man.
I'm not going to send this to him this time.
(I wasn't satisfied.)
No.
If I wasn't drunk,
I would never end up like this.
No.
Satisfied?
I don't care. Why should I be bothered?
Remembering the past?
Is it worth it to stoop so low
for her?
The whole city knows
her attitude towards Mo Lian Cheng.
Do you also want dissatisfaction?
You won't blame me.
But I blame myself.
I don't want to stay at this manor anymore.
If you refuse to help me...
I shall do it myself.
I hope you could help me leave this place.
(He was so determined to get the repudiation paper.)
(But now he served her in the chamber.)
Could it be the reason he asked for
the repudiation paper
is that he's afraid he and the Mo family would
involve Tan Er in trouble in the future?
Vent your frustration on me if you want.
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
Do not cause damage to the plants.
If you're a man, just face it bravely.
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
(No one knows)
(that I insisted on leaving,)
(so she wouldn't be in danger.)
(I must get the repudiation paper tonight.)
Young Master.
Young Master, your face...
You don't need to serve me tonight.
Lock me inside the room.
Open it at this hour tomorrow.
What about your meals?
I need nothing.
Young Master. Is this necessary?
I violated the code of man, I deserve punishment!
Leave.
Humans...
are hard to understand.
A step forward brings glory.
A step backward...
will send a man to darkness.
Are you drunk again?
Unsatisfied.
That's the most powerful word in this world.
If it weren't for you,
this headache...
might have cost me my life one day.
We need to cure the root of this sickness.
Your Majesty's condition has become worse.
Perhaps breaking the taboo was the cause.
He's the cause of this sickness.
A little pain is worth it.
Did he get the repudiation paper?
No.
But there are rumors.
They say Eighth Young Master of the Mo family
left Her Highness unsatisfied.
Unsatisfied?
Perhaps...
Her Highness found out Eighth Young Master
was using her,
so she spread rumors to tarnish his name.
It's a punishment.
Judging by that...
Such actions
do not fit Tan Er's personality.
Is Your Majesty suspecting
something is amiss?
Summon him to the palace.
Your Majesty.
I need confirmation.
Yes.
Don't you have anything to say?
Nothing. What should I say?
So you weren't unsatisfied.
You were messing with me!
I said before that everyone was born equal.
Why a woman can disown her husband,
but a man can't disown his wife?
Men can disown their wives.
You...
Then allow me to disown you.
Disown me?
Did you wake me up just for that?
I made the same request so many times.
Did you ever listen?
You...
Princess.
Her Majesty summoned Secondary Prince Consort.
From what I heard,
Second Princess's Residence
has been very lively.
What does Your Majesty mean?
Do you not know?
If it's because I violated the seven
types of grounds
and moral codes for men many times,
please punish me, Your Majesty.
Second Princess is of the royal bloodline.
Breaking the seven grounds is a serious crime.
Her actions and behaviors will serve
as examples for the people.
You should behave yourself.
Pardon my intrusion.
Marriage involves both men and women.
Who only women have the right
to decide everything?
It seems like Second Princess's Residence
is more distasteful than I had imagined.
If all men can't get their repudiation papers,
breaking the seven grounds is the only way.
Your Majesty,
how should they be punished?
Do you really think all men
are the same as you,
that they would act rashly just to get disowned?
Your Majesty!
If all women in the country
neglect the men's willingness,
refuse to disown their husbands despite
breaking the seven grounds,
what will happen to this country?
Insolence!
Kneel outside the main hall and reflect yourself!
Your Majesty.
The way he speaks...
was just like that man.
But as Your Majesty said,
there would be no other man like him.
He showed wisdom in his words
and showed no fear in his speech.
He is no longer
the same man he used to be.
Secondary Prince Consort does have
become different over time.
It's more than that.
It's like he's been reborn!
I await Your Majesty's order.
Since he wants to leave,
I cannot ignore his request.
How long can the lotus survive
out of water?
No matter how long,
it made the decision.
There shall be no regret.
Tell me.
How badly do you want to leave?
Even the shortest freedom
is better than living in a cage
which brings only suffering.
So the Second Princess's Residence
is only a cage to you.
In that case,
I'll announce a new law.
Every man will have the right to end a marriage.
It will be implemented in the capital first.
We'll observe the effect.
Your Majesty is wise.
Since you've made up your mind,
you could make the request now
and become the pioneer of this law.
(Tan Er, I'm sorry.)
(I can't put you in harm's way.)
(Not anymore.)
(Tan Er, I'm sorry.)
(I can't protect you anymore.)
(I can no longer protect you.)
I am grateful to Your Majesty.
I'm aware of my duty,
so I must not act rashly.
What do you mean?
Your Majesty's wise policies have
earned people's respect.
People should use it with caution.
Second Princess and I serve
as role models for the people.
We cannot act recklessly.
So
you don't plan to make use of this new law.
Flowers will lose their brilliance eventually.
Marriage is the same.
If one celebrates the wonders
and neglects the hardships,
a marriage won't last.
I should work with Second Princess
in this difficult time,
so Your majesty's effort won't go in vain.
You looked so determined.
Was it just a trick?
I wouldn't dare.
I came to a realization while kneeling.
I thought my impulsive behavior
would get me punished.
But Your Majesty showed me mercy.
I've come to regret my action deeply.
If you ever act on impulse again,
I will not show any mercy.
I'm grateful, Your Majesty.
If we lose track of the lead now,
it will make future investigations difficult.
Your Majesty, allow me to investigate.
Listen.
He defied Her Majesty in the palace.
Her Majesty?
For real?
(My Cheng Cheng must be back!)
My Cheng Cheng never disappoints me.
All right. Very well.
You can get to work.
Cheng Cheng.
Mo Lian Cheng.
How bold of you!
How dare you trick Her Majesty!
Jing Xin told me about it.
She knows everything
going on in the palace.
Your turning happened at the right timing.
I think Jing Xin is not the only one
capable of spreading gossips.
All right. I have a lot to say to you.
Go to my room with me.
Promise me.
Whatever I do when the amnesia kicks in,
do not divorce me.
Certainly.
You haven't satisfied me yet.
You...
You should be more cautious.
Otherwise,
I might get amnesia again.
If you can't touch me,
how can I be satisfied?
I can't touch you.
But this thing will do.
Give it back!
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪A flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter what
hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have to
travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter
what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have
to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪