♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
=The Eternal Love S3=
=Episode 11=
Eighth Brother.
Since you've already married into
the Princess's Residence,
you need to abide by a code of virtue,
be a loyal husband, and act with caution.
Seeing you and Her Highness bickering these days,
I feel rather worried.
I know
if it were someone else, things would not
be the way they are.
I know you have dreams and great ambition.
But marrying into the Princess's Residence
is the ultimate dream of so many.
Eldest Brother.
What I want
is not always hiding behind women
and enjoying a luxurious lifestyle;
neither is it for self-realization,
nor to achieve what Father has been plotting for
and hurt others.
These years,
I've also known pieces of Father's plans.
Although I'm not in agreement,
I don't have the means to stop him either.
But Eighth Brother,
why did you willingly step into
this dangerous situation after your accident?
Eldest Brother.
Have you felt resentment towards me
for marrying into the Second Princess's Residence
with you?
Surprise, yes,
but no resentment.
Under these skies,
which good man doesn't want to marry into
a good home?
You had a poor reputation before.
Second Princess was kind enough to
not give up on you.
I'm happy for you.
Eldest Brother, you don't blame me,
but I have a guilty conscience.
I don't want to stay in this residence
any longer.
Could you please tell me,
aside from running away,
is there any other way?
What?
Have you gone mad?
If you do this, the rest of your life will be ruined.
I've been thinking about it for quite some time.
You must have known it as well.
You needn't try to persuade me anymore.
I'll shoulder the consequences myself.
If you are unwilling to help me,
I'll do it on my own.
But how can I watch you put yourself in danger?
I will do as I say.
In order for you, as a prince consort to renounce
his marriage,
you have to get the divorce papers
from Her Highness.
But Eighth Brother...
I've made up my mind.
Here.
If I want to get the divorce papers,
I'd have to fit the seven types of grounds.
[*Conditions on which a wife can cast off her husband]
Although you're not one to be compliant,
but the seven types of grounds
aren't that easy to commit.
First, "not being respectful towards female
elders in the family".
You've married into the royal family.
Will you have to disrespect the empress?
About "not having a daughter".
You and Tan Er haven't been married for long.
How can they determine whether you can or cannot
give birth to a daughter?
Aside from "being wanton",
only "being overly jealous", "having a big mouth",
"stealing", and "being unfilial" are left.
Others will only think that I am unscrupulous.
The Mo Family will definitely be implicated.
Or maybe
I could try being seriously ill?
Did you know that every type of grounds
is considered to be a heinous offense?
It would be impossible for you to remarry.
I'm aware.
There's even the danger of being drowned.
Eldest Brother, don't worry.
I'll be sure to take care of myself.
Could you listen to my advice once more?
Eldest Brother, please help me.
Eighth Brother.
Eighth Brother, listen to me.
Was I sincerely trying to persuade Lian Cheng?
But Tan Er has changed too much.
These changes shouldn't happen anymore.
(Princess's Residence)
Qu Xiao Tan.
He who gives you the cold shoulder is not
your Cheng Cheng.
You've definitely not been given the cold shoulder.
Cheng Cheng.
A batch of delicious peaches has arrived,
I wanted to give you...
Stop screaming.
It's me.
Yu Hao, you scared me to death.
- Your Highness, something terrible has happened.
- You scared me.
I was just on my way to report to you.
Last night, Young Master started feeling fatigued,
and then exhibited diarrhea.
I called the doctor over right away.
The doctor said that this illness is contagious.
Young Master might not be able to live in
the Snow Court for much longer.
Your Highness.
The secondary prince consort's room is on fire.
No, no, no.
It's the rhizoma atractylodis incense.
We're burning it.
He was so lively yesterday,
I can't believe he's this sick just a day later.
Exactly.
This illness seems serious.
I only spoke a few words with the prince consort
yesterday.
I may have been infected too.
I need to go take a look.
Your Highness. You mustn't go in.
You really mustn't go in.
To ensure your safety, you two cannot go in.
Your Highness.
Your Highness. To be safe,
it'd be better if you don't go inside.
They're coming in.
- Cheng Cheng.
- Your Highness.
Hurry.
- Pull it over.
- Cheng Cheng, how are you?
Cheng Cheng.
- Your Highness.
- Cheng Cheng.
The secondary prince consort has come down
with a serious illness.
Very contagious. He needs to be quarantined.
This serious?
Your Highness. Please don't get too close.
Cheng Cheng.
Cheng Cheng, how do you feel?
Cheng Cheng, I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
I was being too pushy.
But you can't get sick here,
we have to go back together.
Cheng Cheng.
Your Highness.
Your Highness mustn't come closer.
If you do
and something bad happens,
I'd have to die ten thousand times over.
How is it your fault?
Stop talking about death and such.
As long as I'm here,
don't you ever speak that word again.
We said we'd never leave each other.
Alright.
Rest well. Stop talking.
Leave us.
If this illness is contagious,
I'll stay with him on my own.
Don't want you to get sick too.
You mustn't, Your Highness.
Leave us.
Your Highness.
Cheng Cheng. Cheng Cheng.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- Let's go.
♪Another late autumn, another night♪
♪The swallow has returned, when will you♪
♪Should the yellowing red letters be taken down
or not♪
♪Hope makes it more heartbreaking♪
♪The wind blows, leaves fall on the window sill♪
♪Red brocade in the bronze mirror♪
♪The lonely Jiangnan is still noisy♪
♪And the light sigh from the deep boudoir♪
♪A dip in ink to draw the birds of spring♪
♪Playing zither to press on the heartstring♪
♪Only the wind brings back your scent♪
♪Blindly believing that you are well♪
♪She longs eagerly day and night♪
♪Each stitch sends love from afar♪
♪Only, how could she let you know of her misery♪
♪All is well in her letters♪
Cheng Cheng, you're awake.
Are you alright?
I was so anxious.
How do you feel?
Your Highness. I fell ill out of nowhere
and I'm unsure whether it can be cured.
May Your Highness allow me to live elsewhere.
Don't be stupid.
How can I leave you at a time like this?
Your Highness.
My illness has overcome my body.
If I don't leave the residence,
I'm afraid you and the entire residence
will be infected.
I don't care about any of that.
I just want you.
I will follow you in life and death.
I...
Alright. Say no more.
We've been married for so long,
there's no need to make a distinction between
you and me.
Your most important task right now
is to get better.
I'll go heat up your medicine.
You need to have some since you're awake.
(Moral codes for men)
(The seven types of grounds is needed
to get the divorce papers)
Tan.
Turns out
he's pretending to be ill.
What?
Pretending to be ill?
He wants me to repudiate him.
The secondary prince consort?
Jing Xin.
Why do you think he dislikes me this much?
Am I that unlikeable?
No.
Maybe
the secondary consort has reasons
he cannot speak of.
I've been treating him so well.
He wants to divorce me?
Is it possible
that there's someone else?
Someone else?
As in he's having an affair.
Impossible.
He wouldn't dare.
Even if he dares, others wouldn't.
Everyone knows that
he belongs to Your Highness.
Who dares to challenge you?
That's true.
I have to get it together.
Jing Xin.
If he wants to keep the show going,
we'll have to act our part as well.
Okay.
I will support you in anything you decide to do.
Let's go settle things with Yu Hao.
You're such a great sis!
Let's go.
Your Highness should go rest.
Having Yu Hao here is enough.
Yu Hao is busy. He doesn't have the time
to take care of you.
I plan to stay here
until you recover.
You...
Your Highness.
Are you asleep?
You don't care if
the illness gets passed on to you?
No, I don't.
I only care about whether you catch a cold
on top of everything.
Tuck yourself in.
You...
There, I've been infected too.
I'm not leaving.
Look at your cold sweat.
You need to sweat it out.
When did you find out?
I deceived Your Highness.
I don't deserve to be a prince consort.
Your Highness, please repudiate me.
Did you know?
I'm glad that
you didn't take random medicine in order
to deceive me.
I know you don't believe me
because you lost your memory.
But I remember everything.
Last time, you traveled to the modern era
to look for me.
This time,
it's my turn to look for you and protect you.
Let's work together
and hurry back to Yu Er,
okay?
You don't even understand what I think,
how can you watch over me?
It is absolutely impossible
for me to repudiate you.
Back then, I left my parents.
More recently, I left Yu Er.
If I have to leave you too,
I wouldn't know how to face tomorrow.
Even if you dislike me,
I, Qu Xiao Tan,
will only love Mo Lian Cheng.
I'll wait for you.
I'll wait for you to fall in love with me again.
I...
♪Forgot who started the war♪
♪That unprovoked torture♪
I have already...
Alright, I know you're tired.
You don't have to say anything.
♪To love you like I do♪
You need time to get used to
everything that has been happening.
♪Self-deprecation to the maximum♪
You don't have to respond.
♪But love has become a two-edged sword♪
But don't push me away either.
Anyhow, I'll keep on pestering you.
♪Knowing each other so well,
you know where it hurts the most♪
♪Say everything that can hurt others♪
These past couple of days have been tiring.
Now, relax and rest well.
♪I feel even more lost afterwards♪
Let me stay with you a while longer.
Once you fall asleep,
I'll leave.
♪Why do this♪
♪Ask yourself whether you are willing♪
♪Willing or not, love has turned into hate♪
♪Who are the tears for♪
♪Who loses and who wins♪
♪Who really cares♪
♪It hurts anyway♪
♪Say everything that can hurt others♪
I'm sorry, Tan Er.
With everything that has happened,
I can no longer turn back.
Rather than implicating you
and putting you in danger,
leaving now is the best choice.
♪It will be even sadder♪
♪Who really cares♪
♪It hurts anyway♪
I really think that
Her Highness really cares for you.
She wasn't concerned about her own safety
and kept helping out, right?
This won't do.
The more Tan Er acts this way,
the sooner I have to leave.
No.
It really isn't my fault.
You know how violent Jing Xin is,
right?
It seems that this plan didn't work,
the rest wouldn't work either.
Only acting with more power
can we win with a single blow,
leaving Her Highness no wiggle room.
Then only that is left...
Please give up this last option.
No.
We cannot fail, we can only succeed.
I'm going to get ready.
Go and tip off Her Highness.
Tell her that I've gone to
Yaju Pavillion.
Isn't that...
Young Master, why not rethink your decision?
I've made up my mind.
Please.
This way.
Please take a seat.
Qing Zhu. Qing Zhu. Qing Zhu.
What a pretty face.
How come we haven't seen you before?
Everything has a price.
Could you play one more song?
I'll pay for the whole day.
You and I both want to pursue this gentleman,
we should compete fair and square.
You...
- Exactly.
- We should compete fair and square.
- Fair and square.
Our Cheng Cheng is so popular.
It makes me full of pride.
A fair-and-square competition.
Don't leave, don't leave.
Please leave your name.
Yaju Pavillion needs such a talent as you.
Sir.
Young Master. Shall we call it quits?
Do you also think that I'm without plans and
strategies?
What else are you going to do?
Yaju Pavillion contradicts my nature.
Starting tomorrow,
I'm going to invite friends over
to the Snow Court with poems
and refined activities.
But where will these friends come from?
This list contains
the names of many ladies.
Go to visit them one by one,
and they will come for sure.
Young Master, when did you collect these names?
The owner of Yaju Pavillion gave me the list,
saying that they are all regulars.
Inform Her Highness on my behalf.
Just say that starting tomorrow,
I will be inviting female friends...
my mistake...
...many female friends to Snow Court.
I hope that she keeps her promise and
won't stop me.
I have to be the messenger again?
I'll go right away.
What? Inviting homewreckers over?
Many homewreckers?
Tan.
Judging by what Yu Hao said,
the secondary prince consort
is set on
committing "being wanton".
But in my opinion,
he's probably just testing the waters,
he won't actually follow through.
Besides, you won't agree to it.
I will. Why won't I?
The worst thing
is not knowing who the other women are.
I can take this opportunity
to catch all the women who are interested
in Mo Lian Cheng in one go.
But this will be bad
for the Princess's Residence's reputation.
What do we do if
those in the Palace find out and punish us for it?
I know Mo Lian Cheng too well.
He's stubborn.
He won't stop until he gets what he wants.
I'll take care of those in the Palace.
It's just a book club.
It won't be a big deal
if the invitations are under my name.
But, Tan,
I'm scared...
True warriors
dare to face their opponents head-on.
Don't worry.
Besides, I have a Plan B.
What B?
It's...
She really agreed to it?
Yes.
Eighth Brother.
Just now, Tan Er sent someone over to inform me
that the entire residence will be entertaining
your female guests tomorrow.
Is this true?
If it is,
I advise you to proceed with caution.
I heard about what happened at Yaju Pavillion.
The Palace and the Mo Residence will catch wind
of it as well.
Let's give the matter
of the divorce papers a further thought.
Eldest Brother, I understand your concerns.
However, what's done cannot be undone.
We've already come this far.
Please help me leave as soon as possible.
This way, please.
I've never seen someone so good-looking.
Young Master,
why don't you think it through once more?
Help me sort out my robes.
The weather is great today.
It's my pleasure to have everyone over at Snow Court
to appreciate poems.
I'm going to share a new Ci.
[*A type of lyric poetry in classical Chinese poetry]
Brows in a curving style, the yellow
shadow on her forehead is hard to tell.
The hairs on her temples appear—
as clouds which, against her cheeks, so fair.
Speaking of women's make-up.
Although it is said that men dress up for those
who love them,
but there isn't a woman who doesn't wish for
great skin and a beautiful face,
right?
Greetings, Second Princess.
No need to be so formal.
Sit.
To thank you for accepting
the prince consort's invitation,
I've prepared a small gift
for everyone.
Jing Xin.
Just a little gift.
This is related to
the poem the prince consort just recited.
Who doesn't want snow-like skin?
Then we must mention
the brow powder I'm holding.
Its scent is very unique.
This is a secret formula of the royal family.
And the Princess's Residence's
special rouge.
After putting on both,
you will look like
the loveliest peach.
And I guarantee that
your make-up will stay on for 24 hours.
Its texture is amazing.
Better than what I bought from Daichunlin
a few days ago.
Fate has brought us together.
How about this?
If you register with Jing Xin,
I promise to
only charge for the raw materials
and the products will be delivered directly
to your residences.
- That's great.
- Great.
Let's go to register.
There's no need to rush.
Everyone will get their own.
Please continue appreciating poems,
continue.
Slowly she rises from her bed and paints her brows.
She takes her time, unhurried,
to complete her makeup.
Her beauty is reflected between two mirrors.
Her...
Natural make-up doesn't include
painting on brows.
But in my opinion,
there is quite a lot to eyebrow make-up.
The highest level
would be looking like you haven't put on
eyebrow make-up while you actually did.
Take a look.
Don't my eyebrows look fluffy?
With Chinese knotweed extract inside,
it is definitely a luxurious treat for
your eyebrows.
It's true.
Her Highness's eyebrows are indeed
a work of art.
Just pick it up!
Since we're sharing,
I'll go all out.
The best deal is coming up.
My next recommendation
is this lip rouge.
Let me try it for everyone.
Look.
Look at this exquisite texture.
- What is this?
- This unique scent.
It really brightens up the complexion.
Oh my god.
This is the scent of a noblewoman.
My heart beats for it.
We can switch out our men,
but our lip colour must stay the same.
What are you waiting for? Let's get it!
- Me!
- Me, too!
Ten! I want ten!
I want fifteen!
I'll take thirty!
Leave one for me!
Yu...
The one used on the fourteenth young master.
Fine.
Yes!
Mo Lian Cheng has committed the seven types
of grounds
and wants to receive divorce papers.
However, Qu Tan Er doesn't seem to mind
and has not made any moves.
The seven types of grounds?
This is definitely not something
the original eighth young master of the Mo family
would do.
Asking for repudiation papers is indeed puzzling.
Go.
Find out everything you can about
this Mo Lian Cheng.
Yes.
(Mo Residence)
Mo Lian Cheng acts recklessly and suspiciously.
He is asking for divorce papers and
wants to leave the Princess's Residence.
Could it be...
Lian Cheng's actions have put us in
a difficult position.
I will make sure to inquire about it.
Please focus on the big picture,
don't let this divert your attention.
Mr. Mo, this is a serious matter.
If there is no backup,
what insurance do my righteous troops have?
Besides, it is impossible
for the empress not to notice.
Patience.
Under the empress's orders,
Xiao Zhen has increased the tax rates
for farmers of the four counties of Jingdu
once again.
In a country where its people are suffering,
we should act as one
and not blame each other.
My son is just a pawn
in this grand scheme.
I know what to do.
Okay, I believe you.
I'll be leaving now. Goodbye.
Alright.
Making sales is easy for me, the queen of realtors.
Cheng Cheng underestimated me.
But I have to thank him.
It's you.
You scared me.
You came at the right time.
Prince Consort, you made great contributions
to the sales.
Don't worry.
I'll be giving out dividends periodically.
How about
toasting to our success?
Your Highness is of high social status,
there is no need for you to make a living
out of selling make-up.
Aren't you afraid of
giving others leverage on you?
What's wrong with me earning my own living
with my own skills?
You, on the other hand,
have committed "being wanton" repeatedly.
Are you not afraid of giving others leverage on you?
Your Highness,
I want to...
Do you have
a favour to ask of me?
If you want to ask for a favour,
you should be mindful of your attitude,
shouldn't you?
(Divorce Paper)
Divorce paper?
Your Highness, please consent to my wishes
and allow me to leave the residence as soon
as possible.
Okay.
Okay?
Why didn't...
No...
Are you
saying yes?
I am.
However, I had asked you for divorce papers
as well.
This time, we need to do things the same way
as before.
If this is the case,
so be it.
I am not someone who betrays others.
I won't impose on others what I do not desire.
This last time,
we'll do things your way.
Okay.
A promise is a promise.
Come on.
What is the meaning of this?
Sleep with me.
If I'm satisfied,
you can have the divorce papers.
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪A flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part,
no matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part,
no matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind
in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪