=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 39=
Have you long known that
Bai Jue is back?
He’s...?
Yes.
Houchi,
Qingmu is Bai Jue.
I had thought
you could enjoy a happy reunion
for at least a while.
I never expected...
The day has finally come.
Houchi,
now that Bai Jue woke up,
Qingmu no longer exists.
To Bai Jue,
the relationship between you and Qingmu
means nothing.
No way!
He’s Bai Jue and he’s Qingmu, too.
He won’t ever forget me.
Houchi.
He has forgotten you.
Fengran,
tell me.
What on earth happened?
Why did Jinglei say
you slaughtered the Feng Clan?
I was drawn to the Parasol Forest
when the Feng Clan
had already been exterminated.
Later, Jingjian and I
were trapped by some weird power.
Only Qingmu
fought the woman who pretended to be me.
When we woke up,
he had become Bai Jue.
He didn’t remember anything.
He forgot everything.
He didn’t remember anything
about Qingmu, either.
Where’s Bai Jue?
He rebuilt Changyuan Hall,
and now in the Dome,
he is commanding the Three Realms
as the True God.
Houchi!
Where are you going?
I’m going to see him.
He doesn’t remember you anymore.
If you leave now,
what’s the point
of a hundred years’ captivity?
If I don’t see him myself
and he doesn’t tell me he forgot me,
I won’t believe that
he no longer remembers me.
It was him
who set up this barrier.
Ordinary immortals
can only get in but can’t get out.
Even if
you don’t care about your life,
what about the baby?
You want to die with him?
My life?
Qingmu’s life is mine.
He abandoned everything for me.
He’s waiting for me,
but I’ll only care about my life,
instead of saving him?
Houchi, wake up.
He’s now Bai Jue.
No one is waiting for you anymore.
You said that
if Shanggu woke up,
I might be gone.
Is it the same thing
between Qingmu and Bai Jue?
Do you think
Bai Jue will allow Qingmu to exist?
Then I’ll get back
the Ghost Suppressing Tower!
I must find Qingmu!
Houchi!
Qingmu’s spiritual sense was crushed
by the power of True God.
Let alone the Ghost Suppressing Tower,
even the Ancestral God couldn’t help.
He and I had a wedding
and we promised to grow old together.
He has never changed his promise
or broken it.
Neither will I.
No matter who he is now,
he’s always my husband
and the father of my baby.
Jingyuan,
please let me get out.
If you get out now,
you’ll only hurt yourself.
Jingyuan,
Qingmu has no father or mother.
He even has only a couple of friends.
Maybe from this day on,
no one will remember
his existence in this world.
His feelings
and his life
can’t be decided by someone else.
Now, I’m the only one
who can struggle for him.
When there’s even slim hope
to keep him alive,
I won’t give up.
Unless I see True God Bai Jue in person,
I won’t believe that
he can be so cruel
and fate can be so heartless to us.
Jingyuan,
I beg you. Let me out.
All right.
I can let you out.
But you must promise me something.
What?
Accept the truth
and bid farewell to Qingmu.
I don’t have a choice.
After I kill Tianqi and Bai Jue,
I’ll return to an immortal again.
I hear that
True God Bai Jue has forgotten
all the past.
He doesn’t remember who Qingmu is.
He doesn’t remember
or he pretends he doesn’t?
He split his Original Being
and was in sleep
for sixty thousand years.
When he woke up,
he had a great fight with you.
His Spiritual Strength
must have been injured.
Whether it’s true,
I’ll try and see.
Your Highness,
Prince Jingyang has been waiting outside
for a long time.
Thank you so much
for helping me when I’m in trouble.
I’m flattered, Your Highness.
It was my duty to help you.
From this day on,
we must be very careful
in doing anything.
Keep it to yourself
that I’ve become a devil.
I understand, Your Highness.
Greetings, Mother.
You may rise.
Mother, I come to get you back.
You indeed care for me most.
Jingyang,
it’s not a hundred years yet.
Why did your father
suddenly want me back?
Mother, something happened
to the Feng Clan.
Father invited you to go back
and handle the Parasol Forest problem.
What happened to the Parasol Forest?
I don’t dare to talk about it.
Mother, please go back
and discuss with Father.
Mother,
True God Bai Jue woke up, too.
He did?
It’s great luck for immortals.
Yes.
But Bai Jue is Qingmu...
It doesn’t matter who he was.
Now that Bai Jue woke up,
I should go visit him.
It’s been sixty thousand years.
I wonder if he’s still
the True God he used to be.
Now that you want to visit him,
I’ll tell Jingzhao first.
Why?
Since True God Bai Jue woke up,
he’s been staying in the Dome
and Jingzhao has been looking after him.
At present,
she’s obviously been
in charge of the Dome.
(Changyuan Hall)
Greetings, Mother.
You may rise.
Let me take a good look at you.
Mother, I haven’t seen you for years.
How are you keeping these years?
Everything is fine with me.
I have something private
to tell my mother.
You don’t need to serve us.
Leave us.
- Yes.
Mother,
let me show you around the garden.
All right.
I knew you would come today,
and I asked Master Bai Jue
to order the Flower Fairy
to get all flowers in full bloom
so that you can enjoy them.
Jingzhao,
does Bai Jue really not remember Qingmu?
He doesn’t, I suppose.
Otherwise,
he wouldn’t be so nice to me.
He’s very nice to you?
No one is close to him,
but me.
I also take care of everything
in Changyuan Hall.
But Bai Jue never likes any girl.
Why is he so different to you?
Can he be fooling you?
Mind your words, Mother.
Are you sure
what you exactly want?
Mother,
all I want
is to stay with Master every day.
That’s enough for me.
It’s not enough.
You must get the status you deserve.
There’s no rush about it.
You must make Bai Jue like you
and marry you with a wedding.
Only when you
become the real hostess of the Dome
can you get the most benefits.
Don’t worry, Mother.
When I’m here in the Dome,
I understand it.
No one can be the most honorable,
but the True God.
Good girl.
You look
as dignified as me
when I first took charge
of the Pilgrimage Hall.
Master Bai Jue really cares
for Princess Jingzhao.
When she simply said
she wanted to enjoy the flowers,
he summoned the Flower Fairy
and she conjured the flowers overnight.
Yeah.
Master Bai Jue is cold,
but he dotes on Princess Jingzhao.
He also only lets her serve him.
Looks like there’ll be a wedding
in the Dome.
Ladies,
why did I hear that
Master had married Goddess Houchi
in the Human Realm a hundred years ago?
Could he marry someone else?
Don’t talk nonsense.
It was North Sea Lord
who had an engagement with Houchi.
What does it concern Master Bai Jue?
Besides,
Houchi is no longer a goddess.
How can she be compared
with Princess Jingzhao?
But isn’t North Sea Lord
Master Bai Jue?
His Majesty issued an order.
Qingmu
is a mere body of Master Bai Jue’s.
Don’t talk nonsense.
Or I’ll tell Her Grace about it.
You’ll no longer be an immortal
and will be exiled to the Human Realm.
I won’t.
Lingzhi,
I don’t dare to talk about this again.
Who’s there?
How dare you break into the Dome!
This place is a wild swamp,
under no jurisdiction
of the Three Realms.
Why can’t I get in?
This place
is where True God Bai Jue
cultivates himself.
No one of the three Realm shall come in,
unless summoned.
If you want to get in,
you should tell us your name,
submit a visiting card
and request to see Princess Jingzhao.
Submit a visiting card
and request to see Jingzhao?
Then go ask Qingmu for me.
Can I not come to the Dome
unless he summons me?
You...
You are...?
What?
Recognized me?
Greetings, Goddess Houchi.
Where’s Qingmu?
Goddess Houchi,
do you mean Master Bai Jue?
Don’t ask questions to which
you already know the answer.
Master...
At this time every day,
he’s reading in the peach forest.
Unless the sea gets dry,
I’ll always be with you.
Bow to each other.
In a hundred years,
remember
to get me home.
The tea is cold. I don’t need more.
Qingmu,
I’m back.
I know.
When you promised me something,
you wouldn’t break it.
Qingmu,
is that you?
You can recognize me, right?
You look like her.
But you’re not her.
Qingmu,
I’m your wife who you proposed to
with your body.
You promised
to grow old with me
and never leave me even when we die.
You promised me
you would wait until I came back.
I’m not Qingmu.
I’m not married.
Who are you?
Master.
This is Goddess Houchi
from Qingchi Palace.
Gu Jun’s daughter?
You’re a mere immortal.
How dare you call yourself Goddess!
When you kept mentioning Qingmu,
I answered you a bit more.
Qingmu
is an immoral body of mine.
No matter how you’re related to him,
it means nothing to me.
See her out.
You heard Master.
This is the Dome,
instead of your Qingchi Palace.
You can’t do whatever you want
or disturb Master Bai Jue.
Master?
Look carefully.
Looking at his face and heart,
he’s Qingmu!
All right.
If you’re not Qingmu...
Master Bai Jue,
please give Qingmu back to me.
He’s dead.
His spiritual sense must be there.
Give it back to me.
When I woke up,
his spiritual sense disappeared.
He’s dead.
No matter whether you believe it,
this is the truth.
Also,
I shouldn’t pay the price
for your relationship.
Master Bai Jue is kind to you,
for the sake of his friendship
with your father.
Please behave yourself.
Is dinner ready?
Yes.
All your favorite dishes.
I made them myself.
Thank you.
Forget it.
I won’t punish you today.
Declare to the Three Realms.
Set up a cenotaph in the North Sea
so that Qingmu’s friends of this life
could go and mourn for him.
However,
if anyone breaks into the Dome again
in the name of looking for Qingmu,
I won’t let him go.
Yes.
Cenotaph?
A True God like him
sent me away
with a mere cenotaph.
In his eyes,
is Qingmu only a tool
to make him wake up?
When I see you trapped in love,
I’m overjoyed.
As you can see,
Qingmu has chosen me this time.
No.
I mean Master Bai Jue.
Who cares?
Anyway, I won.
If you’re wise enough to know yourself,
don’t come to pester him again.
He’s the True God, so what?
Even if I have to go against the world,
I’ll get justice for Qingmu.
Greetings, Master.
Don’t bother. You may rise.
It’s been years.
Master, you still look awesome.
I haven’t changed.
But you’ve changed a lot.
Wu Huan,
over the past years,
you and Muguang have protected immortals
and defended the Heavenly Realm.
You’ve had hard work.
Without the instruction
from you and Goddess Shanggu,
I would have still been
a mere colorful phoenix.
That year, Master Zhiyang
left the Immortals to us.
We just did what we should do.
We don’t dare to take credit.
You’re as modest as you were.
Don’t worry.
I’ll remember
what you and Muguang have done.
Now the Feng Clan is in trouble,
and devil power is involved.
You were just back
from the Nether World
where devils are sealed.
You should figure out the truth
as soon as possible,
suppress the devil power
and bring peace back
to the Three Realms.
Yes, Master.
Master,
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
You just woke up
and you may not know it.
The Demon God Tianqi isn’t dead.
He hides in the Demon Realm,
under the assumed name of Jingyuan
and does harm to the Three Realms.
Speaking of it,
you killed the Demon God in person.
What do you mean?
I just have some confusion.
I wonder why Tianqi came back to life.
Tianqi destroyed the world
and he deserves to be killed.
I was badly wounded at that time.
Maybe,
that’s why he kept some
of his Spiritual Strength.
Who knows?
I see.
That year,
demons helped Tianqi
to destroy the world.
Is it the reason
why you keep fighting them
over the past sixty thousand years?
You know the fights
between immortals and demons?
When the God Realm existed,
immortals and demons
could stay in peace.
Now, there’re continuous fights.
I fail to live up
to your trust on me.
You don’t need to apologize.
It’s your duty.
Yes.
Master,
you must have seen Houchi.
Don’t you think
she looks like Shanggu?
Shanggu, no contest.
How dare you compare
an ordinary immortal to Shanggu!
I’m sorry.
It’s just that
when I think of what happened,
I couldn’t help feeling sad.
I couldn’t believe that
Goddess Shanggu indeed disappeared.
It’s been sixty thousand years.
The dead won’t come back to life.
Mother,
Master Bai Jue just woke up.
Why must you bring this up
to make him sad?
Master,
my mother seldom came to the Dome.
Let’s invite her to stay for dinner,
shall we?
Now that you care for your mother,
let’s do it, then.
Thank you, Master.
Lord,
why did you let Her Grace go and suffer?
One has to enjoy and suffer
what he deserves.
What goes around comes around.
Now that she has left,
why don’t you go back
to the Third Heaven first?
When you were away,
the tribe was turbulent.
I know.
About the Demon Gathering Streamer,
he’s been dissatisfied with me.
It doesn’t matter.
I know the score.
But...
All right.
Send Fengran back to Qingchi Palace.
I’ll stay for a few more days.
I’m afraid
there’ll be something wrong
with Bai Jue.
Yes.
No matter whether you believe it,
this is the truth.
Qingmu
is an immoral body of mine.
No matter how you’re related to him,
it means nothing to me.
No matter whether you believe it,
this is the truth.
Declare to the Three Realms.
Set up a cenotaph in the North Sea
so that Qingmu’s friends of this life
could go and mourn for him.
Houchi!
Father.
Fate makes fool of people.
If I hadn’t been softhearted,
you wouldn’t have been suffering.
Houchi,
do you feel better?
Father.
Come on.
He’s lost his memories.
He doesn’t remember anything.
I wonder what happened.
You went to see him?
He doesn’t remember anything?
That doesn’t matter.
As long as I’m alive,
the sky won’t fall.
I couldn’t recognize him at all.
He’s totally another man.
Is there really no hope
to bring Qingmu back to life?
He was an immortal.
But he just disappeared?
Take care of your baby first.
I’ll think of a way for you.
Father.
Look at you.
You’re pregnant,
but you didn’t tell me first.
I mean...
It’s our happy event.
I’m going to be a grandfather.
Take a good rest.
Father.
Tomorrow,
I’ll go prepare something
for my grandson.
Let Fengran do that.
No.
How can I let her go?
She has a bad taste.
Besides,
I picked every single thing
you used
when you were little.
So, when I was little,
I was like a boy.
How can we distinguish the gender
of a little baby?
Then you only bought me
toys for boys,
like carriage, slingshot and weapon?
I didn’t know
what girls would like.
Then why didn’t you
ask the female immortals around you?
You’ve been alone all these years.
Don’t you have even one female friend?
I’m...
I’m not very good at that.
Father,
if I also leave someday,
you’ll be lonely in Qingchi Palace.
You’d better have some company.
Right?
You also leave?
What do you mean leave?
Where are you going?
Houchi,
as long as you’re in Qingchi Palace,
I won’t feel lonely.
Look at you.
You’re so anxious.
I don’t want my grandson
to be like you.
If your grandson
is like Qingmu,
that’ll be great.
Why?
I’m the most important person for him.
After he’s born,
I’ll take care of everything for him.
Don’t cry.
All right.
Have a good rest.
Come on.
Let me help you.
When you wake up,
everything will be fine.
Your Highness,
His Majesty came at dinner.
He did?
What did he say?
Nothing.
When His Majesty knew
you had dinner at Master Bai Jue’s hall,
he was very happy.
He said you suffered in the Nether World
and asked us to take good care of you.
Sounds like he has forgiven me.
I think
His Majesty still cares a lot about you
and wants a good relationship with you.
You’re still the most honorable goddess.
Before,
when I heard this,
I would be very happy.
But now...
After I suffered in the Nether World,
I made up my mind.
I must decide it myself
whether I’m the most honorable goddess.
Even the Heavenly Emperor
can’t decide it for me.
Sorry, I didn’t mean that.
Please punish me, Your Highness.
You may rise.
You don’t need to kneel.
I wasn’t angry.
I wasn’t feeling sorry
for myself, either.
I’m not in such a mood.
In the Dome,
did you figure out the truth?
Bai Jue was very cautious.
He didn’t admit that he was Qingmu
or that Houchi was related to Shanggu.
If Master Bai Jue remembered Qingmu,
he wouldn’t have invited you
to stay for dinner.
Bai Jue is meticulous.
I strongly feel that
he became Boxuan
and lived in Qingchi Palace
so that he could bring Shanggu
back to life.
If Houchi is really Shanggu,
she has seen what I’ve done
over the years.
When she wakes up,
I’ll have nothing, but punishment.
I only meant to suppress Houchi.
But now,
I must find a chance to exterminate her
to get rid of future trouble.
Master Bai Jue won’t let you do that.
I also don’t understand
why he’s stalling.
Bai Jue hasn’t got his power back yet.
He still looks weak.
He can’t cover it up.
To me,
it’s a great chance.
I’ll cultivate myself carefully.
When I achieve enough devil power
and become the Devil God,
I’ll be afraid of no god or goddess.
All problems
will be readily solved.
What are we going to do next?
I’ve completed the first step
of leaving the Nether World.
Fengnyu,
go find Elder Danfeng to me.
When she is still alive,
I can’t sleep soundly.
Yes.
To be a god or devil,
does it matter?
It does, of course.
I’m the Heavenly Empress.
How can I become a devil?
You’re wrong.
Who judges the god or devil,
and who determines life and death...
That’s the most important thing.
Greetings, Master Bai Jue.
I knew you would come.
Master Bai Jue,
I came here
to ask you something.
Do you remember
the Tribulation of Chaos
sixty thousand years ago?
When the Three Realms live, you live.
You’re the Chief God of Chaos.
I won’t let you die.
I won’t let you die!
Master Bai Jue,
my master’s spiritual sense
has been bred for forty thousand years,
but she hasn’t got out yet.
You spent half of your power
to draw the God-reincarnation Spell.
It will disappear tomorrow.
If my master can’t come out today,
our efforts over so many years
will be wasted.
She’s Shanggu.
If she can’t change her fate,
who else can help her?
Master!
Keep your voice down.
Don’t disturb her.
She’s just come into being
and she’s very weak.
You must take good care of her.
Yes.
Master,
why did you seal her Spiritual Strength?
On the Heaven and Earth Platform,
she said she didn’t want
to be a goddess again.
Now that this is her wish,
in this life,
she’ll no longer be Shanggu.
But...
We never know what will happen.
And the future is unpredictable.
When she’s no longer the Chief God,
she doesn’t need to bear responsibilities
for the whole world.
It’s her luck.
Woods sway in the wind.
Houchi means the rising moon.
Houchi will be your name, then.
Houchi,
grow up happily.
I’ll take care of you in this life
and make you safe and carefree.
Houchi.
You gave her the name.
To save Goddess Shanggu,
you became Boxuan and took care of her
for tens of thousands of years.
But when Goddess Shanggu
comes back to life,
it means
the Tribulation of Chaos
hasn’t disappeared.
No one but I
knew that
it was you
who sealed the Tribulation
for the moment.
Why are you bringing this up?
Later,
you suffered the pain
of splitting your Original Being
and made another body
to absorb the demon power.
Ten thousand years ago,
you went to the North Sea,
trying to mix your immortal power
with his demon power
so that you can get the Power of Chaos.
So?
So,
I came to make clear.
When you’re back now,
will you stick to the original plan?
Will you still sacrifice yourself
for Goddess Shanggu
and for the Three Realms?
If you stick to the plan,
why did you pretend
you lost your memories,
destroy Qingmu
and make Houchi so sad?
I planned everything,
but I didn’t predict that
the body that absorbed the demon power
and possessed supreme demon power
had generated his own Spiritual Strength
and swallowed me
when I was going to mix with him.
Tens of thousands of years later,
I woke up and found out that
he had been in love with Houchi.
Why did I pretend to have lost memories?
I should ask you.
What were you doing?
Why didn’t you stop it?
I...
I tried to stop it but failed.
I’m dying already.
Only when I deceive Houchi
and end our relationship
will she give up on me.
But...
When Goddess Shanggu wakes up
and knows you were harsh to Houchi
and you took the Tribulation for her,
she will hate you.
It’s better than losing her life.
As long as she hates me,
she won’t get hurt because of my death.
When she’s alive,
I’ll be satisfied
and there’ll be hope
for the Three Realms.
Master,
I’m in debt to Master Shanggu.
I’ll willing to help you
with this plan.
Over the hundreds of thousands of years,
I’ve already seen Houchi
as my own daughter.
It pains me
to see her heartbroken.
Then why didn’t you do anything
when she confined herself to
the Hidden Mountain for so long?
You could’ve stopped it
but you sit back and watch
the newly-wed separated
for decades.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪