=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 40=
I’m in debt to Master Shanggu.
I’ll willing to help you
with this plan.
Over the hundreds of thousands of years,
I’ve already seen Houchi
as my own daughter.
It pains me
to see her heartbroken.
Then why didn’t you do anything
when she confined herself to
the Hidden Mountain for so long?
You could’ve stopped it
but you sit back and watch
the newly-wed separated
for decades.
I accept whatever my fate is
but it’s not even 100 years.
Houchi hasn’t come back.
I can’t give up now.
No one knows
how much Qingmu
has suffered better than me.
I can’t imagine how Houchi feels.
Give Qingmu back!
He’s dead.
His spiritual sense
must still be intact.
I need that back.
Forget it.
The past is the past.
I understand.
I’ll also
keep everything secret.
But
Houchi is helplessly
in love with Qingmu.
You can’t talk her
into giving him up.
Do you have other ideas?
Not yet.
What about that demon
you fought against
in the Parasol Forest that day?
Do you know who that is?
It was Wu Huan.
I let her out of
the Nether World on purpose.
Strangely,
I couldn’t detect any trace
of Devilish Energy on her.
Why did Wu Huan do that?
She’s the Heavenly Empress.
We need solid proof
to call her a demon.
I don’t care
who she is.
It’s just that after my awakening,
I went to the Abyssal Ridge Swamp.
My power was weakened
to stall the Tribulation of Chaos.
We don’t know what the demons are up to,
so we must be careful.
Check everything secretly.
This time,
no accident
is allowed.
Yes.
Go back and comfort Houchi.
I hurt her feelings
when she came to see me.
She must be upset.
The future can’t be changed.
I have no choice
but to be indifferent.
From now on,
Houchi and I had better
not see each other again.
If you really care about her,
then pay more attention to her.
Better a little loss than a long sorrow.
Yes, Master.
Master.
I saw God Light flash across the Dome.
Was that God Gu Jun?
He came for his daughter Houchi.
Master, you should know
Qingmu and I also had an engagement.
Without Houchi,
we would’ve gotten married long ago.
You two had an engagement?
Yes.
Father betrothed me to him.
I let you stay at the Dome
only because you saved me.
You’d better not
transfer your affections
from Qingmu to me, too.
I didn’t mean that, Master.
You’re a god.
My feelings are insignificant.
But if you wish
to cut all ties with the Qingchi Palace,
once we get married,
Houchi will give up.
I have no feelings for you at all.
Aren’t you worried
about your reputation?
I wouldn’t even dream of your love.
Marrying you
is all I can hope for.
Are you sure?
Heaven and earth can be my witnesses.
Fine. You’ll get what you wish for.
Thank you, Master.
Qingmu.
Do you regret
doing all this for me?
As long as you’re with me,
I have no regrets at all.
Let’s be an ordinary couple,
living long
and growing old together.
Qingmu.
Shanggu, come back!
Please!
I’m entrusting the Three Realms
with you.
In the next life,
I don’t want to be a god,
but to be with you.
The Three Realms live and die with you.
You cannot die!
Turns out Master Bai Jue
cares so much about Master Shanggu.
Who are you?
Chief Goddess Shanggu,
finally, you can see me.
I’ve been alone in this void
for thousands of years.
You’re my first visitor.
You must be lonely.
Why do we look identical?
I wish we didn’t.
Unfortunately,
I was born
to be a container
of your Spiritual Strength.
I didn’t have a choice.
A container?
What does that mean?
Since the Tribulation of Chaos,
I’ve been wandering
in the void, you know?
I feel sorry for you, too.
You don’t know who you are
or why you exist.
I’m fine.
Now, you’re here with me, aren’t you?
Could you
tell me more?
What do you want to know?
Did you
see Bai Jue outside?
Him?
He’s fine,
but Qingmu is gone.
Qingmu?
I’m your surrogate
and Qingmu is Bai Jue’s.
When you woke up,
we’d disappear.
No one would remember us.
I don’t get that.
Bai Jue’s mission
is to guard the Three Realms.
Why would he hurt anyone
for himself?
He just did.
I begged him
to give Qingmu back to me,
but he only saw Qingmu as dust
that he could crush or blow away easily.
Has he ever considered
my feelings?
Fate is always fair to everyone.
When it comes,
we can only accept it.
All we can do
is to ask ourselves
what choices we should make
and what our duty is.
Liar!
If our fate is to be Gods,
what about yours?
You sacrificed yourself
in face of the Tribulation of Chaos.
Was that for the greater good?
Of course.
I’m the Chief God.
Hadn’t I done that,
millions of innocent lives
would be gone
for nothing.
Then before you died,
why did you wish not to be a god again?
Chief God or not,
I’m just like an ordinary person.
I simply wish
I could be with
the love of my life.
I lost Qingmu.
Could I wish for our reunion
in the next life?
Qingmu!
If it were you,
would you forgive them?
Qingmu,
do you know
why I always win you by half a point?
Now,
let me show you my move.
You were an attacker
and you always placed
the pieces like this.
While I’m a defender,
so I could block you.
You know
you were fearless.
You’d rush in and make a mess.
I was cautious
and thorough.
So we always
ended up in a stalemate.
But check out
this move.
I deliberately made a mistake
to lure you in.
You were eager to win
and make a clean sweep.
But I
blocked your way out
and get rid of your help.
That way,
I’d win you by exactly half a point.
I see.
That’s right.
No more no less.
(Qingmu’s Tomb)
Your Grace,
which one do you think
is better?
If Houchi gives birth to a baby girl,
she can wear the pink one.
I like the red one.
It’s adorable.
Keep them both then.
Sure.
Houchi grew up
with these toys.
Put them in, too.
You mean these?
Boys would love them.
Girls may not.
Her Grace
was such a tomboy when she was little.
Put these ducks
and carriages in the case, too.
Girls may also like them.
I agree.
Your Grace,
you’ve been picking toys for four hours.
The case is almost filled up.
You can buy more toys
when the baby is born.
You’re right.
There’s still plenty of time.
Bring these back
to the study.
Yes.
What’s the occasion?
Your Highness,
you probably haven’t heard
that Princess Jingzhao
will soon be married into the Dome.
Really?
His Majesty betrothed her
to True God Bai Jue and he said yes.
Everyone in the Palace
is busy preparing for the wedding.
Enough!
You volunteer to guard the Demon Region?
Yes.
I’ve told you
Master Bai Jue had imprisoned Fengran
simply to
find the demon behind.
So
I wouldn’t blame you for letting her go.
Why are you punishing yourself?
Father,
news came in last night
about Sen Yu’s suspicious moves lately.
I’m getting worried,
so I’m going to the Demon Region soon
for the safety of the border.
How dare those demons
stir up trouble again!
But with Master here,
those demons won’t be a problem.
You can leave
after your sister and Master’s wedding.
Yes.
Father,
have you found anything about
the Devilish Energy
that killed the Feng Clan?
Nothing so far.
The only eyewitness Elder Danfeng
is missing.
Isn’t that my feather?
Where did you get it?
Jingjian?
Father.
Are you alright?
You seem worried
and pale.
I might be sleep-deprived lately.
Father, if there’s nothing else,
I’d like to go back and rest.
Jingjian.
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
I still have work to do.
Please excuse me.
Hold on.
Do I look like a monster?
I know there are
unresolved issues between us
in terms of the Twin Spear.
But that was a long time ago.
Now that we’re finally together,
why not bury the hatchet
and move on?
Mother,
just drop that caring look.
It only
freaks me out.
What are you talking about?
I’ll leave for the Demon Region
after Jingzhao’s wedding.
And
I won’t come back again.
Please don’t
betray Father’s trust again
for my sake.
Jingjian!
Your Highness,
Prince Jingjian has been like that
ever since he came back
from the Parasol Forest.
Did he
stumble on the secret there?
Go check it out.
I want to know
everything he did there.
Yes.
Master,
I failed in my duty.
Fengran has been back at
the Qingchi Palace for days,
but there’s nothing new
regarding the Parasol Forest case.
Do you...?
Demons are the key to that case.
As long as the God Realm reopens,
demons won’t be our match
even with a new Devil God.
We’ve had three out of Four Weapons:
Taicang Spear,
Purple Moon Whip, Twin Spear.
But there’s no trace of
the Ancestral Sword.
All of you, be careful!
You’re holding the fine wine
all races made for
Master and my wedding.
If it’s spilled,
I won’t be easy on you!
Focus!
No mistake is allowed.
- Yes.
I’m getting married.
Why are you sulking?
That’s the spirit.
I didn’t teach her well.
Please forgive me.
Is it true?
Absolutely!
That river deer next door told me.
I didn’t believe him
and went uphill to ask around.
All Three Realms have known it.
They all say Master Bai Jue
and Princess Jingzhao
are getting married.
How could Qingmu do that?
Even if he didn’t remember
young Goddess,
how could he marry Jingzhao?
I’m going to give God Gu Jun a heads-up.
Go tell everyone in the Palace
not to say a word to young Goddess.
Got it?
Have you seen Houchi?
No.
I’ve been looking for you everywhere.
There you are.
What do you need me for?
Jingjian sent us a letter,
saying Qingmu’s tomb
at the North Sea is done.
I guess you’d like to take a look.
Fengran,
Ghost Suppressing Tower
is no longer in the Huajing Pond.
What about Boxuan?
Qingmu began to look for his memory
because of him.
That Tower protecting Boxuan is gone.
Maybe Qingmu
has something to do with it.
No way.
Only Master, you and I
have access to this place.
No one else can come in.
I’m going to the North Sea.
I’ll join you.
I can go there myself.
Houchi!
Your Highness, Fengran went
to the Parasol Forest
to meet with Elder Danfeng.
Why that little bastard?
I heard her mumbling something
about “Queen of Phoenix’s daughter”
and “Abyssal Ridge Swamp”.
It was you!
You killed Queen of Phoenix!
No, I didn’t do it!
I didn’t kill her!
Queen of Phoenix’s fake spirit
didn’t fool me.
When I finally tracked down
Wuxi and Feng Yan,
Feng Yan was already pregnant.
I asked you to kill them,
but unexpectedly,
you let their daughter go
behind my back!
You killed the Feng Clan!
It was you!
You should’ve been dead long ago.
Wu Huan,
once Queen of Phoenix returns,
you’ll end up in hell!
Speak!
Is Fengran
her daughter?
Wu Huan, you’ll meet your doom!
We still have plenty of
unborn phoenixes.
Once our clan is rebuilt,
you’ll be the only Chief Elder.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Fengran,
if you really are her daughter,
then you leave me no choice.
Your Grace,
Bai Jue and Jingzhao
are getting married!
Those two are getting married?
Your Grace,
how could he do this to Houchi?
Fengran!
Don’t worry too much.
Houchi has left for the North Sea.
That place is almost empty.
She won’t hear anything.
Listen,
Master Bai Jue is no longer Qingmu.
Whatever happens in the Heavenly Palace
has nothing to do with us.
Don’t stick your nose
into the Dome’s business.
- Yes.
Master Bai Jue,
is this how you
force Houchi to give up?
It’s rather cruel
to her.
Don’t you find it strange
that His Grace didn’t do anything
when the Heavenly Palace
insulted Houchi like this?
Knowing how sad young Goddess is,
God Gu Jun must be sadder.
I guess he chose to do nothing
in order to
protect his daughter.
Instruction feather from the Dome.
Is Master Bai Jue
inviting us to his wedding?
I’ll go tell His Grace.
Hold on.
It’s not for him.
It’s for me.
You?
He asked to see me in the Dome
to tell me about my background.
How could he know that?
He and Jingzhao’s wedding is a day away.
He’s calling you now...
Perfect timing.
He betrayed Houchi.
His Grace might be able to suck that up,
but I can’t!
My lady,
His Grace just ordered us
to behave ourselves.
I know what I’m doing. Don’t tell him.
Heavenly Empress?
You used Bai Jue’s feather
to lure me here.
That’s right.
I faked that instruction feather.
You impersonated a god.
Aren’t you afraid Bai Jue
will punish you?
Punish me?
Once you’re dead,
who’d know you were here
or punish me
for a missing person?
I’m a member of the Qingchi Palace.
You think God Gu Jun
wouldn’t do anything?
What could he do?
A Fire Phoenix indeed!
When Chief God was around
and asked me to pick
the Divine Beast in the Feng Clan,
you weren’t my best choice
for your humble birth.
But one thing led to another,
Chief God was in favor of you
and you entered The Pilgrimage Hall
of the God Realm.
Also, your distinguished service
in the Abyssal Ridge Swamp Battle
can’t be neglected.
Our whole clan is proud of you.
Now, I’m appointing you
Leader of the Feng Clan.
Wu Huan,
are you up for it?
Leader of the Feng Clan?
I...
I’m only a fifth-level phoenix.
Am I really qualified?
Queen’s nirvana
is delayed for some reason.
Well,
everything happens
for a reason.
But remember,
no matter what happens in the future,
you must wait until
the new Queen is born
and give your position back to her.
Understand?
I...
Keep this in mind
that the Queen of Phoenix is reborn
at the Fire Phoenix’s nirvana.
Only the Fire Phoenix
is our hope.
You should’ve been dead
when you were born.
All these years are borrowed.
But you were still unsatisfied
and insisted on going to
the Parasol Forest
to find out who you are
and steal my position.
Fengran,
you only end up like this
because you want more
than you should have.
It’s greed
that buries you eventually.
You were there when I was born?
I’m really a phoenix!
Who are my parents?
Why did they abandon me?
You don’t know?
Fine.
I’ll tell you everything before you die.
Your mother is Feng Yan,
a phoenix after nirvana
and the only Fire Phoenix.
But she disregarded our mission
to be a Divine Beast
and eloped with Wuxi,
the founder of the Parasol Forest.
You’re their daughter,
so you’re also a Fire Phoenix
and entitled to be the Queen.
If I could be the next Queen,
why did they dump me at
the Abyssal Ridge Swamp
when I was born?
I did that.
How could I allow another phoenix
to threaten my position?
So I had them stalked
and killed by Danfeng.
But little did I know
that she left you there
and spared your life.
You killed my parents!
I’ll destroy you!
Your spiritual power will be sucked dry
and made into a core
by this Blending Formation in 24 hours.
By taking it,
I’ll become the true Queen of Phoenix.
Fengran,
you’ll never be able to
get your revenge!
Today is a big day
for both me and my daughter.
Fengran is in danger!
(Double Happiness)
So what if he married you once?
He’s marrying me now.
Jingzhao.
Greetings, Mother.
You may leave.
- Yes.
Is there anything you’d like to tell me?
When today is over,
you’ll become the noblest figure
in all Three Realms.
Have you ever considered
what you will do
if those of the Qingchi Palace
come to sabotage your wedding?
I won, and she lost.
What else could she do?
Like she could turn
the world upside down!
It’s not that simple.
Never mind.
From now on,
you can relax
and be the prettiest bride.
I’ve asked Jingyang
to send a strong force to the Dome.
If Houchi breaks in to make trouble,
she won’t be able to get out.
Thank you, Mother.
Qingmu,
even to this day,
I can’t accept the fact
that you’re gone.
This is an empty tomb.
What’s the proof of death?
A few words True God said?
I don’t buy that.
(Qingmu’s Tomb)
Qingmu,
I’m pregnant.
You’re going to be a father.
I was
going to tell you that in person
to see how excited you’d be.
But now,
I could only imagine
your reaction.
Houchi.
Qingmu!
♪Become veins and engraved in the palm♪
♪Countless twists and turns
Drifting away for many times♪
♪I can’t help missing you
But I can only hug your back♪
Dear Houchi,
by the time you see this image,
I must’ve been gone.
I didn’t want to leave you,
but I couldn’t do anything.
♪In the name of the world
Protect a heart♪
Since we rescued Boxuan,
I’ve got others’ memories in my head.
Rescue Boxuan?
Right outside the cave in the North Sea,
how Boxuan opened the ice cave
suddenly came to me,
so I followed suit.
Qingmu?
I didn’t know what happened.
Maybe
once we found Boxuan,
he’d have all the answers.
When his ice coffin was opened,
I got shot by his spiritual sense
and had a blackout for a moment.
Qingmu?
I remember
when you suddenly called
Jingyuan “Tianqi”,
I got confused.
Octagon God-trapping Formation!
Tianqi,
focus!
What did you call me?
♪To get myself♪
Since then,
Boxuan’s memories kept flooding in
even in my dreams.
♪In your heart♪
Surprisingly, some of them belong to
Master Bai Jue in the God Realm.
Houchi,
perhaps Boxuan, Master Bai Jue and I
are the same person.
Bai Jue?
I had a rough time
being planted by others’ memories.
The good news is
I saw
what a naughty
and adorable girl you were.
How is that good?
You were becoming another person.
Why didn’t you tell me?
I was afraid that
♪In the name of the world♪
you’d be in fear of losing me.
I don’t know
if I’ll become someone else.
And I’m not sure
how much time I’ve got.
Maybe I’ll never change
and grow old with you.
Or maybe I’ll be gone in a second
and lose you forever.
I wish
we’d be together forever and ever.
In case we couldn’t,
I used my power
on the fireflies at the North Sea
to leave you this message.
I don’t want you
to be sad because I’m gone
or get hurt in order to find me.
♪When tears dizzy the smile♪
Houchi,
my life
may be short,
♪To get myself♪
but it’s complete because of you.
♪Be always stuck♪
Do take good care of yourself
♪In your heart♪
even without me.
Farewell.
♪For millions of miles♪
I love you.
My dear wife,
I’ll forever love you.
My dear!
Qingmu!
Don’t go!
Don’t leave me!
Fengran!
Jingjian!
Calm down.
I’ll untie you right away.
What happened?
What is this thing?
I’ve never seen it before.
Don’t bother.
It’s your mother’s Blending Formation.
You can’t break it.
She did this to you?
She knew who you are.
So did you?
Fengran, I...
Thank you for coming
for old times’ sake.
Just leave.
I won’t.
I’ll get you out.
No one can harm you.
Not even my mother!
Go now!
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪