♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
=The Eternal Love S3=
=Episode 13=
Give it back!
Oh no.
You.
"Why am I here?"
"Why did you still do it
while knowing the consequences?"
I'm tired of imitating it.
Did Her Majesty agree to my request of repudiation?
"Thank you for your sympathy, Your Majesty."
"I'm well aware of the responsibility
I carry on my shoulders"
"and that I should not act recklessly."
I rejected it?
Once I regain my memory,
I always make things difficult for myself.
Do you want to divorce that badly?
Why?
I...
The reason is not important.
You were the one who asked
for my hand in marriage,
and now you are the one
who is asking me to let go of your hand.
But you won't even give me a reason for it?
Don't you think
that this is too unfair to me?
Princess.
Your Highness, many people
have gathered outside the residence,
making it difficult to leave
or enter the residence.
Why have they gathered here?
It's said that it has something to do with the New Law.
New Law?
Her Majesty hadn't agreed to it yet, had she?
(Princess's Residence)
Here comes Prince Consort.
Prince Consort is here.
Come on.
Come on. Everyone, please make way.
Everyone, please make way.
Come on.
The two of us
thank you for your kindness, Young Master!
You are welcome.
What is your elder brother here for?
Young Master, after you
came back from the palace,
Her Majesty had announced the New Law.
The New Law states that all men have
the right to terminate their own marriages.
It has been said that
it's because of your request that
the New Law was announced.
Indeed, Prince Consort.
I had been enduring
constant violence from my wife,
but had no way out.
The announcement of the New Law
has saved my life.
If it weren't for you,
my brother would still be in great pain.
Make way. Move. Move.
Make way. Make way.
Come home with me!
In front of Princess and Prince Consort, there is
no place for you to act disrespectfully.
Princess, Prince Consort.
This is our family affairs.
I'll settle it by myself.
Let's go!
Let go!
Do you think that you can
put a stop to it just like that?
Princess, as you know,
if he leaves me,
he would drown in rumours
and gossip for the rest of his life.
That's true.
Should one be enduring the unfairness
just to have one's reputation be untainted?
Forgive me for asking, Second Princess.
If Prince Consort wishes
to leave you no matter what,
would you agree to let him go or not?
If that is what he desires,
I would not stop him.
Exactly!
Well-spoken!
Exactly! Well-spoken!
Precisely! Exactly!
How does it feel
to have someone supporting you?
Doesn't it feel thrilling?
What I just said,
especially the last sentence,
wasn't it amazing?
Look at you, asking for praise again.
But I suppose helping the disadvantaged
is easier than I thought.
If it weren't for Her Majesty's New Law,
it wouldn't have been this easy.
Besides, when I was at the imperial garden before,
Her Majesty didn't announce the New Law.
The sudden announcement of the New Law
must have some other meaning behind it.
Would you die if you say a word of praise to me?
You didn't have to make
the conversation about Her Majesty.
At this point,
I've almost forgotten why I asked
for a repudiation paper.
If this keeps happening,
Her Majesty would figure out the reason behind it.
Could it be that...
she is using me to combat the Mo Family?
Thank you, Your Highness.
I won't do it again.
You're as stubborn as a mule.
Did you really have to say thank you
in the most unlovable way?
Your Majesty,
I've found that
it's not only Qu Tan Er whose personality
had changed drastically.
Three months ago, Mo Lian Cheng suddenly fell ill.
After he recovered, he also
became more calculating.
I am well aware of his schemes.
But he broke the promise today,
which cannot be explained
by just his calculating nature.
What Mo Lian Cheng did today was truly a surprise.
It must be rather lively outside
Second Princess's residence today.
That is correct, Your Majesty.
By announcing the New Law would be passed
and spreading the word around about
Mo Lian Cheng's request to you,
there are quite the number of people who are
dissatisfied with the New Law
currently gathered
outside Second Princess's residence.
But
they were calmed by Mo Lian Cheng.
It seems that he really has changed.
It is just my lowly opinion but
I believe Mo Lian Cheng's actions
are all to plant doubts in Your Majesty's mind.
Ever since Mo Yuan Long found out
about the secret funds,
he has been on the move.
Mo Lian Cheng also used
his marriage with Second Princess
to his advantage.
But little do they know,
the spotlight of this spectacle is not on them.
All praise thou might, Your Majesty.
There is still a lot of suspicion
that has yet to be confirmed.
If those two aren't just using each other,
but have formed an alliance,
together with the remaining power
of the Mo Family...
Then...
An alliance between husband and wife?
When the Tianji descends,
he will be mine.
My apologies, Your Majesty.
I was simply worried for Your Majesty's well-being.
Besides, if those two were to form an alliance,
they must not be underestimated.
Your Majesty, please allow me
to continue the investigation.
It is time for our appearance
in this spectacle.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Young Master! Young Master!
Young Master!
Please rise.
What happened?
After my brother left his wife,
our father was determined to send him
to the temples to become a monk.
Young Master! Young Master!
I am merely a man and have no one to rely on.
The land of Dongyue is vast,
yet there is no place for me in it.
Wouldn't this be falling short
of Young Master's expectations?
There, there.
You may rise.
Thank you, Young Master.
It seems that the New Law alone
is not able to change the fate of men.
Young Master, there is only my aggressive wife
that waits for me at my house.
I have nowhere to go.
Young Master, please save me!
I beg of you, please save me!
The New Law was passed because of me,
I must take responsibility.
Her Majesty has invited
Secondary Prince Consort to the palace.
Her Majesty's actions last night
and her invitation...
what is the meaning of all this?
But the tough situation brought upon
by the New Law must be dealt with.
The flower is always
the most beautiful in a vase.
Truly a sight to behold,
but it is soulless.
Then do you think that
it would rather be under harsh sunlight and rain
until the end of its life?
I'm not a flower
and will never know what a flower thinks.
Then tell me,
when you asked for my help before,
was it for benefit of all men
or merely yourself?
The New Law benefits all men.
I asked for the New Law to be passed
for both the country and myself.
However, loopholes exist in the New Law.
If left unfixed, it would be detrimental.
What loophole?
Men that leave their wives,
even if they are to succeed in doing so,
will be outcasted by society.
In the end, they become helpless and homeless.
If that is the case,
who would dare use the New Law?
How about
you gift men that comply with the New Law
some perfume sachets under my name,
as a sign of affirmation from me?
What do you think of it?
Such a brilliant idea, Your Majesty.
I'm greatly impressed by it.
Then you and I will make the sachets together.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Tan.
Tan, wake up! Tan!
Don't be afraid, Cheng Cheng. I'll protect you.
Tan, wake up!
Secondary Prince Consort isn't here.
What?
I said Secondary Prince Consort isn't here.
No, wait.
I said Secondary Prince Consort
was called to the palace.
Called to the palace?
Did he go to meet Her Majesty?
Mo Lian Cheng,
what are your true thoughts?
When you made the Knots of Love with me before,
your hands were quite nimble.
But when it comes to making perfume sachets,
why are you so clumsy?
Knots of Love...
that must've happened before I lost my memory.
I apologize for my clumsiness.
I am no craftsman.
Your Majesty, please have mercy on me.
Hold it for me.
Yes, Your Majesty.
You're avoiding me.
I didn't want to get in the way of Your Majesty.
Do you remember what you said to me
when you made the Knots of Love
with me during the Lantern Festival?
Lantern Festival?
That was before I fell ill and lost my memory.
Your Majesty, you still remember?
You said that
the Knot of Love was strong
and unbreakable.
Your Majesty's care towards citizens
and connection with the world
are of course unbreakable.
I know what you are thinking.
I have already written the edict,
which clearly states the punishment and rewards
in order to encourage men
to remarry under the New Law.
But I think that
you should write a template of a repudiation paper
from a man's perspective as an example.
So it can be shown to all citizens
along with the edict.
There are some writing materials right beside you.
Although Her Majesty is hiding
her true reason for doing this,
I can only agree to it under the current situation.
I can protect my people,
so it's only natural
that I can protect those that I love.
This empathy shown by Your Majesty
will be forever remembered by all men.
(Repudiation paper)
By all men?
I thank Your Majesty.
I must hurry now.
I need to hand this sachet out immediately.
Not happy seeing me
going to the palace, Second Princess?
Her Majesty is already suspicious of
what happened last night.
Besides, it's not like I don't know
that Her Majesty has other motives.
Then why did you still go?
Nothing ventured, nothing gained.
What to venture?
A glamorous life?
Do you think I'm the one to chase after glamour
and climb the social ladder?
Give heed!
By the grace of heaven's will,
Her Majesty hereby proclaims:
Prince Consort Mo Lian Cheng
is a man of kindness and bravery,
who knows of justice and integrity.
He is hereby awarded one thousand taels
of gold, ten rolls of cloth,
twenty pieces of jades,
five pairs of silverware,
and three sets of calligraphy tools.
That's all.
Come and accept the decree, Mo Lian Cheng.
I thank Her Majesty for her blessing.
Right, Her Majesty said
that you left in a hurry
after you made the perfume sachets with her
and forgot to take this.
Did you write this?
Yes.
Yes?
But it's not what you think.
Then why did you make
perfume sachets with Her Majesty?
And why did you write me this repudiation paper?
What else can I think of it?
♪Falling into a black hole of stubbornness♪
I always told myself
that you're sick and you don't remember anything,
and that I shouldn't blame you.
♪Even though there are too many sarcastic moves♪
But when I see these, I am reminded
that if this was him,
♪Going from lovers to strangers
makes me confused♪
he would never do it.
♪Happiness slips through fingers♪
If so,
why haven't you let go?
♪Dream is an one-time, uninhibited indulgence♪
Then I'll let go!
♪Do you understand my heartache at all♪
♪All because of your recklessly squander♪
♪I'm starting to not understand
whether there is love♪
♪I'd rather not understand whether there is love♪
I've heard of what happened in the palace.
He even wants to repudiate me!
Jing Xin!
Go to write a letter for me!
Me?
Hurry!
What should I write?
Just write,
di-
vorce
agreement.
I'm done.
What is this?
[*The wrong, but same-sounding characters were used]
I'm going to divorce him.
I'm going to repudiate that Mo Lian Cheng.
I...
Forget it, I'll write it myself.
Tan,
Secondary Prince Consort broke
the seven types of grounds many times,
you didn't have the heart to repudiate him.
Why this time...
Who said I didn't have the heart to repudiate him?
I'll make him regret everything he has done
once he sees this.
But in my opinion,
that Secondary Prince Consort
is just being stubborn.
I can tell that
he still cares about you.
He cares?
If he cares, why would he
secretly meet his ex-girlfriend behind my back?
They were making perfume sachets together
and babbling on
about their nonsense relationship.
Once he regains his memory,
I'll make him feel
remorse!
Go, take this to him.
Tell him that the divorce is effective
once he signs it.
(Divorce Agreement)
(Qu Xiao Tan repudiates Mo Lian Cheng)
This…
What's this?
Second Princess told me to give this to you.
You can just keep it, no need to sign.
(Divorce Agreement)
(Qu Xiao Tan repudiates Mo Lian Cheng)
Divorce agreement.
Qu Tan hereby divorces Mo Lian Cheng…
Young Master! Young Master!
The perfume sachet you gave me
was extremely useful!
When my father saw the perfume sachet
Her Majesty gave us
and the order from Her Majesty,
as well as the repudiation paper template,
he let my elder brother stay.
I thank you, Young Master, on my brother's behalf.
The perfume sachet
and the repudiation paper template
was for Brother Yu?
Yes.
Then this…
I will think about it
before I sign this.
I'll leave now.
Tan. Tan.
Did he sign it?
The perfume sachet
(Mo Lian Cheng)
and the repudiation paper template
were for Yu Hao's elder brother.
His brother was almost forced
to leave and become a monk
so Secondary Prince Consort turned to Her Majesty.
That's what he meant by
nothing ventured, nothing gained.
But even if so,
he keeps distancing himself from me.
Then I'll give him what he wants.
Tan. Tan.
Now that we know
what happened at the palace
was a misunderstanding,
there must be some other reason
for Secondary Prince Consort
to coerce you like this.
He can't even bother to explain.
What other reason can he possibly have?
A reason that he cannot speak of.
But I already gave him the repudiation paper.
What's done is done.
Even if you've given it out,
you can still get it back.
If you two part ways because of a misunderstanding,
it would be hard to get him to return.
Then…
I'll take the repudiation paper back
and see if he has some other reason
afterwards.
You didn't want him to leave,
yet are so reluctant to admit it.
What did you say?
Nothing.
Cheng Cheng.
What?
The paper I gave you just now…
You want me to sign it as soon as possible?
No, no, no.
Then what?
I made too many spelling mistakes in that one.
I'll take that back
and give you a new one later.
No need.
I…
I don't want to... receive two
repudiation papers from you.
Can't you tell that
I'm giving you a reason not to sign it?
Do you really want me to destroy it?
Are you in this much of a hurry
to help me pack up my belongings?
I bought this one, you can't take it.
This one is the dowry, you can't take it either.
This one's mine.
I can at least take my own belongings
as souvenirs, can't I?
You've already signed it?
What? You don't want me to leave?
I almost cried tears of happiness.
Eighth Brother.
Here, sit.
Eighth Brother,
I heard you were successful.
Successful?
Exactly!
You got the repudiation paper
and received blessings from Her Majesty,
and even protected the reputation of the Mo Family.
Isn't that a great success?
A great success indeed.
Right.
These are all the valuables
I've collected over the years.
I was afraid that your life would be hard
after you leave the residence,
so I've prepared these for you.
But it seems like
your life in the future
will only be happier than now.
Eldest Brother, you don't have to do this.
Just take it.
Even if you marry into the royal family,
you would still need some savings of your own.
You never know what Her Majesty is thinking,
so you need to be prepared, just in case.
I think there are also some jewelry,
take those as well.
Why am I so anxious?
It's as if all of Eldest Brother's kindness
would be wasted by me.
Why does the future he speaks of
seem so distant?
Have I really thought of leaving?
Why are you so two-faced?
You were making excuses when you asked for a kiss,
and now you're making excuses to push me aside.
What do you want?
It was you who asked for my hand in marriage
but it is also you who is asking to leave me.
But you won't even give me a reason for it.
Don't you think that
this is too unfair to me?
Right now,
no matter what I say, it would seem powerless.
If I can do something to
make her realize
that I regret what I've done and want to stay,
how good would that be…
Until the very last moment,
I didn't serve her tea,
nor did I help her get dressed
like all other husbands do.
That may be my regret for eternity.
I wonder when he will
hand me the signed divorce agreement.
Can I not take it?
That's right!
I can just hide from him.
I need to find something to block the door.
That way he can't come in.
Your Highness.
Please have some sleeping tea.
Sleeping tea?
What's he up to?
If you keep pretending, the tea will be cold.
You're here?
He's not hiding the divorce agreement
in his hands, is he?
She wants me... to blow on the tea?
Is he serving me tea?
Your Highness.
You drank?
No.
How is the temperature?
Good, good.
It doesn't look like he's pulling a prank on me.
On the contrary, he seems to be
uncomfortable with himself.
You Highness, are you feeling too warm?
Then how about, I help you get changed?
Could it be that he also doesn't want a divorce?
You've already signed the agreement, right?
When are you giving it to me?
Are you in this much of a hurry?
If I don't hurry,
my hunky boy will become a cute little one.
I'll never
try to push you away again.
These past few days,
I've constantly worried
that my actions would hurt you.
It's my fault
for forcing you to let go.
I have never experienced heartache like this.
It felt like
my soul was being pulled out of my body.
It was as if the rest of my life,
no matter how much longer,
had become meaningless.
If you had known it would be like this,
why act as you did before?
Back then, I pushed you away
because
I had some concerns
about myself,
about my father,
and about Dongyue.
I had felt like
going on my way
while being surrounded by overwhelming darkness.
I can take the risk myself,
but if
I were to put you in danger,
I would never
forgive myself.
You underestimated me.
Are you saying that I can't even
protect my own husband?
Your Highness is highly skilled.
I'll apologize
with a kiss.
Then you have to make things clear.
Leaving things like this isn't okay.
You can't repudiate me.
I'm Princess, it's my call.
Say that again?
How dare you?
And?
Still have something to say?
Fine, fine, fine.
I won't repudiate you anymore.
I'm no longer going to repudiate you,
but what if
you keep grouching
over the agreement?
Then I
will be at Your Highness's mercy.
The agreement,
the agreement is now nullified.
Do you like me because you don't want to leave me
or do you not want to leave me because you like me?
I like you,
so I can't leave you.
I found out how much I like you
because I can't leave you.
I like you so much that I feel anxious;
I like you so much that I'm afraid;
I like you so much
that I can't be honest with myself.
I thought I would stop liking you
if I buried my head in the sand,
but when I did,
I started hoping that you wouldn't let me go.
Is the flush on your face
due to drunkenness or bashfulness?
I'm not drunk.
As for bashfulness...
Let's be bashful together.
Alright, stop it.
Of course I like you.
I like you so so much.
Each passing minute,
I've been afraid you'll
lose your original memories,
and because of that, you'll stop loving me.
It's not a problem anymore.
You've finally come back to me.
But I don't have my original memories,
do you mind?
I'll definitely help you remember everything.
We've been through life and death together,
we've confessed our love so many times,
we've made so many thrilling memories,
how can I let you forget all of these?
True.
I've lost my previous memories.
I've only heard things from you.
Thinking of it, it's quite a shame.
Then...
do you like the me right now
or do you like the me from before?
You've lost your memories,
but you are still you.
Do you really need to ask?
I got jealous.
You have always been the jealous type.
No need to be jealous.
Just try to get your memories back.
Don't leave, okay?
♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
I sleep better
with you beside me.
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
Had it always been like this?
♪I still remember the vows we made,
but words would not come to me♪
♪I resent that we act
as if we are strangers♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪A flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part,
no matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part,
no matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind
in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪