[English subtitles are available]
[Moonlight]
[Episode 17]
This is great!
Chief Editor Yu and Ms Suo Heng
finally reconciled.
What are you doing?
Give it back to me!
I have to tell her
to take care of herself.
You're indeed the Mama Duck.
She's my author.
It's my job to care for her.
I'm also your author.
Yet you weren't
so concerned about me when I was writing.
Speaking of that,
I've got some ideas for your new work,
Huang Quan Inn.
Hold on.
I've never said that
you'll be the editor of Huang Quan Inn.
Take a look at my proposal.
I'm sure you'll know
that I'm your best choice.
I've drawn up a detailed plan
regarding the illustrator
and the book cover.
You're well-prepared.
You even carry it around with you.
You've prepared a lot.
It's good enough to be published already.
This is my brand new sincerity.
What's brand new sincerity?
Since every work is different,
I shall show my fresh sincerity for them.
I'll treat it as though it's my first time
being your editor.
I'll do my best.
Why are you so eager to
be the editor of Huang Quan Inn?
A lot of people are eager to do so.
Is that so?
Is that the only reason?
Also...
[If Drama King knows that I'm eager]
[to sign him up]
[for the sake of other author,]
[it'll definitely hurt his pride.]
Also, it's such a great honour
to be your editor.
Are you sure?
It's a compliment. Why are you leaving?
As expected from Ms Suo Heng.
It only took her half a day
to come up with three different topics.
Hello, Chief Editor Yu.
Did you receive the topics from Suo Heng?
Yes, I'm looking at them.
[Send a copy to Mr Xia.]
[By the way,]
I've asked Mr Zhou Chuan.
[I told him that I wish to sign him up]
[so that Suo Heng gets the chance
to publish in our magazine again.]
Mr Zhou Chuan is very generous.
He doesn't have any hard feelings.
[And he understood that.]
You told him everything?
Mr Zhou Chuan is a smart man.
Rather than being told by
someone with ulterior motives,
he might as well hear it from us.
Mr Zhou Chuan,
I know you've had a long day
and so I prepared
a fruit platter that is double in size.
I don't want it if you cut it like this.
What do you mean?
It's the common way to cut apples.
I'm sorry,
Mr Zhou Chuan.
For not telling you about Ms Suo Heng.
I was afraid you'd misunderstand.
About what?
Do I seem petty to you?
No, not at all.
Even if it weren't because of Ms Suo Heng,
I'm genuinely interested
to sign you up for your book.
You're scraping off my scalp!
I have to focus on the ending of
Huang Quan Inn these two days.
Don't knock on my door.
Don't even call me at mealtime.
Leave the food at the door.
I'll open the door when I'm hungry.
Sir,
who will be the editor for Huang Quan Inn?
The insolent little editor
who can't stop talking about
her brand new sincerity.
Really? Thank you, Mr Zhou Chuan!
So sweet.
[Yuan Yue Publishing House]
The topic of Six Eared Macaque
is Suo Heng's idea?
Yes.
It's completely different from
the other two topics.
It broke the usual setting of light novel
that the female writers
in Moonlight Magazine
have always adhered.
Personally, I think this is a great idea.
I like that.
It visualizes
the conflicts between Taoism
and Buddhism.
Ask her if she can
further explain the saying
"The dharma is not to be
transmitted to the sixth ear".
Sure, I'll give her the message.
Thank you, Mr Xia.
Mr Xia, I think Suo Heng's
story outline is good enough
even if we don't
sign Mr Zhou Chuan up for his new book.
It can definitely meet
the criteria
of Moonlight Magazine.
Indeed, the only way to shut everybody up
is to show them the work.
Although we manage to
save Suo Heng
by signing up Zhou Chuan,
her only means of survival
is to rely on herself.
I've got some good news for you.
Mr Zhou Chuan has agreed that
I'll be the editor of his new work.
Really?
Yes, we'll sign the contract
once he finishes his book.
Maybe after the book fair.
That's great!
Push forward the progress
as Chinese New Year is
right after the book fair.
Prepare the contract quickly.
Okay.
By the way,
what's our progress on the book fair?
Director Yang has ordered
that the book fair
must have total sales
of 2 million yuan,
which are 20% higher than
the previous year's sales.
We have to fight a tough battle.
Don't worry about the book fair.
We've already started on it.
But I wonder what
the circulation department
will come up with
to boost the sales.
Hold on.
That's their job.
All we need to do is to
try our best to cooperate.
But you must remember,
circulation and editorial department
are not enemies,
but friends.
I understand.
Since Mr Xia said so,
let's try to get along with them.
Chief Editor Yu.
Congratulations.
Suo Heng is finally back.
But here's a gentle reminder.
Don't forget Director Yang's condition.
Mr Zhou Chuan has agreed
that I'll be the editor of his book.
There's no proof.
Where's the contract?
Mr Liang,
the book fair is around the corner.
You should be taking charge
of the work in your department.
Why did you keep coming to our department?
I know Director Yang
gave you some privileges,
but you're taking it too far.
Chief Director Yu,
don't take this the wrong way.
Mr Liang is here to
talk about the book fair with me.
And you, Miao.
What's written on the staff card
hanging around your neck?
Deputy editor of the second section
of editorial department.
I'm the chief editor.
Mr Liang should have
come to me
instead of you.
Chief Editor Yu,
you have a very strong hierarchical sense.
That's some feudal dross. It's no good.
We're all doing our job.
Does it matter who is the chief
or deputy editor?
Mr Liang, I'm shocked you'd ask.
You said it yourself,
that nothing can be done without rules.
Did you forget it?
Yes,
I don't care about the hierarchy
of authority at all.
I know the only rule that
an editor has to follow
is to take care of the authors.
Okay, Chief Editor Yu, I got it.
Xiao Niao,
and you.
You and Chu Li joined us not long ago.
You must never act like
a brown-noser or
take an opportunistic approach.
I understand, Chief Editor Yu.
Impressive.
Chief Editor Yu, that's so cool.
Kiddos,
your leader is so nice that
she instructs and gives you
sincere advice every day.
You'd certainly succeed.
I see greatness in all of you!
I'm so jealous.
How great it is.
Mr Liang, just a gentle reminder.
Don't eat too much chocolate.
You'll get grouchy.
You went a little too far.
Where's your manner?
Mr Liang, wait for me.
Chief Editor Yu, that was so cool.
Everyone said you're just like me
when I was young.
But I think you look nothing like me.
How is that possible?
I can never be as good as you.
You're much better than me.
Did I just get a compliment
from Chief Editor Yu?
Ms Suo Heng,
you changed your style.
I could barely recognize you.
I'm taking this opportunity
to turn into a whole new person.
Right,
I had a meeting with
Chief Editor Yu and Mr Xia.
All of us think that the third topic
is very interesting.
Especially Mr Xia.
He has a message for you.
He asked if you can further
explain the saying...
The dharma...
The dharma is not to be
transmitted to the sixth ear?
Yes, the dharma is not to be
transmitted to the sixth ear.
Do you have a new interpretation?
I thought you wouldn't
pick this topic.
You said that nobody would like it
if it's not a fluff
romance novel.
Who says you can't sense
the charisma from a document?
I can clearly see
the bold text
on all the three documents
you sent me.
Pick me!
I know
you want to write about this, right?
I've thought it all out.
Even if you decline
all the three topics
and I can
no longer publish my work
in Moonlight Magazine,
I'd never give up.
I'm going to keep doing this
until
I manage to write something incredible.
I don't want my readers
to be disappointed.
I wonder if I have the chance to
participate in the making
of this masterpiece.
In my opinion,
the utmost requirement
to reach your goal
is your passion in writing.
So...
Good luck, Ms Suo Heng!
Thanks, Chu Li.
One more thing.
As a matter of fact, Chief Editor Yu
has always cared for you.
I know that.
But so many years have passed.
I don't know what to say
when I see her again.
Anyway, we are in a good place now.
We get to live our own lives
without resentments
and misunderstandings.
And we won't impose a burden
on one another.
I was relying too heavily on her.
But now I know better.
Only you
can solve your own problems.
Going out late at night?
I have
a movie date with Mr Jiang.
I have to work hard at home
while you're on a movie date with a guy?
Stop making me look like
a heartless rat who is having an affair.
You're working hard
for the sake of yourself.
Say that again?
Mr Zhou Chuan,
I'm sorry.
I know you're working very hard.
Just leave the plates on the table
when you're done.
I'll wash them when I'm back.
Thanks for your hard work.
Hello.
[Hey, Gu Bai Zhi.]
[Do you have movie tickets?]
You're not making any sense.
Buy it yourself.
I want a particular seat.
[Jiang Yu Cheng went for a movie]
[with my editor.]
They are dating behind my back.
I didn't know that until now.
What does it have to do with me?
[Cut it out.]
I asked her already.
They are going to watch
Sui San Duo's movie.
[I know you guys are]
close with Sui San Duo.
I'm sure you have the ticket
for the seat next to Jiang Yu Cheng.
See you at the gate in five minutes.
I'm hanging up. Bye.
Here.
Thanks.
You must have lots of work.
You keep checking your phone.
No, it's Mr Zhou Chuan.
He kept asking about the movie
ever since I left the house.
I didn't know he's interested
in literary film.
I guess he's worried about you.
What should he worry about?
We are not strangers to one another.
Sorry. Excuse me.
Director Gu?
Mr Zhou Chuan?
You're here for the movie too?
Move over, please.
That's my seat.
I don't want to.
Sit with the person who came with you.
I wasn't talking to you.
Did you not hear me?
Sit with the person who came with you.
I'm sitting next to you.
Are you here with me?
You don't have to come.
You think you own the cinema?
Why should I listen to you?
I'm going to sit here anyway.
This is the centre of the theatre.
It's the best spot.
All these four seats are in the centre.
Do you have a cast in one eye
or what?
Why are you fighting
for the centre position?
Are you here to walk the red carpet?
I can tell that from his clothes.
You guys keep moving around.
Are you done with the discussion?
The movie is starting soon.
Fine, get up.
Chu Li, let me send you home.
Zhou Chuan's been working on his book.
I'm afraid he's too tired to drive.
I'll go get the car.
We need to talk about work
on the way home.
Zhou Chuan is still willing to talk
about work at night.
You're doing a good job as his editor.
It's nothing.
I didn't expect that
Ms Sui San Duo's movie
is talking about two people
who met online.
They dated online for three years
but they never met each other in person.
You've known Mr Fox for three years
and you've never met him in person too.
I asked him to come out but he refused...
[How come Mr Jiang Yu Cheng]
[knows that I've known
Mr Fox for three years?]
Don't just stand there. Hop in.
Jiang Yu Chen,
you'll send Gu Bai Zhi back to her home.
Get in the car quickly.
Coming!
I'll get going then.
Drive slowly.
Is it okay for you? Forget it if it's not.
Let's go.
♫ They say strange things
and keep rapport ♫
How did you know I like this song?
I don't know.
But I like this song too.
How is that possible?
You must have peeped my playlist.
♫ Guileless adults are reduced to a joke ♫
Grow up.
Did you?
No.
♫ Unceasingly ♫
Sorry.
When are you going home?
Have you bought your ticket?
So tired already?
Why are you still awake at this hour?
I couldn't sleep.
What's the problem?
Mr Zhou Chuan,
I suspect that
Mr Jiang is Mr Fox.
What?
Right,
I should have figured it out.
Mr Fox's full name
is The Disappearing Mr Fox.
And Mr Jiang's masterpiece
is the Disappearing Series.
How did you link them together?
Think about it.
There's no one in the world
who knows you more than Jiang Yu Cheng.
If there's someone who can
easily mimic
your writing style,
it must be none other than him.
This is so easy.
I should have figured it out.
Say that again?
Easily mimic Zhou Chuan's writing style?
Who are you kidding?
Who can mimic me?
Jiang Yu Cheng?
And I shamelessly boasted
that Mr Fox is my boyfriend.
I made fun of the illustrators and authors
in front of him every day
because I thought he's an outsider.
Besides, I spoke ill about you
in front of him all the time.
Don't be silly.
I'm...
You knew about it, didn't you?
That's why you could deny that
you're Mr Fox
in such a strong way.
I've been busting my ass to sell your book
and yet you and Mr Jiang chose to
keep this huge secret hidden from me.
Don't you feel ashamed at all?
I...
What did I know?
No wonder.
Even though I told him I like Mr Fox,
he wouldn't stop pursuing me.
Turns out they are the same person.
Which means we like each other then.
Are you...
You used to think that I'm Mr Fox,
how come
you never thought we like each other?
Didn't we do this and that stuff
when we were drunk?
We agreed
not to mention it again!
Besides, unlike Mr Jiang,
you've never confessed to me.
Right!
So you're far too excited
to sleep now, is it?
You're going to
confess to Jiang Yu Cheng tomorrow
and tell him you like him, is it?
This...
Why are you getting all worked up?
Where are you going at this hour?
Who is it?
Jiang Yu Cheng!
What did you tell Chu Li behind my back?
She's so convinced that you're Mr Fox!
I have no idea.
She didn't ask my anything.
She went for a movie with you and
came back convinced that you're Mr Fox.
It's not like the old days
where you can just swap in
and pretend to be me.
Calm down.
I didn't get to tell
Chu Li anything
before you came with Gu Bai Zhi.
I...
I don't care!
I want an explanation!
What's the reason?
When you went to get your car...
You've known Mr Fox for three years
and you've never met him in person too.
She's never told me
how long you've known each other.
Could it be because of this?
Jiang Yu Cheng, did you do it on purpose?
So that she'll think you're Mr Fox?
Do you think I'd do that?
I'd never win her heart even if I did.
She thinks you're Mr Fox now
and we're just messing with her.
Not only am I replaced by you,
I also become your partner in crime.
You're not my partner in crime.
You're the main perpetrator.
Aren't you Mr Fox?
I'm the innocent one here.
Why don't I go talk to her
and clear up the misconceptions?
If I choose to confess,
it will work in my favour.
No! How dare you!
If Chu Li were to ask
if you're Mr Fox,
you must never admit it!
Understand?
No.
Enjoy your food.
I have to go somewhere.
Where are you going so early?
Sit down.
Sir,
the Book of Luo He God launch day.
Don't you want to take a look?
No.
It's so crowded. Why should I?
To see how well your books are sold.
I'm not going.
You want breakfast?
Cut it out.
I know what you're thinking.
You're still wondering if
Jiang Yu Cheng is Mr Fox, right?
Did you ask him in person?
Not yet.
I feel perturbed.
What if
he really is Mr Fox?
You think this is a gashapon machine?
Insert a coin and you'll get a boyfriend
who is tall and handsome?
Jiang Yu Cheng is 33 years old,
pushing toward his 40s.
Do you know what it's like?
It means when you were
just a baby waiting to be fed,
he was already learning
300 Tang Poems in school.
What boyfriend?
Do you still wish to deny it?
Why are you blushing then?
Give him a call right now
and clear things up.
No need.
Mr Jiang and I are going to
meet at his house to talk about this.
His house?
Do you know where he lives?
I can give you a lift.
He sent me the address.
I can go by myself.
Bye.
I...
You're here.
Come in.
Thanks, Mr Jiang.
When I heard you on the phone,
I thought I had interrupted your rest.
I didn't sleep well last night.
Have a seat.
Sir,
I've got a question for you.
Are you
Mr Fox?
This won't do.
Chu Li is a sitting duck.
If Jiang decides
to admit that he's Mr Fox,
what am I going to do then?
Or, if he tells Chu Li
that I'm Mr Fox,
things will get
even more difficult for me.
Chu Li is going to hate me so much.
You think it's risky too, right?
That's what I thought!
This won't do.
I need to check on her.
[Little Monkey]
[Saviour]
Thank you.
[Why would you think]
[that I'm Mr Fox?]
I've never told you that
[I've known Mr Fox for three years]
but you blurted it out yesterday.
Chu Li,
what are you going to do
if I'm really Mr Fox?
I told you before,
I like Mr Fox.
[And if you're Mr Fox,]
[I have to...]
Get together with me?
[What is Jiang Yu Cheng trying to do?]
[Saviour]
It got disconnected?
[Little Monkey]
[Hello.]
[The number you've dialled
is unavailable.]
Your words
are tempting me into
admitting that I'm Mr Fox.
But I don't want to lie to you.
I'm not.
How did you know
about Mr Fox and me then?
I saw your post on Weibo last year.
You talked about an online friend
that you've known for two years.
I see.
If you like a girl,
you want to know everything about her.
But I've never thought about
pretending to be someone else
to win your favour.
Besides, you'll know who
Mr Fox is sooner or later.
What's that supposed to mean?
Chu Li,
are you rather disappointed
or happy when you know that
I'm not Mr Fox?
Mr Jiang,
whether you're Mr Fox or not,
you'll always be my favourite author.
Jiang Yu Cheng.
Are you out of your mind?
What do you mean she has to
get together with you?
You're a punk! Scumbag! Little rat!
Try the coffee.
He hung up on me?
Too late. She left already.
I'm not here looking for her.
I'm here because of you.
I told her everything.
That's bad, Little Zhou.
It's too light.
You can't even kill a mosquito.
Let me show you how to do it.
Great.
Okay.
Go on.
Come on.
You should go all out too.
Sure. Come on.
I'll show you a trick.
Flying Scissors Kick!
Pressing from above!
Time out.
I'm exhausted.
I have to take the call.
Hello?
[Hi, sir.]
[I'm calling from Fitness Center.]
[We're having promotion now.]
[Are you interested?]
No!
Who's that?
Cold call.
Well?
Shall we continue?
Let me drink some water.
Have you ever thought of
the reason why you
always get all worked up
when Chu Li is involved?
Never.
I told her
I'm not Mr Fox.
You like Chu Li, right?
I don't know.
You're stubborn.
You need a good beating.
Well then, let's do it again.
I want a drink too.
I'm out.
From now onward,
Chu Li is nothing but an editor.
Why did you come round
to the idea all of a sudden?
You're my little brother after all.
A piece of advice for you.
You better tell Chu Li earlier
that you're Mr Fox.
It will not end well if she
were to figure it out.
Clean up
the blood on your lips.
Here, you should clean up too.
You're back.
Are you
injured?
Who did you fight with?
I slipped and fell over.
Seems like you landed on your face.
It hurts, right?
You deserve it for fighting.
Are you punishing me right now?
I'm teaching you on behalf of your mother.
Aren't you acting like Mama Duck?
You did it on purpose.
You take it out on me
now that you know Jiang Yu Cheng
isn't Mr Fox.
How did you know he's not Mr Fox?
I made a guess.
Why?
Are you sad that
he's not?
I've mistaken two people for him,
shouldn't I be sad?
Actually,
I...
Forget it, I don't care now.
Maybe you were right.
He's just a kid
who's still in school.
By the way,
when are you going home
for Chinese New Year?
Chinese New Year's Eve.
That's great! We still have time.
Let's sign
the contract after the book fair.
You seem so eager to do that.
I just can't wait to go home.
You like Chinese New Year?
Of course!
The dinner one
Chinese New Year's Eve are so delicious!
Just the thought of the pork knuckle,
chicken soup,
lots of fish and meat
and Eight Treasure Rice
at reunion dinner make me drool.
[Book of Luo He God Is Going On Sale.]
[The Most Influential
Book of 2019 Was Born.]
Here.
Our company still cares about
the Book of Luo He God a lot
that they decide to
release the book today.
[Book of Luo He God Is Going On Sale.]
Look at the slogan.
So powerful.
[The Most Influential
Book of 2019 Was Born.]
"The Book of Luo He God is going on sale."
"The most influential book of 2019
was born."
Their slogan is simple and crude as usual.
Move it over.
Put it here.
[Un Oiseau Effray E]
[World-renowned Writer & Director - Maurer]
Maurer?
Xin Dun Books has invited Maurer.
Half an hour signing session
for Un Oiseau Effray E.
Aside from Un Oiseau Effray E,
Maurer will release two other
movie-to-book adaptations worldwide.
The books are translated
into 16 languages.
Xin Dun Books has already bought
the copyright of one of the books.
If Zhou Chuan knows that
Maurer's display board
is right next to his,
he'd be so happy that
he'll write 30,000 words a day.
Mr Zhou Chuan has
great respect for Maurer.
He's totally obsessed with him.
He can recite
all the lines from two movies.
One of them is Lion King.
And the other one
is Maurer's movie, Virgo.
Every time he travels abroad,
he will look for Maurer's CDs.
He has a drawer full of his CDs
under his TV cabinet.
How come she knows so much
about Mr Zhou Chuan's house?
He's the type of guy
who will keep his thought to himself
no matter how much
he likes or admires someone.
He's pretentious.
Hard to get along with.
I guess that's the way he was raised.
He wouldn't even eat the apple
unless you make
a bunny shape out of it.
He's not pretentious!
Talented people
always happen to be eccentric.
He's quite interesting.
I hope we will have
the chance to become teammates
instead of opponents.
How come she knows
everything about Mr Zhou Chuan?
She's not necessarily telling the truth.
Touché.
But did she just ask you
to join Xin Dun Books?
I'm not going to check if
there are CDs in his drawer.
So what if he has a drawer full of CDs?
I know Drama King
likes to sleep with soft toys too.
I won't do anything to find out
if he really likes bunny-shaped apples.
What am I doing?
I've been acting strange lately.
Mr...
Mr Zhou Chuan.
Well,
Xin Dun Books has invited Mr Maurer
to the signing session
for Un Oiseau Effray E
on your launch day.
He'll be there for half an hour.
Is that so?
You're so calm.
Did your previous editor
not tell you about it?
Mr Liang
suggested that we should hire
the Internet Water Army
to come and buy your books
with their arms flailing in the air.
Just to put up a front.
But you might need to pay for it.
What are you hiding?
Nothing.
Take it out.
This is good.
So sweet.
Do you really like
bunny-shaped apples?
What do you mean?
It's just an apple.
What's with the face?
It looks as though
I did something wrong to you.
The apples that I prepared for you before
are not apples, are they?
Besides, did I ever say that
these apples are for you?
Who is this for if it weren't for me?
Er Gou?
It only eats meat.
I prepared this for myself.
Is that so?
How delicate.
These are all for me!
I won't give you any of them!
Fine, it's all yours.
It's all yours.
How did you know
that I like bunny-shaped apple?
I didn't know about that.
These apples
are prepared for myself.
Director Gu told me about this.
And she said you have
a drawer full of CDs.
What's that look?
Are you jealous?
No way!
I'm not jealous.
She's just your former editor,
not your ex-girlfriend.
Even if she's your ex-girlfriend,
that's none of my business.
I'm your current editor.
Why did you tell her instead of me?
I didn't tell her about it.
She knew it from that big mouth,
Jiang Yu Cheng.
Mr Jiang?
Well then...
Mr Zhou Chuan,
you can eat as much as you like.
What else do you want to know?
I'll say everything I know
without reserve.
What's your favourite colour?
Black.
What's your favourite number?
13.