♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
=The Eternal Love S3=
=Episode 07=
Where is the imperial token?
I pawned it.
When the Yin and Yang pieces
of the imperial token are combined,
it can be used to command the armies.
How could you just pawn it?
If you wanted the imperial token,
you could've asked me directly.
Why did you have to use tricks?
If I asked you for it, would you have given it to me?
No.
Because I'm not stupid.
I know what the imperial token is.
And I know that
pawning it as if I knew nothing
is the best choice.
Because someone else had once
used the imperial token to test me before.
Aside from the Empress,
who else dared to test you
using the imperial token?
Someone who is before my eyes
yet I cannot meet.
Before your eyes?
Starting from the Xuanling Continent,
he and I have had our fates
entangled together through several
parallel universes.
Each time, we had to start over.
People only experience
pain and happiness
once in their lives.
However, he and I
loved more than once
and got hurt more than once.
Xuanling Continent.
Several parallel universes?
Your Highness, when you lie,
you should choose a better story to tell.
I'm not the princess.
I'm not Qu Tan Er either.
I haven't been since I met you
during the harem selection.
You're not Qu Tan Er?
Then who are you?
Where did Qu Tan Er go?
It looks like
there is no chance for me to meet her this time.
You only need to remember that I'm Qu Tan.
I'm from another Dongyue.
You won't believe what I said.
You might think I'm making everything up.
However, the person I love
has the same appearance
and the same name as you.
He is in your body.
I insisted on marrying you.
It's not for you,
but for always staying by his side.
Her behaviour indicates
she is acting like a different person
rather than having a change in temperament.
Is there another me in my body?
A person who she truly loves?
Did she really pawn the imperial token?
Exactly.
This Qu Tan Er doesn't act
as I would expect.
This way,
she proves she has no interest
in the imperial token
and also made it impossible for Mo Lian Cheng
to get the imperial token.
However, she also gave up
the power of the imperial token.
So I think
Qu Tan Er doesn't trust Mo Lian Cheng.
She is also afraid that the Mo Family will use her
to do something.
She would rather give up the imperial token
than being manipulated.
Could it be that
they are really faking it?
If that's true,
why would she insist on marrying Mo Lian Cheng?
It's a deal.
No matter what it is,
it's only a waste of effort.
We only need to wait for Tianji to come.
Has the timing of Tianji
been calculated?
We need three more months.
To be safe,
get her to make preparations for
my grand ceremony early.
There must be no flaws.
Yes, Your Majesty.
So that's why I'd suddenly
forgot what I was doing.
Was he also the one being intimate with you?
Is everything you've done for him?
Are you surprised?
Do you care?
He never let me feel
that this is just a suffering dream of mine.
He makes me understand
I'm the most important person in his heart.
You?
It doesn't matter.
I don't care.
If you don't care,
why did you stop me?
I don't care about you,
but I care about him.
I don't care if
you steal the imperial token
or if the Mo Family wants to rebel.
I could've happily
helped you marry into the harem.
But he is still here.
Sometimes,
I subconsciously
think that you are him.
That's my mistake.
I'll make sure to remember that you are not him.
After we get you two to separate,
it'll be none of my business
even if you cause huge problems.
But now,
if you do anything that
will put him in danger,
I won't allow it as I had before.
Wait.
If everything you said just now
is true,
then why did you give me leverage？
Aren't you afraid that I'll expose you?
In your eyes,
aren't we using each other for our own benefits?
We both have leverage on the other,
isn't that good?
♪The string broke and the song ended,
they went their separate ways♪
♪If it wasn't meant to be, why bother
bringing up the vows again♪
Everything happened between us
are not done with true feelings.
Is that really it?
♪We share a night of happiness,
till death do us part♪
It'll be nice if I can get drunk
in broad daylight
and find out that this has all been a dream
when I wake up.
Yan Chen?
Tan Er?
That wine bottle is empty.
I went to get another one.
It seems like
I haven't just sat down and talked to him.
My current situation
is rather similar to his.
You came at the right time.
We didn't fully enjoy ourselves by the lake.
How about having a picnic?
A picnic?
Tell me,
if the person you love changed
into another person
who you can't tell if it's that one for real.
But you can't change the situation.
What should you do?
Tan Er is Tan Er.
If you changed, I can't undo it,
but I'd love you with my instinct.
There is no way.
Everyone said you changed and went crazy
after falling into the water.
However, I'd never forgotten about
the affection we had for one another.
Everyone said
you went crazy,
but it seems that
you never forgot about the affection
we have for one another.
Why did I...?
Eighth Brother.
You...
I...
This...
Family members help each other.
Being together
feels nice.
Is it possible that
the one I just kissed was Cheng Cheng?
It can't be.
Given how disgusted he looked afterwards,
that was Eighth Young Master for sure.
Did you and the secondary prince consort
do that?
Aren't you an emotionless guard?
Finally exposing your gossipy nature?
I care about Your Highness.
But whenever Cheng Cheng comes out,
there is no disconnect in his memories.
That's strange.
When Tan Er and I used to switch,
we didn't remember what the other had done.
There is another possibility.
Cheng Cheng has been the same person
from the beginning,
not two souls in one body.
Then why does he recognize me sometimes
but doesn't at other times?
It sounds like Secondary Prince Consort
is suffering from amnesia.
Yes, he could have amnesia.
This explains why
Cheng Cheng doesn't have Eighth Young Master's
previous memories.
That's because
he is the Cheng Cheng who came from the same world
as I did.
And something caused
him to lose his memories intermittently.
Right, this is it.
Jing Xin,
do you agree with my analysis?
Tan,
I didn't quite understand what you just said.
But if it came out from your mouth,
it must be true.
If this is the case,
I should ask
the imperial physician to take a look.
No, no, no.
We can't breathe a word of this.
Moreover,
you don't have psychologists or
neurologists here.
No way, no way. How can I cure him?
I came up with an idea.
Jing Xin,
prepare a few items for me.
What do you want to do?
You'll see later.
I, Qu Tan, will not fail easily.
I haven't given it all out yet.
I know what to do.
♪If there is a chance to make a choice♪
♪Which one is better♪
♪Both require going through many hardships
and not showing weakness♪
The process of artistic creation
is indeed difficult.
♪Please let me see through this life♪
♪An inch or an acre, don't be too greedy♪
(Stage play: Love under the Sakura tree)
♪Make haste and just be happy♪
♪Just be happy♪
Mo Lian Cheng.
I became an artist from
a realtor
for you.
Although I'd never give up on you,
you should try your best as well.
Jing Xin.
The script-reading session starts now.
That day,
she climbed onto the wall
and jumped off.
In order to free herself from the restraints
of her family.
When she looked down,
she saw a young gentleman
passing by elegantly.
When they looked at each other,
even the Milky Way seemed to lose its light.
We'll have BGM here.
BGM?
That day, she encountered an ambush.
Many assassins came out from all directions.
♪Infatuation leads me to jump into a vortex♪
♪From breaking down the barriers
to falling helplessly in love♪
♪Every step is a desperate struggle♪
♪Happiness experienced, mistakes made♪
♪Taking notes on who has come♪
♪Tears shed, mistakes repented♪
♪Such that life has not been in vain♪
When her life was hanging by a thread,
at the most dangerous moment,
that same young gentleman
came to her rescue again.
He stepped forward and
killed many attackers.
Unfortunately,
he was hit by an arrow,
and his blood flowed like a river.
We have a lot of promises yet to be fulfilled.
You said you'd protect me forever.
I'll fulfill my promise.
As long as you are alright.
They looked deeply into each other's eyes.
No matter which universe we are in.
No matter what kind of lives we live.
You and I
will always fall in love.
My consort
and empress,
is destined
to be you, Qu Tan, and only you.
♪Should I learn to be stingy
when giving out my love♪
No matter where and no matter when,
no matter who we become,
I'll always seek you out,
embrace you, fall in love with you,
and marry you a thousand times.
Lifetime after lifetime, we will never be apart.
♪Strong, burning love will only
push things to end sooner♪
♪Every time I'm reluctant to part ways♪
♪Only anguish and bitterness remain♪
♪There is no choice♪
It looks like
the feedback on my script
is pretty good.
Everyone's tears
are the best praise for me.
Thank you.
This is the most touching story I have ever heard.
Really?
I've decided on the leading actor and actress.
Jing Xin and Shi Si.
You two will play the main characters.
Me?
I want to ask.
Are women in the story
only thinking about love and romance?
Don't they have any social responsibilities
for their country or their families?
Or the need to protect their country?
Don't they have any social responsibilities
for their country or their families?
There is no great love
Don't they have any social responsibilities
for their country or their families?
without small love.
Don't they have any social responsibilities
for their country or their families?
Why do you need tactical palace drama?
Don't they have any social responsibilities
for their country or their families?
I'm making you the female lead.
You shouldn't ask for more.
Don't they have any social responsibilities
for their country or their families?
Right.
Don't they have any social responsibilities
for their country or their families?
Then can you give me
Don't they have any social responsibilities
for their country or their families?
some cool and awesome
Don't they have any social responsibilities
for their country or their families?
scenes of fights and battles?
Don't they have any social responsibilities
for their country or their families?
I can't add scenes for you even if you are
the female lead.
Don't they have any social responsibilities
for their country or their families?
This is the script.
Don't they have any social responsibilities
for their country or their families?
You should act according to what it says.
Don't they have any social responsibilities
for their country or their families?
Not a single word can be added.
Don't they have any social responsibilities
for their country or their families?
Your Highness.
Don't they have any social responsibilities
for their country or their families?
What role can I play?
Don't they have any social responsibilities
for their country or their families?
You can play the assassin with the best
martial arts skills
Don't they have any social responsibilities
for their country or their families?
among all the assassins that come in flocks.
Don't they have any social responsibilities
for their country or their families?
Okay, okay.
Don't they have any social responsibilities
for their country or their families?
Cheng Cheng, I wrote
Don't they have any social responsibilities
for their country or their families?
Cheng Cheng, I wrote
all our important moments
into the script word-for-word.
You should have a familiar feeling
after watching it.
Ladies and gentlemen.
To enrich
our cultural and recreational activities,
I, as the director and scriptwriter,
have produced an avant-garde play,
Love under a Sakura Tree,
(Love under the Sakura tree)
Love under the Sakura tree.
for everyone to watch.
This play tells the story
of how a young gentleman and a lady
meet and fall into a marvelous
romantic relationship.
This handsome young gentleman is
Romeo.
This kind, smart
and pretty lady is
Juliet.
Now, let's appreciate their
love story.
Move, sprinkle the petals.
(Sakura tree)
Come.
Come help me down.
It's improper for men and women to have
physical contact.
How's this?
Isn't this opening romantic?
Vulgar.
Don't worry. I'll protect you.
Don't worry.
(Sakura tree)
Don't be scared.
Wait for me.
Go die.
I don't want to!
No!
Go to hell!
(Sakura tree)
Don't be scared.
I...
Go away.
I won't die.
Get out. Go away, go away.
Don't worry.
I'll ensure your safety.
Your Highness, you are finally here.
Tan Er.
Why is the man protecting the woman in your play?
Put your focus on the romance.
Okay.
If I'm in such danger,
will you come to my rescue like that?
The Residence is strictly guarded.
(Kiss)
♪I look at her but think of her♪
♪Less capricious, more elegant♪
♪Forget it, don't hurt her♪
♪Pack up and go see the world ♪
♪If I could meet her someday♪
♪Can I still tell her all this♪
♪It's still that entangled story♪
♪If everything can start over♪
♪Originally, I thought I could forget♪
Tell me...
♪Change a city and there are no marks of us♪
♪I ran across every street in vain♪
You're into it?
♪Originally, I thought I could stop♪
♪Change a loved one and time passes by
in the blink of an eye♪
(Kiss)
♪Hard to predict that it'll become a prison♪
Don't you think the story is really touching?
Do you sense any familiarities?
Disgusting.
(Love under the Sakura tree)
Eighth Brother.
Tan Er, please don't blame him.
This play is a little hard to understand.
Look.
If you change the kissing scenes
into them reading together,
won't this be more...
Tan Er.
Shi Si, then let's...
(Sakura tree)
(Love under the Sakura tree)
I think
Second Princess's behaviour has changed
dramatically.
Tell me more.
Second Princess is no longer
as indecisive as before.
She arranges plays at her residence with
no regards to superiority and inferiority.
In the play, the man is intelligent and brave,
but the woman is a deadbeat.
She said it was based on
her personal experience.
Also...
Also what?
Second Princess grew up with the consort.
However, she barely talks to the consort now.
This really is strange.
Is it possible that Qu Tan Er has already...
Is it possible that this one is a fraud?
If someone is really pretending to be
the second princess...
However, we still haven't found
the second princess's corpse.
Someone is always listening.
My mistake.
Get ready.
We'll go visit this Qu Tan Er tomorrow.
Five words drifted from the sky,
so many things are happening in one day.
I wave to the sky,
nothing matters.
Please let me see through this life.
Seize the moment and enjoy the present.
Enjoy yourself, enjoy yourself.
Tan.
Secondary Prince Consort said he doesn't
want to see you.
However, he is
playing with a sword in the yard.
Petty things.
Love starts with
feeling nervous and shy.
The more you don't want to see someone,
the more you want to see them.
Did you scare him earlier today?
Being lyrical is useless
and wouldn't gain any liking.
If I don't do something bold,
he won't even know
how important I am in his heart.
But Tan.
You are a woman
and more importantly, a princess.
It doesn't look so proper to be this proactive.
Even though it's easy for women to pursue men
but extremely hard for men to pursue women.
Cheng Cheng is so dull.
What else can I do if I'm not being proactive?
But, but I think...
It's fine, take it easy.
I have everything under control.
Don't peep.
This is my surprise for Cheng Cheng tomorrow.
Then I'll leave.
Go ahead...
I'm so sleepy.
Stupid Mo Lian Cheng.
Days have passed.
Maybe he's still mad?
(Like you. A prairie.)
There is nothing serious in this notebook.
(Can't take my eyes off you. The sea is the sea.
The mountain is the mountain.)
Childish.
Tan.
Ambushing at the door early in the morning
doesn't match your status.
How about this.
I'll send people over
to get Secondary Consort for you.
Don't.
Come back.
Hurry, come back and hide.
Hide.
Jing Xin.
Calm down.
You really have the mindset of a straight woman.
What is a "straight woman"?
Jing Xin, this way.
Listen to me.
When Yu Hao comes out,
tell him that
the princess
is staying at Mo Yan Chen's chambers every night,
lives licentiously and doesn't care about
government affairs.
You really can't stand it anymore,
so you've come to ask him for help.
Then, what will you do?
I'll just wait here.
I don't think Mo Lian Cheng will be able to
stay put after hearing that.
Okay.
Be careful.
Jing Xin.
You've got this.
Yu Hao!
Mo Lian Cheng,
if you can stay put after finding out that
I'm having an affair,
then you truly don't love me anymore.
What do you need?
Be quick.
Keep your distance.
I have something to tell you.
Please tell your Eighth Young Master that
our Second Princess
is wasting her days away with Eldest Young Master,
and doesn't care about government affairs.
Most importantly...
Most importantly, I can't even rest.
Please tell him.
Oh my god.
This is terrible, terrible, terrible.
Mo Lian Cheng, I'll definitely catch you
this time.
I'm passing on Eighth Young Master's words.
Come down!
What did he say?
Eighth Young Master said that...
Even though it's childish,
it's harmless.
As long as Your Highness is happy.
Her Highness is childish,
and her behavior is harmful.
She can stay with whomever she likes,
and do whatever she wants.
Stay here.
Speaking of government affairs...
In the end, I can't
carry her political responsibilities
for a long period of time.
She should start picking up government affairs
as soon as possible.
I will no longer help Her Highness.
Never.
I wish...
Finally, I wish Her Highness all the best.
Wishing Her Highness and the consort
the best
and looking forward to hearing the patter
of tiny feet.
The end.
The end?
Why don't you leave after you're done?
I'm not telling you next time.
Mo Lian Cheng.
Stupid Mo Lian Cheng.
Jing Xin.
Your approach is more effective.
Break down the door.
Okay.
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪A flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part,
no matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part,
no matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind
in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪