=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 10=
Gather your original being
and break the three realms.
Over these years,
who has been helping me
whenever I was in danger?
Bai Jue once said
the scariest thing
about the Devilish Energy
is that it will attach onto the wound
and gradually erode spiritual power.
It has to be pushed out immediately,
otherwise it will
endanger the foundation.
But,
in the vast Nether World,
I haven’t seen any of
the herbs he mentioned before.
This glossy ganoderma is quite big.
It looks older than
those in the God Realm.
I guess it might work.
Ancestral Sword.
I didn’t know you could do that.
You were wasted in the God Realm.
With you accompanying me
in the Nether World,
I don’t need to worry anymore.
This is the Devil Ganoderma
in the Nether World.
If you take it,
you might have typhoid fever,
or even fall into a coma.
This is all you learned from me.
What I taught you is totally wasted.
♪Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
I don’t know
what they are doing right now.
Yuemi
must have invited a god
to tell her stories.
What story is she listening to today?
I don’t know if I heard it before.
Ancestral Sword.
It must be the orchid
you told me to pick.
After I took it,
I haven’t got better at all.
I’ve got dizzy instead.
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
As the Chief God of the Three Realms,
if I get killed because of an orchid,
they will laugh their heads off.
Shanggu.
You mustn’t fall asleep.
This is a wolf den.
You must be tired.
Have a good sleep.
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
Ice Cube.
I try so hard
just because I want to be
good enough for you.
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
You must treat
those goddesses coldly
as you always did
for the next one thousand years.
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds♪
♪And raindrops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪In the future♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪
Shanggu.
After you inherit Chief God’s
instruction feather,
I will tell you
everything on my mind.
Yuemi, come out!
You’ve been following me
all the way here.
I didn’t do it on purpose.
I wanted to go to the Nether World
to do the same thing as you.
But after hearing what Zhiyang said,
I had to come back.
There is only one way back
to the God Realm.
You can’t say
that I followed you on purpose.
Back to the God Realm?
This is Taichu Hall!
What a lousy excuse!
All right, stop there.
I’m not feeling that bad.
You are lying.
You can’t look someone in the eye
when you are lying.
You...!
All right.
I want Shanggu to ascend
the throne as soon as possible.
But I really can’t bear to see her
suffer in the Nether World.
Yeah.
Of course we can’t.
Now she is in the Nether World.
If she gets hurt,
or if anything happens to her...
You...
She is more courageous than both of us.
Maybe she became matured long ago.
It’s just that we can’t let her go.
I blame myself for being incompetent.
Tianqi.
Master.
Master Tianqi.
Why are you so happy?
Master.
I’ve understood the fourth stage
of Six Moves of Extreme Yin.
That’s why you are so happy?
Gu Jun is already a god now.
Master.
Since I came to the God Realm,
I never slacked off
and I have been practicing every day.
Why did you take it out
on my apprentice?
He can’t even take one punch.
What a loser.
I’m fine.
Master Tianqi is enlightening me.
I’m glad you have some wisdom.
Go ahead.
Yes.
What a muddled
master you are!
No wonder he is
making progress so slowly.
I saw blood stasis in his vessels.
So I got them through for him.
I...
What?
Get inside and have a drink.
Wait for me.
(The Pilgrimage Hall)
Her Grace went to cultivate herself
for one thousand years.
Those Attendant Gods are talkative.
They are jealous of me
because they think Her Grace favors me.
What should I do
if they won’t listen to me?
I got used to being alone
when I was in the Abyssal Ridge Swamp.
I don’t have much experience
in interpersonal relationship.
Gu Jun! Wu Huan!
My spiritual power has improved again.
How about having a friendly competition?
You came just right.
Wu Huan, Muguang has many siblings
and he led troops before.
He must know how to handle it.
What’s the matter?
After Master left,
Wu Huan worries
that those Attendant Gods
won’t listen to her.
Those people never liked me.
But because Her Grace favors me,
they dare not show it.
But right now...
Actually, it’s the time for you
to establish your prestige
while Her Grace is away.
Establish my prestige?
It’s good already not to be bullied.
Although you are
the Divine Beast of Her Grace,
when Her Grace is here,
you are also an Attendant God
just like them.
Now Her Grace left,
and you are the most powerful person
in the Pilgrimage Hall.
Pick those who are kind and obedient
as your people.
As for those who don’t listen to you,
don’t be afraid to punish them
when they make any mistake.
Then give them some favors.
It won’t take long
before they obey you.
It’s the carrot and stick approach?
Yes.
The way to lead troops is nothing
more than to put yourself in their shoes
and employ both kindness and severity.
It’s easy to talk.
What if those disobedient attendants
get more aggressive
and start to bully me?
Don’t worry about that.
You got me.
I’ll beat anyone who dares to bully you.
Okay.
Then I’ll try it.
I’ll manage
the Pilgrimage Hall well
for the next one thousand years.
I won’t fail Her Grace’s trust.
You can do it.
By the way,
did you just say
that your spiritual power had improved?
Master Tianqi helped me with it.
Let’s try it?
Okay, you two go ahead
and bring out the best in each other.
I’ll make some tea for you.
Thank you.
You are ordered
to guard the Nether World.
But you are negligent of your duties.
You are committing a crime.
It’s you.
You’ve been reduced to this place.
Stop pulling rank on us.
How dare you!
I’m the god in charge of
the four seasons of the lower realm.
If you dare say that again,
I’ll tell on you to the God Realm.
Cut it out.
Everyone knows that you were
banished from the God Realm.
Anyone who is demoted
to guard the Nether World
won’t have a chance to go back.
If you have time to bicker with me,
you’d better find a place
and take some rest.
Shanggu.
I’ll go back fair and square
and make you pay for it.
♪Listen♪
♪Under the dome♪
♪It’s the monologue of all creatures♪
♪Watch♪
♪The waves follow the mountains♪
♪Come and go♪
♪Look♪
♪The road ahead♪
♪Is covered with heavy mist♪
♪Standing forever♪
♪Above the clouds♪
♪Outside the world♪
♪Could you lend me more years♪
♪I embrace the Milky Way for long♪
♪But where are you♪
♪Only a shadow is left♪
♪Wandering in the old dreams♪
♪After countless sufferings♪
♪How many years have I wandered♪
♪If you were there If you were far away♪
♪Who♪
♪In the ancient time♪
♪Stood alone♪
♪Snow♪
♪Doesn’t melt
on the top of the mountain♪
♪And it gleams♪
♪Who looks♪
♪Like the moon♪
♪High up in the sky♪
♪I risked my life for the world♪
♪With a brandish♪
♪The world appears♪
Look, who is that?
Such powerful spiritual power.
That’s God Gu Jun.
He was selected by True God Shanggu
for cultivation in the Pilgrimage Hall.
He has a graceful figure indeed.
I wish I could also be selected
at the God-selecting Meeting
to cultivate myself
in the Pilgrimage Hall this time.
Look how lazy you are.
You still want to
enter the Pilgrimage Hall?
Maybe next life.
Thank you, Master.
Good, you’ve improved a lot.
Muguang has been a god for years.
I just promoted him to
one of the twelve apostles.
So he can help me share
my work in the Three Realms.
Be patient and cultivate yourself.
Don’t let your master down.
Yes.
Muguang’s willpower
is much stronger than mine.
Over these years,
whenever I asked him to
play dominoes or cards with me,
he always rejected me.
He never indulges in fun.
By the way,
why did you come here?
You are not here
just to coach Muguang, right?
The gift for your 100,000th birthday.
It’s a few days later.
I can’t wait.
Thanks.
By the way, there is some good news.
What is it?
The air of chaos in the lower realm
is increasing day by day.
Zhiyang and I guess
Shanggu is coming back soon.
That’s great!
Master.
I want to tell the good news to Gu Jun.
Just Gu Jun?
No Wu Huan?
Master,
I’m leaving.
When did it happen
between him and Wu Huan?
He is quite like me in this regard.
Nothing really started yet.
Come on, let me take you
to the warehouse.
I’m going to show Shanggu
all the good stuff
I’ve collected over these years.
No, wait. you have to come with me
to Taichu Hall.
There is one thing I need you to do.
Yeah.
Goddess.
The Dragon King of the East Sea
sent a pair of aquamarine pearls
in person yesterday.
He said it was a gift
for your birthday one month later.
Goddess, you are in charge of
the Pilgrimage Hall now
and are favored by
the True Gods Zhiyang and Tianqi.
Not to mention the Immortal Realm
and the Demon Realm,
even those from the God Realm
want to please you.
Exactly.
You are the head of Pilgrimage Hall now.
Of course your birthday banquet will be
bigger than that in the Moon House.
Don’t be disrespectful.
How can my birthday banquet
be compared with
Goddess Yuemi’s birthday banquet?
Who just broke the Chihe Jade?
Staying silent?
I’m in in charge of the Pilgrimage Hall
by Her Grace’s order.
Every object here
is the treasure of Her Grace.
You know my rules.
If you cover for each other
and don’t tell me who did it,
you will all get out of the God Realm.
Goddess Wu Huan, please calm your anger.
What’s wrong? What happened?
Someone broke Her Grace’s Chihe Jade.
I’m disciplining them.
It’s just a piece of jade.
Admonishing them is enough.
There is no need to be so angry.
The Pilgrimage Hall is a place of honor
in the Three Realms.
The outsiders will laugh at us
if I don’t rule here strictly.
It’s not a big deal.
Just a piece of jade.
If Master is fond of it,
just tell them to be more careful later.
That’s Her Grace’s beloved object.
Of course I need to
discipline them strictly.
I’ll let you go this time.
Leave us.
Thank you, Goddess.
Wu Huan, you punish
the Attendant Gods too often
and it’s not good for the reputation
of the Pilgrimage Hall.
You got more irritable
after Master left.
Her Grace is not here.
I don’t know what to do.
I just want to
manage the Pilgrimage Hall well
and not let Her Grace down.
I know your intention.
But don’t go too hard on yourself.
I know.
Didn’t you go to inspect
the Three Realms
by the order of God Zhiyang?
How come you’re back
in less than a month?
There is great news in the God Realm.
I told him to come back earlier.
Right.
Goddess Yuemi’s
100,000th birthday banquet
is a few days later.
You should come back
to celebrate her birthday.
Master is coming back soon.
What did you say?
A month ago,
the mountains and seas
moved frequently in the lower realm.
Master Zhiyang guessed
that Her Grace must have
obtained the Power of Chaos
and she is coming back
to the God Realm soon.
That’s why there were
all those strange signs.
That’s right. I went there
to take a look with Gu Jun.
There was Power of Chaos flowing over
the barriers in the lower realm.
Masters guess
that True God Shanggu will be back soon.
Wu Huan. Wu Huan?
What’s wrong?
Her Grace is finally coming back.
I’m...
I’m so happy.
You’ve worked hard to manage
the Pilgrimage Hall over these years.
After Master comes back,
I’ll help you cultivate
your spiritual power.
Shanggu.
Long time no see. I really miss you.
No.
That’s too casual.
It’s not serious enough.
Rewrite it.
No, no.
This is too indifferent.
How can that let Shanggu know
how much we miss her?
Then write it by yourself.
I can’t.
Come on, sit down.
Our Goddess Yuemi
is the greatest literary talent
in three generations.
I don’t know how that silly girl
can withstand the loneliness
in the Nether World.
Fortunately, her days
in the Nether World
will be over soon.
After she comes back this time,
no matter what happens,
I won’t let her leave again.
The Origin of God-defending,
I must have you.
Your Grace!
Over the last thousand years,
you’ve had an arduous journey
and many injuries.
Aren’t you tired?
We can’t bear to see you suffer anymore.
Why don’t you go back to the God Realm
and let’s live in peace?
Go ahead!
Why is that?
Could it be that...?
The Origin of God-defending is the most
valuable treasure in the Three Realms.
Does it also choose its master?
What is fighting? What is killing?
Did the Ancestral God create
the world to destroy it?
What is the cause? What is the result?
Endless life, endless killing.
It will lead to no good result
to end war by war.
The Origin of God-defending.
I finally understand
that the Power of Chaos
can create everything
and can also destroy everything.
With my obtaining the Power of Chaos,
the mountains and seas can be moved
or calmed by a momentary thought.
From today on,
the Three Realms are under my feet
and all creatures are in my hands.
That’s what
the Power of Chaos looks like.
Her Grace made it.
Master finally finished her cultivation.
- Yeah!
- That’s great.
Did you just hear any sound?
A sound?
There hasn’t been a shadow of demon
over the last one thousand years.
What sound could there be?
It was not the sound of a demon.
It sounded like...
It sounded like a spirit.
Such pure god power of fire.
It can only be...
Master Bai Jue.
Guard here.
I’ll be right back.
Master Zhiyang.
Master!
Master Zhiyang,
you can’t go inside!
My master is bathing now.
Master Zhiyang! Master Zhiyang!
Master Zhiyang, it’s… rude…
You said he was bathing two hours ago.
I don’t believe it would take him
so long to take a bath.
Step aside.
I’m going inside.
What’s the matter?
Bai Jue, I came to tell you
that Shanggu has got
the Origin of God-defending.
I see.
Why is he so calm?
Did he know it earlier than me?
What? Say it.
Master Zhiyang,
when will Her Grace come back?
There are signs of Power of Chaos
in the lower realm.
Shanggu will return to
the God Realm tomorrow.
What are you smiling for?
Overlord, I’ve accomplished my mission.
You did a good job.
Overlord.
We’ve been preparing and planning
for a thousand years
and we sacrificed so many fellows
so that the Chief God could obtain
the Power of Chaos.
Everything will be
going your way, Overlord.
I just got the news
that the spirit of Goddess of Snow
entered the Nether World.
Do I need to do anything?
They all say that our Nether World
is a purgatory.
But those from the God Realm
came here one after another.
Interesting.
I heard that Xueying
is jealous of Shanggu
and she was expelled from
the God Realm by Bai Jue.
How about
we give her a hand?
It’s very injurious to extract
the spirit from the body.
Master actually did that for her.
Didn’t he know
it would ruin his original being
in this way?
Well done, little girl.
You obtained the Power of Chaos
only within one thousand years.
You just look a little beaten up.
Thanks to you.
Otherwise, I wouldn’t have had
such a miserable time
over the past one thousand years.
If it weren’t for me to help you,
how could you have obtained
the Power of Chaos so quickly?
You are right.
I appreciate
your favor.
Well?
You are leaving?
I’ve obtained the Power of Chaos
and your barrier is also broken.
It’s time to go back to the God Realm.
It took you one thousand years
to obtain the Power of Chaos.
Even Ancestral God Qingtian
also spent that long.
You only used one thousand years,
is it because there is someone you love
in the God Realm?
The other three true gods
are like my real brothers.
Don’t be ridiculous.
I didn’t say the one you love
is a true god.
Considering you’ve had
such a miserable life,
being trapped here for years,
I’ll let that go.
I’m leaving.
Girl.
Take care.
Don’t worry.
As long as you are obedient,
the gods won’t give you a hard time.
I’m leaving.
Those gods have always been so stupid.
They only keep on guard against me.
They never know
their biggest enemy in the Three Realms
is called destiny.
Moyu.
Yes, Overlord.
I’ve learned everything
about the God Realm through Shanggu
over the past one thousand year.
Take my spiritual power
and break the Qiong Qi barrier
at the Red Blood Forest
in the Demon Realm.
Remember.
I’ve cast a spell on Goddess of Snow.
She can be really useful for you
to finish your task in the God Realm.
Yes!
The God Realm has been
peaceful for too long.
It’s time to have some fun.
Shanggu.
It’s been a thousand years.
I’ve been missing you.
It’s not good.
It sounds too formal.
Shanggu.
Ice Cube?
I’ve been waiting for this moment
for a thousand years.
I can’t let you meet Shanggu first.
How is your spiritual power so weak?
It’s not your concern.
It’s a sign that your spirit
left your body before.
Have you been...?
It’s common to have the spirit
damaged during cultivation.
There is no need to make a big deal.
Don’t you think
I will tell it to Shanggu.
I won’t let you
gain Shanggu’s sympathy.
Goddess of Snow, why are you here?
The beast Qiong Qi
broke out from the barrier.
Let me in.
I have to see Master Zhiyang.
Thank you, Goddess Xueying.
Hold the barrier!
We’ve been waiting for long.
Why isn’t Shanggu back yet?
Masters.
Master Shanggu left the Nether World
an hour ago.
Gods.
I don’t know why Qiong Qi
came to attack us.
Isn’t Qiong Qi’s clan
imprisoned in the Wasteland
of the Demon Realm?
It won’t be that easy!
Qiong Qi is fierce and terrifying!
These people are no match for them!
We must guard the gate
and wait for the True Gods to come!
Qiong Qi can’t see with its eyes.
There must be someone who led them here.
If we kill their leader,
they will fall to pieces!
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪