=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 9=
Why don’t you feed me?
Don’t go too far.
How much could
a Nine-Clawed Lotus hurt you?
Didn’t you use to kick
the Nine-headed Snake
and punch the Roc Bird?
Can you be so weak?
When was I that valorous?
You’re too old to remember it correctly.
Shanggu,
just feed me one.
Why allowed you to stand here?
I didn’t invite you.
Are you here for me?
The Nine-Clawed Lotus that hurt Tianqi
was from Changyuan Hall’s east pond.
It has nothing to do with Gu Jun.
It was my oversight.
I’m here to make an apology to you.
Is this your attitude to apologize?
I’m the one who was hurt!
You decide if you accept the apology.
Tianqi,
please be the bigger person
and let go of
the Nine-Clawed Lotus thing.
Don’t bring it up again.
Come on.
Forget it.
It’s not a big deal.
I don’t care much.
Anyway,
I’ve got something more important to do.
Within one month,
I’ll train Shanggu’s disciple,
Gu Jun, with her.
If you do,
Gu Jun will lose.
Why do you think he’ll lose?
Shanggu,
let’s make a good showing.
In a month, let’s make Ice Cube...
The Dark Abyss.
I’d like to lend you the Dark Abyss
to help Gu Jun become a God.
I don’t believe you.
You’re never so kind.
This is the pellet
I made for Gu Jun
to unblock his cold veins.
When did you make it?
How did you know
he was born with cold veins?
You expect him to lose, don’t you?
Shanggu learns cultivation from me.
Gu Jun’s problem
is also my problem.
Shanggu,
have some dignity.
Just pellets.
I’ll make some for you.
Who dares to take any pellets
with alcohol?
I swear I won’t drink any
within one month.
Who believes that?
You!
Come on, Shanggu.
True God Bai Jue, I’d like to thank you
on behalf of Gu Jun.
You’re welcome.
Shanggu,
I’ve got some other things.
Elixirs, magic weapons,
armors and good wine.
I’ve got everything.
Don’t bother.
You don’t like Gu Jun, do you?
Why do you suddenly show some mercy?
Trying to take him away?
Come to the Pilgrimage Hall
at 11 tonight.
I’ll give you the key to the Dark Abyss.
Shanggu,
you promised me last night.
Don’t break your promise.
What are you doing?
Are you done?
Tianqi,
the Dark Abyss
is indeed the best place for Gu Jun.
All right.
Don’t bother to explain.
I don’t want to listen.
See you
at 11 tonight.
Wait.
When we proposed the fight,
we only said if Gu Jun lost,
I would go
to the Nether World immediately.
But we didn’t say
what if he won.
That’s right.
We’re all here.
Let’s discuss about it.
Looks like
I’m asking for a snub again.
Shanggu.
Shanggu!
Bai Jue,
you cultivated yourself alone
in the past tens of thousands of years.
Zhiyang and I brought Shanggu up.
So, you don’t decide
if she goes to the Nether World or not!
Zhiyang,
don’t you think so?
Where’s he?
Master,
something urgent happened
in the lower realm.
True God Zhiyang has gone to handle it.
What a silly old thing!
Are you all right?
I’m fine.
You really do well in swordsmanship.
Her Grace is right about you.
What’s the good of that?
I’m born with cold veins
and chaotic spiritual power.
The cultivation
is over a thousand times harder for me.
Don’t lose heart.
Now that you’re in the Pilgrimage Hall
and Her Grace thinks highly of you,
she’ll figure out a way
to help you complete
your cultivation soon.
If you’re in need,
ask me to practice swordsmanship
with you at any time.
Thank you, Wu Huan.
When I was in the Phoenix Clan,
I was nothing
but a humble colorful Phoenix.
Thanks to the help of Her Grace,
I’ve come this far.
I believe
you’ll distinguish yourself one day.
I don’t care about that.
Master doesn’t despise my humble origin
and she’s nice to me.
I want nothing,
but to win honor for her.
Why were you practicing
even before I come?
Greetings, Wu Huan.
Go on with it.
I’ll leave you alone.
Wu Huan,
please wait.
I see you work hard
to take care of the Pilgrimage Hall.
This is the hot spring mud
we have on Mount Tianci.
Turn it into water
and apply it on your skin.
It’ll keep your skin moist.
Here’s some and please have a try.
Thank you, Muguang.
But you don’t need
to bother for me.
Thank goodness.
You finally smiled.
If you hadn’t stopped me,
I would have fallen out with Ice Cube.
It’s not a festival.
Why did you set fireworks?
As long as you can smile,
I’m willing to set fireworks
for you every day.
Keep such romantic words
for other goddesses.
Shanggu,
do you really not understand
or are you playing fool?
It’s been so many years.
Can’t you see
how I feel for you?
Shanggu,
I like you.
I adore you
and all can be my witnesses
that I’m not lying.
Shanggu,
don’t you have any...?
Tianqi,
I always treat you as my elder brother.
I never have any feeling...
♪Large memories are for you♪
The wind is blowing hard.
I didn’t hear what you said at all.
Shanggu, I’ll come to see you tomorrow.
Tianqi.
♪Engraved in the palm♪
I don’t know how love feels.
But,
I know how it feels
when you don’t get what you want.
You’re my most important elder brother.
♪I can’t help missing you♪
Now that I matter so much to you,
why can’t you love me?
Tianqi.
♪Write down our whispers♪
♪In the name of the world♪
All right.
I was kidding.
Shanggu,
I like you.
I’m already satisfied
when I’ve told you.
You can turn me down,
but you can’t keep me away.
No matter it’s ten thousand years
or a hundred thousand years,
I insist on loving you
and haunting you
until death.
♪Wait until we meet again♪
Tianqi,
why take the trouble?
Yeah.
It’s trouble.
Too much trouble.
Shanggu,
don’t worry.
I’ll always be your elder brother.
No matter what happens between us
or what we experience,
♪When tears♪
I’ll always be by your side.
♪How much luck do I need♪
♪To get myself♪
♪Be always stuck♪
♪In your heart♪
Hongri, what’s the time?
It’s nearly 11.
You’re right in time.
When the competition ends,
leave the God Realm willingly.
Don’t make me
expose your crime in public.
I don’t understand.
Master, what do you mean?
If I made any mistake,
please tell me.
What wrong have I done?
Why are you so cold to me only?
Bai Jue,
I’ve got something to tell you.
About Shanggu.
It’s already 11.
Why hasn’t Bai Jue come yet?
Your Grace,
have some tea and calm down.
Master,
I have had the cold veins
for over a dozen years.
I’m used to it.
Don’t feel anxious.
Now that Bai Jue offered
to lend us the Dark Abyss,
he won’t break his promise.
He’ll certainly complete his promise.
If he has changed his mind,
it’s my destiny.
I’ll forget it, then.
Don’t worry.
Master Bai Jue never breaks his promise.
This is
the Cloud Grass of our clan.
I made it into a sachet.
Carry it with you
and it’ll restrain the cold veins.
Compared to the Dark Abyss,
it has little effect.
But better little than none.
Wu Huan,
you’re so nice to me. I...
Say no more.
Practice carefully.
If you can defeat the Goddess of Snow
in this competition,
you’ll win honor
for the Pilgrimage Hall.
Here.
Don’t worry.
I won’t let you down.
Zhiyang is so busy.
But look at you. You’re drunk.
Ridiculous.
I’m so depressed
that I need liquor to get me better.
What?
Want a fight?
That’s exactly what I want.
I’m helping you sober up.
You’re welcome.
I know.
I’m so close to Shanggu
that you’re angry.
You’re just jealous.
Nonsense!
What a surprise!
You even get jealous.
You look tough,
but you’re timid inside.
You’re even worse than me.
At least, I dare to confess my love
and I live a freer life than you.
Shanggu is destined to be the Chief God.
She’ll take over
the instruction feather of Chief God.
To her,
love is simply a drop in the bucket
and it doesn’t matter.
Are you persuading me or yourself?
As long as she cultivates herself
and lives a good life,
that’s enough for me.
That’s enough for you.
But is that enough for her?
Bai Jue,
I think you’re poor and selfish.
But you don’t deserve any sympathy.
For you,
I’ve waited for so many years.
But you’re doing all this
for Shanggu!
Bai Jue.
Bai Jue, where are you?
Bai Jue!
Shanggu.
I’m sorry.
Gu Jun and I waited for long.
I promise you.
If Gu Jun wins,
you don’t need to go
to the Nether World.
Seriously?
It depends on you, then.
Rest assured.
I’ll urge Gu Jun to practice hard.
I’ll do that, too.
I’ll defeat Gu Jun
and see how you end up.
Thunderclouds have gathered.
Gu Jun, this is the tribulation for you.
Gu Jun, hang in there!
Five thunder strikes left.
Master!
Her Grace is in danger! Shall we...?
I believe she can hold it.
♪Who♪
♪In the ancient time♪
♪Stood alone♪
♪Snow♪
♪Doesn’t melt
on the top of the mountain♪
♪And it gleams♪
♪Who looks♪
♪Like the moon♪
♪High up in the sky♪
♪I risked my life for the world♪
♪With a brandish♪
♪The world appears♪
Master, thank you for helping me
become a God!
I never expected the thunder strikes
to be so horrible.
♪Where are old friends♪
♪Only your figure♪
♪Lingers in my dream♪
♪After countless tribulations♪
What luck do I have?
Even the thunder didn’t strike me.
♪If you’re in front of me or far away♪
When I had the tribulation...
♪I’ll be delighted despite the hardship♪
♪If you’re in front of me or far away♪
♪I’ll break through the way♪
Master, you took the thunder strikes
for Her Grace.
Looks like she still remembers.
She’s become more sensible.
(Report from Chief of Twelve Apostles)
(Lately, immortals keep dying
without a reason.)
(Goddess Yuemi,
please figure out the reason.)
Yuemi.
What makes you so happy today?
Good news.
Gu Jun finally unblocked his cold veins
and became a God.
If he wins the competition,
I won’t need to go to the Nether World.
That’s great.
There’s finally good news.
In case,
I’ve taught him some advanced skills.
He said he was confident to win.
In this way,
I can always stay with you.
You mean with Bai Jue, right?
I don’t want to benefit from him.
What?
You said there was finally good news.
Did you have all bad news today?
Not only today,
for days.
Every day, immortals die
without a reason.
Even heavenly generals have suffered.
Even I might suffer soon.
Devils did that?
Go and ask Zhiyang.
But now I finally understand that
Bai Jue insists on letting you
experience in the Nether World
so that you can acquire
the Power of Chaos
for a right reason.
For several spiritual veins,
how many years
have you fought
and how many members of yours have died?
Your Grace.
Why can’t you stop?
Why is Zhiyang so angry?
He’s upset about the dispute
between seven islands.
You’d better not get in, Your Grace.
I understand.
To block the cracking barrier,
you have few spiritual veins left.
You both are at the end of your ropes.
If the problem isn’t solved...
Why are there few spiritual veins?
Everyone in the Three Realms
is expecting
Your Grace
to take over the instruction feather
of Chief God soon,
because the Power of Chaos
in the lower realm collapses.
The distribution of spiritual power
has already been out of balance.
(Trivial Stories
Love Story of Nine-headed Snakes)
Gu Jun, congratulations.
You’ve made great progress.
Without Master’s help
in the Dark Abyss,
I wouldn’t have become a God.
Wu Huan,
thank you for the sachet, too.
The sachet has little effect.
Never mind.
By the way,
tomorrow you’ll have a competition
with Goddess Xueying.
Don’t waste the efforts
Her Grace made on you.
Don’t worry.
I won’t disappoint you and Master.
You’re used to using spells.
But I got my skills
by fighting in the swamps.
You cheated.
You just became a God.
How could you have such strong power?
Goddess of Snow,
just say it if you can’t accept losing.
You used spells
when fighting my master.
But I used none of them today.
I didn’t cheat at all.
I won the competition.
Master Bai Jue,
please take back the order
sending my master to the Nether World.
I know what to do.
Shanggu,
you must also practice hard
when you stay in the God Realm.
Goddess of Snow,
now that you lost,
shouldn’t you keep your promise?
Forget it.
I’ll make the decision
and spare you.
Thank you, Your Grace.
Wait!
Your Grace,
there was a fire in Taichu Hall
and the Nine-Clawed Lotus
wounded Master Tianqi.
I’ve figured it out
and I want to tell on someone.
Hongri,
it wasn’t a fight of some immortals?
Zhong Li, Xia Hui,
come out and confess!
Master, please understand.
It’s her. Goddess Xueying hinted us
to steal the Nine-Clawed Lotus
from the east pond of Changyuan Hall
and frame Gu Jun up.
Goddess of Snow disobeyed the rules.
True Gods,
please punish her accordingly.
Master, I’m sorry.
I shouldn’t have disrespected Her Grace.
Master, I know I’m wrong!
Stop calling me Master.
For the sake that you made contributions
when fighting devils,
you’re expelled out of the God Realm
and shall guard the barrier
of the Nether World.
Zhong Li and Xia Hui are expelled, too.
They mustn’t come back again.
Leave!
Get up!
There’s already much fun to see today.
I don’t mean to add more.
In fact, no matter Gu Jun won or lost,
I had decided to go to the Nether World.
I’m not coming back
until I complete my power.
Shanggu,
don’t!
Ten thousand years ago,
I was born on Heaven and Earth Platform
in the name of the Chief God.
I feel quite guilty.
When Xuanyi was the Chief God,
he could at least defend the God Realm.
But I
don’t have much power
or make any contribution
to the Three Realms.
It may also be the reason
why Goddess of Snow doesn’t respect me.
Even if you leave
the Three Realms to me,
you’ll be worried, right?
So,
I’ve decided to cultivate myself
in the Nether World alone.
After I complete the Power of Chaos,
I’ll defend the Three Realms.
I may not grow up
unless I leave you.
The world is big.
Time for me to go out for a look.
A thousand years isn’t long.
Wait for me.
Who are you?
How dare you break in the Devil Realm?
Are you not wanting a long life
and seeking for your doom?
Want to kill me?
Let’s see if you can.
She’s heading for Overlord...
Let her go.
(The Pilgrimage Hall)
Shanggu.
Shanggu,
I’ve found some good story books
in the lower realm
and let’s enjoy them.
Shanggu.
What a poor memory I have!
She’s gone to the Nether World.
What are you doing?
You freaked me out!
Well, let me tell the truth.
Shanggu is going to stay in
the Nether World for a thousand years.
Without such treasures,
I’m afraid she’ll feel bored.
So, I came secretly
to bring her some toys and books.
I nearly forgot this.
You!
You’re the obstacle
on her way to success.
Bai Jue is trying hard to instruct her,
but you always make trouble.
You’re complaining about me?
What’s this?
I just miss her.
Ice Cube let Shanggu
cultivate herself alone.
Will she suffer there?
She will, of course.
But Bai Jue didn’t think about
who brought Shanggu up.
You brought her up.
She won’t easily suffer.
You’re right.
When Shanggu is away,
I feel a void in my heart.
She’s there for cultivation,
but I still want to see her.
Don’t you have any business to do?
No.
You do?
Go.
Let me show you
what business I have.
Where are we going?
Why did you take me here?
That’s Altair.
And that’s Vega.
I know.
The Ancestral God punished them
so that they couldn’t
get back together for years.
That’s cruel.
How about
making them get back together
after Shanggu becomes the Chief God?
They meet once a year,
but they have quite a lot of babies.
Altair is taking care of them.
All Vega does is to enjoy her life,
instead of suffering
from raising babies.
She’s quite happy.
She isn’t as miserable as others think.
Is... Is that all right?
Why isn’t it?
As long as they decide
who works and who takes care of babies,
it’s family stuff.
Others shouldn’t interfere.
You know what?
You have a point.
But, sometimes when I see them
miss each other too much,
I let them meet secretly
when others are not noticing.
I appreciate it when you break rules
and behave willingly.
Would you like a chess game?
Where are the chess pieces?
You always look rude.
I didn’t expect you
to enjoy the chess game?
Will you play or not?
I will.
There you are, Your Grace.
What?
Aren’t you afraid of death?
I checked ancient books before I came.
Bai Jue wanted me to cultivate myself
in the Nether World
because the Deicide Flowers
release the spirit of Chaos
when they’re in bloom.
Only the Chief God can absorb it
and it will help me
complete the Power of Chaos.
The blooming will be a thousand years.
So will the cultivation.
Precisely.
But Bai Jue neglected another treasure.
The Origin of God-defending
at the border of the Nether World.
Looks like you did some work.
I come here to cultivate my power.
Before I make it,
I’m not leaving.
I come to see you,
because I want you to set up a barrier
at the border of the Nether World
that even Gods can’t break.
You’re afraid they may regret
and drag you back to the God Realm?
I’m afraid I can’t hold it,
and then I’ll count on others
or miss the comfort in the God Realm.
Your Grace,
you’re still so straightforward.
I can help you,
but on two conditions.
What conditions?
Devils like us are always bloodthirsty.
Many devils guard
at the border of the Nether World.
Even Bai Jue can’t take much advantage.
So, leave your life to destiny.
I won’t show mercy on you.
It’s not that easy to kill me, either.
What’s the second condition?
I’ve been too lonely in this place.
I need you to come often
and chat with me.
Look how I’m chained.
Are you afraid I’ll kill you?
If I die,
I can’t chat with you.
You’re such a lovely goddess.
I don’t really want to kill you.
Once my barrier is set up,
you cannot get out of the Nether World
unless you become the Chief God.
Have you thought it over?
It’s my first time
to think something over so carefully.
- Greetings, Master Tianqi.
Master Tianqi,
Her Grace ordered that
no one shall get into the Nether World.
Get out of my way.
I’ll stay with Shanggu.
Now you know how dangerous
the Nether World is?
All we should do
is respect her decision.
I’m not like you
who likes to reason things out.
I can’t let her take the risk alone!
Zhiyang, be quick.
Break the barrier with me
and get Shanggu back!
What are you waiting for? Do it!
This month, 38 immortals died.
When Shanggu offered
to go to the Nether World,
I was thinking
if we spoilt her too much
and held up her growth.
In fact,
she’s stronger than we imagined.
If we take her out of the Nether World,
won’t we hold her back?
You’d better pray for her safety.
Master,
the leaving of your spirit
consumes great power
and even hurts your lifespan!
Are you sure you’ll do this?
As long as she’s safe,
let alone ten thousand years’ lifespan,
even if it’s
a hundred thousand years’ lifespan,
I won’t mind.
Rest assured, Master.
I won’t leave this place
and I’ll protect your body.
You must be very careful.
If the devils
or Xuanyi finds your spirit,
your body will be ruined, too.
I know.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪