Previously on Lucifer...
Seriously. Tell me, what
do you actually want?
My father was a cop. He was a great cop.
I really do want to help people.
She starred in Hot Tub High School.
And two weeks later, her father died.
You were right before.
We've been living in
the past for too long.
It's time we get a divorce.
I need to figure out where
I fit in in this world.
So, we're still good
to be roomies, right?
I need you to be honest
with me about who you are.
No more lies.
Very well.
Sloths move faster, Petey.
Snails. The humble tortoise.
- You can't rush perfection.
- This is true.
Hawaiian bread. Just
the way you like it.
- Thanks, Petey.
- No, thank you, Officer Decker.
Before I forget... for you and Grace.
- Hot Tub High School?
- Opens Friday.
My little monkey's gonna be a star.
- We wouldn't miss it.
- Do me a favor.
I hear there's some funny
business about 15 minutes in...
- Oh, you mean that scene where...
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's not finish that thought.
Just tell her it was a good movie.
- Kids these days.
- Yeah, I know.
But, hey... I'm proud of her.
You okay, Petey?
Hey, listen...
Hand over the cash.
- Yes, don't shoot.
- Come on.
- Here, here, here you go, don't shoot.
- Hurry up.
Empty the whole thing.
Come on, let's go, let's go.
No, Warden, you listen to me.
This man killed my father.
He cannot be released.
Detective!
- I have a bone to pick with you.
- Not a good time, Lucifer.
Agreed. It's a horrible time.
Dr. Linda just canceled my session.
She won't take my calls. I
think I... truly scared her off.
Something happened with your shrink?
Yes... and it's all your fault.
I mean, you're the one who
suggested I open up to her.
Well, smashing advice, Detective.
I don't have time for this right now.
What, do we have a case?
I'm dealing with my own issues.
Oh! Even better.
- Let's solve those, shall we?
- Lucifer, stop!
I'm sorry, but there is no way
that you can help me right now.
You're just... you're too you.
Oh.
Yes, you're right, Detective.
Being me seems to be
a problem, doesn't it?
Everywhere I go, someone gets hurt.
Well, clearly, I need
to be Not-Me instead.
Someone... better, more helpful.
- More boring.
- Okay...
got you a hot, soy latte, extra foam.
Thank you.
You okay, Chloe?
Mm-hmm. All good.
Just on my way out.
Something's seriously bothering her.
Hmm?
Oh, I hadn't noticed.
But you did.
This isn't right, Warden.
Joe Fields is a convicted
murderer, a cop killer.
You're letting him off on family leave?
Detective, I understand how you feel.
Oh, respectfully, there is no
way you understand how I feel.
I'm sorry.
I know it's your father we're talking
about, but... this wasn't my call.
Fields has been a model
prisoner for over a decade.
He lobbied the Prisoner's
Rights Board and they said yes.
What's he gonna do with his leave?
Go destroy another family?
It's for his
granddaughter's christening.
My dad never got to go to his
Where is the justice in that?
I'm sorry, Detective.
I wish there was something we could do.
- Uh... Decker.
- Ah, Detective!
I think I may have found a
way to make myself useful.
What? It's not a good time, Lucifer.
What if I told you I
wasn't Lucifer anymore?
What?
I've decided to try and walk
a mile in another man's shoes.
See the world from a
different perspective.
I'm going to learn how to Douche.
I... may have to rephrase that one.
But do I have your permission
to follow Daniel and...
Yeah, do whatever. I got to go.
Hello?
- I'll take that as a yes.
- Yeah, I'm just following up on...
Uh, yeah.
Joe Fields.
Come out.
You're not gonna get away with this.
Joe Fields...
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
I still don't get it, man.
Why the hell are you following
me around all of a sudden?
Because I want to learn what
it's like to be you, Daniel.
Your approach to life intrigues me.
This from the guy who
punched me in the face?
That was last week.
Anyway, the detective
already agreed to it.
You're the department bottom,
so you have to do as she says.
What's this really about?
Look, people like you.
They find you helpful, like duct
tape or a trusty socket wrench.
I want you to teach me your secret.
I want you to show me how to be a tool.
You should stay out of the way.
Follow my lead. I call all
the shots, you understand?
This feels like something that
you would agree to, so yes.
What do we got?
Three gunshot victims,
shot execution style.
The van driver got a
single bullet to the neck,
guard got one to the head.
The prisoner got a
double tap to the chest.
Prisoner's name is Joe Fields.
- Wait a minute, the Joe Fields? As in...
- Yeah.
The guy that killed my father.
They targeted him while he was
vulnerable. This was a hit, Dan.
W-Wait a second.
The guy who killed your dad was just
murdered and you caught the case?
Yeah.
That is totally messed up.
- Mm-hmm.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- Fine?
You should be ecstatic.
Your father's killer just
got the ultimate punishment.
- Who was first on the scene?
- It was me.
I made the call.
- You followed him?
- Yeah. I know this looks bad.
You stalked your father's murderer
right before he was killed.
That was a terrible move, Detective.
It was, right?
What were you planning to do, Chloe?
Crash the christening?
I don't know, Dan! I was angry.
The guy killed my father.
He had the nerve to smile at me.
Do you have any idea
what that feels like?
No.
No, I don't.
But you still shouldn't
have followed him.
No one actually thinks
that you did this,
- but you know what it looks like, right?
- Yes, I do.
That's why I'm gonna
step away from the case.
It's a massive conflict of interest.
Don't worry, Chloe.
I'm gonna stay on this.
Yes, Detective Dan and I won't
rest until we catch the killer.
I don't think that it's a good idea
for Lucifer to be part of this case.
I agree.
I mean, the last thing this
case needs is a loose canon.
She needs someone like you. A
reliable, helpful, boring detective.
Now, the good news is that's me as
well now. So, the Dans are on the case.
Can't you take anything seriously, man?
I assure you I'm taking
this very seriously.
Oh, really? You're doing a
great job of showing that.
Guys.
It would mean a lot to me if
you worked together on this.
Hmm.
Of course, Chloe.
Okay, so...
whoa, this looks heavy.
Like waiting-for-STD-results heavy.
- I can come back later.
- Oh, no, it's fine. What is it?
Okay, so, I went through
all the prints from the van.
Okay? And all of them
cleared as prison personnel
except for an ex-con named Rodney Lam.
And get this...
he served time with Joe Fields.
- We're on it.
Nice.
You working on a new role?
Hmm?
You're wearing that to an interview?
What's the job?
Preschool aide.
Do you like little kids?
I've dealt with filthy,
screaming humans before.
At least these are smaller.
I'm not sure this is you.
Ms. Perez says we should
choose jobs we love doing.
So, what about you, Maze?
What do you love to do?
I don't know.
Well... just be yourself.
Thanks, little human.
So good.
Well, the secret ingredient
is the Hawaiian bread.
And then you just cut a hole
in the middle for the egg.
Can we have this for every meal?
You know, this one used
to be my favorite, too.
Grandpa used to bring me this sandwich
every Thursday after acting class.
Why don't you ever talk about Grandpa?
Mm...
I guess 'cause I miss him.
Do you think he would've
brought me sandwiches?
Mm-hmm.
I think he would've loved that, monkey.
Come on. It's time for your homework.
- Can I help you?
- Chloe Decker?
You're gonna pay for what you've done.
Okay, take it easy.
My father was a good man.
He didn't deserve to get
gunned down like an animal.
All he wanted was to meet my daughter.
You're Tina Fields.
You killed my father.
- I didn't...
- Thought you were getting revenge,
but you murdered an innocent man.
Tina, think about your baby.
If you pull that trigger,
you'll never hold her again.
Mommy? Who's here?
It's nothing, honey. Stay in your room!
I didn't kill your father.
You have to believe me.
Mommy, is everything okay?
Yeah, honey. Everything's fine, monkey.
Go back in your room.
Mommy just needs to help another mommy.
- Okay?
- Oh, God, I'm sorry.
I was just so angry.
I never wanted to believe
my dad killed a cop.
And then today, when I got the video...
What video?
His lawyers sent this to me.
Said I was to receive it
upon the event of his death.
Ah. Sorry, not sorry. I had
to stop for a costume change.
Nice jacket. Thank you.
Oh, man, what the hell?
Are you here to work, or
are you here to play games?
I'll have you know I take the
School of Dan quite seriously,
even if it does involve
skinny-fit jeans.
Any news on our suspect?
His name is Rodney Lam.
A CI told me that he's obsessed with
this place. He eats here all the time.
So if he shows up,
let's try to see him before he sees us.
Oh, I get it now.
So your boring attire is
like camo for the average Joe.
Blend in, catch the baddie off guard.
Afterwards they'll
forget you're even there.
That is very clever, Daniel.
This guy has a serious
history of violence.
All right? He might have a gun.
He might take a hostage.
Who knows what he could do?
So he wouldn't, say, be openly eating a
nacho burrito dog, sitting on that car?
- You watch my six.
- Absolutely.
Rodney Lam. LAPD. No sudden
moves. You're under arrest.
Rodney?
Maybe we blend in so well
he doesn't even see us.
Rodney Lam!
Good call, Rodney.
Nice and easy.
Oh.
I just wanted one last meal.
You want a bite? Aah!
No, thank you, we're
not doing carbs, are we?
Baby...
it's Daddy.
If, uh, you're watching this,
that means I'm dead.
Now, I know it sucks.
I don't know if you'll get this tomorrow
or, uh, 30 years from now,
but I want you to know the truth.
I didn't kill that cop.
I'm sorry for...
missing all your birthdays
and graduation... your life.
But Daddy wants you to know, baby...
I love you.
See? He's innocent.
Tina, I can tell your
dad loves you very much,
but... this video
doesn't prove anything.
His lawyers had this tape for 16 years.
He made them promise to
give it to me when he died.
That has to mean something.
16 years.
He recorded this the
day my father was killed.
Three minutes before he died.
What part of town is this?
It's our old apartment in Venice.
My father was killed across
the city in Korea town.
There's no way your father
could have recorded this
and gotten to the crime scene in time.
So it's true. He didn't do it.
Which means whoever did kill my father
got away with this
and is still out there.
I did it.
I killed Joe Fields.
He disrespected me in the yard.
So when I heard that he was getting
some sort of temporary leave,
I knew that it was my
chance to make things right.
Well, there you have it.
Looks like our douching paid off.
The detective will be pleased.
And, you know, you make it look so easy.
Where did you say you
stopped that van again?
- Spring and College.
- We found it at Hill.
That's what I meant.
Then you went and you emptied
the clip into the driver, right?
Hell yeah.
The driver died from a
single shot to the neck.
Dan One, why are you spoiling
a perfectly good confession?
You're lying, Rodney.
You don't know the facts
because you didn't do it.
Oh, I see what you did there.
Gosh, that's why you're Dan One.
Why are you confessing to
a crime you didn't commit?
Where are you going?
Well, just slow your roll for a second.
I think, for the sake of the detective,
I'm gonna take a time-out
from my Dansformation.
Oh, God.
Rodney, what do you
want out of life, hmm?
To be a good provider and
take care of my family.
So you confess to a
crime you didn't commit.
That's quite counter-intuitive.
Unless you got paid to do it.
You've been locked up
for most of your life.
That's all you know.
Now you're free, you've
got mouths to feed,
No way to earn.
Out here I'm no one, guys.
And if we don't arrest you,
you don't get any money.
But if he really wants
back in the slammer,
then false confession's a
criminal offense, correct?
- Definitely an obstruction of justice.
- Mm.
Could get you a few years.
We could get you a narcoleptic
lawyer and a merciless judge.
Who knows? With your prior history,
they might throw the book at you.
- Hmm?
- All right.
Here's how it went down.
I put word out that I needed money,
I was desperate.
And some people came
to me with an offer.
Linda, you there?
I need a character reference.
Linda?
Wha...?
Can you teleport?
What? No.
You left your window open.
Hey, are you okay?
Wait.
You know, don't you?
He showed you.
I saw his face.
Well, you're taking it
really well, actually.
Linda, you're not afraid of me, are you?
Of course I am.
You're a demon.
He told me.
I thought it was a sexual metaphor.
Well, you're not wrong there.
But you really are one.
Aren't you?
Yeah... I am.
Is that really so bad?
Please go.
Ah, Detective...
Joe Fields didn't kill my father.
- Wait, what?
- He's a fall guy.
He made a false confession in exchange
for regular payments to his daughter.
All these years she
didn't touch the money.
She probably thought it was stolen.
I have the account number
that made the transfers.
Well, we just met a chap
who did the same thing.
What?
Rodney got paid to
make a false confession.
Money was transferred into his wife's
account right after we arrested him.
This is the same account
that paid Rodney Lam's wife.
That's no coincidence.
So whoever killed Joe
Fields killed my father...
and is still out there.
Hey, don't blame yourself.
- You were just a kid back then.
- Yeah, well, I'm not anymore.
Hey, rookie!
You're late!
I thought I was early.
Your FTO's been looking
all over for you.
What, you want to get
written up your first day?
- No, I-I honestly thought...
- Knock it off, McMillan.
Get back to work.
You gotta watch out for this guy.
He gave me hell on my first day, too.
- Hi.
I'm Dan Espinoza.
- Chloe Decker.
- Nice to meet you.
Can I help you with those?
Sure.
Come on, I'll show you around.
The most important place,
first, is the kitchen.
We got bagels over
here if you want them.
Interrogation's that way...
and the lab is that way.
Are you John Decker's daughter?
I-I'm so sorry.
He's kind of a legend around here.
It was a little before my time,
but he sounded like a great guy.
The best.
Um... bagel?
Never fear, Luci-Dan is here.
Or is it Douche-ifer? Actually, it's
got more of a ring to it, hasn't it?
- Why are you two dressed the same?
- Don't ask.
The bank account traces
back to a bathhouse on Pico.
It's a dummy front for a
Russian syndicate in L.A.
So the real killer is somehow
connected to the Russian mob?
We have a suspect. His name is
Boris Sokolov. Owns the bathhouse.
Connects criminals but
keeps his own hands clean.
No one has ever been able to get to him.
Yet.
Detective Dan and I won't rest
until we get to the bottom
of this, I promise you.
Wow. Look who bought a
ticket to the gun show!
Divorce becomes you, Detective.
I do not sound like that.
Of course we do.
We sound like two totally normal dudes.
Will you cut it with the "we" stuff?
I need you to stop playing
around and take this seriously.
You got it, partner.
This is gonna be epic.
Lucifer, I'm not kidding.
Very well.
So, what's the plan?
Well, you are exactly the kind of
person that Boris would deal with,
so I need you to approach him,
and try make a deal with him.
All right. Tell him I need a fall
guy for a murder I'm gonna commit?
- Exactly.
- Hmm.
But like I said before, he spooks
really easily. So, don't go...
Boris!
Like that.
Hello there.
Uh, I'd like to talk with you, if I may.
- I don't know you.
- You don't.
So, let's fix that, shall we?
The name's Dan.
- Deputy Warden's here for you.
- Oh.
Joe Fields' personal effects.
We usually turn those over to the
next of kin within 72 hours, but, uh...
I thought it might help you, Detective.
Thank you.
This is great. Thank you.
Well, if there's anything else I
can do to help, please, let me know.
Thanks.
I know.
Joe Fields isn't my case.
I'll just... I'll leave it for Dan.
Well, I mean, nothing is stopping me
from helping out with
the Joe Fields case,
while you tackle your dad's, right?
I mean, if it's the same
killer... divide and conquer.
- You don't have to do that.
- I kind of already started.
Uh, right over here. Thanks.
Last six months of your dad's paperwork.
You know, incident reports,
booking slips, arrest records.
I mean, half of it's on
microfiche and, like, papyrus,
but I don't know, I thought
it would help, you know,
to figure out what your dad was
working on when he was killed.
See?
I knew you were a hugger.
So. What do you got so far?
It was a clever cover-up.
But what kind of robber would
be so well connected? You know?
They gave Joe Fields
everything he needed
to pose as my father's killer.
I mean, he confessed.
And he had the gun that
was used in the shooting.
Ballistics confirmed that
it was the murder weapon.
Well, yeah. No wonder
it was case closed.
Yeah. I-I... These prints
are un-I.D.'d from the scene,
but they could be the killer's.
And did they ping
anyone in the database?
No. Dead end.
All right.
Maybe I can dig a little deeper.
So, tell me.
Why would I help you two?
Because we're just two regular
fellows who need your help, Boris.
I don't believe you.
- Mr. Sokolov...
- People call me human lie detector
because I look in my clients' eyes,
and I can know if
they're telling the truth.
Well, I respect that, Boris.
I have a trick myself, that's
quite similar, actually.
And you're right.
We haven't told you the whole
truth. So... here it goes.
I want someone dead.
Who?
Lucifer Morningstar.
And what has this person
done to deserve death?
Well, he hurts people.
And not just his enemies,
those close to him, as well.
In fact, I think he
hurts them most of all.
He's right.
The guy's violent, he's
a total loose cannon.
Yes. Believe me, when I say, Boris,
that the world would be a
better place without him.
You both have true hatred for this man.
Apparently so.
Do we have a deal?
Go and take care of this Lucifer person.
I'll find you your patsy.
Lovely.
I hear you won't talk.
Okay.
We have hard evidence linking your
bank account to two different murders.
What do you have to say about that?
I heard you're a human
lie detector, is that true?
One of those murders was my father.
It's why I'm not on the case
and it's why I'm not supposed to
be in this room talking to you.
But I'm not a cop right now, Boris.
I'm a daughter.
And I'm not gonna let this go.
So, you point me in
the right direction...
or I swear to God, I'm gonna
make your life a living hell.
I believe you.
His name was John Decker.
I admit to nothing
but I did once hear
about a John Decker.
And as I recall,
he was sniffing somewhere
he didn't belong.
What do you mean? My father was a
beat cop at a robbery gone wrong.
Hey, man.
I just want to say nice work earlier.
Was it? Yeah.
We got Boris.
And I don't know how you
lied to him like that.
- Well, it's simple. I didn't lie.
- Well...
Well, then you have
some serious issues, bro.
Obviously. I mean, why do you
think I'm doing all this Dan-ing?
Yet, you know, I'm still no
closer to figuring out your secret.
- Because I don't have a secret.
- Well, you must.
One that explains how
you're able to be so...
you know, frustratingly you.
- You see, man...
- Hmm?
I try to compliment you, and...
Hey.
I think my father's death was a hit.
I-It sounds like he
stumbled onto something huge,
and-and someone took him out for it.
Chloe, do you want me
to help you with this?
No. I-I... I got it on
this end. But thank you.
Well.
Where to now, Twinsy? Hmm?
Wow.
- What's the job this time?
- Topless Maids.
But apparently, I still
have to do some cleaning.
Screw that.
- You okay?
- No. I just...
I can't find the right job.
My only friend stopped talking to me.
"Only"?
What's all of this?
My dad's stuff from storage.
After he died, the department
boxed up his desk and sent it to us.
You find anything?
Not yet.
One of the cases he
assisted on got him killed,
and I have to figure out
which one it is, but...
It's funny, he always talked about
how he didn't want to be a detective,
how it was too much work, and yet...
here he was doing all
this detective work.
Guess the apple doesn't
fall far from the tree.
Hmm.
I tried a bunch of stuff, but...
after my dad died, this just felt right.
Yeah, but like... how do
you know what feels right?
Mm...
You just know.
No secret, indeed.
So, what's behind door
number one, Daniel?
Oh, no, no. Not this.
Better a snuff movie, a human centipede,
clown porn, but not improv!
Hey, thanks for picking me up, man.
What's your name?
Lucifer... Morningstar.
Wait, I'm hitchhiking with the Devil?
Oh, yes indeed.
I didn't expect the Devil
to be driving around L.A.
Oh, yes, I live here, actually.
I do whatever I want.
Oh, like what?
Drink, mostly. And insult people.
You ponce.
- You got a girlfriend?
- Yes. Lovely.
- Can I borrow her?
- But she's the love of my life.
Perfect.
- Let's make it a threesome.
- That is not me!
- Relax, you'll get your turn.
- What's your problem, huh?
You gotta sign up, pal.
Good scene, man. You crushed it.
You too, pal.
Detective Douche!
How dare you subject me to
this pathetic caricature?
You have the nerve to stand there
and accuse me of making fun of you,
after everything you've
done in the last couple days.
Hell, ever since we first met.
- Detective Douche, I...
- Dan! My name is Dan.
Or Detective Espinoza.
Right.
Dan.
I only did it because you're
everything that I'm not.
Boring, helpful.
- Your life is simple.
- Oh.
- My life?
- Yes.
Come on, man. You're
rich. You're handsome.
You drive fancy cars,
you date hot girls.
You have no kids, you
have no responsibilities.
How much more simple can life get?
Afraid you don't know the whole story.
Well, fine. Tell me.
You see, that's just it, Dan.
The last person I opened up to, I hurt.
A lot.
Let alone how I've hurt
my own flesh and blood.
It's all I seem to be able to do.
Welcome to the club.
You think Chloe divorced me
because I'm a perfect guy?
I did a lot of things that
I'm not... proud of, man.
And I'm just trying
to work through them.
What, through mime?
What do you do, stuff your feelings
in a box and throw away the key?
It's not mime.
It's improv.
And I started the class after the
divorce because I needed a distraction.
Perspective.
A way to step out of my own skin
for a bit. I don't know, I...
I'm not a spontaneous guy.
I don't live in the moment like you do.
So, you were trying to
learn how not to Douche.
Yeah, I guess that's one way to put it.
Don't tell Chloe.
All right?
Oh.
Oh, it's you. Hello, Detective.
- I got your message.
- Oh, hi.
Feeling back to your old self?
I suppose. So I doubt
I'll be of much help.
Ooh. On second thoughts, it looks
like I came at just the right time.
I've have nothing to say to you.
Thanks to you, I lost my friend.
Friend? What friend?
The doctor.
I was just working through some stuff.
- I didn't think that showing...
- See, that's the problem.
I wish for just one second
you would think about
someone other than yourself.
And there we have it, ladies.
My wake of destruction.
Anyone else you need harmed, hmm?
Okay, Lucifer? Enough.
I'm close to something, I can feel it.
Help.
Fine.
Actually, there is something
that's been bugging me, Detective.
Do you mind if I play the me's
advocate for just a second?
Go ahead.
Well, there's one part of this
puzzle that just doesn't fit.
Joe Fields.
Wha... why doesn't he fit?
Well, you said that he smiled
at you when he was released.
Yeah, I forgot about that.
So, why would an innocent man
smile at the daughter of a man
he took the fall for killing?
He wouldn't.
What are you looking for?
The prints that Ella found
on Fields' transport van.
But those only gave us Rodney Lam.
But there were other prints.
But they cleared as prison personnel.
Like Deputy Warden Perry Smith.
- These are his prints.
- What, you think the warden did it?
Well, deputy wardens are
desk jockeys, bureaucrats.
So his prints shouldn't have been there.
Yes. What if Fields
wasn't smiling at me?
What if he was smiling at the
person next to me? The warden?
So you think that Joe Fields and
the warden had some kind of deal?
- Yes.
- What, Fields serves 16 years...
as a fall guy and then
suddenly has a change of heart?
Well, he had a grandkid.
Maybe he got sick of the deal,
told the warden he wanted out?
And the warden said yes, but
only as a ploy to kill Fields.
Right.
Deputy Warden Perry Smith
worked in the prison
system for 20 years.
Started as a guard. He's our guy.
Let's go.
Right, well, wouldn't
Dan be more helpful?
What?
If I'm gonna take this guy down,
I need my partner
and that's you. Lucifer Morningstar.
Right.
Good-bye!
I guess I'll just clean up.
I'm dressed for it, apparently.
It looks like the cavalry's arrived.
- Dan, what's happening?
- I'm so sorry, Chloe.
- The warden gave us the slip.
- What?
Are you okay, Detective?
This whole time, my father's
killer's been out there.
And today I let him get away.
So, no, I feel like a failure.
What... you are nothing of the sort.
Detective,
for the first time in 16 years,
you know who the real killer is.
It seems to me that
justice is in your sights.
You're right.
I put out a BOLO.
FBI and DHS are looking at
airports, border crossings.
Well, I've still no idea what
that means, but it sounds good.
It means I'm gonna
get the son of a bitch.
Right. Well...
in the meantime, since
your offspring's with Dan...
What?
I'm simply suggesting that you
open a bottle of wine, or three,
for yourself, and just have a nice...
Shut up!
Well...
Bravo, Maze.
- How did you get...
- I was bored.
Had nothing to do.
So, I tracked down the scumbag myself.
It just... felt right.
It's gonna feel good to call this in.
What? No, hold on, Detective.
- You have a choice to make here.
- Yes.
So much punishment.
Mm. Order off-menu for once.
Maze and I certainly won't judge.
You took my father away.
You tore apart my family.
I tried to get him to drop it.
But he wouldn't take the hint.
That's all you have to say?
After everything you've done?
No, no, no. No, no, no. I-I'm sorry.
I'll give you all the
players in my operation.
I'll give you money.
Oh.
We'll see how you do in
the prison that you ran.
I'll bet your inmates
will treat you real nice.
No. No, please, please.
I can get you whatever you want.
All I want is for you to know
that John Decker's kid got you.
Linda.
I know you're in there.
I have something to show you.
My first check.
I got paid.
As a bounty hunter!
LAPD paid me this finder's fee
to track down some human scumbag.
Hunting humans is a job.
Who knew?
First thing I wanted to do was
to celebrate with my friend.
That's you, Linda.
Okay.
I just...
wanted you to know.
Maze, how can we be friends?
You're a...
you're a demon.
Lucifer's the Devil.
How am I supposed to get over that?
He's still the same old Lucifer.
You're still Dr. Linda Martin.
And I'm still Maze.
What's changed?
Come on.
Let Mazikeen Smith buy you a drink.
Maybe I'll devour
your soul or something.
- Here you go, monkey.
- Mmm. Yummy.
- Lucif...
- Mmm.
Why should the child go first?
I'm far larger. And hungrier.
It's okay, Mommy.
He must've really wanted it.
Is she always so... her?
Baby, it's time to get dressed.
What are you doing?
- Bye, Lucifer!
- Yes.
Yes.
I don't care much for my dad.
But... you clearly... care about yours.
Which is why you followed
in his footsteps, I suppose.
Hmm.
So, w-what I'm trying to say is...
I think he would be proud of you.
Oh. My apologies, Detective.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
No, no, it's...
Wh... Then why are you... crying?
- Just... Oh, just shut up.
- What...
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com