- Previously on Lucifer...
- Who escaped Hell?
Mum.
Dad got pissed off and
tossed me out of the house.
And what did your mother do?
She just stood there and let it happen.
A couple of a thousand years later,
Dad kicked her out, too.
So I did the same for her
as she did for me: zilch.
So, Mama Morningstar's on the loose.
I never could break that woman.
She wouldn't submit.
- What are you doing here?
- I've been demoted.
Been reassigned to assist on cases.
You lied to me about being a doctor.
Do you realize
the ethical position you've put me in?
If she's not coming to kill me,
then I don't know what she's doing.
That's truly terrifying.
Lucifer.
Mum.
Help me.
Hello?
- Are you okay?
- He just collapsed.
- Does anyone know CPR?
- No, I don't know.
Hello? Are you okay?
Call 911!
Uh, heart attack maybe?
I think he might be dead.
Sir? Sir?
- Lucifer?
- Sir, are you okay?
Lucifer? Where are you?
Sir, are you okay?
Has anyone seen Lucifer?
Lucifer.
I need to find Lucifer.
Man. Thought I killed your ass.
Hey, Mom?
Mommy...
Lucifer.
And that's when I started
looking for you, son.
At least I've managed to keep
this flesh sack in one piece.
It has not been easy.
Quite a few of the male species
have been eying me hungrily.
Do humans eat their own?
Well, say something.
Aren't you glad to see me?
I apologize for my human form, but...
at least this one has supreme hindquarters.
You're lying.
No. They're quite sturdy. Feel it.
I wasn't referring,
nor will I ever refer,
to your butt, Mother.
I simply don't believe
your wounded bird story.
You're the goddess of all creation.
Not anymore, unfortunately.
Now I'm just trapped in this stinky human
with the exceptional ass.
I swear, all I've done for three
days is wander this cesspool,
asking these vacuous
cretins how to find you.
What are you doing?
Calling Amenadiel.
Oh!
Wonderful. He's here, too?
Yes. And he'll be the one
taking you back to Hell, so...
What?!
Why?
Because you're dangerous and terrifying.
I promise you I'm not
here to hurt anyone.
You have to believe me.
My entire focus has been
on finding you, son.
So you can eviscerate me? Got it.
No. We've wasted enough
time being... estranged.
I'd do anything to rectify that now.
Sure you don't mean "revenge that"?
Lucifer, your father put me in Hell.
Not you. I know that.
Yes.
But I was your warden.
Not by choice.
We were both wronged.
But you could have at least visited me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
When Dad cast me out,
who stood by and did nothing?
Hint: it's a palindrome for "mum."
Well, maybe if you had talked
to me in Hell instead of sending
your little demon torturer,
I could've explained the whole thing.
You're right, you're right.
But I'm here now, so by all means, explain.
You wouldn't believe me.
I know how suspicious
and untrusting you are.
You don't know anything about me.
Lucifer.
I'm your mother.
Not for a very, very long time.
Well, I want to be now.
Then I'm going to need you to prove
your little origin story to me.
We'll retrace your steps.
If I don't find a trail
of bloodshed and carnage,
then perhaps I'll believe you.
Fine. We'll begin where I found
the tiny spear in my neck.
- Fine.
- Hmm.
Gonna need to get you some clean clothes.
Humans tend to frown
at the sight of blood.
Yes.
I've noticed.
Uh, just leave it, would you?
Gosh, perhaps we shouldn't
have borrowed from Maze.
Her clothing is insufficient.
Yes. Half my hide is exposed.
Human attire is very impractical.
They're morons, aren't they?
Oh. So you admit you revile them?
To revile them would
be to care about them,
which I do not.
Then all those rumors
about why Dad sent you to Hell...
the plagues,
the floods... they weren't you?
Well...
Yeah. That's what I thought.
I was angry.
But humans weren't
the reason your father
and I were fighting.
At least, not then.
Uh, Mum?
Hmm?
I think you left out a minor detail.
Oh, dear.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Liar, liar, slutty dress on fire, Mother.
Whoever destroyed my human suit
must have killed this little
imp as well, it's obvious.
Lucifer, honey,
why would I bring you here
just to disprove my story?
I don't know.
But that's exactly what
I'm going to find out.
Management.
- Don't... Wait! Wait.
- Why?
Because there is a dead
man lying on the bed.
Humans don't like that sort of thing.
- Fine. Then let's fly out the window.
- What...
I don't have wings anymore, Mum.
What?
It's a long story.
Come on. This way.
Management.
Yeah, this way.
What happened to your wings, son?
I cut them off.
Why would you...? I mean, come to Earth,
get a haircut or something,
but that's a little extreme.
Hey, bud.
Can I tag in next?
Excuse me?
With the lady.
How much?
This one you could kill. Come on.
I'm joking!
I'm joking, Mother.
Gosh.
You're gonna have to lose those clothes.
They're a serious problem.
Taking you home,
'cause this being out in public
thing obviously isn't working.
And then I'm gonna see my colleague...
Mum!
- Yes?
- You're naked!
Well, you said the clothes were
a problem, so problem solved.
Get in the bloody car, will you?!
God. Traumatized for eternity now,
so thank you very much for that.
Maze?
Ah, good, you're still here.
I have a job for you.
On my way out, Lucifer. No more jobs.
Yes, yes, I know.
You don't work for me anymore.
Very clear. But I have a feeling
you're gonna love this one.
Just think of it as a parting gift.
Come on.
Hello, Mazikeen.
Is that her?
Mm-hmm.
In a human body?
Well, unfortunately.
For you.
I appreciate your enthusiasm,
Maze, but hands off.
What?
You're kidding.
Millennia, Lucifer...
with no physical form.
But now...
...look at all that flesh.
Yes, but sorry,
dear. No torture.
Just don't let her out of your sight.
Until I've worked out
whether she's lying or not,
she can't be trusted.
You want me to babysit?
Well, "my mum in the body of
a disturbingly hot woman"-sit,
but yes, for now.
Mmm.
I was just trying to give
Tammy Twinkletoes a makeover.
Honey, you... you popped out her eye.
Yeah.
That was an accident.
Well, I think she looks rather fetching.
Lucifer.
Hello, Detective. Sir Douche. Offspring.
You know, I bet you're actually
behind this, aren't you? Sadly, no.
Can't take the credit, but I do approve.
Can we get to work now, please?
I'm just wondering if there's
any fresh homicides popped up.
Ooh, you know, when you make that face,
you look a bit like the doll.
- Hey.
- Ah, look.
You can disco a bad guy into confessing.
This isn't a game; this is parenting.
And it's important.
She mutilated Tammy Twinkletoes.
And I'm sure there's a real mutilation
out there to solve as we speak.
Something that screams
"crazed witchy woman on a rampage" perhaps?
What? Not that I know of.
Okay, I'm gonna go back in there.
Detective!
Just a doll.
I don't know what all the fuss is about.
It's not just a doll, it's manipulation.
- What?
- Trixie's best friend Landa got a new
All-American doll, and
now Trixie wants one.
So what does she do?
She destroys her old doll,
- expecting me to replace it.
- Mm, impressive.
But, then, I'd expect nothing
less from the shrewd little minx.
Why don't you comply,
then we can get on, yes?
No. And I'd appreciate it if you
don't undermine my authority.
But you're being a bad mother.
Abandon the child in its time of need,
and it won't trust you in the future.
- Is that what you want, Detective?
- Decker.
Yeah.
Got it.
New case. Hotel Gleam.
Ah, finally! Fantastic news.
He's practically a kid.
Yeah, 19 or so.
How long has he been here?
I don't know, maybe a few days.
Guess the maid really took
the "do not disturb" sign seriously.
Cause of death: single
puncture wound to the neck.
I'm thinking ice pick.
Or a screwdriver, perhaps.
Five-inch, head?
Huh.
Yeah. Maybe.
You're good.
I know. Detective,
interesting pool of blood through here.
I'm assuming it belongs to Cinderella here.
Cinderella? Sure we don't
mean evil stepmother?
Really?
Are we really still on the whole
"my mother did it" thing?
I thought she was responsible
for our last murder.
What, you're just throwing homicides at her
- until one sticks?
- No, I'm simply saying
that the missing woman
may well be our killer.
A murderous psycho whose rampage started
by impaling that poor lad.
Okay, my guess is that this
is an affair gone wrong.
Jealous husband follows
his cheating wife here.
He kills the young lover, he wounds her,
and then he drags her home or she escapes.
Definitely the latter.
Well, we would know more
if she had left more than a shoe.
We don't have a purse.
No wallet, no keys.
Would the woman's phone help?
Well, yes, of course, but we don't have...
A phone!
Wow!
Good eye, Luce!
...ifer.
I'll get this back to the lab.
See if I can restore it.
Yeah, fast as you can,
Ella, we have to proceed
as if this missing woman
is still alive, okay?
- Yeah.
- I don't want to find another body.
Trust me, you will not find another body.
I found a body.
She's a maid at the hotel.
Explains why she didn't
find our dead guy.
'Cause, you know, she was dead.
Anyway, okay.
No open wounds, so she's
definitely not our Cinderella
who bled all over the place.
You see the bruising
and the semi-circular marks on her neck?
- Strangled.
- Aha.
Long fingernails,
which means the killer's female.
Not necessarily.
I mean, the marks aren't deep.
It could just be a dude
- who's not serious man-groomer.
- Come on.
It's so obvious, your Cinder-hellion
had just plunged a
screwdriver into the poor lad,
when she was interrupted
by the chambermaid,
who she then snuffed
out with her bare hands.
Chambermaid?
Who's the killer, Mrs. Peacock
in the library with the candlestick?
I love that game.
I really don't think it's
the missing woman, Lucifer.
It's a little unusual for a
woman to strangle someone.
But look at the size of the bruising,
clearly not man hands.
I've seen some guys with
some pretty tiny lady hands.
Dan doesn't count.
- Come on.
- Okay, regardless,
the maid's death wasn't planned.
I still think we're
looking at a third party...
someone attacking the couple
when the maid entered.
The killer then dragged
the maid into the bedroom,
where they struggled until he
finally managed to strangle her.
Which gave our Cinderella time
to get the hell out of there.
I couldn't agree less.
And she needs to go straight to Hell
as soon as possible.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I need to make a call.
Oh, did we get anything on that cell phone?
Oh, right! Uh, totally forgot.
No, no.
Could not recover anything
from the SIM card.
Water and phones, bad news.
I dropped mine in the
toilet once... that sucked.
- Damn. So much for that.
- Had to reach in, I didn't have my gloves.
Uh, no.
No, 'cause I did get a
serial number off of it,
so I know who bought it, at least.
Richards and Wheeler.
High-end law firm in Beverly Hills.
Cool.
Next time, if you want, you know,
you can just lead with that information.
If you want.
Okay, boss, where do you want me?
I'm not your boss, I'm just,
you know, kind of...
My boss.
It's okay, Chloe.
I've accepted my demotion like a big boy.
And besides, it's kind of hot
when you give me orders.
Sorry.
Old habits.
Why don't you
start with missing persons,
see if there are any new
leads on our Cinderella.
Lucifer and I will go to the law firm.
- Okay.
Lucifer.
- Lucifer.
- Hmm?
Oh. Uh, are you praying or...?
Yes. Usually works.
He must've gone for a wank or something.
Come on, Amenadiel, where are you?
Hello?
Is this thing on?
I keep waiting for God to talk back to me,
too.
But you know what,
don't get discouraged, okay?
He is listening, it's just
a one-way intercom kind of deal.
Come on, brother, where are you?
Linda.
Surprised to see you're still coming in.
I mean, after all, this is a...
a real facility for real
therapists with real patients.
Unfortunately,
I can't talk right now, Linda.
I've got some research to do.
Oh, sure, I bet.
Learning more about psychiatry?
Or is it time to switch it up?
Be a lawyer maybe.
Astronaut.
I understand.
You're upset that I told
you I was a therapist.
Maybe you are one,
'cause your intuition's uncanny.
Linda, listen. I did what
I had to do, all right?
Now, you wouldn't understand this,
but I was dealing with
matters of great importance.
I didn't have a choice.
Yes, you did.
You used me.
You didn't have to do that.
I'm used to my patients lying
to me, not my colleagues.
Not my friends.
I confided in you, trusted you.
And you betrayed that trust.
It is difficult to explain,
but things have been very trying for me.
Mm-hmm.
Maybe if you didn't think
so much about yourself
and more about how you treat others,
things wouldn't be so trying.
It's called karma.
Might want to research that.
All right, the most
effective way to do this
is with a discreet and systematic approach.
Understood.
We can start with the partners and then...
Attention, lawyers! Hello!
Hello. Attention, please.
Uh, now, does anyone recognize
this critical piece of evidence
found at a gruesome crime scene?
Yeah. See?
That's our corporate-issue phone.
We all have one.
That could be anybody's.
Right.
What about this
Louboutin power pump
with the ombré finish in
a size, uh... seven?
- Six, U.K.
- Lucifer...
Oh, my God.
Th-That's Charlotte's shoe.
Is she okay?
Prince Charming, I presume.
Richards. Charlotte Richards.
She's the owner of this firm.
When she didn't come into
the office, I just...
assumed she was out of town on a case.
Was this man involved in any of
those cases, by chance?
- Oh, my God, is he...?
- Dead as a doornail.
Yes. Or in this case, a door screw,
'cause the hole in his
neck's from a screwdriver.
And I happen to think that
Charlotte may well have done...
Could provide us with more...
information on his death.
Well, I-I don't recognize him.
Wait, does that mean
you think Charlotte is alive?
Define "alive."
When was the last time you saw her?
I did this!
Oh, Charlotte, I'm so sorry!
All right, Bradley, listen up,
'cause I've got personal
trust issues at stake here.
Brad, look at me.
Did you want Charlotte gone?
No. No.
That's the last thing I wanted.
Right. Then what do you desire?
T-To be with Charlotte.
We were in love.
Mr. Wheeler,
um, would Charlotte maybe have, um...
also... slept with the guy in the photo?
No.
We were completely monogamous.
She wouldn't even sleep
with her own husband.
She was married already?
Yeah, but she hated that guy.
Sorry about the mess.
I'm sorry about those shoes.
Excuse me?
Mr. Richards, when was the last time
your wife was home?
Oh, God, uh...
Three days ago, maybe.
You didn't file a missing person's report?
She's always traveling.
Doesn't always tell me when.
Did she tell you she was
bonking her associate Bradley?
Lucifer.
Did she?
I knew.
What could I do?
Well, one option would be
to stab her in the neck with a screwdriver.
Do you recognize this man?
Oh, God.
Uh... h-he came by
the house with a package for
Charlotte, uh, last week.
Pretty sure it was, like, a work thing.
Well, it depends what kind
of package, doesn't it?
- Uh, I-is Charlotte all right?
- Can you account
- for the last three days?
- Yeah.
I've been up to my ears in puke.
My kids are home sick.
Uh, I haven't left the house since Monday.
And not showered since, I see.
Are your children home?
I'd like to confirm with them.
Yeah, sure. Uh, just down the hall,
and, uh, uh...
When exactly did you
surrender your manhood?
Excuse me?
I mean, I'm all for stay-at-home dads,
and believe me, I personally commend you
for not abandoning your children,
but that's still no reason to give up.
Oh, I-I... I haven't given up. I'm...
Mr. Richards, you have an
entire slice of salami
stuck to your shirt.
Oh, God.
Come on.
Where's your closet? Up here?
Mm.
Oh, goody. They come in more colors.
There's only one body part
- rubber should be worn on.
- Oh!
Not that you'd know.
You've clearly castrated yourself.
But don't worry. I'm here to help.
Hawaiian print?
The eighth deadly sin. Out.
Dave Matthews tribute tank.
Now I'm doubting your sanity.
What have we got? Ah! Here we go.
This is more promising.
Not worn since the...?
- Wedding.
- That's what I thought, right.
Let's have a look.
Come on.
Come on!
Is that, uh...
Cocaine!
Oh, and the good stuff, as well.
Ah, Detective, welcome to the party.
Ready in a minute.
You know, feeding a whole
ball team isn't too big a job
when you have macaroni
and cheese dinner handy.
Okay, boys, come and get it!
Mazikeen, what is this
strange gooey substance
that this boy is cooing about?
You watching porn?
What is this?
It's like money.
Humans use it to buy
things they can't afford.
Wish I'd found this
before I ate out of those street bins.
Humans are silly animals, aren't they?
Weak. Fragile.
That's what I'm counting on.
Now... where were we?
That's a lot of coke.
Think the attorney's husband was dealing?
I don't think he's the
entrepreneurial type.
Thinking maybe the lawyer was.
Doesn't make a whole lot of sense,
but it would explain
why she ended up bleeding
in that hotel room.
Well, maybe the kid was her
street dealer or something.
Yeah, maybe. Anyhow, Ella got
a big fat print off the plastic.
I'm running it through AFIS now.
What's with the box?
Delivery for you.
- What?
- Yeah.
Dan, I thought we talked about this.
A united front, especially now.
Hey, don't look at me.
Oh, she's here! Lovely.
Did the mini kitchen come, too?
Lucifer, you shouldn't
have gotten her the doll.
It's fine. You can say it's from you.
Oh. Hello.
Luis Mendoza.
He's a known associate of
drug kingpin Victor Perez.
He's a scary dude.
Smart though,
to partner up with a
high-powered defense attorney.
Which would explain why he's
eluded the FBI for years.
I have a friend in the Bureau.
I'll call him, I'll see
what I can find out.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
Oh, look, she comes with an
adorable little chocolate cake.
Your child's favorite.
I will deal with you later.
You're welcome.
Eeny meeny miney...
You are wasting your time, Mazikeen.
You couldn't break me in Hell.
What makes you think you could do it here?
Maybe I couldn't hurt you
because you weren't human.
Well, now you are.
No, it's because I wasn't
guilty of anything.
Hell gives the damned what they deserve.
I didn't deserve to be punished.
And you know it.
No.
I think it's because I just
didn't find your weak spot.
Everyone has one.
Human bodies have several.
Careful.
This body only heals once,
and Lucifer told you not to harm me.
You may have him confused
right now, but he's smart.
He'll come around, see you
for who you really are.
A mother who loves her son.
Loving mothers don't abandon their sons.
I threaten your relationship
with him, don't I?
Nice try.
Even though you say you're on your way out,
you're still here doing his bidding.
You need him.
And if I stay, then he won't need you.
Trust me, you won't stay.
Lucifer made a deal with your
ex to take you back to Hell,
and he doesn't break deals.
Don't think he'd start with God.
He made a deal?
Wait.
Is that a weak spot?
Are those... tears?
Oh!
You're a bad mother.
Really? I think you might
be projecting a little bit.
Oh, really? How's that?
Well, you keep trying to pin
murders on your own mother.
I'm guessing you and her don't
have the best relationship.
There.
At least I get to keep the
cute little chocolate cake.
Oh, come on.
Talked to Agent Colburn.
Charlotte wasn't working for the cartel.
She was working to bring it down.
So was that poor kid.
His name's Marco Sanchez.
Got in over his head
with the cartel,
was trying to make it right.
So he was working with Charlotte
and the FBI as an informant?
Trying to build a case
against Perez, yeah.
That's why he and Charlotte were
meeting at the hotel in secret.
But look at this.
Perez's hit man is Jimmy the Carpenter.
Want to take a guess at his M.O.?
- Screwdriver?
- Boom.
So the woman isn't a
ball of homicidal fury.
No. Perez is.
- Or his hit man anyway.
- Right.
Well, shall we arrest
the Perez chap, then?
The FBI has been trying
to do that for years.
He's Teflon. He launders
everything through his
tanning salon franchise.
Yeah, we can't risk
derailing the FBI's case.
We have to go through the court,
and we have to get a warrant.
I'll see if I can rush one.
Perez could have Charlotte now.
Ah, I doubt it.
Well, if not, he's after her.
I don't doubt that.
Yeah, why don't you stay
here and get the warrant.
I think I've left the cooker on.
Ah, lovely. You got one on the go.
Right. New information, Maze.
Seems Mum might not be a lying
sack of savagery after all,
but it also seems that she's the target
of a vicious cartel hit man.
So you mustn't let her leave the penthouse
until this whole mess is resolved. Right-o?
Your mom's gone.
What?
Well, how did that happen, Maze?
She tricked me,
then head-butted me, then left.
Sorry.
Oh, well.
Suppose the worst that could happen
is that she's brutally murdered.
If so, she'll just find a new body
and run right back like a good mum, yeah?
Or not.
I may have let
the whole deal with God thing slip.
So I think she might be running away.
So if she goes into a new body,
we'll never find her.
Okay. Then we'll just have to
find her before that happens.
I mean, how far can a celestial being
trapped in a feeble human
body for the first time get?
Well, let's see.
She's stupid hot, wearing my clothes,
and she's got a corporate credit card.
Bollocks.
Hello, chaps. Just looking for
the head of a big drug cartel.
Is he home? Vicky?
Victor?
- Oh!
- Oh. Sorry, love. Vicky!
Ah.
Ah. Hello.
Mr. Perez, I need you to know
that I'm not here to talk to you
about your criminal drug enterprise.
I'm here about Charlotte Richards.
Are you, by chance,
holding Charlotte prisoner?
- Who?
- Right. I'll take that as a no.
Here's my point.
You may think that she's
dead, but she's not,
which is fine, because you also think
that she's still Charlotte,
which she's also not.
- Is that clear?
- Ow!
I simply need you to promise
to stay away from Charlotte
Richards. Deal?
Oh. Oh, look at that.
Snowstorm in a tanning
salon. How ironic.
Oh. Detective.
I think Vicky here is ready for
a little bit of show-and-tell.
Emphasis on the show.
Wait a second.
You think I had him killed
'cause he's a narc?
Why would I do that?
I was using him.
Fed him bogus information on purpose.
Had the FBI chasing after their own knobs.
Kid was an asset.
Be stupid to hurt him.
Well, you forgot to tell your
buddy Jimmy the plan.
Screwdriver to the neck.
The Carpenter? He's dead.
Did I throw a wrench in your works?
Get it? Screwdriver? Wrench?
It's a whole theme.
Ah. How's my little drug kingpin panini?
Not our guy.
We have to find someone
connected to Marco and Charlotte
that didn't know Jimmy
the Carpenter's dead.
Well, Jimmy's dead? Tragic.
So assuming the whole cartel
knows that, it rules them out
and points us to the only way
that Charlotte and Marco are connected:
the law firm.
Two shakedowns in one day. I'm in.
No more shakedowns, no more
tanning booth shenanigans.
You and I have been working
together long enough
for you to know how to follow protocol.
I'm sorry, Detective,
but Charlotte's in danger.
We need to find her.
How did she go from big bad
wolf to little lost lamb?
Well, maybe she's a
wolf in sheep's clothing,
but right now she needs
to return to the flock.
Yeah, I worked on that case.
I work on every case
that comes through here.
Okay, but the Perez case was sensitive.
You were the only one here
besides Charlotte who knew about it.
Which means you're also
the only one here who was aware
of Jimmy the Carpenter's methodology.
Wait. You don't think that I...
Got handy with a screwdriver
and tried to pin it on the Perez cartel?
Yes. That's insane.
What's insane is
a guy with a Harvard law degree
still working as an associate.
Yes. Passed up for partner
by old Tom Cruise out there.
Guess you should've been
slipping the boss your top gun.
If you're suggesting that I killed
an innocent kid and my boss...
my mentor of 12 years...
all out of professional
jealousy, you're crazy.
Hold on.
I don't believe that we
mentioned two murders.
I mean, we showed you the
crime scene photo of Marco,
- but not Charlotte.
- Lucifer...
Well, given the information
that you presented...
the phone, the shoe...
I just assumed that she was...
Dead? No.
Just missing. And if we find
her alive, it's gonna be
very interesting to hear what
she has to say about you,
her loyal protégé.
This line of questioning is now over.
Why don't you go speak to my attorney.
He's two doors down.
Why would you divulge
privileged information to a guy
who's now clearly our lead suspect?
Sorry. I'll get that
protocol thing down one day.
Why aren't you dead?
What? Who are you?
Don't give me that, Charlotte.
By the way, thanks for using
the credit card we opened
for the Perez case.
Did you forget I'm the only
one that has access to it?
That I'm the only one
who did anything for you
at that hellhole?
Hellhole? Are you a demon, too?
Why?
Because I'm a little upset?
Wouldn't you be, too,
if you got passed up by Wheeler
with the big wiener?
Oh, I know who you are now.
You're the one who killed me.
Well, apparently not. But I am now.
Sorry.
- Can't kill my mum.
- Oh!
Lucifer!
Detective.
If you're gonna follow me following him,
we should have just drove together.
Right, you get him, Detective!
I'll stay here and protect the poor lady!
Protect me? From what?
Ow!
What'd you do that for?
Well, the detective knows
you're alive now,
so you're gonna have to sell
the whole Charlotte charade.
Need to explain that blood pool somehow.
- Oh, you little...
- Devil?
Yes. But about that...
we've never met until now,
don't know each other.
I fear it's too much for
the detective to handle.
Well, it looks like she
can handle quite a bit.
Yeah.
Well, it seems that wound was
re-aggravated in all the hubbub.
Poor woman.
You want to tell me what
the hell you were doing?
Well, leading the mouse
to the cheese, of course.
I mean, I was gonna be the cat,
but then you showed up, so
I suppose that makes you the dog.
What am I gonna do with you?
Well, I can think of a few things.
Might need a stretch first though.
You need to follow the rules.
You tell me not to ravage
suspects in front of you.
Now I can't do it behind your back either?
I mean, make your mind up, Detective.
No more buying my daughter $200 dolls.
Well, why not? You weren't going to.
I was teaching her a lesson.
Neglect 101. You're abandoning her
in her time of need, Detective.
I don't know what happened
between you and your mother.
And if you ever want to talk
about it, I'm here for you.
But listen to me.
Doing what's best for your child...
it doesn't always make 'em happy.
I hate to interrupt so late, but, uh...
I just wanted to apologize.
Oh?
Yeah, you were right, Linda.
You see, I really do have
a lot to atone for.
I've... made so many mistakes lately.
But a big one was hurting you.
I may have forged a friendship with you
under false pretenses, yes.
But I did consider you a friend.
And I'm deeply sorry that I ruined that.
If anyone understands mistakes,
it's a therapist.
Not that you'd know.
Apology accepted.
Thank you.
Night.
Good night.
What on earth is that?
Cheesy noodles.
It's what mothers make to
bring their children joy.
I saw it on the flat-screen.
That explains all the cheese.
Lucifer...
I wish, with all my being,
that things could go back
to the way things were.
With you...
and all my children again in Heaven.
I want what your father took from me.
I want my home back.
But I know that's not possible.
So I want to do what I can
to be a good mother to
you here, on Earth.
It's too late.
You abandoned me, Mum.
You just stood by and
watched as I was cast out.
Thrown into Hell and
vilified for all eternity.
There aren't enough cheesy
noodles in the universe
to fix all that, I'm afraid.
Okay.
Your father never sent you to Hell.
I did.
Oh, great. Much better.
I did it to save your life.
After the rebellion, your
father was angry.
Deeply angry.
He wanted to destroy you.
I begged him not to.
I asked him to send you to Hell instead.
I did it because I love you, son.
And I always will.
However...
if you still need me
to return me to Hell, I understand.
You do what is right for you.
That's very gracious of you, Mother.
Okay, but please don't
send me back to Hell.
But I meant the rest.
I know you did.
All right.
All right, you can stay.
For now.
Just until I...
figure out what I need to do.
Thank you, son.
Yeah.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --