Previously on Lucifer...
What does Father want?
Someone's escaped from Hell.
I think He wants me to
bring our jailbird back.
Mum.
What are you hiding?
Nothing.
I admire the steps you're taking.
It's hard going out on your own.
I need to figure out
where I fit in in this world,
and to do that, I need some space.
You see, I did make a promise.
I told you that you could stay here
until I figured out how to
reconcile my deal with Dad,
and now I have.
You shall remain right here,
on Earth, amongst the creatures
you so despise,
as one of them.
But that husband...
And there's children, right?
Have you
considered how your fighting
affects those caught in the middle?
You've been working
so hard to make it right.
You were right, before. We've been living
in the past for too long.
It's time we get a divorce.
Damn it, Leroy.
S-H-A-G.
"Shag."
Oh, eight points to me and suck it, Maze.
I see you have a new toy.
Oh, this? No, no, no.
This is for work.
It's hard to believe I've
never had one before.
I actually have a rule about...
phones during session.
- Really?
- No phones
during session.
Oh, why not?
These things are incredibly therapeutic.
1,000 Tinder dates and
Sex Words With Friends?
Gosh, it's more addictive
than a whore's navel cocaine.
Uh...
Fine.
Oh!
Lovely. Gummies.
Love these.
And, do you know,
I've never understood these.
Are they just decorative,
or are they for juggling?
I mean...
Yeah, you seem very distracted today.
Oi!
Oh, nearly.
Okay.
Sometimes, when we're in crisis,
we create distractions for ourselves,
also known as barriers to facing
our deepest fears.
Oh, sorry... right.
This is the part where you, um,
dissect my deep psychological wounds, eh?
The emotion-charged gong
show of a child of divorce
who may or may not have
broken a deal with his dad
by allowing his mum to stay on Earth.
Mm. Has the visit with
your mom been hard?
Piece of cake, actually.
Mum's all sorted, not a problem.
Really?
Because the last time you were here,
you used the word "frightened."
And that's not like you.
Well, turns out Mum's a peach.
Hmm. And the "deal" with your dad?
To send Mum home?
What, you think I'm scared
of Him or something?
I think you're trying to avoid
the unpleasantness of conflict.
Hold on.
So you're saying
that distraction is a way
to avert your problems.
- No.
- Ergo, the more I distract,
the less I worry.
No, I did not say that.
Well, you didn't need to,
Doctor, I just did,
and it's bloody brilliant.
Right.
Where are you going?
Distraction calls.
This really is a breakthrough, thank you.
- I'm just gonna...
- Sure.
I mean, who needs
a gun and a badge
when I've got... oh!
Hey, it's a crime scene. Will you focus?
Well, someone's a grumpy pants today.
Well, sorry, I got a lot on my mind.
Yes, sorry, you have, haven't you?
D-word, moving out of your mum's,
finding a new place...
Yeah, well, I'm a big girl
and I need my space,
and it's time.
Not that I have much
with work and Trixie.
Stress can be so aging.
You need a distraction
from your woes, Detective.
It's a highly effective tool.
Mm-hmm.
When was the last time you had fun?
Oh... well...
No, seriously,
name three friends you
could call right now
for a drink. And you can't say me,
your child or the man you're divorcing.
Well, trust me,
Dan is not on my list
of drinking buddies.
Well...
- Daniel.
- Hey.
I didn't mean it like that.
She did.
What do we have on the vic?
Young female.
C.O.D. unknown.
Another fresh-faced ingenue.
- Truly tragic.
- I.D.?
No personal belongings, just a, uh,
a triangular-shaped ink
stamp on her hand.
Oh, hold on. I might be
able to help with this.
This is something someone
might find at a "night club."
You know, where humans go to have "fun"?
We found an abandoned
vehicle registered to Uber.
No sign of the driver.
Password's "Carnal," capital "C."
Uber I.D.s are usually linked
to the driver's phone, not the car.
And now that we have his number,
by the looks of this map,
our guy is on the corner
of Crescent and Third.
Impressive.
Yeah, it's called "police work."
Let's solve a murder.
I can
assist you with that.
It's brilliant.
Her name's Daria Mitchell.
We traced her credit card
to a small bank in Nebraska.
We know you were the last
one to see her alive.
- I didn't touch her!
- Well...
except to toss her cold,
dead corpse into the bushes and run.
I told you.
I picked her up on the
corner of Gower and Franklin,
gave her a ride,
and then she jumped
out of my moving car.
You just left her there to die?
By the time I pulled over and
found her, she was already...
I'm on new meds. I wasn't
thinking straight.
I just got this job. I panicked.
Killer cliché: "I panicked,"
closely followed by...
T-Talk to the other guy!
- What other guy?
- She used
my phone to call somebody.
Her boyfriend, I don't know.
She wanted to go over to his place,
he threatened to kill her.
Oh! Excuse me.
Oh, it's you.
Ella's got something.
Looks delicious.
Did you come here to gloat?
I just came to see how the
supreme goddess was acclimating.
Well, I wouldn't plan a
festival of celebration
just yet, my dear.
I will not let this...
spicy chicken casserole beat me.
I'm stronger than you think.
Glad to see you're
fitting in so well.
Ha. Well, of course there
have been challenges.
Nothing I can't handle.
I'm still on a sabbatical from work,
so I spend the bulk of my day
at home with the... children.
Factories of filth.
Of mire.
They remind me of you,
actually, if I'm being honest.
And how's that human husband?
I discovered a trick with him.
Whenever he asks a question,
I just have sex with him.
Seems to render him mute.
Hmm. Took me a while to
figure that one out.
As for the rest of it,
for lack of a better
word, it is absolute...
hell.
Well, if it's so bad,
why don't you just go back?
Why?
So that you could go back to torturing me
for another millennia?
- Sounds like fun to me.
- Yes, these humans
are awful.
They breathe through their
mouths, and they won't...
shut up about something called gluten.
But existing in this punishment
allows me to be closer to my family.
Understand?
Of course not.
You're all alone.
Oh. Sorry. I...
I like to rock it old
school when I'm working.
- Know-what-I'm-sayin'?
- I do.
And rock you should.
I'm sure, studying murder all day,
you could use a little diversion.
Everybody could!
Mm!
Thank you.
What do you got for me? Well...
I found a poison in
Daria's stomach contents.
It's called mandrake,
it's like this crazy
organic hallucinogen,
and... you want to know
the really interesting part?
Mm-hmm!
It would've taken at least 90 minutes
- for it to kick in.
- The Uber driver
had back-to-back rides all night,
and he didn't pick up
Daria until 30 minutes
before she died.
Exactly. He would've barely had time
to torture her with his
subpar jazz and creepy
dude cologne, let alone poison her.
Right. We get anything from
vice on the hand stamp?
Nada.
But tech did track down that
number that Daria called.
Davis Fitzgerald.
Owns some hot restaurant in Silver Lake.
Food is supposed to be amaze-balls.
Deadly and delicious.
Mm-hmm. It's been on my list of places
to check out since I moved here.
Oh, social butterfly, are we?
Perhaps you should, uh,
drop by Lux sometime, and we...
could, you know... Yeah.
Thanks, Ella.
Well, looks our murderous boyfriend's
doing well for himself.
Yes, your realtor did say
this is a lovely area.
- I have a realtor?
- Well, I took the liberty
of calling several on
your behalf, actually.
It was a good hour of distraction.
Since when have you ever cared
about my living situation. And B:
I could never afford this place.
Well, I...
Get the hell off of my property!
Well, you're in luck, Detective.
If this home's the site
of a recent massacre,
you may well be in an
excellent negotiating position.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Put down the knife,
and no one else needs to get hurt.
Yes, the Sweeney Todd thing's
a bit histrionic, don't you think?
Oh, you're cops?
Sorry. The militant vegans next door
been up in my grill all day long.
I assumed it was them again.
Come on out back.
I hope you hungry.
Tasty as charged.
See?
We're making artisanal sausage.
Ah. DIY butchery?
Macramé class all full up, was it?
Farm to table, man.
For my restaurant Ellipsis.
Oh, yes. I've heard the
grilled polenta's divine.
We also brew our own
kombucha, keep bees.
Keeping it real.
Yeah, there's no hormones in this meat.
And speaking of your meat, Davis...
are blonde Nebraskans organic or GMO?
Your girlfriend Daria Mitchell
was found murdered last night.
- Murdered?
- Girlfriend?
Is there a waitress
you haven't slept with?
My gosh. Is hipster infidelity
really more egregious than homicide?
Babe, I don't know anything about that!
- Infidelity or homicide?
- Just...
Either.
Okay, look, I had a little
fling with Daria,
but I didn't kill her.
We got into a fight last night when
she wanted to come over,
because I was with...
So you're saying your wife is your alibi?
Actually, no.
I was with another waitress,
and Daria found out about that.
And that's what we were fighting about.
Okay, well, I'll need the name
and number of the other waitress.
Yes, and I'd like to talk to you
about your herb garden, Davis,
because I was thinking about
taking up rooftop botany.
You know...
Excuse us.
Botany? Realtors?
Look, I get it. I know
your mom's in town.
We're both going through some stuff.
If you need to talk, I'm here, okay?
- All right, understood.
- No, now.
What's going on with you?
Why is it so hard for you to focus?
What's up?
Just give me a minute, would you?
Face chat Maze.
What?
My hands are kind of full right now.
Right, well, here's the sitch:
The detective is annoying
me with questions
that clearly won't lead anywhere,
so I need a favor.
Favors are your thing, not mine.
All right, then.
What about a wager?
What's in it for me?
Whatever you want.
Your convertible.
Fine. But you need to take
the detective out and have fun.
Three drinks should do the trick.
Sucker's bet. Easy.
Yes, but you're not allowed to tie her up
and pour booze down her throat.
Less easy.
Fine.
- All right. Deal.
- I said get naked!
Oh, hello.
Want to watch?
Okay, you were the last
one to talk to Daria,
you're telling me you have no idea
who she was with last night?
No. She was having a girls' night.
She was roomies with another
waitress, uh, Naomi.
Maybe she was with her.
Do not leave town.
So did Casanova's alibi check out?
Working on it, but in the meantime,
Daria's roommate, Naomi,
might have an idea of her timeline.
Oh, lovely. Then can we
go for grilled polenta?
Well, I can't focus on an
empty stomach, Detective.
Hey...
Oh. Hi.
Hey, uh...
I just wanted to return this.
Oh. Uh...
Therapeutic Truth.
So much for that, right?
Are you okay?
One exhalation yes, two...
- none of my business?
- Yeah, listen.
Thanks for your concern,
but, um, I'm fine.
No more false pretenses, remember?
Friendship means honesty.
You can talk to me, Amenadiel.
Apparently, that is your real name.
It is.
This is hard to explain.
Uh, it's kind of a, uh...
physical problem.
Oh?
And things aren't working
the way they used to.
Oh.
And I-I don't, I don't know
what to do about that.
I see. Well, you know, it's very common.
I doubt that.
Generally stress related.
It is very stressful.
My advice?
Don't overthink it.
You need to relax.
Try to put it out of your mind.
Maybe have a bit of fun.
- Fun?
- Yes.
Maybe a cocktail.
And before you know it...
It doesn't make you any
less of a man, Amenadiel.
Not even a bit.
Was everything okay?
I haven't seen Daria or Naomi all week.
We feed each other's cats.
Oh, gosh, I detest cats.
Want an animal to stare
at you with contempt?
Get a cat. Open box of excrement
in your house? Cat.
Oh, gosh. Can you smell that?
Foul, incontinent creatures.
That's not a cat smell.
That's a dead smell.
Oh, my God! Naomi!
She's got the same
triangular stamp as Daria.
Same signs of poison.
Well, well. Talk about a
girls' night gone wrong.
Lovely. Why don't we
go up to the penthouse,
and I can show you the
original Stairway to Heaven.
Ah, Detective.
After 6:00 on a school night?
Ella's final forensic report came in.
Right.
Um...
Sorry. Can this wait?
I mean,
those deaths were fiendishly tragic,
but I'm pretty certain that
tomorrow, during office hours,
our dead girls will still be dead.
I just wanted to run a couple...
Good. Saved me a trip.
You, me, drinking. Now.
- I'm in!
- What are you doing here?
Lucifer said I should drop by.
But we're working.
No, you're working.
Who the hell is she?
Oh, sorry. Hi, I'm Ella!
I was about to
give him the rundown
- on your report. Do you want to...
- No, go for it.
I got to dehydrate. Whew!
Okay. Anyhow, first off,
there was tissue damage
to Daria's stomach lining,
caused by liquid nitrogen,
the stuff that makes
fancy cocktails smoke.
It's probably how she
ingested the poison.
Well, excellent lead, Detective,
but you just ruined my ménage à trois.
Second, I assumed that Daria
was at a club on Gower,
and we found an abandoned
building on the corner.
It looked like they had
recently had a party there.
Fascinating.
I'm thinking it was a rave, so...
Any way you could make some
phone calls to help me out?
You know, you seem to have
your finger on the pulse.
Not the appendage I'd
hoped to be pulsing by now.
I know that hood.
There's a great tiki bar
across the street from that building.
I know the bartender.
Course you do.
We could go and have a drink,
ask about the dead girls.
Yes. That sounds like a
very good lead, Detective.
If you want to retrace the steps
of two hot girls on a girls' night,
you need to think like two
hot girls on a girls' night.
With your lady parts.
And piña coladas in hand.
Oh, my God, I love piña coladas!
Lovely!
So, I was watching Chinatown, right?
And all of a sudden, it hits me.
I need to go to L.A. I mean,
do you ever feel like
God is telling you to do something?
No.
Oh. You think Chloe's gonna drink that?
Hey, guys. Do you
recognize this hand stamp?
What about these women?
No.
Okay, look. I'm LAPD,
and if there's any info
that you can give me
on any...
How not to get laid.
I'm not trying to get laid, Maze.
I don't get it.
Well, did you talk to the bartender?
Yeah. He said something was going on
across the street in the
abandoned building.
I put a call in for a warrant to the judge,
and I'm waiting to hear back.
Great. Looks like you
have some time to kill.
Have a drink.
No. I'm gonna call it a night.
Hello, ladies.
Hi. What are you doing here?
Maze invited me.
- She said it's girls' night.
- Yeah.
No. I'm working a double homicide.
Would it kill you to just relax for once?
All you do is
work, work, work.
Wow. Like you're one to talk.
You're at Lucifer's beck and call 24/7.
It's like you're his personal concierge.
I'm not his personal anything, anymore.
Hmm. Well, you basically still
live there, and it's not like
he's pouring you any drinks.
Least I know how to have fun.
What about pleasure?
Men?
When's the last time you had sex?
Hey, why does
everything always have to be
- about work or sex?
- Yeah, I agree.
Girls' night, done right,
is about female bonding.
- Exactly.
- Really getting to know each other.
Sharing problems,
origin stories, secrets.
- Can't we just drink?
- Fine.
I'll start. Um...
I worked my way through med school as
a phone sex operator.
1-800-ProfessorFeelGood.
I would totally call that.
Nice.
I'm Ella, by the way.
I love that we just
skipped the small talk.
Yes.
Um, okay. I'll go next, I guess. Um...
I used to steal cars.
Who's next?
I was forged in the bowels of Hell
to torture the guilty
for all of eternity.
Interesting share.
Okay, so...
Now, you go, Chloe.
Female trust.
Come on.
What's on your mind?
What's on my mind...
like, other than the case?
Yeah.
Um...
A little divorce.
- Uh...
- Mm-hmm.
Single parenthood...
uh, possible homelessness and...
most likely many, many cats in my future.
Or things that require batteries.
Okay, you know, that's-that's...
that's what I'm talking about.
You guys, this is so fun!
- Is it?
- Yes!
Yeah, uh, tequila, stat.
- Yes.
- Keep 'em coming!
This is really
gonna help you feel,
you know, anything.
Ugh!
Cosmopolitan?
Perhaps this really is girls' night.
There are only two reasons to
drink alone, brother.
Either you're a chronic dullard,
or you're trying to avoid your problems.
If it's the latter, I approve.
My problems are your problems.
Ooh! Aren't we the little empath?
You think letting Mom stay here
on earth doesn't affect us all?
Why?
Because you think Dad is gonna
forgive and forget about the
fact that you broke a deal?
Haven't broken anything.
I found a loophole.
As such, I'm not
thinking about it at all.
You should try it.
There will be consequences!
I don't get it.
If you're so concerned,
why don't you just
fly Mum back to Hell?
Because I can't!
That was a tad dramatic.
Why not?
It's complicated.
Never fear, fun brother's here.
I'm gonna show you the
magic of distraction.
But no more girly drinks. All right?
Cosmos are yummy.
Oh... Bourbon. Stat. Keep 'em coming.
Yes!
Thank you, Los Angeles!
And then Lucifer's all like...
"Hey Chloe, name three friends
that you could go call
and have a drink with."
- So smug, you know?
- Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Well, one... two... three!
So, you're saying,
if I called you guys,
you would drop everything
and come and have a drink with me?
Mm-hmm. 'Cause that is what
girlfriends do for each other.
Yes, especially during tough times.
Exactly.
I've never had friends like that.
Like, ever.
Well, you're a lot more tolerable
when you're drunk, Decker.
- Is that true?
- Yeah.
And then Lucifer's like,
"You use work to avoid having fun."
Oh, yeah. Well, not anymore, lady.
'Cause we're your tribe, now.
And we like to party!
I wish I had my knives.
We could have made a blood pact.
- Ooh, next time.
- Aww... Yeah, yeah.
Next time? This is progress.
To tribes!
Sip it.
I think we should go back up there.
- Mm-hmm.
- Mm.
Mm.
Oh, it looks like someone's
made a fourth friend.
Oh, you get it, girl!
Oh, no!
- Abort! Chloe!
- Oh... don't do that.
I don't think she...
Does she wear contacts?
- She's really into him.
- And she's bringing him over.
- Is she?
- Look!
Same hand stamp
as Daria and Naomi!
Where did you get this?
I saw some hot women, uh,
g-going into a party across
the street last night.
- Okay.
- It was just...
Do you recognize these women?
Did you see these girls there?
What's your deal?
Hey, she's just asking a few questions.
Well, he's taken. So back off, skank!
- I...
- Hey!
No one calls my skank a skank.
- I'm hurting her.
- No! Oh, no, no...
No. Okay, no. No, no, Maze.
Maze...
Wipe that smile off her face.
Maze, remember... aggression
is not the answer, okay.
Clearly, this woman is having
some serious trust issues.
Clearly.
Or maybe she's just a raging bitch.
Oh!
LAPD! Hey!
Everybody take a breath!
Oh! Oh, my gosh.
What is happening?!
Maze, Maze, Maze!
Maze, I wasn't done questioning him!
Ugh!
Carry on.
Hey.
Did you see these girls?
Yeah, maybe.
- Where?
- It was... it was...
- Where?!
- It was a crowded sex club,
and there was so many hot girls...
A sex club?
Yeah, just...
Don't tell my girlfriend. Just...
Girls' night out.
Oh...
Oof.
Happy hour over already?
Must have been some party.
Yeah...
other than the half hour-ish
from 8:47 to 9:17
that I can't quite remember anything.
Classic Chloe.
Only you would make
a point of remembering
the exact amount of
time you can't remember.
Mm. Well,
I was lucid enough to destroy a tiki bar
and get a lead on our two dead blondes.
I found a guy with a hand stamp.
The same club that Daria
and Naomi went to?
Not a club.
More like a roving, pop-up sex party.
Secretive, invite-only,
caters to rich jerks
who like to pay for it.
So gross.
So those two girls were sex workers?
Looks like it.
But the only way to know for sure
is to get you into the next shindig.
Which hand stamp guy told me...
Right before he passed out...
Is happening as we speak.
Me?
Uh-huh. Men only. And I got you a date.
- Nope.
- Yes.
- Mm-mm. No way.
It's good to have Lucifer
there with you as back up.
So they don't think you're a cop.
I don't look like a cop.
Uh-huh.
Hey.
Do I look like a cop?
Ah. Finally, you're here. Right.
I promise this will be more fun
than light beers and Bachelor reruns.
Your jokes never get old.
Oh, come on, who doesn't
love a sex party?
Then again, if you're me,
every party's a sex party of sorts.
It's illegal, for starters.
Why do you think they change
the location every night?
No liquor license, underage girls...
Well, the world's oldest profession
seems to be surviving quite nicely.
Hello, chaps.
Yes, my first startup was
a sex club, actually.
Little place called "Eden".
Perhaps you've heard of it?
I'm... good. Thank you.
Best case scenario,
this club exploits women.
Worst case? It got those
girls a belly full of poison.
Mm.
- One other thing.
- Hm?
I'm not sure why he's here.
Only dullards drink alone.
Yes, he's a tad anxious these days.
I thought a night out would do him good.
Right. Well, we have one mission:
to find out who knew the dead girls.
And remember... We're undercover, okay?
As if you could look
like anything other than a cop.
I do not look like a cop!
Cop.
All right, will you guys just please,
for God's sake, be chill?
And three rules: no
drinking, no touching...
...and just keep everything low-key.
Yes!
Oh, my God.
This is not helping us find
out who knew the dead girls.
Agreed. His shimmy is a tad off-putting.
Come on, Luci!
Come cut a rug with your big bro!
Uh. No, no, no, no, no.
White man's overbite,
that is definitely where I draw the line.
Hold on a second.
Look at the bar.
It's liquid nitrogen.
It's the same thing that caused damage
to Daria Mitchell's stomach lining.
Yes.
Hey, buddy.
Hey.
What do you know about these two girls?
Not so fast, buddy boy.
Seems my martini isn't the
only thing here that's dirty.
Mmm.
A drink to savor, don't you think?
Ah...
Want to explain why you ran?
Come on. You're obviously a cop.
Shut it.
I figured you were here to bust me.
Yes, we are here to bust you.
For the untimely fate of two
innocent Nebraskan girls.
Wait... what?
It's funny how killers go deaf
at the moment of reckoning, isn't it?
No, no. I...
I'm no killer.
I-I-I keep an eye on
the girls that work here
and serve the pervs drinks.
And pot...
Maybe a bit of "E."
- What about mandrake?
- Who's Mandrake?
Did you put poison in
these two girls' drinks?
No-no. What? No.
I-I remember these girls.
Their drinks were clean when I made 'em.
Who was paying for 'em?
I don't know, it was some
Hollywood dirtbag
with a gold card.
You'll need to be a little more specific.
It's... Yuri something.
He's not here tonight though.
I guess your two dead girls
and the other blonde must
have really worn him out.
Wait a minute.
- There were three blondes?
- Yeah.
Your two newbies and their hot friend.
Right. First name:
"Hot", last name "Friend"?
They don't use their real names.
She's one of our regulars though.
You know, life of the party.
Oh, she won't be the life of anything,
if we don't get to her
before lady killer Yuri has his way.
If he hasn't already.
Thank you.
Oh, silly me.
Come on. Rise and shine, Crantini.
Time to go.
Yeah. Let's do this.
Gosh, I wish I got that on video.
Oh, I can get that on video!
Hold on. Douche-cam.
Must have been some party.
Ah, that's funny.
And I'll laugh after we
find this Yuri scumbag.
You have anything on the third girl?
Bartender said she was, "Blonde, hot,
and had an exposed midriff".
Which describes half
the population of L.A.
Well, the chef's wife, Gisele,
fits that description.
Yeah, but when you saw
her, she was healthy.
You think she could have
worked with Naomi
and Daria at the sex club?
She knew them
through her husband's restaurant.
I mean... but part-time sex worker?
Would that be the first thing
you put on your résumé?
No. But if she was there,
she was witness to everything
that went down that night.
So, maybe Yuri's after her.
Yeah, well, the tech got Yuri's info
from the credit card he
used at the sex party.
Only has a P.O. box.
No home address, but I did get
a cell and a plate number.
Okay, good.
Lucifer and I will go find Yuri,
and, uh,
and, um...
...you track down Gisele.
Oh...
Copy that.
- _
- That is...
What did Maze win
and why does it involve
my tragic drunk face?
Just a little wager.
Well, you had a lot on your mind,
so I decided to distract you,
with "girls' night."
Last night was a setup?
Yes. Well, you had fun, didn't you?
You should be thanking me.
What are you doing?
Detective...
_
Uh, hey, Davis hasn't seen Gisele,
and she's, uh, not answering her cell,
so if Yuri has her,
we've got to get there fast.
I'm on my way.
Detective...
What did you say to her?
LAPD. Get out of the car, Yuri.
Good Lord, you could at least
fork out for a room, Yuri.
No, no, no, no!
Not the Italian leather!
Bloody hell!
Yeah, more like karma.
We know you were at
the sex club last night,
and you're responsible for
the death of two girls.
What do you know about Gisele?
I don't know anyone named Gisele.
You have it all wrong.
I only went to that club
because Crystal promised me newbies.
I paid five grand apiece
for those two sweethearts.
Who's Crystal?
She was with Daria and Naomi.
Then you should most definitely
- ask for a refund.
- I know.
Those girls had no idea
that I was their date.
You're telling me Daria and Naomi
had no idea it was a sex club?
No.
When they found out,
they wanted to leave.
Crystal bought them drinks,
but they drank them and bailed anyway.
I was so upset that I
took the last sip and...
You drank the rest of the poison.
I have been sick ever since.
Oh, God.
Oh, no, no, no. Not again.
Is Gisele Crystal?
Oh, you mean the chef's wife?
Could she be the one who
killed Daria and Naomi?
Well, Daria was sleeping
with her husband,
so if anyone had a bone to pick,
it would be her.
Yuri, do you know Crystal's real name?
No. But I have a picture.
Oh, lovely. I'll take that.
Right. Ooh, pecker pic.
- Pecker pic.
- Eww!
Oh, hold on.
That's not Gisele.
No, and that blonde hair
doesn't look real either.
You're right, it's a wig.
And the girl wearing
it looks real familiar.
Oh, it's just rush, rush,
rush in this town, isn't it?
Oh, hi, detectives.
I'm just putting a few things in storage.
I'm going back home.
Right, you can take the
girl out of Nebraska,
but you can't take
Nebraska out of the girl.
Or can you?
I don't feel safe in L.A. anymore.
You wouldn't either if
two of your neighbors
wound up dead.
Don't you just hate that?
I'm sorry, I have a flight at 3:00.
Yes, and I've just discovered
this wonderful thing called Facebook.
- Have you heard of it?
- I have to go, please.
'Cause Facebook's heard of you.
It knows that you're a big deal
in your small town.
A ten back home,
but in L.A., just a five.
Things haven't worked out for
you here, have they, Lily?
So much heartache, struggle, compromise.
It made you desperate enough
to turn against your
own sorority sisters,
Daria and Naomi.
No. Daria and Naomi were my friends.
Were they?
Because we know you were with
them the night they died.
You said you hadn't seen 'em for a week.
You have no proof of that.
Except for a photo taken by
your charming buddy Yuri.
Nice wig, by the way.
Really brings out the
murder in your eyes.
Seems kitties do have claws.
Please, just let me go.
Is this the part where you
wish I had a gun, Detective?
Shut up, Lucifer, I got this.
You pretended to be
a friend to those girls.
Shame on you.
They called me!
They were desperate for my help.
The best workout class, where to hike...
this apartment!
They asked you for help
and you preyed on them?
I was doing them a favor.
What, by putting mandrake in their drinks?
I thought it was an
organic kind of roofie.
I didn't know that it would kill them.
I was just trying to loosen them up.
You were trying to make an extra buck
by bringing in a couple newbies.
I won the Dame Judith
acting award in college.
I was the president of our sorority.
I should have made it by now!
L.A. was supposed to be easy!
Oh, phones...
They can be so distracting.
There's a special place in Hell
for women who fake friendships
as a way of manipulating other women!
She's right, you know.
And I think we have
silver lining, Detective.
What with Lily going away,
and Daria and Naomi dead,
I believe that there's an
apartment vacancy.
Are you seriously suggesting
that I should move
into a dead girl's apartment?
No, no, no, the killer's
place is much nicer.
I mean, just look at this view!
How'd you get in here?
Let's just say Samantha at the front desk
is no longer into men.
What, you still mad?
What was all that stuff
about being my tribe?
You had fun, didn't you?
I don't have time for this.
I have work to do. You can go.
I wasn't totally faking it.
Like when I strangled
psycho chick for the win.
That was genuine.
Gee, thanks.
You know, I wouldn't
just kick ass for anyone.
Okay, fine, I would.
But this time it was... sweeter.
This is some twisted
version of an apology?
I don't do apologies.
But I don't want to kill you anymore.
You're a very, very deranged person.
Thanks.
So, we're still good to be roomies, right?
What are you talking about, roomies?
We shook on it.
Post-karaoke, pre-potbelly dude.
What?
I told you I was in between places.
You said that you were
looking for someone
to share expenses.
Don't you remember?
The missing half hour.
Look... I've got money.
I like your kid, and you dress like crap,
so I won't be stealing
any of your clothes.
What, you got a better plan?
You said you wanted fun, Decker.
Fun.
Oh, my...
Roommates?
You and Detective Decker?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
And have I mentioned
"no," and also, "no"?
- You're not my boss anymore.
- Well, that may be.
But I can't have the women
in my life teaming up.
I'll be outnumbered.
Dad forbid you manage
to have sex with her
before I do.
Oh, actually, can I interest
you in another wager?
No. Done deal. Pay up.
Fine, the convertible's yours.
I'm over that.
Well, the hot, new bartender.
Been there, done that.
Well, spit it out then, Maze.
What is it you want?
I want a drink.
What, that's it?
Fine. Pick any bottle, pull two glasses.
No, I want you to pour me a drink.
All right.
To newly defined relationships.
Cheers.
Oh... please...
don't drink in front of me.
Bad case of the distractions, brother?
Well, I better go.
I'll let you deal
with the lightweight.
Judging from your behavior last night,
that lunatic dancing,
I fear that my advice
may have created a whole
new set of problems.
No more turning a "blind eye," Lucifer.
Listen...
We both know that Dad is not the kind
to forgive and forget.
No distraction on earth
is gonna change that.
I said that I would punish Mom,
and I'm doing so here on earth.
Deal maintained, loophole achieved.
What if He doesn't feel that way?
There will be real consequences, Luci,
for all of us.
Especially me.
You know, I liked you better drunk.
Tell me something, brother,
what deal did you make?
What was worth writing
Father, of all people,
a blank check?
Not a what. A who.
You made a deal for Chloe's life?
Don't look at me like that!
At the time, it made a
certain amount of sense.
Don't you understand?
You made a deal to return Mom to Hell.
In exchange, Chloe's life was spared.
Well, that's one interpretation.
Despite whatever loopholes
you think you found,
and the lies that you have told yourself,
you still haven't delivered
on your end of the bargain.
Luci, what if Dad decides to
take back His side of the deal?
One silly human soul?
I can't imagine Dad would
take much interest in that.
Yes, two adult women and a child.
Just bring over a
deposit, and the apartment's yours.
Really? Oh, yeah, I will, uh...
Great, I'll drop off a check right away.
- Okay, thank you.
- Of course.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --