Previously on Lucifer...
You stalked your father's murderer
right before he was killed.
I know this looks bad.
Whoever killed Joe
Fields killed my father.
What, you think
the warden did it?
This man killed my father.
You tore
apart my family.
I can get you whatever you want.
All I want is for you to know
that John Decker's kid got you.
His name is Boris Sokolov.
He connects criminals,
but he always keeps his own hands clean.
People call me Human Lie Detector.
So, you point me in the right direction
or I'm gonna make
your life a living hell.
Mom, this is Lucifer. Lucifer, Mom.
Mama Decker.
You shall remain right here
on Earth amongst the
creatures you so despise.
You're going to send me into
the life of Charlotte Richards?
I thought I'd dive into my employment.
I was pretty surprised
when you called me.
You are fairly attractive.
The only place I've ever felt
wanted or respected...
Is here with humanity?!
This is my home!
Deal with it, Mother!
You seem attached
to these creatures and
I can't figure out why.
Let me at least buy you
dinner tonight to celebrate.
Excuse me.
- Yeah.
- I'll get it for you.
Thank you.
You can't kill her, Mom.
Well, of course I can.
I just press this button.
Mom, please...
give me the detonator.
No. This little bug is the reason
that Lucifer doesn't want to go home.
Squash her, problem solved.
Are you really gonna make
me force it away from you?
Trust me, you don't want to do that.
But I can't let you kill Chloe, Mom.
Since when can you...
I tried to warn you.
Apparently, paltry human flesh can't
contain my divinity.
Oh, here we go.
Bomb's in the car.
So exciting.
Mom, stop!
I am trying to help you.
I know Lucifer better
than he knows himself
and if you kill Chloe,
he won't rest until he
finds out who did it
and when he does, Mom,
he will hate you forever.
Come on.
One little human can't mean
more to him than his family.
He killed Uriel to protect her.
Well...
what's so damn special about this one?
That I don't know.
But, Mom, the bottom line is
if we want Luci to go home with us,
then we need to make sure
that it's his decision
to leave Chloe behind.
Well, that was anticlimactic.
So, I need to find
a more subtle way
to end Lucifer's silly crush.
Tell me everything.
Well, there's...
nothing to say, really.
You had a date...
with Chloe.
That's a big deal, Lucifer.
I need to hear about it.
You know, as your therapist.
Well, for one, I wouldn't say
it was a big deal and...
it wasn't a date, just dinner...
more like a snack,
actually, between friends.
Oh, how was the food?
I've heard their branzino is amazing.
Well, yeah, it's...
hard to say, really.
Too caught up in the moment to notice?
Caught up, in-in a way, yes.
You chickened out, didn't you?
What?
I'm the Devil, Doctor.
I don't chicken out.
I just simply thought that she should
enjoy the food without any...
distractions.
Listen, you know, I get it.
Our last breakthrough spooked you
and now you're running scared.
I don't "run scared"
any more than I "chicken."
Not literally.
But you're avoiding the truth.
Also known as lying.
That I know I don't do... ever.
But yet...
you are lying, Lucifer...
...to yourself.
I owe you an explanation.
Really? Why?
Was it for...
leaving me all alone at a
restaurant so the busboy
could give me pitiful glances all night?
I know what your explanation
is and I don't want
to know her name, especially not today.
Actually, Detective, that isn't
what I was going to say, I...
Look, Lucifer, I don't
have time for this.
I was just on my way out.
Besides, this is my fault.
I should've known how selfish
and thoughtless you can be.
Lucifer.
How thoughtful.
Penelope.
You are the sweetest
to come support us on
such a difficult day.
Oh. I bet you
an arm and a leg, Mom,
that he has no idea what today is.
Well, that's rather unwise
of you to wager your lovely
extremities, Detective.
Particularly as I'm perfectly aware
of what today is, actually.
It's a very difficult day...
because...
- Today.
- Today is...
- The first day.
- The first day...
of the of...
trial of the trial of...
- my dad's killer.
- My dad's killer!
Nietzsche? No, wait.
Your dad's killer. Yes, no, I knew that.
I knew that. That's why
I'm here, to support you.
Not talk about myself
'cause that would be selfish.
- Yeah.
- So...
consider me
an emotional jockstrap
for the Decker family jewels.
Hey.
Hmm, someone's chirpy
for a Monday morning.
Yes, I am.
Why?
What's going on?
What, do I need an excuse to be happy?
Hmm, I mean, you're whistling.
You've been... working out lately.
Mm.
Musk-scented aftershave.
Did you...
get laid?
No.
Oh, no, no.
Don't waste your poker face on me, buddy.
I know that grin.
I'm still in shock.
I knew it.
- She's gorgeous.
- Yeah, well,
- it's not like you're Quasimodo.
- No, no, no, no.
Trust me, she is way out of my league.
I mean, she is
goddess-like.
And she came back for seconds.
Then maybe she's the one who
sent you the mystery package.
A mystery package?
Mm-hmm.
I don't recognize the return address.
Oh, jeez.
God!
Wish I could say it was my first.
That's Boris.
Chloe's gonna lose it.
So poised.
The detective obviously
gets her strength from you.
This?
It's just acting.
Sadly, I've had... practice.
I played this role before, 16 years ago.
Well, maybe it's like butt stuff.
Easier the second time around.
The severed
head of Boris Sokolov
just arrived at the precinct.
That's horrible!
Who's Boris?
He's the prosecution's key witness.
He's our key witness.
He was the only person
that could connect Perry
to the Russian gang. I mean, without him,
the entire case could fall apart.
Oh, God.
How very convenient for Mr. Perry.
This is the worst thing
that could be happening right now.
What are you up to now, Mother?
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
I had no idea Charlotte Richards
was defending Perry.
Wishing we hadn't saved
her life about now.
Well, not to worry, Detective.
I hear Charlotte is a changed woman
since her disappearance, so...
maybe she's not the shark she once was.
At least not in the courtroom.
All rise.
Court is now in session.
The Honorable Judge Estrada presiding.
Given the sudden death
of the State's number one witness,
I assume the defense is
moving for a dismissal?
A motion for dismissal?
Why would I want that, Your Honor?
Looks like Jaws
has been harpooned.
My apologies.
I'm a little... out of practice.
Um...
Oh, I see.
You're saying that with Boris dead,
the State doesn't have
enough evidence to proceed?
So, if I don't move for dismissal,
then he'll probably make a
complete fool of himself?
Your Honor, our case was
and still is unshakable.
The State has plenty
of other evidence that'll
prove 16 years ago,
the defendant, Perry Smith,
murdered Officer John Decker
and paid Joe Fields to go
to prison for that crime.
Oh, and when Fields
wanted out of their deal,
Perry also killed him.
Your Honor, with all due respect,
granting a dismissal
would be ludicrous.
Boris Sokolov's death,
while undoubtedly tragic,
changes nothing.
Well, the defense agrees.
What?
His death doesn't change a single thing.
With or without Mr. Sokolov's testimony,
my client should never have been charged
with these crimes.
Well...
seeing as both parties agree,
the trial will proceed immediately.
Actually, Your Honor,
the State would like to, uh,
request a continuance.
In light of the death of our key witness,
our office needs time to, uh, reexamine
its strategy.
But I'm confused, Your Honor.
Didn't we just hear the prosecution say
their case was "unshakable"?
We did.
Request denied.
Session will resume after lunch.
What the hell are you doing, Mother?
Oh, calm down, Lucifer.
This isn't pleasant for me, either.
Oh, yes, I can see
you're suffering terribly.
I was good up there, wasn't I?
Not sure why humans spend
so much time in law school.
Two nights seemed plenty.
Mum.
I had to find a way to open your eyes.
You need to see that this
Chloe you so adore
isn't worthy of you.
I admit I enjoy working
with her, but adore,
that's a bit much.
Oh, please. You've
sacrificed more for her
than you ever have for anyone else.
Have you forgotten?
You killed your brother,
my son, to protect her.
Do you think there's anything
even remotely similar
that she would do for you?
I suppose...
I don't know.
Well, if all goes according
to plan in that courtroom,
you will know.
Know that she doesn't deserve you,
because she doesn't care about you
like you care about her.
You need to see that you're
not meant to be together.
You belong with your family.
Which is why I have to do this.
Do what, Mum?
What sort of evil plan
are you concocting?
And please don't tell me
it began by killing Boris.
Oh, actually, that was just
a happy twist of fate.
I was gonna blow Chloe up,
but Amenadiel talked me out of it.
You what?!
Mother, I swear,
if you hurt her, I will rip...
Well, looks like your brother was right.
Just promise me that you won't touch her.
I'm not going to hurt anyone.
Lucifer, you promise me,
whatever that was,
that it doesn't affect the trial.
First of all, Detective,
there is no "that."
And secondly, rest assured,
everything will be okay.
I've got this.
You looking for Boris' forensics report?
Uh-huh.
Hasn't come in yet.
Ella should have it any minute now.
I know this isn't my case,
but I'm freaking out, Dan.
I can't let Perry get
away with everything.
You won't.
You didn't see Charlotte
Richards in court today.
Char...?
I'm sorry. Uh,
Charlotte Richards is,
uh, defending Perry?
Yeah.
Really? She's that good?
Yes, she's the best.
Which is why it would be
helpful if we could...
Well, if you could tie
Perry to Boris' murder.
Okay, well, motive and M.O. line up.
Boris' tongue was cut out.
So the killer was sending
a really clear message...
Loose lips get their head clipped.
Perry did this so Boris
couldn't testify, I know it.
But hasn't he been behind
bars since you arrested him?
Yeah, but he could have
orchestrated it in prison.
It's also his M.O.
Exactly, and if Perry is
good at anything,
it's making other people
pay for his crimes.
Okay, well, whoever
Perry hired to do this
was one sharp dude.
The cut on Boris' neck is
extremely precise.
I'm thinking industrial-size
professional slicer.
Listen, I'm gonna do
everything I can to find him.
Even if I have to interview the owner
of every single meat slicer in L.A.
You won't have to.
There was also non-human DNA on Boris.
Swine, to be exact.
A unique cross-bred
for its delicious meat.
And there's only one place that sells it.
Ah!
Hi.
That's so sweet of you,
but you don't have to stick around.
- Trials can be so boring.
- Well,
not this one.
What do you mean?
Mr. Morningstar,
we're ready for you.
Wonderful. Lovely. Right.
Off I go to shield you from
that Quid Pro Ho, Detective.
Lucifer, what are you doing?
Well, I figured there's no reason for us
to lose our heads just
because Boris lost his.
I swear to tell the truth,
he whole truth,
and nothing but the truth,
so help me Dad.
Mr. Morningstar,
you were there when Boris was arrested.
Right? Working with Detective Espinoza.
That is correct.
Except I call him Detective Douche.
But that's another story.
So would you please describe to us
what happened?
Yes, I'd love to, actually.
May-may I have the floor?
By all means.
Thank you.
I'm going to need...
Hello.
May I borrow your scarf?
Your Honor, is this necessary?
Well, you want the full story, don't you?
I mean, the Devil's in the details.
Thank you ever so much.
Right. Myself and Detective Douche...
Sorry, Detective Espinoza...
Were asked by the LAPD
to perform a sting operation.
Not the singer.
So we had to go undercover
at Boris' bathhouse.
Guns of steel...
Got up there...
Walked over like he's constantly got
a gun between his legs...
Boris looked me in the eye, and he said,
"People call me human lie detector."
He was going to kill...
Shook my hand like some
kind of Roman warrior...
...and it was sealed,
and I handed over the investigation
to Detective Decker.
Thank you.
I got a question.
Do you ever get the feeling
like you've been used?
You mean, by... Oh, I don't know...
The woman who's defending the
killer of your ex-wife's dad?
What?
Charlotte Richards is the gorgeous lady
you slept with, right?
How the hell did you know that?
Well, I saw a long, honey-blonde hair
on your coat the other day.
It was curlier than Chloe's. And then,
I spotted a smudge of lipstick
on your cuff... Burgundy shade.
Bold, but not too sexy. Lawyer color.
Really?
No. I just saw your butt pucker
when Chloe mentioned her
name in the lab this morning.
God.
Why are you so worried?
I mean, you didn't tell her
anything about the case
that she could use in court, right?
- I don't think so, but...
- There you go.
Mezcal cocktails, man.
Oof. Those sneak up on you.
She did keep wanting to
talk about our exes,
and all I thought was, you know what,
she's so easy to talk to.
She's so sympathetic.
God, I'm such an idiot.
- Hey...
- No, her taking Perry's case
right after we...
It can't be a coincidence.
Why not?
- Maybe she really just likes you.
- Yeah.
- 44.
- Hi. We'll take
the headless body of a dude
named Boris, please.
I was going to call you guys.
I was just... scared.
A few days ago, this guy approached me.
Big creepy dude.
He demanded the keys to use
the equipment after hours.
No questions asked, unless I wanted
to end up in the sausage myself.
- Do you know his name?
- No.
Asian, big.
Very scary.
But the scar on his neck
it's very distinctive.
Thank you, Mr. Morningstar.
What a, uh, vivid picture.
It's almost as if Boris
himself just testified.
Except a more handsome version.
Oh, stop it, Judy.
Thank you.
Right actually, to that,
I would like to add one
more thing, if I may...
I think we've had enough, Your Honor.
Shh! Please...
continue Luc...
Mr. Morningstar.
Thank you, my darling.
Yes, I'd just like to
say, for the record,
the LAPD, and Detective Decker,
in particular,
acted impeccably on this case.
This whole courtroom,
nay, the entire city
can rest assured that someone as honest,
trustworthy,
and reliable as Detective Decker
is out there protecting them.
She is... truly good.
And I don't mean in bed.
I wouldn't know.
That's how good she is.
Thank you.
Miss Richards?
Your witness.
I have no questions at this time.
Hey!
That's Chloe's car.
What are you looking for?
Hey.
I was, um...
You.
I was looking for you.
Really?
Yeah, I've missed you.
It's true, I still think about you, Maze.
Every day. And every
time that I see you, it's...
I miss you, too.
It's like fireworks, isn't it?
But are you sure that's the kind
you're looking for?
Or was it this?
One... tell your mother no one
is hurting Chloe on my watch.
And, two...
Don't ever lie to me like that again.
And what did Boris have to say
when you interrogated him?
He confessed that he
routinely provided fall guys
for the Russian gang that runs the prison
where the defendants worked
since the late '90s.
And is there anything else
that is remarkable about this prison?
It is the very prison whose corruption
John Decker was investigating
when he was murdered 16 years ago.
Holy cow.
It's all so coincidental, isn't it?
Just like the odd timing of Boris' murder.
I withdraw that, Your Honor.
No further questions.
Thank you, Detective.
I have no questions for this witness.
The prosecution
rests, Your Honor.
Your turn to shine, Ms. Richards.
As its first witness,
the defense would like to
recall Lucifer Morningstar.
Oh, it's fine.
Just one small question, Mr. Morningstar.
And please remember that you're still
under oath.
Who was first on the Fields crime scene?
First on the scene was
the detective, I believe.
I'm sorry, which detective?
Detective Decker.
Are you sure? How do you know?
Quite sure. Yeah, she told me.
It's kind of strange, isn't it,
for the man accused
of killing John Decker
to be found dead by
Decker's own daughter,
Chloe Decker?
Objection, Your Honor. Relevance?
I'm getting to that.
Would you please read who,
according to the official police report,
was the first officer on the scene?
What's wrong?
I'll tell you later.
Well, it says Detective Espinoza.
I thought you said Chloe Decker
was an impeccable detective.
Objection, Your Honor!
No, I-I'd like to answer that.
She is. That's why she
took herself off the
investigation immediately.
But not until after she'd
found her dad's killer dead?
Objection!
What's he objecting to... Air quotes?
I'm simply stating that if
what we just heard is true,
then there's a very
plausible alternative story
to the one that the State is presenting.
Chloe Decker had motive, opportunity,
and the LAPD to protect
her and help her frame
an innocent man for
her personal vendetta.
With all due respect, Your Honor,
Chloe Decker is not on trial here.
And my client shouldn't be, either.
Because it appears he is the victim
of the LAPD's incompetence.
Unless, of course, the report is right,
and it is you that is lying,
Mr. Morningstar?
What you're implying is preposterous.
The Detective would never hurt anyone.
But yes.
What I said is the truth.
Under oath or otherwise.
I don't lie.
Detective?
Please.
Trust me, you do not
want to talk to me right now.
You're right, I don't. You look scary.
But look, I apologize for
my controversial testimony,
but I was clearly bamboozled.
You didn't expect me to lie
on the stand, did you?
It's not about your answers.
It's about Charlotte's questions.
She wouldn't have even asked
them unless she already knew
I was first on scene.
Let's see. Who could've told her?
Detective, I didn't.
You say that, but you also said
your relationship with Charlotte
wouldn't affect this trial.
It just did.
Detective!
Charlotte?
How could you do this to me?
What exactly?
I've done several things to you.
Did you sleep with me to
get intel on this case?
Of course, but it's not like you
didn't get anything out of it.
"Mind altering," I believe you called it.
Yeah, literally, apparently.
Because I don't remember telling
you anything about this case.
- Did you roofie me or something?
- I didn't need to.
I've learned sex puts your
gender into a mild coma.
Offered the perfect window
to go through your phone.
So, maybe...
next time, you should put your phone away
before we have the sex.
"Next time"?
Mm-hmm.
Are you insane?
You tell me.
I wish I could say
that I'm surprised
Maze blew up your car.
She is...
Maze.
I know, right?
Slightest provocation,
- and she turns into a little...
- Hellion?
Exactly.
Let me ask you though...
Why do you think that she reacted so...
passionately?
Because she's a complete maniac
fueled by rage and violence.
Now, as your friend,
not your... therapist,
you feel you did nothing
at all to anger her?
Well, s...
Maybe not nothing.
I may have obscured the truth a bit.
- Otherwise known as lying.
- Linda,
I had no choice.
You have to understand that.
Oh, I do. Oh, I do.
You were... you were dealing
with matters of great importance.
So important, you feel justified
to act any way you see fit.
Even if that means hurting
people you care about.
You "did what you had to do."
That's, uh...
that's what I did to you.
I treated Maze the same
way that I treated you.
Yeah, except I'm just your friend.
And Maze is...
well, more.
So, it's way worse.
And as my friend,
your advice is?
Apologize your ass off.
Or next time, she might blow that up.
Maybe you don't understand.
Mommy Dearest tried to kill Chloe.
Oh, I understand. She told me.
- She did?
- Yes. We're past that.
What I don't understand, though,
is how the detective
can think I'm the one
who leaked sensitive
information to my mum.
How could she?
Yeah, Chloe's the bad guy.
Mm.
If only I knew who really gave
Mom that information.
Right. If only.
Oh! Good. You came.
Yes, he did.
Thanks for coming, Dan.
Anything up lately?
I don't know. You tell me.
Lucifer called me here.
Yes. Well, I was thinking,
as my testimony didn't go
quite as planned, that it
might help fix things to prove
that Perry was behind Boris' killing.
- Already working on it, man.
- Fantastic!
Well then, please tell me
you have some scintillating
cop-speak on how to
accomplish that tiny task.
Well, uh, the guy who chopped
Boris's head off had this scar.
It's actually a brand.
Signature of the Alhambra Triads,
they're a Chinese crime syndicate.
Lots of them were in the
prison that Perry ran.
Triads hate the Russians, so
makes sense to pit them
against each other.
Yeah. You should
definitely probe this angle.
Mm.
Rumors are they use a Chinese
cultural center as a front.
Right. Well, let's start
there then, shall we?
These guys
are notoriously violent,
so let's try to get
in and out as quickly
as possible, all right?
Oh, speaking of "in and out,"
this case really seems to be
touching you, Dan.
You know, in a very personal way.
All right. Shh. Yeah.
It's personal, obviously.
Just try to keep it down, all right?
Well, it's almost like you want to take
Charlotte Richards down yourself.
Like, way down, and give her a hard time.
What are you trying to say, Maze?
Yes, what are you driving at, Maze?
"Driving at."
Good one.
N-No. I'm just...
really impressed with how
much Dan wants to penetrate
this thing from every
position.
You know?
- Oh, yeah.
- Know what?
I bet that's what she said, didn't she?
Oh, yeah!
Oh, Dan!
- Big boy.
- All right, all right!
Fine.
Yes. It's my fault.
I leaked the information to Charlotte.
Among other things.
I'm why she knew Chloe
was first at the scene.
She must have looked at my
text messages after we...
You what?
Made... love.
You slept with my... M-arlotte?
You bastard!
Whoa!
Oh, now look what you've done.
Wha...?
Da-da... Don't be a Dan.
I'll deal with this.
Right.
Which one of you chaps is in charge?
Oh, very well.
You speak Chinese?
- What...?
- I'm the Devil.
Of course I speak Chinese.
I speak everything.
...Lucifer Morningstar.
Lovely.
Furen Li Chunhua.
...Daniel.
What's he saying over there?
No idea.
Xie xie.
Okeydokes. I think I've
brokered a fair deal.
Madame Li is gonna give us
the man who killed Boris.
All we have to do is defeat Kang.
And who the hell is Kang?
And who's supposed to fight him?
- Aww, hell no.
- No, no.
Much as I'd like to see
Crouching Tiger, Hidden Douche,
I'd actually like to win this.
I was pointing at Maze.
Why not?
Okay, sure.
She's terrifying.
But what happens if we lose?
They kill us.
Well, you.
'Cause I'm immortal.
Right. Shall we?
Choose your weapon.
I choose those.
You done?
Hoo-ah.
She likes that move.
Down, girl.
- Are you serious?
- Well,
I mean, you did get two new toys.
Well, that sucked.
Hmm?
But a deal's a deal.
- Indeed.
- The one you seek
was banished for working
outside the family.
We don't break bread with strangers.
You'll find him at this address.
Xie Xie.
No problem.
See? Easy peasy, Chinese-y.
Dan's got a lead
on Boris' killer,
and it may implicate Perry.
So, if he is responsible,
it might not matter
what happens in this trial.
Well, that's great, 'cause we
are getting our asses kicked.
Well. I have to testify next.
I just hope I don't make things worse.
Oh, you'll do great, honey. You're a pro.
Right, Mom. A real pro.
Like when I followed the prison van.
Mom, what if I'm the reason
Dad's killer goes free?
Don't you dare.
No father in the world was
more proud of his daughter
than your dad.
And nothing you could do in that courtroom
or anywhere will ever change that.
I just miss him.
I want him to get the
justice he deserves.
Justice is what we all want, dear.
For your father,
and for my client.
You're a mother.
Aren't you?
Yes.
Then shame on you.
We need to talk.
Man, he better be here.
If we can convince him to give up Perry,
I won't feel so bad about
having slept with Charl...
La la la la! No more talk
of that disgusting offense, please.
I thought you said you
hadn't slept with her.
I haven't, wouldn't ever.
I'm just upset for the detective.
What, you think I'm not?
I would do anything to right this.
I know you would.
LAPD! Put your hands where I can see 'em!
Whoa!
Well, looks like we found Boris,
at the head of the table, ironically.
And that's Da Young.
I'd say we were right.
Perry hired him to go
behind the Triad's back
to kill Boris, knowing that
they'd punish him for it.
Clever Perry,
killed two birds with one stone.
Three, if you count the chicken.
You've got a lot of nerve.
Yes, I've been told.
And legs for days.
Now, listen, you're losing bad.
Without Boris, the prosecution's evidence
is mostly circumstantial.
And, unfortunately for you,
Lucifer's testimony basically handed me
a non-guilty verdict.
This trial is over.
Maybe.
But the investigation into that monster
that you call a client is ongoing.
So one way or another,
he wi...
Hmm.
Bad news?
I may have a solution.
My client isn't fully
aware we're winning.
However, he is more than aware
that he's facing the death penalty.
And we both know he's a coward.
I could use the possibility
of a lethal injection to
get him to plead guilty.
You're supposed to be on his side.
Why are you doing this?
Well, there is one condition.
You'd have to betray Lucifer.
So...
you want Perry to go to jail,
call Lucifer a liar.
"A liar"?
If there's one thing he cares
about more than anything,
it's his honor.
See you in court.
Detective Decker,
Lucifer Morningstar is
your partner, correct?
Yes.
He's a civilian consultant for the LAPD.
We work cases together.
And how is he qualified for this role?
He is very, uh, intuitive.
He, um, understands people's desires.
And in addition to that,
I assume he studied law enforcement?
Not to my knowledge, no.
Oh, okay.
But he has a professional background,
which is somehow relevant
to law enforcement?
He owns a nightclub.
Okay, but then,
I'm sure his previous job
was more relevant to his role
as a civilian consultant for the LAPD?
- Right?
- Mm.
Well, if you believe his claims
that he used to run Hell...
...then yes, he's accustomed
to punishing bad guys.
It's true.
I'm confused, Detective.
Are you suggesting your
partner is delusional,
or just lying?
Lucifer Morningstar is many things,
but he is not a liar.
Everything that Mr. Morningstar said
on this stand is absolutely true.
I was the first person
on that crime scene.
And, yes, I shouldn't have
been anywhere near it.
But I...
let my emotions
get the best of me.
Lucifer is the...
...best partner
I have ever had.
And I can only hope that
he can count on me
as much as I count on him.
Your Honor,
we request the jury be instructed
to disregard Detective
Decker's entire testimony.
We'll take a ten-minute recess.
Harry, are you surprised
by that "not guilty" verdict?
No. I'm never surprised
to see justice served.
I believe in our legal system.
And now I can finally return to my family
a free man, so, if you'll excuse me.
I'm sorry to bother you, um, I was, um...
I'm looking for Maze.
Do you know what apartment she lives in?
Oh, yes, but she's not home.
Why, did you get in a fight?
I'm sorry, it's none of my business.
It's just, my husband...
always gave me flowers after an argument.
Are you all right?
I used to believe
everything happens for a reason.
But now, I'm not so sure.
Me, neither.
But I do know that no
matter how bad things get,
the true test is how we choose to respond
to the pain we suffer.
Or inflict.
That's well said.
Maze is a lucky girl.
Hope she forgives you.
Ha! Huh.
I'm sorry, you... you
look really familiar.
I'm Chloe's mom?
Have we met?
No, I don't believe we have.
I never forget a face.
If you'll excuse me, I have to go.
Oh.
Good night, Rosie.
Perry Smith.
I know you had Boris killed.
I also know you're responsible
for the murder of Jill Fields
and John Decker.
Aw, such a shame there's
no evidence, right?
The system kind of needs proof.
Yeah.
You clean your mess, we got nada.
But you know who's okay with nada?
Or shall I say nichego?
Yeah, that's right.
You see, the Russians,
they don't like it when one of their own
is taken out without permission.
But who knows?
Maybe they won't hear about it.
Whoa.
Aah!
My pleasure, Meesha.
Dozvidanya.
I didn't think you had it in you.
I'm impressed.
Drive.
You were right.
You are nothing like Father.
Oh? What changed your mind?
If I tell you this, you have to come
completely clean with me, Mother.
No more secrets, Mom. No more lies.
Okay.
What happened?
35 years ago, Father,
He asked me to come down here
to bless a couple who was
unable to have a child.
He had never asked me to
do anything of this sort,
and He never did again.
Today...
I met the mother again.
And I found out what the result
of that miracle was.
Or, rather, who.
- Oh, hey.
- Detective.
- Sorry, I thought...
- What are you doing here?
Are you on your way out?
I am, yes.
- Oh...
- To see you, actually.
Oh.
I believe I owe you dinner.
Now we know why
Chloe's so special.
Don't we?
Your Father put her here.
In Lucifer's path.
You know what this means?
It means... that I was a pawn.
Say when.
When!
When.
I hope you know it takes months
to get a reservation at this place.
Oh, yeah. The fries are amazing.
Oh, thank you. I made them myself.
It means Chloe's not an obstacle.
She's how you'll get your wings back.
She's how we'll get it all back.
Detective?
What you said today in the courtroom...
It was the truth.
We're going home, son.
And Chloe is the Key.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --