Previously on Lucifer...
Tell me, what do you desire?
This is it? This is your big trick?
Why don't I affect you, Detective?
I guess we both have our mysteries.
35 years ago, Father
asked me to come down here
to bless a couple who was
unable to have a child.
You look really familiar. Have we met?
Your Father put her in Lucifer's path.
We're going home, son.
And Chloe is the key.
Andy Kleinberg? Jana Lawrence
was found murdered this morning.
One of them broke. I
spilled a little on myself.
What the hell is happening to me?
So what if you slept
with Charlotte Richards?
You slept with my...
Whoa!
He's different when he's with you.
Chloe Decker is causing
your vulnerability.
I'm bleeding.
Do you think I'm boyfriend material?
Perhaps you've been
underestimating yourself.
You deserve someone as good as you.
Oh, Detective.
Detective, are you sure
you want to do this?
Shut up.
I see you've found my love handles.
How was it?
What are you doing in here?
What? I heard you
scream, so I ran in to see
if you were in danger.
Then I figured out
what was really going on, you know,
so I stayed to watch the show.
Hey.
What was that... That
thing you were doing?
You were like...
Okay, Maze,
get out.
Now.
All right, at least you're
getting laid in your dreams.
'Cause it's not happening in real life.
You don't know that.
I just wish you'd loosen up, Decker.
You know, throw caution to the wind,
be impulsive,
just once.
Instead of, you know,
being you.
Maybe this time will be different.
This time will definitely
be different, Doctor.
I've decided to take
things slow, for once.
Hmm, and why is that?
Because I'm a responsible Devil.
And I... well, I know what
a big deal the kiss was...
for the detective.
For her?
Well, I'm sure it must have made
quite an impact on her.
I mean, it, it is me.
No doubt she's overwhelmed
by emotions she's never felt before.
She's overwhelmed?
- Mm.
- Uh-huh.
Is that why you went your separate ways
after the kiss?
Precisely.
Yes, although she did have
that wretched dependent
waiting for her at home.
Well, two, if you count the child.
I think I know what's happening.
Y-You do?
You're stalling, Lucifer.
Stalling?
Sex? Me?
Doctor, have we even met before?
You're stalling because you've realized
how complicated your relationship is.
Look...
the, um, the truth is that...
I still don't understand why,
after everything I said about
my less positive qualities,
she still chose to kiss me.
I mean, do you think she's ill?
Or maybe...
she's just taken by you?
Well, that's impossible.
The detective is completely
immune to my charms.
Or she was immune.
Maybe that's what's changed.
Of course, I mean why
else would she kiss me?
But there's also the possibility...
No, no, no.
No. That's very good.
Thank you, Doctor.
I know what to do now.
Morning.
Hey.
So, how was the rest of your night?
It was fine, thank you.
How was the rest of your night?
Uh, fine, thank you.
Excellent. So we're all fine, then.
But before we deal with
whatever atrocity awaits,
there's something important
I need to ask you, Detective. It's...
well, it's about us.
Okay.
So what is it you truly desire now?
Lucifer, what the hell are you doing?
You know that stuff doesn't work on me.
Right.
Yes, no, of course. I was, uh, joking.
I was just trying to...
Maze said this morning, you know,
throw caution to
the... Never mind, it...
That was weird. Yeah. We... let's go.
Right.
Right, what have we got?
Meet Rick Cormier.
19-years-old. Malibu State freshman.
Friends thought he was just
hungover after the big win
against the Pasadena Gray Hawks.
Turns out, he be dead.
Of poisoning.
- Ooh.
- Like alcohol poisoning?
No, like poison poisoning.
Check it out:
petechial hemorrhaging,
ribboned skin,
ocular discharge.
Sorry, she said "discharge,"
it gets me every time.
Any idea
of how long it took
the poison to activate?
Well, it's hard to say
for sure, but best guess,
maybe 24 hours?
I hope poor Ricky made 'em count.
Enjoying what little life he
had left with sex or friends.
Or sex with friends.
I just figured that's where
you were going with that.
Yeah, well, I mean, I don't know
how down he was to party,
but, you guys,
I've seen a lot of messed up stuff.
This toxin tore through his body
like it was burning
him from the inside out.
I mean, I'm gonna have to reach out
to my forensic contacts just
to see if anyone knows anything.
Who found the body?
I thought he was just
sleeping it off for once.
I didn't realize he was freakin' dead.
Do you know anyone who may
have had a problem with him?
No way.
We all loved Ricky.
Did you notice anything
strange in the last few days?
Any unusual behavior?
Like what?
Like someone carrying a
small apothecary bottle
marked with a skull
and crossbones perhaps?
No, nothing like that.
But Johnny Kane came
by the dorm yesterday.
- Mm.
- What, Johnny Kane Johnny Kane?
As in the actor Johnny Kane?
Yeah. My mom went pretty nuts
when I told her.
He even signed one of my DVDs.
- No.
- Huh.
Oh. To Love Is to Die.
Impressive work.
I mean, to be a man playing
a woman playing a man.
It's absolutely dizzying.
What, should I have said "spoiler"?
Apparently he was here
researching a role.
Hmm, committed.
He's, like, 40 years old, there's no way
he could pull off
playing a college student.
Um, surely you misspoke, Detective.
I mean, Johnny Kane's a spry
and handsome young
man, wouldn't you say?
No, he's quite old. And
since when did you become
the president of his fan club?
Since he just walked in
here wielding a large knife.
Am I too late? Is he dead?
- Is he dead?
- Freeze. Drop the knife.
It's my fault. He's dead because of me.
Put down the knife, Johnny.
Yes, listen to her, Johnny.
She's quite a good shot.
You don't understand!
I couldn't do what the man said.
What man?
The man said he would kill that kid
if I didn't cut my face.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Mr. Johnny Kane, you're an amazing actor
with an impressive library
of films under your belt.
Beloved by critics and the public alike.
Many would say
you're at the top of
your profession right now.
Which is why it'll be so interesting
to see what decision you
make for this experiment.
You can either...
carve up your own face, or...
Rick Cormier, an innocent
freshman at Malibu State,
will die of poisoning.
You have 24 hours to decide.
Do what's asked and an
antidote will be delivered.
The choice is yours alone.
Well, that's dramatic.
When did you get this video?
Yesterday. At first,
I thought it was some sick joke.
Fans send bizarre letters
to my manager all the time,
but this was sent directly
to my personal e-mail,
and it was so...
disturbing.
I couldn't get it out of my head.
- I had to check it out.
- So you went to the school.
Yeah, when I realized
that this kid was a
real student at Malibu,
I... I started thinking
that this "experiment"
might be real, too.
I went home and I stared
at that knife for hours.
But I couldn't do it.
I couldn't cut up my face.
Well, of course you couldn't.
That's an impossible choice.
This killer is clearly playing God.
I mean, no one would
do something like that
unless they're being manipulated.
Not unlike someone
showing affection when
it made no logical sense.
What?
I mean, what kind of sick bastard
would do such a thing?
That's exactly what I'd like to know.
Excuse me.
Where are you going?
Okay, look, we are
doing everything we can
to trace that e-mail,
but in the meantime,
did you have any connection
to the poisoned student?
Or any idea why he was targeted?
No, until yesterday I'd never
met him before in my life.
Like that, is it?
Excuse us, thank you.
Fess up.
What did you do to her?
I'm afraid you're gonna
have to be more specific.
I've done a lot of things
to a lot of people by now.
Don't play silly buggers with me, Mum.
The detective kissed me
and I need to know why.
Did you say you kissed?
Please spare me the
appearance of surprise
and just tell me how you did it.
Well, I wish I had that
kind of power, but, sadly,
I can't take credit.
Why are you so upset?
I assumed you'd be pleased
by such a development.
Well, I...
I'm upset because I just
don't know if it's...
real.
All I can say is,
follow your heart, son.
These things have a way of
working themselves out in time.
- Really?
- Hey.
Detective.
- Counselor.
- Douche.
- Dick.
- Well, I suppose
that's my cue.
Remember what I said, Lucifer.
Bye-bye, Daniel.
I just came by to tell you
that Chloe's looking for you.
Cyber got a hit off that e-mail trace.
Great.
We traced the e-mail to a grad
student named Matthew Hoffing.
He works here part-time.
Libraries. Dreary places, aren't they?
They smell like feet.
I don't know.
I think they can, uh,
be kind of romantic.
Have you ever, you know,
made out in a library?
What...
Detective, what has
gotten into you today?
This is usually when you
tell me to focus on the work.
And yes, of course I've
made out in a library.
Right. Yeah, I was-I was...
I've been trying to kind of...
You know what?
Never mind.
It's definitely not getting
the reaction I was expecting.
- Right.
- So, just... no.
You know what? No.
Since when have you've
been one to avoid sex?
- What?
- LAPD.
- Show us what's in your hands.
- No,
raise your hands above your
head where we can see them.
- Well, it might be a gun, Detective.
- It's not a gun.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just...
I don't know any kid...
Ah, ah, ah. Better safe than sorry.
Right.
Look, I don't know what
you're talking about.
I don't know any kid named Rick.
You are Dee-man69, yeah?
That's a very clever
play on words, by the way.
Was "Nevergetslaid №1" taken?
Yes, that's my e-mail, but...
I only ever use it for... you know....
porn.
Care to explain why you sent
Johnny Kane a threatening e-mail
yesterday at 9:10 a.m.?
Busted, Mr. Hoffing.
You may as well come
clean now. Pun intended.
First off, I'm kind of
a fan of Johnny Kane.
I think he's super talented,
but not enough to e-mail him.
And secondly,
I couldn't have
e-mailed him at that time
even if I wanted to.
I was T.A.ing a class.
- Oh.
- Here, I can prove it.
Okay.
There is an e-mail there.
Oh, wait for it.
But it wasn't me.
Do they ever get less predictable?
No, I'm serious. It must've been hacked.
I didn't send that e-mail, and
I didn't send this one either.
- What other one?
- This one, sent an hour ago.
It wasn't me.
Dr. Gwendolyn Scott.
You're a world-renowned
thoracic surgeon.
Who's saved an awe-inspiring
number of lives.
Which is why it'll be
so interesting to see
what decision you make
for this experiment.
You can either destroy your hand or...
Ashley Corbett,
an innocent sophomore
at Malibu State, will die
of poisoning.
You have 24 hours to decide.
Do what's asked, and an
antidote will be delivered.
The choice is yours alone.
This isn't just about Johnny Kane.
We have to find Ashley Corbett now.
Okay, Dan's with Dr. Scott.
All we have to do now
is find Ashley Corbett.
Look, once we get inside,
let me handle this.
Okay, Detective, in order to do so,
we need to... blend in.
Meaning?
Meaning less hall monitor,
more, sort of, hot for teacher.
So, do you mind if I...
- Thank you.
- Right.
- I got it.
- Well, come on.
- You're staring.
- I... fine.
Okay.
How do I look?
Beautiful.
Um... but, um, one last thing.
Voilà.
No college rager is
complete without one.
Right. Shall we?
These are the future leaders
of America, Detective,
engaging in sex, drugs,
and lecherous behavior.
Makes me proud.
All right, well, don't
get too comfortable.
Remember, we're not here to party,
we're here to find Ashley.
And she could be sick already,
so let's split up and we'll
cover more ground that way.
Right. Find the girl,
don't have fun. Check.
Mm.
Yeah.
Excuse me, have you seen this girl?
I think I saw her an hour ago.
- She's, like, way hot.
- Yeah, great.
Uh, do you know where she is?
'Cause she might be in danger.
Danger of getting wasted! Whoo!
Ashley Corbett?
Anyone seen Ashley Corbett?
Uh, Ashley Corbett? No...
- Oh, hello. Oh. Hi.
- Hi.
Right, uh, yes, uh,
you're all very lovely.
Very lovely.
Dear, how do I turn this thing off?
I'm looking for Ashley Corbett.
Uh, can you tell me where she is?
We'll tell you.
But first you have to
do something for us.
We are almost through, Dr. Scott.
I really appreciate you
answering our questions.
Probably should've called
you when I got the e-mail.
I was afraid.
It's okay, Doctor.
We're here now.
Can I ask you something, Detective?
What would you do?
If you were me,
and it were your hand
or an innocent girl's life?
What would you do?
I don't know.
I've dedicated my life to saving people.
Taken an oath to do no harm.
H-How am I supposed
to make that choice?
You don't have to.
They've drawn blood
from the first victim
and they're already
working on an antidote.
That's great if they find the girl.
But what if they can't?
They will find her.
I promise you.
Some of our best people are on it.
Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug!
Right. Now,
can you please tell me where Ashley is?
Mm. Come with me.
Whoa! Hey...
Was that an earthquake,
or did you just rock my world?
I don't think so.
You got a boyfriend or something?
Definitely not.
Now, I suppose what
I'm saying is, you know,
how do I know that it's real?
It's real if you're
two halves of a whole.
If you're stronger together
than you are apart.
Right, right, but what
does that actually mean?
Damn it, Lucifer, I was so stupid
to think I could actually take a leap
and trust you for once.
I mean, a woman's life is on the
line and here you are doing...
Wait, what are you doing?
Well, I was actually working, Detective.
Oh, my God.
- Is this her?
- Yes.
She's so pretty.
Oh.
Well, I-I mean I was
working and maybe, sort of,
you know, asking about you.
- About me?
- Well, we had some time to kill
whilst we're waiting for Ashley.
'Cause apparently
she's in that bathroom.
Don't know what's taking her so long.
Ashley Corbett. LAPD.
Ashley.
It just won't stop.
So, this is where the...
healing happens.
It's cute.
So, what brings you here?
I have some upsetting
information to give to Lucifer.
It's a revelation that
might send him over the edge
against his Father.
Okay.
But considering
that Lucifer and I have
a bumpy track record,
I'm afraid he won't believe me.
I'm afraid he might think I have some...
ulterior motive.
Do you?
I'm not going to tell him
this information for you,
if that's what you're asking.
What if I say pretty please, hmm?
Apparently that's
supposed to do something.
Look, I understand that you have been...
Uh, are the goddess of all creation.
You're very...
uh, tall.
And most certainly
quite powerful.
But my loyalties are
to my patient, your son.
Doctor-Devil confidentiality.
But I'm not asking
you to break his trust.
In fact, I'm asking you to
illuminate the truth for him.
If he's going to make an
informed decision about Chlo...
...about his future here,
he needs to know the facts.
Right?
I said please, right?
If this information is as upsetting
as you're making it out to be,
I'm not interested in
being the messenger.
Afraid I'm too smart for that.
So what you're saying is I
need to find someone he'll trust
that is foolish enough to
help me deliver the news.
That's the exact opposite
of what I'm suggesting.
Thank you, Doctor.
I know just the person.
Now I see the resemblance.
All right, well, call me as
soon as you hear anything else.
Thanks.
How is she?
- Is she going to be okay?
- They found Ashley.
She's in the hospital.
But the poison must be
different from the first victim.
The antidote they made,
it's... it's useless.
But don't worry, we
will figure out a way.
We always do.
It just takes time. Okay?
I, um... I need to get a glass of water.
This is Espinoza.
I need to get an update
on Ashley Corbett.
I'm sorry. Can you say that
again? I can't hear you,
there's a...
garbage disposal...
Doc!
Don't.
No!
We e-mailed back a photo of your hand.
Doubt we'll get a response.
The killer knows that
we may be monitoring.
That poor girl was going to die.
I had no choice.
Oh, don't be ridiculous.
You had a choice not to be so foolish.
Lucifer.
Well, who's to say the killer wouldn't
demand her other hand?
Her spleen? Her heart?
'Cause, believe me, there is no winning
when you play by a
twisted tyrant's rules.
Excuse me. Can I talk
to you for a second?
You are out of line.
Me?
The doctor just destroyed her hand.
When are people going to understand?
Thou shalt not negotiate
with terrorists!
Oh, surely you can see
this is a fool's game.
The only thing I can see is,
you are letting your emotions
get away from you. We can't
let our feelings get in the way
of our work, Lucifer.
We have to work together as a team,
or else someone could get hurt.
Yes.
Yes, I suppose they could.
Hello?
I've got a delivery for a Dr. Scott.
Uh, I'll take that. LAPD.
Thanks.
"I'm a man of my word."
The antidote.
We need to test this
and get it to Ashley now.
Right.
Boo-yah.
Remember how I sent a
shout-out to my peeps
- for other poison victims?
- Mm-hmm.
Well, meet Monsieur John Doe.
Now, according to my buddy at DHS,
this guy was found in the cargo
hold of a plane in Chicago.
Similar symptoms to our poison vic.
And get this, the flight he was on?
Came out of Los Angeles.
So, he might actually
be the first victim?
Mm-hmm. I mean, the only difference
is he has hot spots all over
him, almost like the poison...
Spilled on him.
Exactly.
But this stuff is so strong,
Dan, that it killed him anyway.
I mean, we are talking
designer poison here.
Engineered from controlled substances.
Each one just a little bit different.
So, how do we get an antidote?
Well, that right there
is the tricky part.
Designer poisons need
designer antidotes.
This guy, our killer, is really good.
I mean, bad.
But really good.
Oh, my God.
I know.
It's tough. But we'll
get through this, buddy.
No. No, that photo. Hold on one second.
Where is it?
What?
The same birthmark.
Your dead guy from Chicago
is Andy Kleinberg.
The rich guy that we
looked into for the murder
of that stewardess.
We were searching for
a... a special package
that was smuggled into the country,
- Okay.
- We never found it.
It had to be the poison.
Kleinberg must've been
the one who stole it.
And look what happened to him.
This is the other
student that was poisoned?
I'm sorry.
I don't recognize him.
It's okay. We just need
to ask you these questions
now that you're feeling better.
Yes. Now that your inside's
no longer bleeding out.
Do you have any idea, Ashley,
when you could've been
poisoned yesterday?
No. I mean, it was a normal day.
I woke up. I had a bio exam.
Lunch at the dorms...
Then I just, I went to the
gym, I couldn't even work out
'cause my arm was kind of sore.
Why was your arm sore?
I don't know.
Uh, I guess, 'cause of
the flu shot that I got?
Do you think that could have been it?
So, according to the M.E. report,
the other kid got a flu shot, too.
Ah. Well, what do you know?
Ashley, where did you get the shot?
The university health van.
Great. Thank you.
Yes.
- Excuse me.
- Get well soon.
The guy who gave the flu shots
was Dr. Jason Carlisle.
This is footage of a
car accident he was in.
He was a professor at Malibu
until this video went viral.
No!
Want to know why?
Because the poor sap saved himself?
Correction. Because he saved
the dissertation he'd been
working on for four years,
while an innocent college student
working as an Uber driver died.
He was publicly humiliated,
his wife left him,
he lost his job, his entire
world spiraled out of control.
So he took a job as
a mobile health tech.
I thought our killer
was just raving mad,
but he's trying to prove a bloody point.
That everyone would make
the same choice he did.
Saving their livelihood
over someone else's life.
Johnny Kane's face is
his bread and butter,
and so is the surgeon's hand.
So he's recreating
his own moral dilemma.
He's picking everyone by design...
- The kids, the professionals...
- And he's not done.
Unis searched the professor's house.
They found files on over
a dozen possible targets.
Okay. Well, we need to find him
or else we need to figure out
a way to draw him out carefully.
Or we could just get a big stick
and poke the bear as hard as we can.
What does that mean?
Well, this man clearly
has an oversized ego,
comparing himself to the likes
of Johnny Kane and Dr. Scott.
If we threaten that ego,
trust me, he'll respond.
How do you know?
Because I know his type, Daniel.
Used to live with him, in fact.
Called him Dad.
What are you doing?
What are you doing, Detective?
Sending him an e-mail.
What?
"You pathetic sad sack,
"no wonder you didn't get tenure,
your experiments are
as ugly as you are."
Well said, Detective.
Seriously? Insulting the serial killer?
That's an awesome idea.
Thank you.
Also, his mask is a bit lame.
Could be much creepier. Put that in.
Chloe. Don't send this.
All right? It's not you.
This is... This is, it's a rash move.
That's great.
I mean, what could go wrong, right?
I mean, surely this won't
force the psycho underground,
it won't cause him to
do anything crazy...
Chill out, Dan.
He responded.
Ah, told you.
With a link.
Hello, Detective.
You don't need that mask
anymore, Professor Carlisle.
Ah.
So much easier to breathe
without that thing.
What do you want, Professor?
What do I want? To finish my
experiment without interference,
but here we are...
Your experiment failed, Professor.
We proved your theory wrong.
The doctor chose to save
the girl. So, clearly,
not everyone's as egregiously
selfish as you are.
I am not a selfish person.
I was vilified for doing
what anyone in my position would do.
You went back for your computer.
That's not about survival,
that's about stuff.
It was about instinct, but thank you
for reminding me why I'm doing this
and for helping me
to improve upon my experiment.
Truth is, Dr. Scott
only mutilated her hand
because she was being observed
by you.
So this time I'm
controlling my variables.
Meet...
Benjamin Tibi.
Innocent student,
attached to a poison drip.
And here, Leon Klem,
accomplished track
star, stuck in a vice.
If Leon simply pulls the lever
and severs his leg within 60 minutes,
Benji here
gets... this.
You guessed it.
The antidote.
Oh, and please, for your sake...
don't waste your time
trying to make another.
They're all unique,
and the only place the formula lives
is right here,
in my head.
Not bad for a sad sack
who couldn't get tenure, huh?
Professor, wait!
Well.
Bear officially poked.
You have two minutes. Talk.
It's simple. There's something
Lucifer needs to know.
I think you should tell him.
Oh, really? And why's that?
Because it's about his beloved Chloe.
He'll take it better from
you. You're his closest friend.
Lucifer may be stubborn,
but he listens to you.
Mm-hmm. Hate to break it to you,
but if you're buttering
me up, it ain't gonna work.
You have bad news to give your son?
Suck it up
and do it yourself.
Good talk.
God made Chloe.
Yeah.
He kind of made them all.
No. Chloe wasn't supposed to be here.
God put her in Lucifer's path.
She's a...
miracle.
Granny Panties Decker? A miracle?
Please.
35 years ago,
Amenadiel was sent to this
bar, where he sat down,
had a chat, then blessed Penelope Decker
so that she and her
husband could have a child.
That child
is Lucifer's partner.
It's no accident that they met.
Mm. So, what, Amenadiel
blessed Penelope's lady parts?
Wait, is Amenadiel
Chloe Decker's daddy?
Oh, don't be ridiculous.
Think...
about it.
Haven't you ever wondered
why that particular human
makes him vulnerable?
Mm.
But if you still don't believe me,
there's something you should see.
No luck. I called every lab
the professor's ever
been affiliated with...
No one's seen him.
He could have built that lab anywhere,
and the video link was untraceable.
What if I made a mistake?
What if by sending that e-mail
I just sped up his timeline?
There's two lives on the line here.
Two lives that you're going to save,
- Detective, I know you will.
- Exactly.
- Found something.
- Please tell me it's good news.
Eh, more like medium news.
So, Kleinberg's autopsy came back.
Turns out he didn't die of poisoning.
I mean, he would have died of poisoning,
except he was strangled.
Impatient little killer.
Since I finally got time of death right,
I was able to ping
Kleinberg's cell to Van Nuys Airport,
where I got this.
It's the professor, clear as day.
So we can assume that
he killed Kleinberg.
Right. But this only tells
us where the professor was.
It doesn't tell us
where he actually is,
hence "medium" news.
Uh, can you rewind it to the part
where he goes through security?
Why, what are you looking for?
Okay, freeze there.
And then zoom in on the tray.
Looks like a key card with a logo.
Oh, definitely a bird.
School mascot maybe?
We checked every lab at Malibu State.
Well, he wouldn't go
back there, would he?
Trust me, when you get
kicked out of a fancy party,
the last thing you want
to do is sneak back in.
You do the opposite.
Who's Malibu's closest rival?
The lab in here is
closed for renovation,
so maybe he's here.
Well, well, isn't this a surprise.
It's locked, Detective.
But with that said, I'm
actually glad you made it.
Why, because you'd like to surrender?
It's a bit anticlimactic,
but very well, we accept.
No, because now you get to see firsthand
what I'm trying to prove.
It's over, Professor.
Afraid you're wrong about that.
Acrylic glass, Detective.
Please don't kill yourself
with your own bullet.
We wouldn't be able to conduct
the final part of this experiment.
Time for you to make a choice.
In this vial, an antidote
that will save Benji's life.
In vial numero dos,
poisonous gas that will kill you
if you enter the room.
Simple, really... You decide
what's more important.
No.
- W-W-W-What are you doing?
- If I don't get in that room right now,
that kid is gonna die.
Word of advice, Detective.
If you go into that room
right now, you'll die.
What are we supposed to do?
- I can save him.
- What?
But in order to do so, you
need to go after the professor
right now, before it's too late.
- What?
- I promise you
I can get to that antidote
without harming myself.
- How?
- We don't have time to explain.
Do you trust me?
- Yes.
- Then go.
Go!
Freeze!
Right.
Okay.
Oh!
Oh, come on, Detective,
a bit of help here!
I need you further away.
Freeze!
There's nowhere left to run, Professor.
Lovely.
I knew you'd save yourself.
It was the only choice you could make.
Put down the knife.
It's not too late.
You can still make a different choice.
The right choice.
You can still save that kid back there.
You still don't get it.
I didn't want anyone to get hurt,
but I needed people to understand
I'm not a monster, I'm human.
You call it biology, call it God,
but choice is an illusion.
I didn't have one
when I pulled myself
out of that burning car.
And I certainly don't have one now.
You'll understand soon enough.
Where is he?
Where is Lucifer?
I'm right here, Detective.
See? I told you everything
would be all right.
I'm so glad you're okay.
Hey.
I guess we make a good
team after all, don't we?
This is real, isn't it?
What if he doesn't come?
If he said he'll be here, he'll be here.
Mazikeen!
Interesting choice of venue.
My, my,
how the tide has turned.
What's this, celestial
enemies' night out?
Why don't you have a seat, Lucifer.
There's something that
we need to tell you.
Ooh, some sort of supernatural
intervention, is it?
Well, doesn't matter what shenanigans
you two have got cooking up,
'cause, quite frankly, I'm too happy
for you to spoil things.
- Happy?
- Yeah.
The detective and I... Sorry...
Chloe and I are real.
I mean, I didn't think it could happen,
but it has, and I've got
this overwhelming sensation...
I can't even describe it, but...
I feel invincible.
So come on, ladies, bring it on.
Whatever it is, I'm
sure I can deal with it.
Forget it. Come on.
What?
There's nothing to talk about.
- What? I've only just got here.
- Go. Go.
We discussed this, Mazikeen.
No. You discussed this.
And I don't want to have
anything to do with it anymore.
I thought you understood.
We're doing this for him.
Is that it?
Or are you trying to
get back at your ex?
You don't know what
you're talking about.
I knew
- you were up to something.
- What the hell is this?
What's Amenadiel doing with Chloe's mum?
I think you already know.
Don't toy with me, Mother.
What is this?
I've been trying to find
the right way to tell you.
But there is no right
way, because the truth...
...is... this is your Father's doing.
Chloe...
is His doing... He put her in your path.
So...
none of it was...
None of it was real.
Don't!
Lucifer.
Detective, I need to talk to you.
Detective!
Did you know? Huh?
This whole bloody time, did you know?
Lucifer...
something's wrong.
It won't stop.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --