=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 13=
Fortunately,
we both were born with God bones.
From this day on,
I’ll give you the rest of my life.
When the Three Realms are there
and the world is there,
I’ll be there,
all right?
Master,
you have no idea
how nervous Her Grace was yesterday.
She even went to the Phoenix Clan,
asking for the Pith of the Plane Tree
as your medical usher.
I’m so happy for you.
Bai Jue.
I brought you something to eat.
Later, you...
Your clothes...
What’s this?
Hongri just gave it to me.
(Report)
It records the treasure Zihan stole.
Let me have a look.
What happened?
It’s not possible.
(Report)
If Tianqi stole these things,
he’s going to set up
the Destruction Formation,
to destroy the Immortal, Demon
and Devil Realms.
What’s the Destruction Formation?
When Devils rebelled,
the God Realm was nearly destroyed.
To defeat them,
the Ancestral God created a formation,
based on the Three Rocks,
instruction feather of Chief God,
Original Being of True Gods
as well as the air of chaos
from Immortals and Demons.
With the sacrifice of everything,
the one who uses the Formation
will become mighty God of Chaos.
Once he becomes God of Chaos,
he’ll outstrip the Ancestral God
and become the most powerful man.
Why have I never heard
about such a formation?
It’s quite inhuman
to sacrifice everything in the world.
So, the Ancestral God didn’t use it.
Instead, he defeated the Devil God
by exhausting all his power,
and then suppressed Devils.
Then Tianqi took away the Three Rocks...
No way.
Tianqi isn’t that cruel.
He must have another purpose
or he was on impulse.
We must trust him.
He wouldn’t make such a big mistake!
If he wanted to be the Chief God,
powerful as he was,
he needn’t have waited until now.
Yeah.
I don’t believe that, either.
But...
But he did.
I’m going to ask him in the lower realm.
No way.
You can’t go see him.
If you go there rashly,
you’ll get yourself in danger.
Now,
Gods are gossiping about his escaping.
If you go see him,
you’ll make the Pilgrimage Hall
the target for all.
Everyone is panicky in the God Realm.
They’re all afraid that
Devils will start a war again.
As the Chief God,
you should pacify them first.
But...
Don’t worry.
Zhiyang and I will figure out the reason
and stop Tianqi.
Why did you summon me?
Any news about Tianqi?
What happened?
Why do you look so serious?
Nothing.
I just want to borrow
you Immortal-seeking Bell.
To look for Tianqi?
Yes.
You let him go for your old friendship.
Why do you want him back now?
Do you know he stole the Three Rocks
from the Hidden Pavilion?
The Destruction Formation?
No way.
Tianqi is never competitive.
How would he set up
the Destruction Formation?
Even if we believe him,
how will other Gods believe him?
If I figure out what he’s after,
we’ll be risking everyone
in the lower realm.
Will you simply ask him
or will you get him back?
If he really sets up
the Destruction Formation,
what will you do to him?
Yuemi,
I know
how nice he’s to me.
If he didn’t,
I would have ordered to get him back.
Tianqi and I have known
for ten thousand years.
I know he’s quite loyal.
But everyone in the God Realm thinks
he betrayed us.
I feel so sad for him.
You’ve never been so sad before.
Do you...?
But he only treats me as a friend.
He cares for no one, but you.
I only care for Bai Jue.
You know that.
If I knew you liked him,
I would...
I know.
I know you only regard him as a brother.
I also know
it’s not your fault.
But Shanggu,
you know what?
Do you know how much I envy you?
You don’t want someone
I could wish for.
I also envy you
for your mutual love with Bai Jue.
But Tianqi...
He never cares for me.
You take me as your close friend.
But I never realized
your feeling for him.
In love,
no one can be forced.
All I want is to accompany him
and stay with him.
Even he can’t think of me
when he’s happy,
I don’t care.
As long as I can get drunk with him
when he’s sad,
that’s enough for me.
That’s not enough.
You’re such a good girl.
You deserve the best love in the world.
After I handle this problem,
I’ll tell him how you feel for him.
Don’t bother.
For some question,
I’ve already known the answer.
Telling him or not
makes no difference.
All I want
is to keep him safe.
Shanggu,
I can lend you
the Immortal-seeking Bell.
But please promise me something.
No matter what happens,
keep him alive.
I beg you.
Yuemi,
you don’t need to
beg me like this.
Don’t worry.
I won’t let anyone kill him.
Master,
you just recovered.
Would you like to have some rest
and look it up tomorrow?
(Destruction Formation)
The Destruction Formation
has never been used before.
I must look up in the books
for the solution.
I can’t feel relived
until it’s solved.
Master,
think about it.
Master Tianqi sometimes
went a bit too far.
But why did he do
what the Devil God did?
Before we know the truth,
don’t gossip.
I never expected you
to find me so quickly.
You’ve grown up
and you’ve been more powerful.
Tianqi,
where are you? Come out!
Look what a condition you’re in.
Why are you still joking?
You must explain to me.
You stole the Three Rocks,
embezzled the instruction feather
of Chief God,
and rebelled with Demons.
What on earth do you want?
Now that you know the answer,
why bother to ask?
I don’t believe that.
You’ve made great efforts
to manage the Immortal and Demon Realms.
I don’t believe
you want to destroy them.
Listen.
You sound so benevolent.
You’re really
a good disciple of Bai Jue.
But he forgot to teach you that
Gods
could also pretend.
You think you matter so much to me
that you can talk me over
and I’ll give up?
Shanggu,
are you getting too dizzy
after being the Chief God for long?
When you were a baby,
I was already commanding Gods.
I simply pretended to be close to you
in the past ten thousand years,
but you take it seriously?
Eyes don’t cheat people.
If you want to be the Chief God, be it.
You don’t need to do this.
How innocent you are!
I’m a Demon God.
Even if you want me to be it,
how will other Gods agree?
I can’t be
the most powerful Chief God of Chaos
and reign the whole world with a reason
unless I set up
the Destruction Formation
and absorb the spiritual power
in the lower realm.
Now that I’ve come,
I’ll take you back
so that you won’t make more mistakes.
Tianqi,
go back with me.
You hurt me?
I’m just telling you that
you can’t do whatever you wish.
Get out of the Abyssal Ridge Swamp!
What if I don’t?
Shanggu,
listen.
I never liked you.
Everything I’ve done for you
is simply to make you alive
until you get the instruction feather
of Chief God.
I’ll always be your brother.
No matter what happens between us
or what we experience,
I’ll always be by your side.
Get back to the God Realm!
When I become
the most powerful Chief God,
I may keep you alive,
for the sake of our old friendship.
Don’t let those stupid Gods come again!
Or I’ll also do
what Xuanyi did.
Your Grace,
how were you hurt?
I’m fine. Don’t let others know.
Master,
True God Bai Jue asked to see you.
Take him to my study.
Don’t tell him I’m hurt.
Yes, Your Grace.
Master.
Did anything happen
in the God Realm again?
No.
Where’s Shanggu?
Still sleeping?
Her Grace didn’t sleep last night.
She just woke up.
Leave us.
Why did you suddenly come?
You’re hurt?
Let me check.
He hurt you?
Where’s he?
Don’t go.
He’s made up his mind.
You won’t change anything.
I’ll just make him know
he can’t hurt you
without paying a price.
I’ve made a mistake
that can’t be forgiven.
Even if he didn’t hurt me, I would...
He made the mistake.
Don’t blame yourself.
But that day,
I let him go.
He told me that
he accompanied me
for all these years,
simply to get the instruction feather
of Chief God.
He’s my closest brother.
I never expected us
to end up like this.
Maybe,
I shouldn’t have come back
from the Nether World.
Go somewhere with me.
Why are you taking me here?
Before you were born,
Tianqi and I often drank in this place.
Gods at that time
all helped the Ancestral God
to create the God Realm
and bred everything in the world.
We were so close
that we could live and die
with each other.
On the eve of the last battle
against Devils,
we also came here.
But most of them
have gone.
After the battle,
I blamed myself
for not protecting more people.
But our life is very long.
We can’t be stuck in regret.
If we keep missing the past,
what can we do about future?
You’re right.
Even if there’s a battle for sure,
I can’t waste my time now.
When we still stay together,
let’s enjoy the scenery,
drink some wine,
and have a nice talk.
Immortals in the lower realm think
Gods like us enjoy ourselves so much.
We move the world with one thought
and change everything with one thought.
But they never know
the destiny is like an invisible hand.
Even if we reign the Three Realms,
there’s something we can’t do.
Bai Jue,
if one day,
I make such a capital crime,
what will do you do?
With me around,
this day never comes.
What if it comes?
If you asked before,
I would tell you
principles mattered more
than personal relationship.
But now I don’t know how to reply.
Maybe you’ve got a reason for that.
I’d like to be punished with you.
When I hear an impartial God like you
say this,
I’d die without anything to regret.
Don’t talk nonsense!
You’re the Chief God.
You exist with the Three Realms.
But no matter how important
Tianqi is to me,
I can’t forget the safety
of the whole world
for my personal feelings.
Because I’m the Chief God.
Shanggu.
Don’t worry.
I’ll stop him from destroying the world,
not only for him,
but also for my own duty.
The Formation can really arouse
the Power of Chose in the lower realm.
It’s the Formation
the Ancestral God created.
It wouldn’t go wrong.
But it takes at least 24 hours
before the Formation is completely done.
Gods won’t give us such a long time.
I’ll stay here
and catalyze the Formation
with Power of the Original Being.
Out of the Abyssal Ridge Swamp,
I’ll leave it to you.
I won’t let you down, Master.
Zihan,
once the Destruction Formation is done,
the Demon Realm will be ruined, too.
That’s your homeland.
Don’t you hate me for that?
- They...
- Master.
Every spiritual power in the Demon Realm
comes from the Demon God.
Once the Demon God is gone,
what’s the point of the Demon Realm?
The True Gods are your friends.
So are we.
When you give an order,
even if we’ll be universally condemned
or forever cursed,
we’ll always follow you.
Your Grace,
before Tianqi’s problem is settled,
you rang the Chaos Bell.
What on earth happened?
Right.
We kept asking to see you but failed.
Please explain to us.
Today, I summoned you,
to tell you something.
Bai Jue and I figured out that
Demon God Tianqi would set up
the Destruction Formation
in the Abyssal Ridge Swamp.
He’s powerful
and has the instruction feather
of Chief God.
When he wants to destroy the world,
who can stop him?
We haven’t figured out how he escaped.
Your Grace, are you going to let it go?
Right.
I let him go,
for the sake of our friendship.
I confess and I’ll take the blame.
Our priority is
to get Tianqi back to the God Realm
and stop him from initiating
the Destruction Formation.
Bai Jue,
assemble troops
and head for the Abyssal Ridge Swamp.
Zhiyang.
Yes, Your Grace.
The God Realm is the base of everything.
Guard the Heaven and Earth Platform
with other Gods
and keep everything safe.
I see.
Gu Jun,
go with me to the South Sea
in the lower realm
and put down the disturbances.
Yes.
Your Grace,
I’d like to go to with Master Bai Jue
and get Tianqi back.
Please let me go.
Nothing can go wrong in the world.
After thinking it over carefully,
I think
only Bai Jue can be impartial enough
to handle the problem.
In the battle against Devils
ten thousand years ago,
eleven apostles and I
were the vanguards.
When the world is in danger,
we can’t keep out of it.
Your Grace, please let me go.
Now that you want it,
go with Bai Jue.
Thank you, Your Grace.
The God Realm is heavily guarded.
I don’t care
if you want to make trouble.
But you mustn’t make trouble for me.
Why are you so nervous, Goddess of Snow?
All Gods are trying
to protect themselves.
Other Gods are busy with their affairs.
They have no time to bother about you.
By the way,
Shanggu summoned all Gods
with the Chaos Bell.
Did anything happen?
Your Overload cares a lot
about the God Realm.
He wants the same as you.
He certainly cares.
You don’t need to sound it out.
I can tell you directly.
Shanggu told all Gods that
Tianqi stole the Three Rocks.
She sent Bai Jue and Yuemi
to the Abyssal Ridge Swamp
and get Tianqi back.
She would go to the lower realm
and stabilize it with the Power of Chaos
so that it couldn’t be ruined.
However,
if the Demon God
destroys the lower realm,
the Nether World will be ruined, too.
What on earth does Overload want?
Now that Bai Jue will go
to the lower realm,
the Destruction Formation
wouldn’t be done.
Master Bai Jue led the troop
to the Abyssal Ridge Swamp.
If you dare play any trick,
I won’t spare you!
Don’t worry.
Considering his power,
who’s able to hurt him?
As long as you complete your mission,
you can get
whatever you want.
Plum blooming in the snow.
Good name.
It’s what made me wait
for thirty thousand years.
It’s not what I said
that made you wait,
but you own obsession.
Master. Master. Master!
Do you know how many efforts I made
to come back to the God Realm?
Master,
why do you still not glance at me?
Master, Master!
Master, I adore you,
but you only care for her.
Don’t blame me for that.
The God Realm is in trouble.
All registered Gods have work to do.
Wu Huan, you’re in charge
of the Pilgrimage Hall.
But why don’t you have anything to do?
That’s weird.
In case I’m in danger,
or someone makes trouble here,
Her Grace asked me to stay.
Sounds like a good reason.
I was from a humble clan,
but I’m not stupid.
If you’re bored,
go back home and lock yourself up.
Why do you bother to be sarcastic?
I told you about the Queen of Phoenix
in the Pilgrimage Hall.
It’s true, isn’t it?
I just want to tell you that
your master is born to be heartless.
If you don’t want to be expelled
and go back to your clan,
serving as a maid again,
you need to do something for yourself.
What do you mean?
Today’s battle is your best chance.
If you can stop Tianqi
from destroying the world,
you’ll have an extraordinary position
in the God Realm.
When you and I want
to get a firm foothold
or get higher,
we must depend on ourselves.
Weak as I am,
I can’t even defeat Zihan.
How can I stop the Demon God?
Devil Weapon?
It was the Sky Bow
an elder devil lost in the battle.
I’ve been keeping it.
It can even hurt a True God.
I’ll lend it to you.
Wu Huan,
you’re a smart girl.
You decide
if you’ll serve or be served
in the God Realm.
(The Pilgrimage Hall)
I’m ashamed.
I should have led the troop
to get Tianqi back.
But so far,
I still don’t want to believe it
or make the ruthless decision.
The Abyssal Ridge Swamp
is plagued by crises.
You must be very careful.
If Tianqi refuses to stop...
I know.
Say no more.
Yuemi,
I won’t worry if you deal with anyone,
but Tianqi.
What?
You only allow yourself
to care for the world?
In your heart,
I care more for love than business?
I don’t mean that.
All right.
I was just joking.
Be careful not to be
as stubborn as Bai Jue
after you stay with him for long.
Wait and see.
I’ll go get Tianqi back.
I’ll punch him
to work off your anger.
Why are you here?
I hear Her Grace ordered you
to have a battle with Demons
in the lower realm.
I don’t want to stay here alone.
Take me with you.
Don’t be absurd!
It’s dangerous. Go back.
Even you think I’m too weak
to do anything important
and all I can do is trifles?
I don’t mean that.
Master Tianqi set up
the Destruction Formation
in the Abyssal Ridge Swamp.
A battle between Gods and Demons
is unavoidable.
I don’t want you to be in danger!
Yes.
I have weak power.
But I also want to fight
for Her Grace.
If I stay and do nothing,
how can I be relieved?
How can I stay in the God Realms?
In case of fight,
you must follow the order
and never take any action
without permission.
Understand?
Don’t worry.
I won’t make trouble for you.
Without my order,
no one should take rash action!
Yes.
Let’s go!
Zihan,
Her Grace ordered us
to arrest the Demon God Tianqi.
Go back to the Demon Realm
with your men,
and we won’t hurt you!
In your dream!
We only take orders for the Demon God.
If he destroys the lower realm,
you’ll die, too.
Why do you help him?
Cut the crap
and just fight!
You won’t get in the Abyssal Ridge Swamp
unless you get over me!
Since when was a ﻿Demigod
among the Demons?
He has Tianqi’s Power
of the Original Being.
Looks like Tianqi made him a Demigod
by using ten thousand years
of his lifespan.
I’m Sen Jian, chief of Tiger Demons.
I’d like to fight as the vanguard.
I won’t stop fighting until I die.
Zihan!
Master Bai Jue doesn’t want
to fight Demons!
Neither do I!
It’s not up to you.
The Destruction of Formation
is nearly done.
They’re stalling for time.
I’ll get in and persuade him.
Even Shanggu failed to persuade him.
What can you do?
Half an hour.
Give me half an hour.
Trust me.
Tianqi isn’t the man
who doesn’t care for the world.
I will persuade him.
All right.
You have half an hour.
No matter what you get,
I’ll meet him personally.
All right.
She got into the Abyssal Ridge Swamp
behind others.
Does she collude with the Demon God?
If I find the evidence
for their collusion,
and stop the Destruction Formation,
I’ll see who dare
look down on me again.
Screwed.
The spiritual power is disappearing.
We must fight, or it’ll be too late.
- Charge!
Go!
Enough!
We shouldn’t have been enemies.
All Gods, on my command!
Protect your Original Being
and never let the spiritual power
disappear again.
The barrier of the lower realm cracked.
If we don’t seal it immediately,
beasts will run out of the Wasteland
and bring disaster.
All Gods, on my command.
Enhance the seal.
Master,
if the south sea bursts its banks,
the sea water will flow backward.
There’ll be a disaster
in the Immortal Realm.
We can’t let the flood
hurt the immortals.
Make up the seal.
Set up the formation.
Yes.
Tianqi,
when will you stop?
How can you ignore the lives
in the lower realm?
Shut up!
I don’t want to listen!
If you come to persuade me,
leave immediately.
The Destruction Formation
has been set up.
I’ll soon have the air of chaos
in the lower realm.
Even if the other True Gods
come personally,
they can’t defeat me.
No way!
It’s not what you are.
I don’t believe you would do this!
Haven’t I made myself clear?
Get out!
Well,
let me help you, then.
Yuemi,
what are you doing?
Even if others don’t believe you,
I do!
I never fail anything I want.
Now that I can’t take you back,
I’ll die in the Destruction Formation!
You think I’ll care
for your own life?
Now that you don’t care,
why don’t you let me die?
All right.
Die as you wish.
But don’t stain my place!
Master,
the power of the Destruction Formation
seems to decline.
Hope they can stop Tianqi.
Master,
are we going to the Abyssal Ridge Swamp
to help with Master Bai Jue?
The barrier isn’t totally fixed yet.
We can’t leave
until we ensure the safety
of the lower realm.
Yes.
I know
you wouldn’t let me die.
It’s enough when I go crazy alone!
Why did you come?
Tianqi,
no matter what reason you have,
I’m on your side, at least.
Go back with me.
We can solve every problem in the world.
We have Bai Jue, Zhiyang
and Shanggu.
Since you left,
Shanggu has never smiled again.
Gods keep condemning her every day.
Don’t you even care for her again?
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪