=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 14=
Tianqi!
No matter what troubles you,
at least you’ll have me stand
by your side.
Please come back with me!
There’s no problem that
we can’t solve it in this world!
You also have Bai Jue, Zhiyang
and Shanggu!
Shanggu has been
very sad since you left!
The people in the God Realm
condemn us every day.
Don’t you care about her anymore?
When we were in the God Realm,
you followed around me every day.
And the way you are behaving now
annoys me even more!
I’ll say it one more time.
Get out!
And don’t let me see you again!
You are lying!
You always
avoid my eyes
when you lie to me!
Tell me
what happened exactly.
Does it have anything to do
with Shanggu?
Maybe…Maybe…
Maybe I can…
You can what?
As coward as you are,
you think you can help a traitor God?
Tell me
why you set off
the Destruction Formation.
If it really has anything to do
with Shanggu…
No one
is able to understand me.
So what?
We’ve overcome
so many difficulties together
over the years.
How do you
I can’t help if you don’t let me?
Yuemi,
we are not ignorant kids anymore.
If I get you involved,
you’ll be in trouble!
Then let it be!
I’m not even afraid of death,
let alone the things related to you!
But…
No buts!
It’s been hundreds
of thousands of years!
We were born and grew up together.
We fought side by side.
We went through thick and thin together.
We got drunk together.
We experienced joy and sorrow together.
In fact, I like…
Yuemi!
Yuemi! Yuemi!
Goddess Yuemi!
I just wanted to stop the Demon God
from destructing the world!
I’ll kill you!
Don’t!
Don’t make Shanggu hate you!
♪Large memories are for you♪
♪Engraved in the palm as patterns♪
Yuemi!
♪Through ups and downs,
drifting from place to place♪
Don’t
waste your energy.
The core of my God power
has been shattered.
No way!
She’s not even a demigod!
How could she shatter
the core of your God power?
Shanggu is right.
A God’s length of life is too long.
But no matter how long it is,
it can’t afford to be idled away.
I just want to tell you
that I know you love Shanggu,
but I wouldn’t give up on you.
It’s so tough
to be friends with someone I love.
I love you!
I finally said it out loud today!
I know.
I know it all the time.
But I was afraid that I’d lose you
if I turned you down
So I’ve been pretending that I didn’t
know your feelings over the years.
Yuemi, it’s my fault!
I was being selfish
and greedy!
I don’t deserve your love!
I get to decide if you deserve it.
Lying in your arms right now…
I’ll take you to the God Realm!
I’m sure they’ll have a way to save you!
I don’t have any strength.
The Destruction Formation
will be completed soon.
Don’t… Don’t let
the mortals suffer anymore!
Don’t talk!
Please don’t talk!
I’ll take you back right now!
It’s too late!
Tianqi, take good care!
Take good care of yourself!
For me!
♪In the name of the world♪
I’m really,
really happy
today.
♪Let me be the gleam in your eyes♪
♪I’m willing to♪
Yuemi!
Yuemi! Yuemi!
♪Wait until we meet again♪
♪Exchange a second of encounter
with my life♪
Yuemi! Yuemi! Yuemi!
♪I’m willing to drown in our memories♪
♪Wait till your smile reveals
in your tears♪
Yuemi!
You died because of me.
If I fail in protecting Shanggu,
♪To get myself♪
my life will be pointless!
♪Be always stuck♪
♪In your heart♪
It can’t be!
The star is falling!
Is Master already…
Master,
why did the star suddenly disappear?
It’s impossible!
It’s definitely impossible!
Wait here.
I’ll bring that stupid guy back,
and I’ll beat him so that
you can vent your anger.
Wu Huan.
How come you were in there?
Did you see my Master?
Master Bai Jue,
the Demon God killed Goddess Yuemi,
and used her God blood
to fuel the formation!
The Destruction Formation
will be completed soon!
No way!
My Master wouldn’t kill Goddess Yuemi!
What happened in there exactly?
How did Yuemi die?
If you lie to me,
I won’t forgive you!
Master,
it was the Demon God!
He pushed Goddess Yuemi
into the formation core.
I witnessed the God power
of Goddess Yuemi being shattered!
She lost her God power
and was devoured by the formation!
I tried to save her,
but the Demon God almost killed me.
If Goddess Yuemi hadn’t
sent me out
with the last of her strength,
I wouldn’t have been able to escape!
Wu Huan!
So the Demon God killed my Master!
Sen Jian, go!
Tell Master
that we can’t hold it anymore!
Ask him to leave!
Stop! All of you!
We haven’t found out the truth yet.
If we wanna survive,
we need to hold the formation together!
Hongri,
watch them.
Don’t let them hurt each other!
Yes!
Hold the formation together!
Tianqi,
you used her blood
to fuel the formation!
We won’t let you leave here
no matter what it takes!
I will protect Master Tianqi
with my life today!
Master Tianqi!
You’ve fulfilled your duties today.
When the Three Realms are rebuilt again,
Sen Jian,
you will no longer be the Head
of the Tiger Demons,
instead, I’ll have you in charge
of the entire Demon Realm!
Master Tianqi!
Go ahead!
Master!
If he really killed Yuemi,
I will not let him get away with it!
Let’s break
his Destruction Formation first!
How did Yuemi die?
Tianqi,
don’t make any more mistakes!
Bai Jue,
you and I are both true Gods
and created by the Ancestral God.
It’s not your place
to judge me!
Then I’ll take you back to the God Realm
and let Shanggu decide!
Are you really going
to fight me for these people?
Don’t forget that only
the four of us share the same ancestor!
These people?
These people are the ones who made
great contributions to the God Realm!
The Destruction Formation will destroy
everything that the Ancestral God
and all deities created,
as well as all the beings
of the Three Realms!
So what?
The Three Realms
can be rebuilt,
but some things can never
be replaced once they are gone!
Is that what the Three Realms
mean to you?
Since when did you become so ruthless?
I should’ve left you in the God Realm,
Yuemi wouldn’t have been killed
if I had!
You have no right to talk about her,
much less accusing me of being ruthless!
Tianqi,
stop making mistakes!
Shut up
Muguang,
calm down!
Let’s wait till Master
finds out the truth!
Hongri,
if the one who died were Master Bai Jue,
would you still be able to stay calm?
Tianqi,
I promised Shanggu
that I’d bring you back.
For the sake of Yuemi,
Shanggu
and all beings of the world,
don’t make mistakes anymore, Tianqi!
I’ll let you pay for my Master’s death!
Stop!
Today I’ll let you know
that I am the ruler of everything!
Because of you, the Three Realms
are in disorder
and people are dead.
Tianqi,
I can’t let you live anymore.
Bai Jue,
you’ll regret it!
One day
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods♪
♪And memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed♪
♪And I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away♪
♪And loving you greatly♪
How did you do that?
Dangerous?
Why would it be dangerous?
You think my teaching will
alienate the God Realm?
Shut your mouth.
A sign of spirit leaving your body?
For all these years, have you been…?
It’s normal for the spirit
to get hurt during cultivation.
It’s not a big deal.
Don’t think I’ll tell this to Shanggu.
Wanna play the sympathy card?
You wish.
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past♪
♪When we wake up♪
The eleventh deity star has fallen.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods♪
♪And memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
Master!
♪Years have passed♪
♪And I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away♪
♪And loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
Gu Jun,
please stay here and
keep an eye on the barrier.
I’ll go find Bai Jun.
Okay.
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
Master,
Zihan has returned to the Demon Realm.
Please leave me alone.
Master, you…
Leave!
♪Figure out the past when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
Ten thousand years ago,
I was born on the Heaven
and Earth Platform,
and the first one I saw was Tianqi.
He and Yuemi took care of me every day
and watched me grow up.
He’s my dearest brother,
whom I trust the most
in the Three Realms.
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
Where’s Yuemi?
♪Tears turn into clouds♪
♪and rain drops♪
Do you know where she is?
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll♪
♪Enjoy a free life with you♪
♪For a thousand years♪
And Tianqi.
Where is he?
He killed too many Gods.
I had to end his life.
Why did he kill so many people?
Did he tell you the reason?
I’ll go find Zihan.
Zihan has been with him
for all this time,
he must know the reason.
He won’t see you.
At least not for the next
tens of thousands of years.
I failed in protecting them.
It’s not your fault.
I’m the Chief God of the Three Realms.
I should take full responsibility.
I will do whatever it takes
to find out the truth!
There you are, Shanggu!
You are drinking alone at here again!
Why didn’t you ask me to join you?
He killed too many Gods.
I had to end his life.
Yuemi,
I failed in protecting you,
and I failed
in fully understanding Tianqi.
I should be responsible
for everything.
If you hold a grudge,
don’t blame Tianqi,
just come to me.
I was brought up by you and Tianqi.
Tianqi
was a careless man
who joked around all the time.
Yuemi,
could you come to my dreams
and tell me
why Tianqi wanted to destruct the world
and what he kept from us?
Your Grace.
Has your wound healed?
Thank you for your care, Your Grace.
It’s much better now.
Alright.
I’m a light drinker anyway.
I should go back.
You should go back and take a rest, too.
Your Grace,
the night before my Master left,
she asked me
to bring you a message
if she couldn’t come back.
What did she say?
She said
in her whole life she’s been pursuing
happiness,
fine wine,
and a clear conscience.
But there’s one thing
she did feel sorry about.
She’d never done
anything she should feel sorry about.
The day when you prepared
her birthday banquet,
she took you to the Taoyuan Forest
and told you about what happened
to Master Bai Jue
for her own benefit.
She hoped that you’d forgive
Master Bai Jue
and that the Demon God
could give up on you.
My Master had been feeling sorry
about that
and she didn’t know how to tell you
or how to face the Demon God.
Pass my decree,
no new owner
shall be assigned
to the Taoyuan Forest of the Moon Hall,
which will forever belong to
the Goddess of Moon & Stars.
Yes, Your Grace!
From now on,
I’ll light up the stars
in the God Realm for you.
As long as I’m here
and the God Realm exists,
the Goddess of Moon & Stars
will always be yours.
Thank you, Your Grace!
Are you here to comfort me?
No.
Come with me.
Yuemi!
What happened in there exactly?
How did Yuemi die?
If you lie to me,
I won’t forgive you!
it was the Demon God!
He pushed Goddess Yuemi
into the formation core.
I witnessed the God power
of Goddess Yuemi being shattered!
I’ll kill you!
My injury is self-inflicted.
Would they really trust me?
(Moon Hall)
Muguang.
What are you doing here?
Goddess Yuemi was killed.
I…
I’m concerned about you.
Goddess Yuemi and Master Tianqi
were very close.
Although I saw it in person,
it’s still hard for me to believe
that Master Tianqi killed Goddess Yuemi.
Don’t call him Master anymore.
He’s not worthy of it!
Master Bai Jue has ended his life.
He deserved to die!
What’s wrong?
When thinking about
Goddess Yuemi had loved the Demon God
Tianqi for all those years,
I feel sorry for her.
It was obvious
that my Master loved the Demon God,
who, however, always
played dumb.
It’s cold at night.
And you have an injury.
Please go back and rest.
I’m sorry about your loss!
Why did you bring me
to The Hidden Pavilion?
I need your help.
The Purple Jade Whip!
I was going to put it
in The Hidden Pavilion,
but…
You can’t handle
such a small thing like this?
I’m not in the mood for jokes.
It’s weird.
Your cultivation base is the highest
among the Three Realms,
yet you can’t control
the whip with your power?
The Purple Jade Whip has its own spirit.
It wouldn’t obey the person
who killed its owner.
The others must see you
as a cold-blooded person
who doesn’t feel sorry and sad
about killing his brother.
But actually, you feel sorry the most
that you stabbed him dead
with your Taicang Spear.
I’ve had people investigate.
Nothing major happened in Taichu Hall
before Tianqi set off
the Destruction Formation.
I’m afraid
he really had no other choice.
I’ve put a seal on it.
It won’t make trouble anymore.
Thank you!
And this is yours.
Xuanyi used to be chosen
as the Chief God,
but he betrayed and left the God Realm
right before he took over
the instruction feather of Chief God.
Tianqi had never been
an aggressive person,
but he made such a mess
before I took over
the instruction feather.
How I wanted to take over
the instruction feather before,
but now it makes me uneasy
when I see it.
I’m tired.
I’ll go back and rest.
Bai Jue, you’ll regret it!
One day you’ll regret it!
Xuanyi betrayed and ran away.
Tianqi was going to destruct the world..
It all comes down to the succession
to the instruction feather of Chief God.
Is there any connection
between the two incidents?
A thousand years ago,
Zhiyang told me
that the Power of Chaos
in the lower realm was vanishing,
and he urged me to cultivate the power
and become the Chief God of Chaos.
Bai Jue thus came to me
and taught me patiently.
This time, I can’t let them down again!
Why is the Power of Chaos
in the lower realm vanishing so quickly?
Why are there
only few spiritual veins left?
Because all the Three Realms are waiting
for the day when you can
take over the instruction feather
of Chief God.
Why did Zhiyang and Tianqi who always
allowed me to have my fun
suddenly ask Bai Jue to teach me?
What fills the heaven and the earth
are all living beings,
which can compensate the air of chaos.
But I finally understand
that Bai Jue has his reason to make you
practice in the Nether World
to accelerate
your cultivation of the Power of Chaos.
Bai Jue could have
taught me little by little,
but why would he ask me
to master a power that usually takes
ten thousand years to cultivate
within only one thousand years?
You carry the responsibility
of the Power of Chaos.
You should be aware of that
all the time.
When you take over
the instruction feather of Chief God,
you’ll be responsible
for all living beings
and for creating the Human Realm.
Why
would Xuanyi give up a righteous way
of ruling the Three Realms,
instead, choose to betray
and leave the God Realm first?
Why did Tianqi who’d loved me so much
act like a totally different person?
I am the most powerful God
in the God Realm!
And I will become the most
rightful Chief God in the God Realm!
Why?
There must be something I don’t know.
I can’t lose anybody anymore
for no reason!
Master.
What is it?
The Pilgrimage Hall
just issued a decree,
Master Shanggu will close the hall
for a day
to cultivate the instruction feather
of Chief God.
It’s been 70,000 years.
The Chief God of Chaos
will finally be born!
Ring the Chaos Bell
and inform all Gods
of the arrival
of the Chief God of Chaos!
The Chief God of Chaos will be born!
Congratulation, Overlord!
Your wish will soon come true!
Overlord!
Take this magic weapon to
the Heaven and Earth Platform,
and show them
what a chaos tribulation is all about!
Yes, Overlord!
I didn’t expect that the first thing
the Chief God of Chaos would do
after getting rid of the Demon God
is to take over the Chief God position.
Such a quick move is surely
like something a ruler of
the God Realm would take.
My Master is doing this
following the Heaven’s will.
You are in no position to judge her,
Goddess of Snow!
And who do you
think you are
to talk back to me?
The Demon God made trouble
and threatened the lives of all beings.
The God Realm needs to be rebuilt.
We need the Chief God of Chaos
to lead us.
Taking over the instruction feather
of Chief God at this critical time
shows the real courage of a ruler.
If I’m right,
you are the disciple of
the Goddess of Moon & Star.
You’ve become a God already?
Struggling as you are,
you sound so arrogant!
How will Goddess Yuemi
and the eleven apostles feel
in the heaven?
Goddess of Snow, as a senior,
please watch your mouth.
You are just an insignificant disciple!
How dare you be rude to me?
So you know you should show respect!
You…
Goddess Yuemi died
for all living beings.
My Master has issued a decree yesterday
that Muguang is promoted
from one of the 12 stars
to the God of Moon & Stars.
From now on,
he’ll also be a Magic God,
just like you!
The Wasteland of the Demon Realm.
Tianqi!
Master,
the Qiong Qis that startled Her Grace
escaped from here?
Tianqi!
Let’s walk around and take a look.
I can’t believe Zhiyang.
Just a few Qiong Qis.
What’s the big deal?
Say, about Bai Jue,
what are the odds of such thing?
He went to the Lower Realm
and bumped into Shanggu?
He must’ve followed her.
Apparently he likes Shanggu,
but he pretends that he doesn’t.
Master,
now that we are here,
let’s take a look at it.
Take a look at what?
So troublesome!
Ancestral God’s Barrier of Chaos
is broken!
That’s weird!
Although there’s a small sign
of Devilish Energy,
the seal seems
to lift itself.
The Barrier of Chaos in the wasteland
was made of the Power of Chaos.
Except for Her Grace,
no one else is able
to control the Power of Chaos
and break the barrier.
Could it be…
Master?
Do you remember
the warning that the Ancestral God
left when he was falling?
When he was falling
he warned us that the Tribulation
of Chaos would come soon.
The tribulation can only
be avoided when Her Grace
becomes the Chief God.
Master, you are saying
the barrier is broken
because of the tribulation?
But Her Grace has mastered
the Power of Chaos.
Tomorrow she will take over
the instruction feather of Chief God.
Why is the Power of Chaos
in the Lower Realm still vanishing?
Something’s not right!
Come on.
Let’s go
to the Heaven and Earth Platform.
Master,
are you going to consult
the Ancestral God with Yingsheng Stone?
At this point,
this is our only way to find out
what the warning really means.
But usually, we’d wait for the Ancestral God
to send us instructions.
- If we ask the Heaven ourselves…
- It concerns Shanggu.
We can’t afford any risk.
I’ll be responsible for
any consequences.
Ancestral God,
what is Tribulation of Chaos?
Master!
Go away!
Master! Master!
Ancestral God,
what is Tribulation of Chaos?
Master!
When the tribulation occurs,
the God Realm will be destructed.
All living beings will die
unless the Chief God of Chaos
sacrifices herself to the tribulation.
You evil
old jerk!
You made Shanggu cultivate so hard
to master the Power of Chaos
and take over the Chief God position
so that
she can die for your living beings?
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪