♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
=The Eternal Love S3=
=Episode 22=
You lied to me!
Move.
Tan Er was summoned to the imperial chamber?
The security has been tightened as well?
Will Her Highness be in danger?
(It seems like my guess is right.)
(Her Majesty noticed)
(the relation between Tan Er
and the Soul-guarding Bead.)
(So she must have been taken)
(to the Altar of Souls.)
Tan Er!
(This is a serious matter.)
(I can't let them get involved in this.)
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
It's only a minor headache.
You knew Her Highness was taken there,
but you didn't tell us.
Trust me.
It's better for you not to know.
Eighth Brother.
Do not keep secrets from me again.
Do you know
a place known as
the Altar of Souls?
I heard it was forbidden ground.
But I've never been there before.
I have no idea
whether it existed or not.
Not only does it exist,
its entrance...
is right inside Her Majesty's bedroom.
Why would Her Majesty summon
Second Princess to the Altar of Souls?
When I was in the palace for the prayer ritual,
I stumbled upon that place.
There is a strange bead at the altar.
That bead
is closely related to Tan Er.
I think Her Majesty
wants to use this bead and Second Princess
to increase her might.
But she doesn't know
doing so
will put both of them in grave danger.
How did you find that place?
What exactly happened?
Back then,
Her Majesty
tried to alienate Second Princess and me.
She kept summoning me to the palace.
I had the chance to find that place.
I knew it.
Before I told you,
I knew you would have such a reaction.
But I told you nonetheless.
I just wanted to know
whether you are still
the same person
you used to be.
Do you expect me to break the law
and side with you blindly?
I only hope that...
you would think about
this matter from different perspectives.
Is it my fault?
Or should Her Majesty take the blame?
Eighth Brother!
From what I remember,
status and power
would never make you submit.
(The Soul-guarding Bead is really here.)
(So in this parallel universe,)
(the Soul-guarding Bead belongs
to the Qu family too.)
(Is she the host in this world?)
(Does it mean)
(Cheng Cheng and I can return
to our world with the bead?)
(Did the Soul-guarding Bead backfire on her)
(while harnessing its power?)
(But Xiao Zhen)
(brought me here)
(and forced me to admit)
(my relation with the Soul-guarding Bead.)
(Is he going to use me as a tribute)
(as Qu Jiang Lin did?)
(But I don't have the Soul-parting Xiao.)
Seems like
Your Highness remembers what bead this is.
As I expected.
More guards.
We need a decoy
to distract their attention.
Shift change.
She changed her mind.
You can come out.
I'll follow you inside.
After that,
I'll try to persuade Her Majesty.
If any of you tried to harm her,
I would not show mercy.
Let go of me!
Do you really think
using me and the bead will be
enough to reawaken Her Majesty?
Don't you know the risks?
You know the secrets.
I do.
But I also know
whatever you plan to do
will only push Her Majesty and me
into deeper darkness!
But sadly,
Her Majesty is already deep in the darkness.
Now,
let's see if you can save her.
The rumor about Her Majesty building a dungeon
to harness great power was true!
Her Majesty
has more secrets.
The contraptions were shut down.
Something is amiss.
Be cautious.
The spirit energy backfired on her.
Xiao Zhen lied.
He wants to use Tan Er
to reawaken Her Majesty
with the power of the Soul-guarding Bead!
But if he fails,
Tan Er and Her Majesty
will both die.
He forged a fake imperial decree.
That is treason!
Tan Er!
Cheng Cheng!
Tan Er.
Mo Lian Cheng.
You trespassed the forbidden ground.
You should be executed for it!
You should face execution instead!
You hid Her Majesty's injury
and forged an imperial decree!
How dare you!
I was ordered by Her Majesty.
My plan
will save Her Majesty
without harming Her Highness.
But you, Mo Lian Cheng.
You planned a rebellion.
General,
you should help me arrest him!
I'll warn you again.
Underestimating the bead will bring
catastrophic consequences.
Both Her Majesty and Tan Er
will in grave danger!
Barely no one in the palace
knows the Soul-guarding Bead.
But you sounded like an expert.
Perhaps you had planned this long ago
to overthrow the throne!
Official Xiao,
it's time to put an end to this.
If you side with him, General,
then I shall
show no mercy for you.
Seize Mo Lian Cheng!
Cheng Cheng, watch out!
Cheng Cheng.
Your Majesty.
Tan Er.
Tan Er, hang in there.
Tan Er!
- Cheng Cheng.
- Tan Er!
Find a way home.
Protect our son.
Don't be silly.
As long as you're there,
no matter how dangerous it is,
that place will be our home.
Without you,
no place can be called home.
I followed you
from one lifetime to another.
I would never abandon you
and go to a world you're not in.
Tan Er.
Hang in there.
How could you be so silly?
Now that I saved you,
let's go through this together.
Your Majesty.
This is all my fault.
Watch out!
Cheng Cheng. Wake up!
Cheng Cheng.
Your Majesty.
(The mark from the backfire is gone.)
Wake up.
Cheng Cheng.
If anything happens to him,
I will make you pay dearly.
Your Highness!
Lian Cheng!
You broke into the forbidden ground.
But you tried to protect Her Majesty.
Take her and leave.
When Her Majesty is awake,
I'll explain everything to her.
♪A haggard look is left, why do you
remain aloof and indifferent♪
♪Did loving me become too burdensome♪
♪The sky turns Grey as it is about to rain,
covering inevitable pain♪
(A day of marriage,)
(comes from centuries of fate.)
(Our destiny of three lifetimes)
(is like a surreal dream.)
(We meet at the wall in three lifetimes,
the blossoms were falling like rain.)
(Our consummations in three different lifetimes
all ended on a canopy bed we shared.)
(The cycle of a nightmare brings about
a lifeless yearning.)
(Without sorrow from our parting,)
(we will lose faith in our love.)
♪A dream is the one-time, uninhibited indulgence♪
(I'm waking from the dream.)
(But I missed the chance to bid her farewell.)
♪Falling into a black hole of stubbornness,
forcefully making up far-fetched lies♪
♪Even though there are
too many sarcastic moves♪
♪Going from lovers to strangers
makes me confused♪
♪A dream is the one-time, uninhibited indulgence♪
♪Do you understand my confusion at all♪
♪All because of your silence♪
♪Why can't you see it?♪
♪Give me a warm embrace♪
♪Do you understand my heartache at all♪
(Cheng Cheng!)
♪All because of your recklessly squander♪
(Cheng Cheng.)
♪I'm starting to not understand
whether there is love♪
(Cheng Cheng.)
♪I'm beginning to feel pain for knowing love♪
Cheng Cheng?
It's been three days.
Why are you still in a coma?
As long as you can wake up,
I can serve you tea and give you
a massage every day.
I'll do whatever
you tell me to do.
I'll hold you to it.
Cheng Cheng, you're awake.
Do you have to wait for me
to make such promises to wake up?
(Having memories from three lifetimes)
(is such a bizarre sensation.)
(The person in front of me)
(still looks the same,)
(but she has a much more important
place in my heart now.)
Well?
Does the wound still hurt?
(Maybe I should withhold from telling her)
(I've regained my memories.)
My wound...
Don't you remember?
Is this another amnesia?
I only remember
that at some point
Feng Yang came to me and told me
you were taken to the imperial chamber.
And then...
I saved you
and got hurt.
If I had known you remembered nothing,
I would have twisted the story a little.
Someone
should serve me tea...
and give me a massage.
Those are jobs for men.
I haven't done them in a long time.
What?
Are you already regretting it?
Not at all.
As long as you can wake up,
I will walk my talk.
Then...
Before I become normal again,
you must get used to this lifestyle of serving me.
When you're bossing me around,
it seems like
you do have your memories.
I think...
I lost my memories again.
Are you disappointed?
Certainly not.
Let me rub your feet.
You...
You don't need to be too sensitive.
I told you.
We will create new memories
together.
Do not be troubled by the memories you lost.
(When I lost my memories,)
(she was always concerned with my thoughts.)
(She even had to be careful with her words.)
Right.
Maybe you could
go on a walk with me in the garden.
You just woke up.
Why would you want to go there?
(To snuggle with you, of course.)
(Then we can create new memories.)
I can't remember how long I've been in bed.
I want to stretch my limbs.
My injury really took a toll on me.
I think you might have to look after me
for the rest of my life.
At the Altar of Souls,
I thought I would lose you for sure.
But it seems like
as long as the worst has yet to happen,
whatever the future holds for us
will be great.
(After the life-and-death experience,)
(it's not just me,)
(she's changed a lot.)
(Perhaps I should tell her the truth.)
- But...
- Tan...
Cheng Cheng, seriously?
You...
You should lose some weight.
I'm tall.
My weight is just fine.
It's heavier now.
Are you messing with me?
How could you
doubt a patient?
You seemed to have no problem talking.
Maybe...
you're doing just fine.
You're giving me a heart attack.
The pain has become more intense.
(The way he fools around)
(looks exactly like Cheng Cheng
when he regains his memories.)
(Could it be...)
(he's faking his amnesia?)
(No.)
(I need to pry deeper.)
How did it get so serious all of a sudden?
Let me help you back.
I'll change your bandages.
Take it slowly.
Be careful.
I should change the bandage
on your arm too.
Didn't you lose your memories?
How do you know your left arm was hurt?
I...
I lost my memories,
but I didn't lose my mind.
It's natural
that I can feel the pain.
This is odd.
When we were at the Altar of Souls,
there wasn't any intimate contact.
How did you lose your memories?
I should ask you that.
How can I know
if you fondled with me?
You were the one who groped!
Me?
Groped?
See?
You know what groping means!
I...
You have your memories!
Fine.
If you were any more dim-witted,
I couldn't keep acting.
You scared me!
Right.
I need your help with an experiment.
No!
I don't want you
to lose your memories again.
When we
first met at the wall,
what did I call you?
I don't remember.
See?
You used yourself as a lab rat.
Look at you now.
You've undone all the progress.
Why don't you
ask me
why we signed an unbreakable pact?
And after we fell off the cliff,
how heartbroken I was?
In the Xuanling Continent,
we were forced to be apart.
How did I find you,
protect you,
and win your love?
Do you really remember everything?
I will never forget.
But you don't remember what I called you.
My Princess Consort is relentless today.
Perhaps I should
teach you some manner.
All right.
I know you remember everything.
I lost.
I also
have this strong feeling.
After we returned from the Altar of Souls,
the memory trigger malfunctioned.
I won't lose my memories again.
Are you sure?
While I was in the coma,
I saw the memories from my
three different lifetimes.
All of this
felt so real
as if I was experiencing it.
So for the rest of my life,
I won't lose those memories again.
That's great!
My dear Cheng Cheng has really come back to me.
I missed you so much.
Don't leave me again.
Please?
The spirit energy from the Soul-guarding Bead
made you remember all of it.
I tried to recall.
I arrived in this world several months
before you did.
Like my amnesia,
it must have been
the temporal disruption
the Soul-guarding Bead caused.
Without my memories,
I couldn't have faith
in your promise.
I even...
doubted your intention...
and challenged your sincerity.
If you really gave up on me,
whatever the reason was,
I wouldn't blame you.
But when I saw...
how you never gave up on me,
I wished to hold you in my arm
as I am now.
I want to tell you...
I won't let you face the harsh reality alone.
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
That moment...
has finally come.
♪It's too late to pluck the dawn blossoms at dusk♪
No amount of concern...
can compare with a large amount of cash.
Paying a due debt
is still a viable option.
♪We remember the promise from a previous life,
but we've become speechless♪
♪I resent that we act as if we are strangers♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
Jing Xin.
Why don't you go in there?
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
Keep it down.
Prince Consort is finally awake.
I should visit him then.
No.
They are...
So
Eighth Brother
has recovered well.
You're an unmarried man.
Mind your language.
Eighth Brother has been married for half a year.
But they still love each other so much.
Of course I would envy them.
Before Prince Consort woke up,
Her Highness told me
the two of them
shared three lifetimes of destiny together.
The way she described their love...
was beyond romantic.
♪We remember the promise from a previous life,
but we've become speechless♪
♪I resent that we act as if we are strangers♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
If there is nothing else,
I should get going.
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
Even three lifetimes of destiny
must start from this lifetime.
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
Feng Yang and I
prepared this tonic soup with a Xiyue recipe.
Take it on time.
It helps with your recovery.
Eighth Brother,
are you sure you're alright?
Yun Xiu and I have been worried about you
every waking moment over the past three days.
Three days?
Every waking moment?
It seems like
you've given him your answer.
He risked his life for me.
I have no reason not to answer his kindness.
Don't worry.
I will find a right opportunity
to disown him.
I really have to thank you this time.
Don't mention it.
Other than the repudiation paper,
we also prepared a small ceremony for you two.
A ceremony?
The two of us
wish to witness your martial art prowess.
So this time tomorrow
Feng Yang can come here
to test her skills
against Yun Xiu's martial arts.
Yes!
That's what I meant.
- Maybe...
- Are we...
We should wait for a while.
I don't want anyone
to interrupt us.
I'm surprised Yun Xiu
is so talented.
He's a fast learner.
After you passed out,
Yun Xiu and Feng Yang
helped me carry you here.
What happened after I passed out?
Why would Xiao Zhen
let us go so easily?
You shielded me with your body
and got hit by the spirit energy.
But the Soul-guarding Bead
stopped attacking at that moment.
The mark of the backfire Her Majesty
had also disappeared.
Xiao Zhen realized he was wrong.
That's how all of us
managed to get away unscathed.
But one thing still baffles me.
Why would your sacrifice
make the Soul-guarding Bead
spare us?
It didn't stop because of me.
It was because of you.
Me?
In the most critical moment,
you hugged me from behind.
So the bead's spirit energy
attacked both of us.
And because
you share a special bond with
the Soul-guarding Bead,
it stopped attacking.
In other words,
your love for me
saved us all.
However,
do not
be so reckless again.
In worst cases,
we need someone
to look after Yu Er.
I told you
the exact same words at the Altar of Souls.
How dare you use my lines against me.
But judging by the situation,
Her Majesty
is the host of Soul-guarding Bead
in this world.
And it's likely that
she also possesses
the Soul-parting Xiao.
The power of the Soul-guarding Bead alone
might not be enough to bring us home.
There must be other requirements to meet.
But what
requirements do we need to meet?
I think Her Majesty and Xiao Zhen
must know some secrets.
If Xiao Zhen can sense
the anomaly of the Soul-guarding Bead too,
or perhaps he might have a certain
amount of control over it,
the answer we seek is likely in his
and Her Majesty's hands.
So we must search deeper
for a way to return to our world.
However,
it's best to be cautious.
I think Her Majesty
is keeping
some unspeakable plan.
I used to think babysitting a kid was tiring.
I even complained about it to you.
But it's been six months.
I really miss him.
Believe me.
We will find a way home.
My actions
had put you in harm's way.
If I could,
I would share your pain.
I was out of line.
Your Majesty.
Why am I here?
I deserve the worst of punishments.
Please punish me.
You were hurt because of me.
I'm fine.
Please don't be concerned.
It's fine.
Later
I'll order the imperial physician to
prescribe the best medicine.
Get well soon.
I will forever be in Your Majesty's debt.
After the ritual backfired,
you asked Second Princess to come?
My apologies.
After I found out
the Soul-guarding Bead resonated
with Her Highness,
I've been suspecting her identity.
So I took it upon myself
to force Her Highness to cooperate with me
in using the energy of the Soul-guarding Bead
to wake you up.
But in the end,
I lost control of its energy.
If Mo Lian Cheng did not come to save us in time,
I'm afraid...
I would never be able to atone for my mistake.
Mo Lian Cheng saved me?
He had two followers.
Yun Xiu and Mo Feng Yang.
Although they don't know
the true nature of the Soul-guarding Bead,
I knew I had made a grave mistake.
It seems like...
it wasn't me that he saved.
It was Second Princess.
Your Majesty.
You're still recovering.
Please stay calm.
You did well...
for this matter.
Had it not happened,
I would still have false hope
for a lost cause.
And now,
I realized...
I can't be a sitting duck.
I must...
make haste with my plan.
Qu Tan Er...
will be sacrificed for the greater good after all.
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪A flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter what
hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have to
travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter what
hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have to
travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪