♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
=The Eternal Love S3=
=Episode 21=
Feng Yang.
You're here.
Do you notice any changes?
You look brand-new.
Since I've come to Dongyue,
I want to be
a Dongyue gentleman for once.
Good for you.
The sunshine is glaring.
Why don't we
go stand under the tree?
Ready.
Pull.
♪The night was spent in yearning♪
♪The flowers bloom in the morning♪
I'm just being polite.
Don't mind it.
♪Quiet rain on the lonely hill♪
♪I intoxicate myself♪
You care more about
other people's relationships more than your own.
♪My yearning has no place to be,
the melodies echo at night♪
I asked you to come
because I want to return this to you.
♪So is your silhouette♪
Why are you returning it?
I misunderstood you before.
So I don't deserve this present
that represents peace.
Keep the sword buckle.
If you really want to apologize,
you should do it in the Xiyue way.
The Xiyue way?
♪I've discarded my wariness♪
♪All I want is to quietly tell you of my affection♪
A year ago, you never would've imagined
that we could drink from the same bottle of wine
under the same moon.
A year ago, I never would've imagined
that the wild General Pu Gu
can be
this gentle and virtuous.
You are surprised, aren't you?
It's fine as long as Princess is happy.
What about you?
It's not important.
What if it's important to me?
Perhaps you are drunk.
I also have a headache.
His nature is unconventional and uninhibited.
He is more attractive than
the graceful Dongyue gentlemen.
What am I thinking?
He is Prince Consort of Second Princess.
♪Every night, I open the window and breathe♪
♪Missing the back hugs from you♪
♪Every time I want to listen to your whispers♪
♪Missing the sunshine on you♪
♪I gradually leave, gently saying goodbye to you♪
♪Turmoil is the sea of tears♪
I'll wash it and return it to you tomorrow.
General, since when did you
start caring about details?
Prince Consort, why are you being
so gentle tonight?
Didn't you say
that you like Dongyue gentlemen?
That's why you suddenly changed the way you act?
♪Life was so wonderful your eyes was beautiful♪
You're drinking while having a headache?
In my opinion,
being wild and uninhibited
suits you
better.
(Princess's Residence)
You're awake.
Do you still have a headache?
Did you stay here the entire night
because you were worried about my headache?
You might've caught a cold
from getting drunk last night.
I'm fine.
You should go back to your room and rest.
I need to handle some emergencies.
Feng Yang.
In fact,
there is one thing
that you don't know.
This sword buckle doesn't represent
peace.
What does it represent then?
My heart.
Prince Consort, do you know
what you are talking about?
Feng Yang.
I fell in love with you
on the battlefields long ago.
When I was forced to have a peace-making marriage,
the only thought that supported me
was being able to meet you again.
I can overcome
all misunderstandings and barriers.
The only thing that supports me
is seeing you again.
You are Main Prince Consort of Second Princess.
You've consummated your marriage
on the wedding night.
How can you say such inappropriate words?
The marriage wasn't consummated.
Princess.
What do you mean?
On the wedding night,
everything Yun Xiu did
was for Officer Xiao to see.
Instead of consummating the marriage,
he made a deal with me.
If I help him pursue you,
he would help me annoy Mo Lian Cheng.
You were acting.
Acting is an expedient measure.
But my feelings are genuine.
If your feelings are genuine,
then you wouldn't have
hidden the truth from everyone,
and manipulated others like your puppets.
Feng Yang.
Shut up.
I don't want to see you anymore.
Neither do I want to hear you calling my name.
I'll move out of Princess's Residence immediately.
Good luck to you.
Feng Yang.
Maybe she is just
being stubborn,
her heart could be attracted already.
We'll leave her alone
for a few more days.
Let her realize how she really feels.
Maybe she'll come back to you.
No, no, no.
I think we've used
enough tactics.
Do you really think
Feng Yang cannot tell
that all our tactics were targeting her?
I think,
at this moment,
you should put yourself in her shoes.
Open your heart to her.
Now the person who has
their heart closed is not Yun Xiu,
it's Mo Feng Yang.
If you can really put yourself in each other's shoes,
you will realize
that in a relationship,
if tactics that you look down on are missing,
it will be boring.
Are you talking about Yun Xiu or me?
Even though we have been married for a long time,
you should still use some romantic measures
to keep our love fresh.
I thought
you love me for who I am.
This is different.
Asking you to be a little more romantic
can turn you into a different person?
Are those superficial things
that important to you?
Are things that you don't understand
superficial?
You don't even want to answer me now?
In this world,
no relationships are the same.
No relationships
are comparable.
Is asking you to be a little more romantic
and to make changes
this difficult?
You always think
about what makes you happy.
Have you thought about what makes me happy?
Alright, alright.
Don't think you're the only one
who can walk away,
I can too.
(Mo Residence)
♪No one appreciates the early morning sun♪
♪It was you who taught me to enjoy
the turbulence in life♪
♪But you have already gone far away♪
(Ocean makes all other waters unworthy of the name,)
(after Wushan mountain, all other clouds
are mere puffballs above.)
[*The character "yun", namely, "cloud",
in this poem has been left out]
♪I really want to write you a letter,
telling you I am still here♪
♪Waiting to hear from you♪
♪I really want to send you a message,
want to hear your voice♪
Is that possible
that I've really fallen in love with Yun Xiu?
♪In this city filled with indifference♪
Feng Yang.
Why have you left out all the "yun"s
in the poem?
What are you doing here?
I...
I know you haven't eaten for the whole day.
I came to ask you to go eat.
How did the character "yun"
annoy you?
Go away.
Jing Xuan.
Did she
really not eat for the whole day?
And when she was practicing calligraphy,
did she intentionally avoid the character "yun"?
Why do you look so happy?
She didn't let me tell Father anything.
I'm so worried.
Tell me once again.
Which poem was she writing over and over again?
"Ocean makes all other waters unworthy of the name,
after Wushan mountain, all other clouds
are mere puffballs above."
Don't worry.
I promise
that after telling her one sentence,
she'll recover immediately.
What sentence?
See you at five o'clock by Wangyou Lake.
That's it?
That's it.
You're in charge of telling her.
I'm in charge
of making a miracle happen.
This...
Be quick.
Be quick, be quick.
Yun Xiu.
Stop practicing.
Save your energy for meeting Mo Feng Yang
at five o'clock.
Did she finally ask me out?
Not yet.
But if you follow my instructions,
five o'clock
will be the moment that determines your fate.
Someone should stay away,
or our tactics will
lower his level.
You're here.
It looks like
he used your tactics
against you.
What do you mean?
Playing hard to get.
Intentionally giving you the cold shoulder.
Well.
Then
don't ever talk to me again.
After seeing the clouds of Wushan Mountain,
how can I still
look at other clouds?
[*This is a reference to the previous poem]
Sister, Sister.
My kite is coming down.
Please help me.
Okay.
Sister, you are great.
Is this higher?
It's time to reel it back.
It's you?
Don't move.
♪Another late autumn, another night,
the swallow has returned, when will you?♪
♪Should the yellowing red letters
be taken down or not♪
♪Hope makes it more heartbreaking♪
♪The wind blows, leaves fall on the window sill♪
♪Red brocade in the bronze mirror♪
♪The lonely Jiangnan is still noisy♪
♪And the light sigh from the deep boudoir♪
You idiot.
"Ocean makes all other waters unworthy of the name."
After meeting you,
all I have in my mind is you,
all I can draw is you,
all I can think about is you.
♪She longs eagerly day and night♪
Why do you always see me
at my most embarrassing moments?
You don't need to hide your fragility from me.
Everyone has
extravagant hope
in their hearts.
Mine is
in front of me now.
Therefore,
no matter how much the world has changed,
I won't let you go.
However,
if it's a natural moat,
you will be crushed into pieces if you fall.
Her Majesty has already passed an order
to encourage men to marry again,
and awards them perfume sachets as encouragement.
So, if we are on the same side,
we can overcome natural moats.
Give me three more days to think about it.
I'm always directing romantic plays for others.
My heart is broken into pieces.
Damn that Mo Lian Cheng.
It's good you still have a conscience.
Sad tears.
Twinkling eyes.
Looking scared.
Warmest heart.
Passion for my chest muscles.
These are a hundred reasons
why you attract me.
Let me see what else you wrote.
Before,
I was not romantic enough.
I promise
from now on,
I won't let you be jealous of
other people's relationships.
I forgive you
since
you like me touching your chest muscles.
However,
sometimes you misunderstand me too.
I just forgave you,
and you're at it again?
Okay, okay.
Which one is your favourite?
My favourite is the one
with the flowers.
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
(Unwavering heart)
Unwavering heart.
Ever since the time
Her Majesty punished you because of
the equal-rights movement,
I knew
I wanted to be
the only person who can protect you.
I also knew
you are always my Cheng Cheng.
No matter what your turn into,
I'll always accept you.
♪I resent that we act as if we are strangers♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
Your Majesty.
Information from Second Princess's
Residence indicates
that Second Princess wants to repudiate
Prince Consort,
and is trying to bring him and General Mo together.
How can Yun Xiu and Feng Yang
let her manipulate them?
According to my investigations,
before Prince Consort came to
marry Second Princess,
he had feelings for General Mo.
Therefore, Second Princess made an excuse
to ask General Mo to stay over at her residence
and created opportunities for them.
So...
She wants to overcome the scheme of disunity
and make generals from two countries work for her.
Your Majesty.
Does she think
I'll let her do whatever she wants?
Your Majesty.
Don't hurt yourself
because of anger.
Take me to the Altar of Souls.
But you are not in a stable condition,
I'm afraid...
Be quick.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
Be careful.
The Altar of Souls is still under construction.
You are not in a stable condition,
don't risk your body's limits.
Your Majesty.
Is it possible that the spiritual power
has backfired?
Your Majesty.
Right now,
someone must control
the Soul-guarding Bead with me
to wake Her Majesty up.
She
may be the only hope.
(Princess's Residence)
It has been a while, but she still hasn't responded.
Could she have gone back on her words?
No,
I can't just wait here.
I need to go talk to her
to understand her thoughts.
Too much concern is as bad as too little.
You need to trust her.
You need to give Feng Yang time to think.
We don't have the time.
Of course I trust Feng Yang,
I just don't know what I could do
if I keep waiting like this.
Don't worry.
You will become
an excellent chess player.
Official Xiao has arrived.
So all three of you are here.
Greetings.
Official Xiao, what are you
doing here?
Her Majesty issued an emergency order
to summon Second Princess to the palace.
Emergency order?
Do you know what for?
I do not.
Official Xiao, would you please
wait in the front hall?
Prince Consort,
show Official Xiao the way.
Second Princes, please be quick.
Oh, no.
Could it be that Her Majesty knows
that we want to bring
Yun Xiu and Feng Yang together?
Even if she has noticed,
she can't do anything to you
if she doesn't have evidence
and you deny it.
Reading your facial expression,
could there be
more serious issues?
I have a strange feeling.
Her Majesty intentionally led me to investigate
the Altar of Souls.
She must have noticed
that you have a special connection
with the Soul-guarding Bead.
This is such a grand scheme.
She wants us
to walk right into a trap ourselves.
Her Majesty will be inpatient
if Your Highness doesn't go soon.
Anyhow, keep in mind
that the Bogu Shelves in the imperial chamber
have a set of drawers.
Pushing the second one inward
can open the secret passage to the Altar of Souls.
If not out of absolute necessity,
don't get close to it and don't touch it.
Because
if you get close to the Soul-guarding Bead,
the bead will react.
Her Majesty will notice
and you will be in danger.
Okay.
I'll figure out Her Majesty's intentions.
Before that,
don't let her
get anything disadvantageous on you.
If not out of absolute necessity,
wait until
I come.
Okay.
Your Highness.
Let's go.
Does Her Majesty know about us?
Calm down.
I'll ask Feng Yang
if anyone has leaked information.
(Mo Residence)
Eighth Brother.
Didn't you say that I have three days
to think it through?
Her Majesty summoned Tan Er to the palace.
What is that for?
Xiao Zhen knew but didn't say anything.
I'll find out what's going on in the palace.
Oh, right.
When you enter the palace,
even if it's not for this matter,
you should act accordingly.
If Yun Xiu and I implicated her,
I will apologize to Her Majesty.
Wait.
Why are there no guards here?
Where is Her Majesty?
This way, Your Highness.
Isn't this the secret passage to the Altar of Souls?
Cheng Cheng reminded me not to get close to it.
What is
this place?
It's not good for you
to pretend like you don't know.
You can feel the strange movements
within the Soul-guarding Bead,
so can I.
What pig?
[*In Chinese, "pig" has the same pronunciation as "bead"]
Why can you
feel the pig moving?
You must know what I'm talking about.
Keep acting like an idiot
doesn't do good to either of us.
What are you doing?
If Her Majesty knows you threatened me
with a sword,
she must...
Her Majesty knows everything.
Go in.
Her Majesty wants to see me
inside here?
Your Highness, be quick.
Her Majesty is going to be impatient.
Can't Her Majesty change the location?
This is too dark.
If my claustrophobia gets triggered
halfway,
my heart would stop beating,
I would die.
Disobeying Her Majesty's order
is also punishable by death.
Then I have to face the challenge.
I can't be beaten by fear.
Go on.
General Mo, are you here to see Her Majesty?
Her Majesty is not in the royal study.
Thank you for reminding me, General Lu.
However,
you look concerned.
Is something
wrong?
I heard
that Her Majesty never left her imperial chamber
and she refused to meet with any officials.
I heard that Her Majesty
just summoned Second Princess to the palace.
On my way here,
I did see Xiao Zhen bringing Second Princess
to the imperial chamber.
The strange thing is
that the guards were suddenly changed
at the imperial chamber.
Not only were the unnecessary people cleared,
but more armed forces were also added.
Something may be going on.
There are a few questionable points.
Don't worry too much, General.
Maybe Her Majesty wants to discuss
some government affairs with Her Highness
and doesn't want others to interrupt.
If that's the case,
maybe I thought too much.
Thank you.
She seems a little different from usual.
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪A flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part,
no matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part♪
♪No matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind
in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪