=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 48=
Let me out!
Where’s Muguang?
I’ve governed the Immortal Realm
for sixty thousand years.
With the help of all immortals,
we have been in peace.
But I’m obsessive about fighting demons.
I started several wars against them
so that the Three Realms were in unrest.
I also connived the Heavenly Empress
to make big mistakes
which were beyond retrieval.
I’m too ashamed
to be the Heavenly Emperor.
I’d like to be a stone dragon,
separating immortals and demons forever
and always keeping the world safe.
The Queen of Phoenix Fengran
is fair and impartial.
She’s the best person for the throne.
Hope you’ll assist her wholeheartedly
and protect the Three Realms forever.
(Fuyao Hall)
Jingyang.
Jingzhao.
Jingyang,
Father and Jingjian died.
Only we three are alive.
Are you really leaving
the Heavenly Palace?
What will Mother and I do?
Leave the Heavenly Palace?
No. You can’t leave.
Your father is dead.
If you leave,
Fengran will take the throne.
I won’t let you leave.
Mother,
I made too many mistakes.
I’m too ashamed
to be the Heavenly Emperor.
I’m the Heavenly Empress.
You’re my son.
If you’re not qualified, who else is?
If I had a choice,
I would rather be Father’s son
and Jingjian’s elder brother.
But I don’t want to be your son.
Jingyang!
I care for the Heavenly Palace.
I’ve done everything,
simply to keep our family safe.
What have I done wrong?
To keep our family safe?
When will you stop deceiving yourself?
It’s because you made so many mistakes
that our family broke.
Everyone else can complain about me,
but you can’t!
I brought you up.
Mother,
I came to say goodbye to you.
Goddess Shanggu punished me
to go to the Human Realm,
develop it with all my power
and help people in distress
to make compensations for my sins.
Immortals and devils go different ways.
I’m afraid
you and I won’t meet again.
This is where we part ways.
Jingyang,
don’t leave.
Son.
Son!
Mother.
Son,
come back!
You’re satisfied now?
My family is ruined
and I can’t fight back at all.
You finally avenged yourself
for being questioned in public
and being fooled.
Master, please let go of my mother!
Muguang is dead.
Wu Huan, do you regret it now?
Without you,
how would he be dead?
If someone has to regret,
it should be you!
I indeed regret.
I don’t like to recall the past
or admit my fault.
But I regret taking you back
to the Pilgrimage Hall
sixty thousand years ago.
Kill me if you want.
Don’t bother to nag.
You punish me on
the Green Dragon Platform,
simply because you want me
to be humiliated
in front of all immortals.
Where are they?
Show them how cruel you are.
Don’t bother.
I won’t let them come,
for Muguang’s sake.
I won’t be grateful.
Wu Huan, even if you die,
you can’t atone for your crime.
But Muguang is innocent.
Yuemi is innocent.
Jingjian is innocent.
I won’t put you in prison
in the Nether World
or totally crush your soul.
You had your sins,
because I brought you back.
I should put an end to it.
Mother. Mother!
Mother!
You have no God power now.
I’ve taken back your bloodline
of the Feng Clan.
From this day, you won’t get old or die.
You’re not a human, demon,
immortal or devil.
You’ll suffer all kinds of illnesses,
but never have a reincarnation.
You’ll be lonely forever.
Goddess Shanggu,
you’re loved and respected.
How can you be so heartless?
I curse you.
I curse you never
to get the man you love
so that you also live forever
and be lonely forever!
Jingjian,
I swear to heaven.
As long as I’m alive,
the Echo Drum won’t ring.
The peace between immortals
and demons is his lifelong wish.
Hope you’ll keep your promise.
Jingjian, if the crack on the drum
can’t be fixed,
I’ll kill myself and apologize to you.
I’m going back to the God Realm.
The Immortal Realm is in chaos.
I can’t be relieved
unless I leave it to you.
Master,
I can only fight,
but don’t know how to govern it.
I’m afraid I’ll let you down.
You’re very clear
about what is right or wrong.
When you always follow your heart,
you won’t make a big mistake.
But the responsibility is heavy.
I just want to stay here
and be his company.
Immortals and demons
have deep resentments.
If we want to eliminate
their misunderstandings and prejudices,
we need more than Sen Yu.
Like you said,
it’s Jingjian’s lifelong wish.
I promise you.
If immortals and demons
get back in peace again,
you can quit as you wish.
(Tomb of Immortal Jingjian)
You knew I would come?
Who else would come to me?
Take Shanggu back as early as possible.
I’ve put all spiritual power of the Dome
in Taicang Spear.
With the power of you and Shanggu,
you will be able to open the God Realm.
When Yuanqi knows,
he’ll lose his temper.
You were its master.
Even sixty thousand years ago.
Hongri?
After we leave,
you will be lonely.
Let Hongri stay with you.
What?
Nothing to say?
Say hello to Zhiyang when you see him.
When will you go?
Soon.
Before we leave,
spend more time with Yuanqi.
In this life,
you should feel the sorriest for him.
Yuanqi is naughty.
In the past hundred years,
you had hard work taking care of him.
It was a nice job, in fact.
I quite like your son’s temper.
He isn’t
like you at all.
But look at you.
From time to time,
you disguised yourself as Fengran
and played with him secretly.
What? Isn’t it trouble?
If you turn up in front of him
as his father,
do you not know what to say
and fear that he can’t accept you?
I have a good idea
to help you out.
Go on.
Yuanqi loves magic weapons.
He always wants
his exclusive weapon.
For this,
he’s haunting me for nearly ten years.
When he wanted a weapon,
you could have made one for him.
Why didn’t you satisfy him?
It’s a nice job.
I’d like to leave it to you.
When Yuanqi had his first tooth,
walked for the first time,
and said the first word,
I witnessed them for you.
As for his first magic weapon,
it’s better that
you make it for him.
What do you think?
Isn’t it a good idea?
Yuanqi, what are you doing?
Fengran has become the Heavenly Queen.
I’m catching some fish for her.
Yuanqi,
didn’t you say
you wanted to marry Fengran
when you grew up?
Fish isn’t enough.
Besides,
it’s not the way to catch fish.
Let me teach you.
Uncle Tianqi,
why did you let him in?
Leave.
I don’t welcome you.
Yuanqi,
have you heard that
Wu Huan has been severely punished?
It got about in the Three Realms.
What does it concern him?
It’s time to tell you something.
What is it?
(Always Acquire New Knowledge)
Yuanqi, when you were born,
Wu Huan had become a devil
and was hurting people.
I was badly wounded
and I had no evidence.
I didn’t dare to take rash action.
Also, I feared more that
you and your mother
would be implicated.
After thinking carefully,
I didn’t recognize you.
But in the past hundred years,
I studied carefully
and cultivated myself hard.
At last, a couple of days ago,
I revealed Wu Huan’s sins.
Who are you fooling?
It’s not what my mother said.
What did your mother say?
She said
you didn’t deserve us.
Yeah.
I don’t deserve you.
Don’t try to fool me.
I’ve grown up.
I can tell right from wrong.
Yuanqi,
what your father said is true.
I can be his witness.
I still don’t believe him.
Unless...
Unless Fengran can be his witness, too.
Why do you want her?
Because she’s the Heavenly Queen.
I’m even a True God.
I don’t care.
I just trust her.
I even changed your nappies.
Why don’t you trust me?
Fengran often took me
to the lower realm for fun.
I believe whatever she says.
Come on.
All right.
Ask Fengran in a couple of days
whether I tell you the truth.
Yuanqi,
you can’t tell many things
only with your eyes.
I trust my eyes.
Yeah, no matter what reason I have,
I’ve been feeling guilty for you.
You’ve grown up.
I didn’t come today,
to ask for your pardon,
but to have a word with you
about what adults should think over.
Over what?
Death.
Death?
Have you learned
about death?
Uncle Tianqi said
Jingjian was gone.
Does that mean he’s dead?
When someone’s sense disappears
and his body collapses,
he’s gone and dead.
After he is dead,
nothing will be left.
Will I die, too?
Everybody has his fate.
Everybody dies.
But I don’t want to die.
I also don’t want anyone I know to die.
Death isn’t horrible.
Watching anyone you know die
isn’t horrible, either.
Death is destined,
like the blooming and fading of flowers.
No one can change his fate.
When Jingjian died,
Fengran was weeping all the time.
But as time goes by
year after year,
she won’t feel as hurt as before.
Will Jingjian feel hurt?
He won’t, of course.
Because he died for who he loved
and for the whole world.
It’s a happy thing.
He won’t feel hurt.
Hungry?
Let me take you somewhere.
Where?
The Human Realm.
Let’s go.
Sir.
Toys. Funny toys.
Small pendants.
Delicious sugar-coated haws.
Funny toys.
Come and have a look.
Here they are.
Gentlemen,
your dishes are ready. Enjoy yourselves.
How do you know my favorite dishes?
I’m your father and I know you.
I haven’t recognized you yet.
Have you read books today?
I read the Classic of Mountains and Seas.
But I remember you read it
a hundred years ago.
Fengran said
such an ancient book was obscure
and hard to understand.
I need to work hard on it.
Then I read it many more times.
Let me test you, then.
Come on.
Forget it.
We shouldn’t talk
when eating and sleeping.
Test me as you wish.
I can reel off that book.
After having the meal,
shall we gamble
and fly the kite?
You can gamble?
Sure.
Your mother loves it
and I learned to play it.
You must be poor at it.
I taught you how to play.
Liar.
Fengran taught me that.
Compete with me.
What punishment?
Old rule. Stickers on the loser’s face.
How do you know the rule
between Fengran and me?
She told me.
I asked Fengran many times.
She said she didn’t teach you to gamble,
fly the kite,
or fight for you.
She just didn’t admit it.
Anyway, I’m not lying.
Today, you aren’t as annoying
as you were.
Let’s take a rest here.
All right.
I won again.
You’re awesome, Yuanqi.
I give in.
I won several times in a row.
Your face is too full for more stickers.
What punishment
do you want then?
You’ll do whatever I want?
Yes, bet is bet.
The other day,
Fengran took me off the mountain
and we met Xiaoba from Flower Demons.
He was holding a dagger.
A magic weapon for cultivation!
I want a magic weapon.
It should have matchless power.
Why did you give me a peach wood sword?
What is it made of?
It’s an ordinary peach wood sword.
Ordinary?
Then why is it so powerful?
It has half of my power in it.
No other weapon can be better than it.
Do you like it?
Xiaoba will envy me in return.
When you have a master,
cultivate yourself with this sword.
It’ll help you be a god soon.
Thank you, Fa...
One more thing.
Don’t hurt people without a reason.
I understand.
You put half of your power
in the sword.
If you meet a bad person
like Wu Huan again,
will you not defeat her?
I can handle that.
When I have it,
I can fight with you
shoulder to shoulder.
If you’re in trouble again,
come to me in Qingchi Palace.
Yuanqi, you know what?
You were born with the Power of Chaos.
Unless something goes wrong,
you’ll be the Chief God.
In the future,
you should mostly count on yourself.
Remember, never stop learning
and always be diligent.
Did you really not recognize me
because you didn’t want Mother or me
to be involved in trouble?
Right.
All right. I trust you.
Shouldn’t you call me
Father?
You’re a young man now.
You must protect your mother
and don’t let anyone bully her.
I will protect her.
Let me give you something.
What’s this?
Don’t open it
before I leave.
Where are you going again?
I’m going to travel around the world.
You’re leaving me again?
Uncle Tianqi will explain to you.
How soon will you come back?
Remember what I just told you.
Which do you mean?
Your mother is still mad at me.
What happened today...
Let’s not tell her, all right?
I’m leaving, then.
Father.
When you come back,
bring me some magic weapons.
Will you?
Father,
why don’t you answer me?
♪She turned into ashes♪
I will.
Father, I’ll be waiting for you.
♪Perseverance♪
♪It’s still echoing in ears♪
♪Repeat it again♪
Father has changed his temper.
It’s great.
On the tenth day of the ninth month
in year 60569
of the post ancient calendar,
the Chief God returned.
The Three Realms come back in peace.
- Welcome Chief God.
Mother, the house is made of jade
and the stairs are made of glaze.
This place is full of treasures.
Let’s go to the Heaven and Earth Platform.
In the past sixty thousand years,
it was them
who didn’t disappear
or die.
They exhausted their god power
to maintain the God Realm silently.
They were waiting until we came back.
But no one told them
when we would come back.
Zhiyang,
we’re back.
Shanggu,
will you really not let Bai Jue
come back to the God Realm?
I said that
I wouldn’t see him ever again.
Why can I wish him to be back?
You mean you wished?
Yuemi’s birthday is coming.
Why are you still here?
Yuemi’s birthday?
I’m having a dream again.
What are you waiting for? Come.
I seldom have a dream.
I can’t wake up so quickly.
Or it’ll be wasted.
Shanggu,
take good care of yourself.
Don’t think of me
or dream about me again.
I don’t often dream about you.
Just sometimes...
Don’t open your eyes.
Let me have a good look at you.
♪Large memories are for you♪
♪Engraved in the palm♪
I love you.
♪Countless twists and turns♪
Farewell.
♪Drifting away for many times♪
♪I can’t help missing you
But I can only hug your back♪
♪Love never changes♪
♪Write down our whispers♪
♪In the name of the world
Protect a heart♪
♪If love finally♪
♪Becomes ashes♪
♪I will be the shadow in your eyes♪
♪I’m willing to♪
♪Look for you at thousands of
days and nights♪
♪Wait until we meet again♪
♪Exchange a one-second encounter
for a lifetime♪
♪It’s not a pity
if we can meet each other♪
♪I am willing to indulge in the past♪
♪When tears dizzy the smile♪
♪How much luck do I need♪
♪To get myself♪
♪Be always stuck♪
What?
You’ll practice the Power of Chaos?
Precisely.
The Tribulation of Chaos
is aimed at Shanggu.
It can’t be handled
without the Power of Chaos.
After she left,
I found a clue from the Deicide Flower.
When I trawled through all books,
I finally realized that
I couldn’t get the Power of Chaos
unless I mixed the immortal power
with the demon power.
But the two kinds of power
repel each other.
How can you mix them?
It’s too risky.
My Power of the Original Being
is the immortal power.
All I need to do
is to split my Original Being
and let the other half
cultivate the demon power.
Then I’ll mix them.
♪If love finally♪
♪Becomes ashes♪
♪I will be the shadow in your eyes♪
Gu Jun,
Shanggu died once in front of me.
I won’t let it happen
ever again.
If she knows
the Tribulation of Chaos
hasn’t disappeared,
what do you think she will do?
♪How much luck do I need♪
♪To get myself♪
♪Be always stuck♪
♪In your heart♪
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪