=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 47=
Look.
Why do the devils
have the Demon Gathering Streamer?
Even the Demon Gathering Streamer
was taken away.
I’m too ashamed to live.
Sen Yu!
You’re the Demon King.
At this moment, you must be determined.
Under such circumstances,
we can’t stop the war,
unless we do the dismemberment.
Master, after sixty thousand years,
I never expected you
to be still so powerful.
You’re the Heavenly Empress
and a goddess.
But you became a devil?
Wu Huan, you really let me down.
You should’ve been dead in the Tribulation
sixty thousand years ago.
You let me down, too.
Sixty thousand years ago?
Dead in the Tribulation?
Wu Huan,
you deliberately started the war
in the Demon Region?
It’s wise of you.
But however wise you are,
you never expected
to be killed by me,
your humblest maid
in the Pilgrimage Hall.
Taicang Spear?
What did you do to Bai Jue?
In such a cruel world,
how will I let Bai Jue live?
Devilish Energy?
Your Highness,
Overlord asked you to leave
and keep yourself safe.
Fengnyu?
Mother?
Why does Fengnyu
have so much devil power?
My mother must have given it to her.
My mother
is the new Overlord in the Nether World.
Fengran,
guard the formation for me.
I don’t care what reason you had
or why you became a devil,
for public and private purposes,
I can’t let you live.
You don’t have to say this
before you defeat me.
Give up.
Then you don’t need to be tortured.
Your power
is far less than mine.
There’s justice in the world.
Evil can never prevail over good.
Why can you represent justice?
Why can you represent the good?
Why can’t low phoenixes
control their own lives?
Why can’t I be the lord of the world?
I’m not convinced!
Bai Jue?
From this day on,
I’m the lord of the Three Realms!
You’re still alive?
You can’t be!
I killed you in person.
There’s no way you’re still alive!
Tianqi?
You...
I can not only hold my liquor,
but have also improved in acting.
Didn’t I just pretend to be dead?
Now that you prepared the wine
to fake my death,
why didn’t you prepare
a set of armor for me?
Wu Huan is cunning.
If she suspected you,
you would have been dead.
Ice Cube,
since you woke up,
you’ve been doing annoying things.
It hurts!
Now Wu Huan has been unmasked.
After dealing with her,
I can leave without concern.
The formation can only last for a while.
Unless the Demon Gathering Streamer falls,
they’ll break into the Demon Region
sooner or later.
What will you do?
I’ll protect immortals.
I’ll protect you, too.
How dare you!
Fengran,
don’t blame me.
Jingjian!
Don’t!
My mother started this.
I should pay for it.
If you dare,
I’ll kill Wu Huan in person
to avenge my parents!
I will totally forget you
and never think of you again!
Fengran,
I’ll leave the Immortal Realm
to you.
Don’t!
Don’t, Jingjian!
♪Write down our whispers♪
Don’t!
♪In the name of the world
Protect a heart♪
♪If love finally♪
♪Becomes ashes♪
♪I will be the shadow in your eyes♪
♪I’m willing to♪
Jingjian!
♪Look for you at thousands of
days and nights♪
♪Wait until we meet again♪
No!
♪Exchange a one-second encounter
for a lifetime♪
No!
♪I’m willing to♪
♪Look for you at thousands of
days and nights♪
♪Wait until we meet again♪
No.
♪Exchange a one-second encounter
for a lifetime♪
♪It’s not a pity
if we can meet each other♪
♪I am willing to indulge in the past♪
Miss, you saved me?
Or who else?
This is the phoenix feather.
My grandpa used it
to send messages to me.
I’m going home.
Miss.
♪Be always stuck♪
♪In your heart♪
♪Pursue you♪
♪For millions of miles♪
No wonder
whenever I was in danger,
you turned up.
Without Zhiyang,
you think you can stop me?
Zhiyang isn’t here, so what?
If I hadn’t been badly wounded
with damaged power,
when I woke up,
I would have killed you long ago.
Wu Huan,
what is good?
What is evil?
And what is justice?
I don’t need to explain, do I?
I lost, so what?
If I guess correctly,
you came back to life,
because of the Tribulation.
Bai Jue,
you had a careful plan.
You really think this will bring
the least harm to her?
Shut up!
After she knows the truth,
what you have done
will haunt her like Devilish Energy
and torture her.
Then she’ll regret all her life.
When someone is heartbroken,
the longer she lives,
the more she suffers.
What’s she talking about?
Flame of Queen of Phoenix?
Fengran is in trouble.
I beg you, Master.
Save him, please.
He used the dismemberment.
Since ancient times,
if immortals or demons use it,
they will lose their souls
and can’t have the reincarnation.
Even I...
I can’t help.
In the Three Realms,
I can’t find him anymore.
Jingjian.
Jingjian!
It’s you!
You killed him!
You hate me for taking away your throne.
So, you killed my son!
Jingjian.
Wu Huan,
no one killed Jingjian,
but you.
Master.
Master,
I beg you!
I beg you to save him!
You used to care for me most,
didn’t you?
I will take any punishment.
I beg you.
Please save my son!
Save him!
Jingjian.
Even Shanggu
can’t bring a man back to life
when his soul is gone.
It’s been sixty thousand years.
Time to reveal the truth
to the Three Realms.
All immortals are here
and the Heavenly Emperor has come.
What’s your point?
Wu Huan,
tell me.
During the Destruction Formation
in the Abyssal Ridge Swamp,
how did Yuemi die?
Yuemi...
She is dead?
Isn’t she sleeping in the God Realm?
Right.
I killed Yuemi.
Everybody says that
True Gods are incomparably wise
and powerful.
But over the past sixty thousand years,
I still managed to deceive you,
made Tianqi an enemy of the Three Realms
and let you four fight each other.
Your Grace,
you’re finally awake.
Who are you?
I’m Wu Huan,
from the Feng Clan.
Wu Huan,
for the coming thousand years,
do you want to be my Divine Beast
and go back to the God Realm with me?
I...
I do.
Wu Huan,
you’re my Divine Beast now.
Now that you’re in my hall,
you’re one of us.
Don’t bother how you were bullied
in the Feng Clan.
Cultivate yourself carefully
and impress those bad men.
Isn’t it great?
Yes, Your Grace.
You little phoenix,
shortly after you came,
you’re getting bold
and you dare to mock me.
I don’t dare.
By then, our Pilgrimage Hall
will be the strongest
in the God Realm for real.
Your Grace,
cultivate yourself carefully.
I’ll take care of the Pilgrimage Hall
so that you and Gu Jun
won’t be distracted.
I brought you back
to the Pilgrimage Hall.
When I was in the Nether World,
Yuemi taught you carefully
for a thousand years.
How did you have the heart to kill her?
Right.
You took me back
to the Pilgrimage Hall, so what?
In your eyes,
I was always a substitute for Feng Yan.
In Yuemi’s eyes,
I was always imperfect!
She even advised you to wait
for the return of the Queen of Phoenix.
Forget it.
What’s done is done.
I didn’t let it go at that time.
After sixty thousand years,
I no longer care.
The winner takes all.
I’ll take the punishment.
Shanggu knew
Wuxi and Feng Yan lived in seclusion.
She also gave Feng Yan’s fake spirit
to Elder Feng Yun.
What did you say?
Since she took you
to the Pilgrimage Hall,
she had never wanted you
to be replaced.
That’s not true.
That’s not true!
Three-head,
what on earth did Wu Huan do?
Tell everybody about it.
Master,
in the past years,
Wu Huan started all the wars
between immortals and demons
for her selfish motives,
because she wanted
to cultivate her devil power
with the evil force in the war.
Father.
Wu Huan, do you admit your guilt?
Wu Huan, you killed gods
and cultivated devil power.
You started wars for selfish motives.
You’re too wicked to be pardoned.
In three days,
I’ll execute you personally
on Green Dragon Platform
to stem everyone’s anger.
I’m too wicked to be pardoned?
Yes. I’m too wicked.
I deserve to be killed. What about you?
Who will convict you?
As the Chief God of Chaos,
you stole the Spirit Gathering Bead,
the Ghost Suppressing Tower
and the Demon Gathering Streamer.
You ignored the Three Realms
for selfish motives.
Now that you punish people
on behalf of the heaven,
why don’t you punish yourself?
Shut up!
Let her continue.
You keep the secret from everyone.
Others dare not say it.
But I dare.
Shanggu,
you think you’re superior
and you’re the Chief God.
Funny.
Everyone else knows something, but you.
You were discarded
by the man closest to you.
You’re a goddess, so what?
You’re the Chief God, so what?
You’re the biggest joke
in the Three Realms!
Even poorer than me.
How dare you!
Master!
Even if you kill me,
you can’t change her fate.
Wu Huan,
this is what you accuse me of?
The Spirit Gathering Bead,
the Ghost Suppressing Tower
and the Demon Gathering Streamer
were generated from my Power of Chaos.
These three things
belong to me.
When I wanted
such three weapons,
I didn’t need to steal them.
I’m afraid you’ve been away
from the God Realm for too long
and you’ve forgotten everything.
About anything else,
whether I know it
or I don’t,
you have no right to judge.
I’m now imprisoning you in Fuyao Hall.
Muguang,
you’ve been her husband
for sixty thousand years.
I’ll keep her alive for three days
for your sake.
Thank you, Master.
Everybody, leave,
except True God Bai Jue.
Shanggu.
Why did I lose my memories?
As the Chief God,
I wasn’t sick or hurt.
But I was asleep for as long
as sixty thousand years.
After I woke up,
even Wu Huan and Jingzhao
dare to judge me.
They mocked and humiliated me
with their ignorance.
Wu Huan didn’t mean you,
but Houchi.
Don’t take it to your heart.
I almost knew about Houchi.
She was hurt because of you.
Her families and lover died
because of you.
You hurt her so much.
But now you’re sitting here
and not feeling guilty.
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
You’re right.
It’s my fault.
I don’t deserve to be the True God.
I wish
I wouldn’t go back to the God Realm.
♪Memories last♪
You mean it?
Yes.
Very well.
♪And I keep staying♪
I’ll go back to the God Realm.
But never will you.
Before I leave,
give back my memories.
All over the world,
I can’t think of a second person
who could take away my memories.
What are you keeping from me?
You want your memories.
But I don’t have them.
I don’t know
what you’re talking about, either.
You don’t know what I’m talking about?
I don’t think you want to see me again.
I’ll make your wish come true.
Bai Jue.
I swear to the Ancestral God.
In my life,
I won’t love you
or hate you.
We’ll be strangers
and never meet again.
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past♪
♪When we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds♪
♪And rain drops♪
♪When everything♪
♪Works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪
Shanggu.
Tianqi,
I really don’t understand.
Why did Bai Jue owe so much?
Everybody has his confusion.
Bai Jue told me
it was his fault about Houchi.
Wu Huan said
I should have submitted to fate
sixty thousand years ago.
What on earth happened
after I left the Nether World?
Where are my memories?
Everybody has loss of memories, too.
What exactly is
the Tribulation of Chaos?
Shanggu,
I didn’t experience it.
I’m not sure.
Bai Jue is so cruel to me.
Even now,
I don’t want to believe it.
Does he have some reason?
What on earth are you keeping from me?
When something is unfinished,
leave it there.
Tianqi,
I’m exhausted.
Let’s go back home.
All right.
Qin,
tell me the truth.
Am I too cowardly
and self-righteous?
What do you think, Your Majesty?
Stop calling me Your Majesty.
I feel ashamed.
During the war in the Demon Region,
I was sorry for Jingjian,
for the late king,
and for the demons.
Qin,
you were right to reject me that day.
I’m not good enough for you.
Your Majesty, you’re young.
You’ve got a long way to go.
Take your time.
I’ll take my time.
In the God Realm
when I first saw you,
it was just like now.
You were wearing the uniform
of the Pilgrimage Hall.
You looked so proud
and outstanding.
At that time, I never expected you
to be the one
who I spent my life with.
In the old years,
thank you for choosing me.
It’s been sixty thousand years.
In all these years,
you lived with me.
We also have Jingyang,
Jingjian
and Jingzhao.
I’m satisfied.
Huan,
I should have told you.
I don’t love
the most honorable Heavenly Empress
after the God Realm is sealed,
but the old Wu Huan
who could be happy all day
because Goddess Shanggu praised her.
What’s the point of saying this?
In three days,
I’ll die.
In the God Realm
or in the Heavenly Palace,
I’ve done nothing wrong.
The fate is wrong.
And the world is wrong.
Huan,
may I hug you one more time?
no matter you’re right or wrong,
you’re always my wife
and the mother of my children.
So, you already knew
what Wu Huan did?
Please understand it, Master.
For my selfish motives,
I...
Under such circumstances,
you still want
to take the blame for her?
Is this what Yuemi taught you?
Wu Huan made a huge mistake.
I just want to beg you
to keep her alive.
You really don’t respect me at all.
If I don’t keep her alive,
I’ll be wrong?
Muguang,
Wu Huan has been married with you
for sixty thousand years.
She had children for you
and accompanied you.
It’s alright when you defend her.
But have you thought about it?
In these years, she’s been honorable
with the supreme glory.
But your master Yuemi
has been sealed in the stone statue
by the Swamp
and has never been let out
or rested in peace.
Goddess Yuemi had
great expectations for you.
She made you the Star Messenger
when you first came to the God Realm.
So did Zhiyang.
Before the God Realm was closed,
he entrusted you with the lower realm.
But what did you do?
You really let us down.
In my life,
I’ve been too indecisive
and made a big mistake.
At last, I can do something
I should have done
sixty thousand years ago.
Let me out!
Where’s Muguang?
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪