Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ No longer panicking on the night of the blackout ♫
♫ You're by my side, illuminating a beam of light for me ♫
♫ Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet ♫
♫ Your breath brushes up against my cheek ♫
♫ With you warming up the stage,
happiness never comes to a close ♫
♫ Boring jokes add some sweetness to the dinner ♫
♫ Daily life is even more like a comic than comics themselves ♫
♫ Happiness and sadness ♫
♫ Make up the moments of life ♫
♫ Rainy days become very special because of you ♫
♫ Picked up a pitiful youngster off the street ♫
♫ No matter when and where, you always appear ♫
♫ Holding me tightly and spinning in circles ♫
♫ Rainy days make me so nostalgic because of you ♫
♫ Becoming some part of the memories ♫
♫ Walking down a street with lights lighting up
one after another ♫
♫ Warming up the whole world ♫
[Please Feel at Ease Mr. Ling]
[Episode 10]
I, Ling Yue, promise to rent this house
to Miss Gu Anxin.
To never raise the rent; never to sell.
If the terms of the contract are violated,
all of the rights to the house will be lost
and the house will be returned to Miss Anxin.
Aren't the terms of this contract unfair to you?
I'm the landlord. You're paying me rent. It's very fair.
It's like payment of an IOU for taking advantage of you in the beginning.
Now it's your turn.
Thank you.
This is where our feelings for one another began.
Now, is when our feelings can grow.
We can become closer and closer and never be separated again.
Let's go home.
Wait.
We are official sweethearts now. A good-night kiss isn't going too far.
You should go home and get some rest.
Then, tomorrow, I'll come pick you up.  Good night.
Good night.
Wait a second.
Good night, brother-in-law.
Who's his brother-in-law?
Come on; let's go home.
Come on.
- He hugged me.
- He likes you.
Brother, don't be mad.
Have some Wiexun.
What's between you and Ling Yue?
You can so easily agree to be with him?
It's...it's a feeling.
You really have fallen in love with him.
Brother, I heard...
You Your told me what happened yesterday.
Yesterday, maybe she was....a little...nervous.
Don't use You You to change the subject.
Exactly what is going on between you and Ling Yue.
It's exactly what you saw.
No, Brother. Ling Yue and his family are all good people.
Other than that...brother....Ling Fang
All the others are great.
With one meeting you already know they're a good family?
Seeing this, I can see you've fallen deep into a pit.
If you really like him that much,
I'm willing to let you two give it a try.
But you have agree to one condition.
If he mistreats you, you must tell me.
No matter what, you can't let anyone make you suffer.
I understand.
i just knew you were the best.
Where's your bracelet?
When I was leaving, I put it back in the box.
You should wear it. If you do, I'll feel more at ease.
It doesn't matter. These days, I rarely have nightmares.
Really?
You've worn it for so many years;
one day, suddenly you don't need it anymore.
- What?
- Nothing.
Oh, by the way, I have one more thing to tell you.
I'm getting ready to move back to Yangmei Lane.
-Was...wasn't that apartment sold?
- -Yes, it was.
But the owner of the house is still planning to rent it out.
So I'm not being pushed out. I just met him.
If this new landlord pushes you out just like the last one, what will you do then?
He won't.
I signed a very special contract with this homeowner.
He won't turn me out. Don't worry.
You just moved in and now you're you're leaving.
Do you really like the place that much?
That place isn't as nice as yours,
nor as comfortable.
But, I really have gotten used to it.
Besides, there...I have some very, very, very precious memories.
Brother, I'm just moving houses.
You don't need to treat it like we will never see each other again.
You can come see me whenever you feel like it.
And I can come over here to see you often.
But, I've grown up.
I can't always live at your house.
You can always live at my house.
Okay, okay.
Whenever you want to move, I'll help you.
Hello; I'm here to help Miss Anxin move houses.
Ai Li, I've caused you a lot of trouble today. Thank you so much.
It's nothing. It's my job.
President Ling planned to come personally today,
but suddenly, he had to go to a meeting. So...
Hadn't we agreed to do this move tomorrow. Why do it this suddenly?
It's almost like he's a little narrow-minded; of two minds.
Moving back sooner is because President Ling is on tenterhooks and wanted to get it done as soon as possible.
Then, I'll be going.
Be careful.
- Drive carefully.
- You don't need to see me off.
That's it for today's meeting.
If you don't have anything to add, we can end it.
What, Anxin?
Manager, I have a...
an idea that isn't fully formed that I'd like to get everyone's opinion about.
Fine, then let's look at it together.
Okay; I'll hold everyone up a few more minutes.
I'd like to make a story about 9-headed bird [a fabulous bird which used to be regarded as a bad omen] who enters the human world.
My inspiration comes from the 9 headed bird character in the Chinese "Classic of Mountains and Rivers".
"Classic of Mountains and Rivers"; the phoenix.
Because I think something can be combined with this traditional two-dimensional myth.
It can be stretched into new, modern circumstances.
I think we could try it out.
These are some new characters I've imagined.
There are also some broad idea outlines.
It doesn't seem like this style of drawing suits our company's audience.
That's true, but I think we could
try out Anxin's idea.
But, the audience for this kind of idea is very narrow.
Besides that, it doesn't really conform to the taste of today's youth.
Have you done marketing research?
Of course not. There's nothing in this sector.
Besides, these kinds of demonstration sketches are too crude.
Our company has indeed not used this kind of idea before.
But this theme is quite original.
It's not that we couldn't do it.
How about this. Anxin, right now,
come up with 10 more and we'll look at the results.
Can you do that?
I'd like to try it.
Ling Yue!
I have to work overtime today. You should go home.
Why do you have to work overtime again? Did your boss arrange more work for you?
No. I haven't finished the work I was supposed to do.
Then, how late will you be working?
I think it could be an all-nighter.
Don't wait for me. If you're down here waiting for me, I won't be able to focus on my work.
A young girl working until daybreak isn't safe.
It's fine. Our company's security is great.
What's great about it?  I can't see even one security officer.
Enough; you don't need to hang around. Go on back.
I'll wait for you to go in.
- Bye-bye.
Why are you still here?  You didn't wait here all night, did you?
How could I do that?  Do I have that much free time?
Get in.
Here, eat some breakfast.
Have you eaten?
Eat it all.
I have to eat quickly. I have to go back when I finish eating.
You have to go back to work?
You can't sleep a little while?
How could I sleep?
I have a blanket in the car; sleep awhile.
You said you didn't wait for me. If you weren't waiting for me, where did this blanket come from?
You haven't realized who I am.
I am the best boyfriend.
My boyfriend is very cute.
I haven't brushed my teeth.
It's fine. I haven't brushed my teeth either.
Gu Anxin. Why should you be so happy?
Gu Anxin, you can do this.
Don't panic.
[ranking list]
I saw it. I can't believe Anxin is that awesome.
She just released number 19 and it's already at the top of the rankings online.
First time in history.
What? You can't even tell?
It's obvious that she brought it.
She brought it so that she can be ranked first?
No way! Normal people don't have the ability.
Of course normal people don't have the ability.
The rumors are true?
I heard the Boss reporting to the President of New Way today.
The numbers weren't even that high.
I didn't expect
that Anxin had such a backup.
What do you think then?
How did a rookie like her that doesn't know anything join our company then?
There's so many artists that couldn't even join.
She is a bit greedy.
but she insisted in wanting to be ranked first on the website.
I'm sorry for taking up your time.
Even though I'm a rookie, I won't buy numbers.
I will go investigate on this.
I'm sorry.
Hello, if you don't have an ID then you may not enter.
Then please help me notify that I'm looking for your President Ling.
Please give me your ID.
Anxin?
You came just in time. Do you have an ID? They're not letting me enter.
I don't need it. I use my face.
What's going on with you two?
This is your future Lady Boss of New Way.
It's all his fault!
I told you to let the Lady Boss go in.
- When did you say that?
- What about it?
What did I do?
Let's talk alone.
You two may leave first.
What did you come? Did you miss me?
It's not convenient to say some things over the phone.
What words?
Was it your arrangement for me to join Jiang Group?
You already know?
the numbers were brought by you, right?
Yes.
I actually thought
as long as I keep trying
even if its slow or even slower,
I will eventually become a talented mangaka
using my own abilities,
but why did you let all this happen so quickly?
I'm not qualified to have all this yet.
I'm sorry.
I didn't hide it from you on purpose.
I just wanted you to focus on what you liked.
Even without me, you can use your abilities to join Jiang Group.
It's like your the cloud that helped me up to the sky.
The higher I fly, the higher I'll fall from. Don't you understand this logic?
Compared to secretly drawing at home
Going to an honorable company to do what you like
isn't this killing two birds with one stone?
Honorable?
So you think...
getting a job that others never thought of and without having to do anything is considered honorable?
Besides, I never thought that secretly drawing mangas at home was never considered not honorable.
Is this embarrassing? Is it?
What you called honorable
ignored all my efforts.
That's right.
In your world,
you can even use feelings as a bargain chip for the stocks.
One thing is one thing. How is this related to the stocks?
I did all this for your own good.
Is it necessary for you to be so mad at me?
You think its not necessary, right?
Let's separate and calm down for some time.
Let's talk about other things later.
No, we can't separate. Not even a minute not a second.
I already said what needs to be said.
Can we talk it out?
Let's make things clear.
I already made it very clear.
You're the one who can't understand me.
Are you trying to detain me here?
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm fine.
As long as you're fine.
I'll sit with you then.
It'll be find in a few days.
What right do you have to still come here?
I'm still Anxin's boyfriend. How do I not have the right?
You still dare to say that.
As her boyfriend, you let Anxin be this upset?
This is our issue.
What does it have to do with you?
Since I was young,
Anxin's issues are considered mines.
She's being upset over someone that's not worth it. I won't allow that to happen.
Then what do you want to do?
I will protect her.
If you can't give her happiness, then get lost.
Amazing!
The higher I fly, the higher I'll fall down. Don't you understand this logic?
What you called honorable ignored all my efforts.
- Amazing!
- You're so noisy!
God, please continue.
- Don't you need to go to school?
- It's the weekend today.
Can't you find something else to do?
Banhua originally asked me out to play games today
but he's mad at me so he went to tutoring.
You two are really alike then.
Chubby kid, make way. The adults are going to talk.
My mom said that this isn't being chubby.
It's bodybuilding.
Schwarzenegger.*(US actor and politician)
I knew that you would be here.
You're more and more like your dad now.
What do you mean?
Don't you're always annoyed by your dad's
arrangement to be the president and not giving your chances to prove yourself?
What's the difference from you arranging this for Anxin and your dad's arrangement?
You always say that Anxin is very stubborn.
She's so stubborn
yet you still dare to do that. You're really something.
That's not my intention.
Then your dad must have good intentions too.
Anxin, the person that you're looking for is in the haunted Bishu Village recently. Her address is
No. 189 at Bishu Village, Ningyuan Town
Sorry, the caller that you're dialing is temporarily unavailable.
- Alipay.
- Okay.
Brother, I found Yu Guo. I'm going to Bishu Village. You don't need to pick me up at night.
Sorry, the caller that you're dialing is temporarily not within the area. Please call again later.
Hello.
May I ask, have you seen Ms. Gu Anxin?
Anxin? She got off work early today and already left.
She left early? Did she mention where she's going?
She's visiting an old friend.
She's at Bishu Village.
Thank you.
President Ling, Yu Guo seems to be at Bishu Village.
Yu Guo, are you home?
Why are you here?
It's too dangerous for you to come here alone.
You don't need to bother about my business.
Wait a second.
Wait a second, okay?
Yu Guo, I'm coming in.
Yu Guo?
It's about to rain. Let's go back.
Her luggage is still here. She'll definitely come back.
I'm going to wait for her over here.
What happens if she doesn't come back? Are you going to keep waiting for her?
Let's go.
It's about to rain. Hurry and get in the car.
It's not like I don't have legs. I can't walk by myself.
Are you sure? It takes 30 minutes to walk to the train station from here.
If it rains, then let it rain. It's not like I haven't been drenched before.
I know you're not afraid of getting drenched,
but your outfit is so see-through today. What happens if I see everything?
I'll do it myself.
Why are you hands so cold?
Do you feel better?
I already transferred the transportation fees to you.
We don't need to talk about money. I'm not accepting it.
I accepted it for you. If you don't accept it, then I won't ride your car.
Are you rich? Why do you always use money to solve problems?
I don't have money. I'm just copying the look and learning from some people.
The car has no gasoline and there's no gas station nearby.
I don't think this rain will stop any time soon.
If we don't want to spend the night in the wild, then we must have other plans.
Boss, sorry to interrupt.
Do you have a phone for us to borrow?
- Boss.
- Booking a room.
Welcome.
Boss, can we borrow your phone?
The heavy rain was so spontaneous.
The signal isn't working. I can't even watch my live broadcast.
- Does he not want us to borrow the phone?
- Seems like it.
If you couple want to talk, then do it in the room.
- We're not a couple.
- You're not?
Then why are you two so close?
Help us open two rooms.
Okay, one master bedroom.
No, its two rooms.
What a coincidence.
We only have a master bedroom left.
Impossible that only one is left.
It doesn't seem like many people are here or full.
- Why don't we go to another place?
- Okay.
Go ahead.
Look several hundred miles around this small area.
And see if this is the only shop.
I'm afraid that the master bedroom would be gone by the time you guys come back.
One bedroom then.
Okay.
Hotels are like this nowadays.
They always like to do weird things.
Why are you getting that for?
[Super Thin]
Put up with it tonight.
But there's only one bed here.
- Why don't─
- We can't.
We can't what?
I meant why don't I sleep on the floor and you sleep on the bed?
What? You want to sleep with me?
As if!
Hurry and go shower. Don't catch a cold.
Got it.
[Clean Living]
I already helped you blow dry your clothes.
Thank you.
Let's sleep early. Hurry and go shower.
- Sit down.
- What's wrong?
Your hair is all wet. You'll catch a cold if you sleep like that.
What are you doing?
There's a cockroach!
The cockroach can't run as fast as you.
Are you comparing me to a cockroach?
Okay, go down and sleep. It's dead.
I already smashed it. It's gone.
You sleep on the floor then.
I'll sleep then.
Okay, you can sleep on the bed,
but I have to create a border that we can't cross.
We'll sleep on our own sides, understand?
This is the border.
You can only sleep on that side and I can only sleep on my side.
Do you understand?
Goodnight.
Since we already slept together─
Why are you so unconcerned when talking?
What do you mean by "We already slept together." This is called,
"Using a bed together."
Okay.
Since we already used a bed together,
then can you forgive me for what I did before?
Did you say that everything can be solved after a sleep?
I really don't know where you learned these words.
Answer me first.
You're making me forgive you, but do you know where you were at fault?
I know. I thought about it a lot these past few days.
Look at me.
I shouldn't of interfered with your issues.
I forgot to think about how you felt
regarding the 5%, leaving you,
and the job arrangement.
These are all actions of not respecting you.
I thought that doings these were for your own good,
but I never asked what you needed.
I won't interfere with your issues in the future.
I will love you using the method that you want.
Are you willing to give me more time to learn?
Why are you laughing?
You never said
so many words in one go.
It's like you're writing an essay now.
Promise me first.
I actually calmed down and thought about it.
We're from two difference words after all.
There will be different opinions.
Just like how I like to eat roasted sweet potatoes, but you say that its unsanitary.
I don't think that way right now.
What I meant is that even if its like that,
its still fine.
As long as its for our own good from the start,
then I'll try my best to understand you in the future.
We have to communicate when anything happens
and be honest with each other, okay?
Okay.
We don't need this border then, right?
Since we made up, then we don't need it.
Okay then, but you have to promise me
that you can't do that "Hm" thing.
What "Hm" thing?
It's...
Nothing. If you don't understand, then forget it.
Okay.
Anxin!
The money has been transferred to your account. Immediately move somewhere else to live. Don't act impulsively.
I understand.
You said that you wouldn't do anything.
You started it.
Weren't you already asleep?
You kept moving around that I ended up waking up.
Impossible. I was moving very quietly.
If I don't hug my entire world, then how can I sleep?
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Soaking the memory wet ♫
♫ Fate works bizarrely ♫
♫ The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly beats out of normal ♫
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Obviously, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness,
for it has always been you ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Yet the reminiscing has never been able to stop ♫
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Using all of my most beautiful adjectives ♫
♫ Is still not enough to describe your name ♫
♫ Our story is exclusively ours ♫
♫ Our palms hold onto the key to the future ♫
♫ Using love to slowly open up a lifetime ♫