♪You crossed the sea of ​​stars
and came with light♪
♪My heart is like the dust, and I
couldn't bear to stain the hemline♪
♪To love in a different way,
the fireworks are in the stars' good graces♪
♪I turn around and realize that
my heart is empty♪
♪I miss the overflowing galaxy
surging into the sea♪
♪Even the fireworks desire
to give the stars a future♪
♪As long as you are around♪
♪Even the fireworks fear to bloom♪
♪Looking at you,
the light in your eyes dimmed♪
♪I laughed at myself
and that I deserve it ♪
♪My heart skips a beat, but I'm afraid
I'm not worthy of the future that you desire♪
=You Are My Glory=
=Episode 26=
Wake up.
They're hugging.
She's leaving.
She even gave him a heart sign.
After taking photos for two days,
even I feel like I've become innocent.
It's true.
I'll edit the videos to make them
look nicer.
We can't make them look obscene.
Yes.
Am I right?
You must edit them well.
You can't bash them.
After observing them
in the past few days,
I think it's true love.
That's hard to come by
for Qiao Jingjing.
I have an idea.
Later,
let's check the identity and background
of this guy first.
When the time comes,
let's expose the relationship first.
Everyone will surely be very curious
about this man's occupation.
For the second scoop,
let's reveal the boyfriend's identity.
Won't this week's hot news
be ours then?
I think that's good.
Let's do it that way.
Let's all
go back and have a good sleep then.
It's Monday tomorrow.
He'll surely go to work.
Let's go.
He has a very healthy lifestyle.
Not bad.
But he wakes up too early.
We almost missed him.
Let's follow him.
He's coming out.
Sir.
One pancake.
This handsome guy is quite simple.
He's similar to us.
Even that yogurt looks quite delicious.
I'm getting hungry now.
I must get one later.
(Research Room One)
Mr. Hu.
Yu Tu.
Come to my office immediately.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Have some tea.
Okay.
Mr. Zhang, Mr. Hu.
Close the door.
Yu Tu.
These gentlemen
are from the National Security Bureau.
They have some questions for you.
Answer them honestly.
Please have a seat.
Okay.
All right.
Don't be too nervous.
We just have a few questions.
Last Friday to Sunday,
who were you with?
My girlfriend.
What is your girlfriend's name?
Qiao Jingjing.
That actress, Qiao Jingjing?
Yes.
In the past three days,
she just stayed in your house?
Yes.
During one of those days,
she went out to attend
a brand's promotional event.
We went there together.
Didn't you notice
that people were following you?
According to them,
they've been filming you
for three days.
On Monday morning,
they even followed you to work
and took some videos.
Then
they were treated as spies
and got arrested.
National Aerospace Research Institute?
This guy's into scientific research?
Yes, I should have guessed.
I checked before,
and those who live in his community
work for the Aerospace
Research Institute.
It's a confidential unit.
We can't go inside.
We can only take some shots outside.
Just get some materials.
Let me see if the materials are enough
for the second article.
Sir.
Let me ask you something.
Around the area...
We're from the National Security Bureau.
Please come with us.
Get off the vehicle.
What will happen to them?
Since what they told us
matches with what you said,
we might need to investigate a bit
and confirm
that there's no problem.
Then we'll educate them,
and they can be released.
We've already confiscated
the photos and videos.
When youngsters date,
don't go in over your head.
Did you attend
so many confidentiality classes
in vain?
You weren't cautious at all.
We'll pay attention in the future.
We'll educate them
to let them know what they can do
and cannot do.
They can't just wander around
taking photos
outside a confidential unit.
All right.
We'll go ahead.
Sirs.
We'll get going.
Stay here,
there's no need to see us off.
I'll get to work.
Go ahead.
Come.
This is a good thing.
This is definitely a good thing.
However,
keep it low-key.
Don't publicize it too much.
Of course,
this is also a very natural thing.
There's no need
to intentionally hide it.
I understand.
Get to work.
Okay, I'm hanging up then.
I'll inform Ms. Ling.
It's confirmed.
What about her look?
We have three sets of clothing.
Prepare 15 sets.
As backups.
Right.
The blue label is good.
Hey, Jingjing.
Let me tell you something.
Go ahead.
I stayed in Yu Tu's house
when I went back to Shanghai,
and the entertainment reporters
took photos of us.
What? They took photos of you?
That's great!
That's because you two
are usually so open and brazen.
Then what should we do now?
After they expose you, will we admit it
or neither confirm nor deny?
Listen, my PR plans
have been ready for a long time.
I have plans A, B, C, D.
I can adapt to the circumstances.
I don't think they'll expose me.
Why?
They were arrested as spies.
What?
Isn't that funny?
I wonder which company's
entertainment reporters
got so unlucky.
They went to the gate
of the confidential unit
and took photos randomly.
Can they just take photos
of the Aerospace Research Institute?
I think they're shocked now.
I'll do it.
Help me with this a bit.
Hello.
Hey, Ms. Qiu.
Well, I'm sorry to disturb you.
You might not know me.
My name is Dou.
I usually
report on minor entertainment news.
I usually rely on everyone's help.
Mr. Dou, I've heard a lot about you.
Don't say that, Ms. Qiu.
Don't say that.
This time,
I called you
mainly to apologize
and thank you.
Last week, Ms. Qiao went back
to Shanghai
and met with a friend.
We
didn't handle matters appropriately.
I didn't expect
that Ms. Qiao's friend
repaid enmity with kindness
and clarified this matter for us.
We all know that.
Loyalty is what matters
in our industry the most.
Don't worry.
We'll stop pursuing this matter.
We definitely won't expose you.
In the future, we definitely
won't film Ms. Qiao again.
Thank you then.
Thank you.
I won't disturb you then.
Ms. Qiu.
In the future, if you need anything,
just call me.
You're too kind.
Bye.
What's going on?
When can my PR plans
be put to use?
I spent the money already.
(After two years)
All right.
Yes, that D is crooked.
Ms. Ling.
Jingjing is trending again.
She's filming in the desert.
Why is she trending?
Let me do it.
No, during Spring Festival,
wasn't Mr. Yu in Beijing
on a business trip
at the Aerospace Control Center?
They went to a movie,
and an ordinary citizen
took photos of them.
Wasn't that a few months ago already?
Let me see.
Take a look.
All right then.
Thank you.
(Weibo)
(A few months ago,)
(I happened to meet Qiao)
(and her boyfriend at the movie theater.)
(It's true that her boyfriend is tall.)
(Qiao was wearing a mask.)
(He was also wearing one.)
(I think it was a couple mask.)
(That kind of mask is a bit cute.)
(Did Qiao force him to wear it?)
(Ha ha ha.)
(I was a coward.)
(I only dared to take side
and back photos of them.)
(Don't believe it without
an official announcement.)
Hey.
Jingjing and Mr. Yu
have been photographed
so many times in the past two years.
Why doesn't she just make
their relationship public?
I don't think she's planning
to officially announce it.
I think it's quite good not to make
an official announcement too.
The PR plan I prepared earlier
is such a thing of the past now.
If she makes a public announcement,
we must spend more money.
Forget it.
(Aerospace Service Site)
What kind of Internet connection
do we have here?
What are you checking online?
Remember to use an alternate account.
I'm not checking gossip.
Why should I use an alternate account?
I'm checking
the Weibo of Mr. Yu's planetary rover.
Didn't it land successfully
a long time ago?
But they will
post some photos from time to time.
Forget it.
Ms. Ling.
It's Ms. Ling.
You're not shooting now?
No.
We're waiting for the sunset.
Is the signal bad on your side,
and you can't go online?
Don't get me started.
I can make phone calls.
WeChat is fine if you have
some patience.
But it takes a lot of effort
to surf the Internet.
That's why
I especially called to tell you
that you and Mr. Yu are trending again.
Mr. Yu is on a business trip.
We haven't seen each other
for almost a month.
How can we trend?
A few months ago,
you watched a movie in Beijing,
and an ordinary citizen
took photos of you.
I don't know why
she posted it today.
Then
your fans
don't believe it without an official
announcement, as usual.
People are cursing entertainment
reporters for being useless, as usual.
I am
preparing to get that off
the trending list, as usual.
Everyone's so familiar
with what he's doing.
In the past two years
that you've been dating,
I've done this so many times.
I think
that you two
should just make it official.
No.
It's not suitable to make it official
due to Mr. Yu's job.
Besides, even if I make it official,
my trending rate might not
become lower either.
And with the way we are now,
at least the public knows
that we really want to keep it low-key.
They'll understand it in the future.
Ms. Qiao.
The director and scriptwriter
will be having a meeting later.
They're inviting you to attend.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Okay, go ahead.
By the way,
is Zhou Xiaoqi joining the filming set?
I have a scene with her after two days.
Don't get into a conflict
with her.
Do you think I'm a child?
Do you even need to tell me that?
Bye.
I'm hanging up.
Rub some on you too.
I'm not afraid of getting a tan.
Let's move the stuff.
I think Zhou Xiaoqi is here.
She's already here today?
Come on, let's welcome her.
Is there a need to do that?
Everyone knows that you don't get along.
Let's just pass by.
I think you have too much free time
since the Internet connection is bad.
Follow me while walking later.
Don't randomly look around.
I came here today
mainly to familiarize myself
with the environment
and have an idea for the filming
after two days.
Ms. Zhou.
You're so dedicated to your work.
By the way,
I brought some beverages and food
for everyone.
Share it among yourselves.
Come and thank Ms. Zhou.
Here. Thank Ms. Zhou.
Thank you, Ms. Zhou.
Come on, let's move these things.
Does Ms. Qiao
often treat everyone with these too?
(Reminder number one.)
(Qiao Jingjing and Zhou Xiaoqi
haven't gotten along for many years.)
(You must handle)
(their relationship carefully.)
Well...
Ms. Qiao did as well.
All right.
I'll take you to the director
to say hi.
Sure.
Okay, come on.
Jingjing.
Qiqi.
It's been a while, I missed you so much.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
I think you were too excited.
You look great.
After being in the desert for so long,
your skin is still so moisturized.
(I rarely have a pimple,)
(and you saw it so quickly.)
My dear, I miss you so much.
You're finally here.
Did you become slimmer again?
Your waist is so small.
(I only gained 4 pounds,)
(and my waist increased by 2cm.)
(Qiao Jingjing can tell?)
If you kill me,
soldiers will still chase after you.
Give me what I want.
Perhaps
your life might be spared.
Stop following me.
Cut.
Thank you.
The look in Jingjing's eyes is perfect.
Xiaoqi isn't bad either.
How did Qiao Jingjing
improve so much?
She's usually so dramatic
and pretentious.
I thought
that she wouldn't be able
to play this character well.
I didn't expect
that once she's in character,
she has great aura.
She almost suppressed mine.
She still wasn't able
to suppress you, right?
Besides,
I think your acting
is way better than hers.
Xiaoqi, do you want
to check the script
and ponder upon it more?
Xiaoqi.
Mr. Chen said that he wants
to visit you on set.
Really?
You're coming to visit me?
Ms. Zhou.
You're so thoughtful.
Look, everyone's eating so happily.
If everyone's happy, I'm happy.
There is a lot of delicious food.
Shouldn't we
thank Ms. Zhou?
Not bad.
Let's thank Ms. Zhou together.
This looks extravagant.
Thank you, Ms. Zhou.
Don't be shy.
Eat more.
Director.
Do you
want to eat something over there?
Go.
Jingjing.
Zhou Xiaoqi's assistant
sent some food over.
Did you thank her?
Of course.
I know my manners.
There is a lot of food.
They're all oily and salty.
I can't eat them late at night.
You're still thinking about food?
Aren't you worried at all?
About what?
Mr. Yu is coming to visit you.
What should I worry about?
I don't have a kissing scene
for this project.
I'm not talking about that.
Zhou Xiaoqi's boyfriend
came before Mr. Yu,
and he brought so much food.
Barbecue, spicy hot pot, snacks.
And he even invited a chef.
Mr. Yu
can't get defeated.
If you're craving food,
eat.
Don't waste
Zhou Xiaoqi's food.
Who's craving food?
I'm worried.
What if
we ask Mr. Yu
to bring stuff for the crew
and reimburse it from Ms. Ling?
We can't lose to Zhou Xiaoqi
on this aspect.
Xiao Zhu.
At a young age,
why are you so competitive?
Don't you always say
that you must be prettier
than Zhou Xiaoqi?
Today, what Zhou Xiaoqi's boyfriend did
was too exaggerated.
Didn't you notice
that the director was unhappy?
He delayed our filming.
If someone does that again,
the director will be furious.
That's why it's better
for Mr. Yu to come
and leave quietly.
Besides,
when I usually ask you
who's prettier between me
and Zhou Xiaoqi,
I was
just joking.
Don't take me seriously.
Why should we compare our boyfriends?
Look at the practice now.
If I want to compete with her,
I'll do it with projects.
Besides,
Mr. Yu
is so smart, talented,
handsome, and chic.
Did I use him to suppress others?
No.
Because
being talented myself
is the most important thing.
That's why it's enough for me
to be prettier than her.
If you didn't use so many adjectives
and that last thing you said,
I almost believed you.
You're right.
Don't waste the food.
Jingjing.
When is Mr. Yu coming?
In three days,
around 11 AM.
Where is he coming from, Shanghai?
I don't know.
He didn't tell me where he went
on his business trip this time.
I think it's confidential.
Anyway, don't aerospace workers
perform experiments
in places
like the Gobi Desert?
When he comes in three days,
I should be filming.
Help me pick him up.
I wonder
where he'll be coming from.
(I'm still very worried.)
(What's the matter?)
(Mr. Yu is coming for a visit today.)
(I'm waiting for him.)
(Isn't that a good thing?)
(Jingjing and Mr. Yu)
(haven't seen each other
for a long time.)
(But two days ago,)
(Zhou Xiaoqi's boyfriend
came for a visit.)
(He made a big deal with his arrival.)
(If Mr. Yu comes here empty-handed,)
(they'll surely criticize him
behind his back.)
(I really don't want to see)
(Zhou Xiaoqi's assistant
to look so pleased.)
Xiao Zhu.
It's been a while.
Mr. Yu, it's been a while.
I'll bring you over.
(You might not receive this now,)
(but I must tell you.)
(It's useless no matter how exaggerated
Zhou Xiaoqi's boyfriend was.)
(We won.)
(Mr. Yu's long legs and army boots
made an instant killing.)
Jingjing, I think
we should
do another take of you crawling
and lifting your head
in the desert, okay?
The look in your eyes is right,
but I hope
that your entire body movement
has more tension, okay?
Okay.
Thank you.
Thank you, Director.
Let's do it when you're ready.
(Production: Sand)
Scene 38, shot 3, take 2.
Cut.
That's a good take.
The director said
that we could rest for one hour.
Everyone can relax a bit.
Director.
This one's fine, right?
Yes, take a look.
What do you think? Are you satisfied?
It's good, I'm quite satisfied.
All right.
- Thank you, then...
- Okay.
- Rest a bit, okay?
I missed you so much.
Xiaoqi.
Is that Qiao Jingjing's boyfriend?
She doesn't care about people
seeing them at all.
He's so hand...
He's all right.
Isn't he the one
who works at the Aerospace
Research Institute?
They've been together for two years.
They've been photographed many times.
Let me check.
Does it hurt?
There's sand all over you.
It's fine.
Come on, let's go to the lounge room.
Look at them.
They're in front of so many people.
She's not reserved
like how a female celebrity
should be at all.
When my boyfriend came,
did I act that way?
Of course not.
You just stayed in the lounge room
and maintained your poise completely.
Aren't you on a business trip?
How can you visit me?
Is it around the area?
If you can't tell me,
you don't need to.
I can tell you now.
I just finished my mission yesterday.
I left this morning.
You were really in this desert?
Around 200km away.
200km?
It was so near.
It's fine.
You just didn't come
at a good time.
I have to shoot all day.
And I have one more scene at night.
But tomorrow, I can rest
during the day.
We can go around the nearby area.
Treat it
as a desert tour
paid by the company.
Jingjing.
I must go to the airport
at 6 PM tonight
and return to Shanghai
with my colleagues.
I have a meeting early tomorrow morning.
You're leaving today?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
I'm busy too, aren't I?
After filming wraps up,
I must take a good rest
for two months.
Sure.
I should
have more free time then.
Really?
At least I don't need to go
on a business trip.
You haven't eaten, right?
I'll ask Xiao Zhu
to get us two portions of lunches.
It's fine.
Let's get down to business first.
Business?
What business?
I...
have two more scenes
in the afternoon.
My make-up can't be ruined.
I can do it by myself.
Jingjing.
Is he your friend?
No.
He's a maintenance staff I hired.
Director.
Go on.
What is he installing?
I don't know.
A signal booster.
I know that.
Huang, didn't we install that?
We did, it's that one.
But it doesn't quite work.
It's quite useless.
Jingjing told me already.
There are mixed qualities
in the market for this equipment.
You might
have gotten one with bad quality.
You can remove it later.
A bad quality equipment
isn't of much use.
The base station interference is bigger.
This will work then?
I think so.
I asked my friend who's a specialist
to make it.
Later on,
if you film in another place,
you can bring it along too.
It's very easy to install.
(Internet speed test)
(Yu Tu)
(I missed you too.)
It's fine now.
Director, it works.
Really?
It really works.
Thank you so much.
You solved
a big problem for us.
You're welcome.
I'm doing it for myself too.
It's too long to lose contact
for over ten hours daily.
Yes, that's a bit long.
Yes.
And Jingjing told me
that you have a lot of
night scenes later on.
Yes, that's right.
Are you done filming today?
No, we're still filming.
Look, today...
So what if I have a lot of night scenes?
You can't sleep if you don't see me?
I can't sleep well.
You're such a sweet talker.
Do you want another one?
Huang.
Hurry, arrange for someone
to treat Jingjing
and her boyfriend
to dinner tonight.
Thank them well.
All right.
Thank you, Director.
But I must reach the airport
by 6 PM tonight.
I must leave at 2:30 PM at the latest.
You're in such a rush?
Hey.
If you're leaving at 2:30 PM,
Ms. Qiao
will shoot a scene at 1 PM.
Then your visit here...
This... This is what we'll do.
Let's push back the afternoon shoot
for an hour.
There's no need, Director. It's fine.
Let's not delay filming.
I know what I'm doing.
It won't get delayed.
It's decided then.
It's decided.
Thank you.
♪You crossed the sea of ​​stars
and came with light♪
♪My heart is like the dust, and I
couldn't bear to stain the hemline♪
♪To love in a different way,
the fireworks are in the stars' good graces♪
♪I turn around and realize that
my heart is empty♪
♪I miss the overflowing galaxy
surging into the sea♪
♪Even the fireworks desire
to give the stars a future♪
♪As long as you are around♪
♪Even the fireworks fear to bloom♪
♪Looking at you,
the light in your eyes dimmed♪
I earned an hour.
Can we do whatever we want?
♪I laughed at myself
and that I deserve it ♪
What do you have in mind?
♪My heart skips a beat, but I'm afraid
I'm not worthy of the future that you desire♪
♪I dreamed of starlight
pulling the sleeves♪
♪A white top
covering the thin shoulders♪
♪I have seen the wounds healed
with each passing year♪
♪There will always be people
running towards eternity♪
♪The bustling intersection♪
♪Looking back all of a sudden
under the dim light♪
♪I loved your eyes
looking at the starry sky♪
♪And I loved the universe in your heart♪
♪Time does not stop, remember the time
that we failed to treasure♪
♪The wind passes by the tall buildings
with no one awaiting it♪
♪I've dreamed of traveling
around the planet♪
♪Seeing the galaxy
pass through the clouds♪
♪I looked at the hills with sorrow♪
♪Will the exit of the dream lead
to the end of the starry sky?♪
♪Looking back all of a sudden♪
♪Which galaxy am I drifting on?♪
♪Looking into the distance,
which of the stars are your eyes?♪
♪It's out of reach,
so dazzling and hard to get♪
♪Time does not hold back, the spring
and autumn in the passing time♪
♪The wind sings the song of freedom
as I listen to the tenderness of time♪