♪You crossed the sea of ​​stars
and came with light♪
♪My heart is like the dust, and I
couldn't bear to stain the hemline♪
♪To love in a different way,
the fireworks are in the stars' good graces♪
♪I turn around and realize that
my heart is empty♪
♪I miss the overflowing galaxy
surging into the sea♪
♪Even the fireworks desire
to give the stars a future♪
♪As long as you are around♪
♪Even the fireworks fear to bloom♪
♪Looking at you,
the light in your eyes dimmed♪
♪I laughed at myself
and that I deserve it ♪
♪My heart skips a beat, but I'm afraid
I'm not worthy of the future that you desire♪
=You Are My Glory=
=Episode 25=
What time is it now?
Why isn't
Qiao Jingjing out yet?
I woke up really early today.
I'm getting sleepy.
They drew the curtains.
I don't think
we can get any scoop tonight.
Let's wait a little longer.
We caught them getting down from the car
and going into the apartment together.
We'll see if we can
catch them coming out together.
Keep a close eye.
Did you use a new hero
to make us lose on purpose?
What?
We lost in the first three rounds
but you were the MVP
in every match.
Who is losing on purpose now?
I still think you did.
Well, actually...
Never mind.
Next time,
I'll introduce my boyfriend to you.
He'll carry you.
He's amazing as the jungler.
He can end the game in 10 minutes.
What?
You have a boyfriend
and you didn't tell me?
Who? Duan Wu?
Get lost.
Come on.
He's not a celebrity.
He's good-looking
and he's really good at games.
He's a liar who likes
giving me the puppy-dog eyes.
He's also perceptive.
My friend.
I don't know
if I should say this.
Just say it.
He doesn't sound like
a decent guy.
He's out! Hurry and take the picture!
Why is it just him?
Where's Qiao Jingjing?
My gosh.
Qiao... Qiao Jingjing is staying the night!
It's confirmed.
That's her luggage.
She's spending the night here.
She could still get away last time
by saying she went to
her friend's house.
But we got her now.
He's taking her luggage upstairs.
We have evidence.
The three of us
will stay here all night
and take turns to keep on the lookout.
We must get pictures of them
coming out of the apartment together!
This is great for us!
We hit the jackpot!
Can I come in?
Hold on.
Come in.
I'm here to get the blanket and pillow.
Goodnight.
(I'm staying at
my boyfriend's house tonight.)
(Will I be able to sleep?)
(What if I'm not at my best
for the event tomorrow?)
(Are you both so full of energy)
(that it's going to affect
you tomorrow?)
(It's going to take all night?)
(I got it now.)
(You played)
(the first three rounds.)
(The rest was him.)
(Am I right?)
(Goodnight.)
(Are you both so full of energy)
(that it's going to affect
you tomorrow?)
(It's going to take all night?)
(You are annoying!)
(It ended so quickly?)
(Why are you blaming me?)
(We just got together not long ago.)
(We are sleeping in separate rooms.)
(That's not my fault, too.)
(It's him.)
(Chen Xue recalled a message)
(He doesn't know better.)
(Goodbye!)
You're not sleeping yet?
Are you feeling cold?
No.
I'll get you a blanket.
I'm not feeling cold.
Why are you still working?
I can't bring my work home.
I'm doing some translation.
What is it about?
It's about the Deep Space Probe
and its low-thrust orbit transfers
design optimization.
You carry on.
You should go to bed now.
Don't you
have work tomorrow?
You're not going to bed either.
Didn't you say
you haven't been able
to rest for the last few days?
But I have to
go through some thesis tonight.
To calm myself down.
I'm going to bed.
Don't you come out again.
Or else...
Get some sleep.
Or else what?
(Send me the interview outline)
(for tomorrow.)
(You're not sleeping yet?)
(You can still read it)
(when you do your makeup tomorrow.)
(Sleep early to get some rest.)
(Just send it to me.)
(I need it to keep calm.)
You're awake?
You look half-asleep.
You look silly.
You're silly.
The pillow is too high.
It's uncomfortable.
Why didn't you tell me yesterday?
I'll change it today.
You asked me
not to come out yesterday.
I think I did.
You could have called me.
I'm starving. Where's my breakfast?
Let's have breakfast then.
What time are we leaving later?
I'm getting my makeup done
at the hotel at 12 noon.
I haven't told Xiao Zhu
that I'm at your place.
(Jingjing, Ms. Ling, Xiao Zhu)
(You don't have to)
(pick me up at Lujiazui.)
(I'm with Mr. Yu.)
(I'll go to the hotel myself.)
Qiao Jingjing.
I can't believe you are at his place.
Can you stop
making a fuss out of it?
My phone is on speaker.
Mr. Yu is listening to our conversation.
I'm making a fuss?
You asked for the interview outline
yesterday in the middle of the night.
You said you wanted it
to keep calm.
Why didn't you tell me
you're at his place?
Didn't I tell you
before you left?
I told Xiao Zhu
to go to the hotel right away, too.
I'll be there after I had breakfast
with Mr. Yu.
Just the two of you?
No way.
I'll come and pick you up.
There's still some time.
Send me the address.
Your house address.
I'll send it to her.
You haven't had breakfast either?
I was waiting for you.
It wasn't very helpful.
Translating the thesis.
Her team is here to pick her up.
Looks like she is going public.
Her boyfriend
is going to the event with her?
They are still in their honeymoon phase.
Follow them.
Let's go.
We'll reach the hotel
at 12 noon.
You'll get your makeup done first.
Then, it's the magazine interview.
The event tonight
starts at 6:30 PM.
Are you still staying at
Mr. Yu's place tonight?
Depends on the traffic.
Last night was because
Lujiazui's traffic
was terrible.
So I went to his house
to stay for a bit.
Then, I was too tired to go back.
Xiao Zhu, watch and learn.
Shanghai's traffic.
Traffic.
What is Mr. Yu going to do
when you do your makeup at the hotel?
He can pretend as one of the staff
and come with us.
Are you not aware of
how good-looking your boyfriend is?
Him pretending as the staff?
Of course I do.
Then, why did you come up with
this terrible idea?
I just want you to compliment his look.
Well then, Mr. Yu.
When we got there,
you'll have to find somewhere
and wait for us there.
Sure.
Actually, Mr. Yu
has a wide range.
Just change his hairstyle,
put on a pair of glasses
and change his outfit.
He can totally
pass as my image consultant.
Ivan's styling studio
is just in front.
We still have some time.
Why don't we stop by?
Let's go.
Today
is the peak of my career as a manager.
Both of them
are my top artists.
But Mr. Yu
doesn't want to be a celebrity.
Zip it.
I can't even fantasize?
Ms. Qiu, that handsome man over there.
Is he your new artist?
He is the new staff
in our studio.
Staff?
Ms. Qiu, what a waste.
He should be an artist with that face.
I'm considering it, too.
What do you think?
Will he be famous?
Of course he will.
He's dashing.
And there's something special about him.
Ms. Qiu, where did you find him?
If Jingjing can bring him
to some events,
everyone will want to offer him a role.
I hope so.
Yu, what do you think?
I'll make you a celebrity.
Jingjing will bring you to some events
and you will be famous in no time.
I can't do that.
I don't simply do that.
If I have to,
that person has to
sign a 10-year contract with me.
Ms. Qiao, I can sign a longer contract.
And how do we distribute the money?
I just need some
living expenses.
All right.
I'll think about it.
Thank you, Ms. Qiao.
Ms, Qiu.
Your company has really strict
contract terms.
Keep it to yourself.
Jingjing.
We prepared
three gowns for you.
You may pick the gown that
goes well with the jewellery.
She is done with her makeup?
Xiao Zhu.
Please bring them downstairs
for afternoon tea.
Get some rest.
We will leave together
when it's time, all right?
Thank you.
I'll leave them to you.
Goodbye.
You can change into the gown later.
Get the interview done first.
But journalists
are more sensitive.
And Mr. Yu is here.
I'll go somewhere else
and wait for the event to start.
Why did you have to
arrange an interview?
It's just a short one.
Yu Tu.
Pick a gown for me.
Which one do I look good in?
All of them.
How insincere.
Come here.
Come and pick one.
This seems heavy.
I think this is lighter?
I... I'm fine.
Carry on.
Go on.
Your reason for picking this dress
is very unusual.
But these gowns are quite revealing.
You don't mind, do you?
I'm not that narrow-minded.
I'm glad, then.
But I am narrow-minded.
You can't wear this.
I'm going to confiscate this.
It's too flashy.
What about my outfit?
Can I change it?
Just wear it for another day.
Just one day.
It's too flashy.
You're mine anyway.
Right.
I'm yours.
Her boyfriend
left the hotel alone.
I suppose he's not joining the event.
Do we go separately or what?
Let's trail the guy.
I checked.
The jewellery event today
is a brand endorsed by Qiao Jingjing.
It's crazy expensive.
It's the same thing
but several times more expensive.
Why do the women love buying it?
Do you think that guy
can afford to buy this jewellery
for Qiao Jingjing?
I don't think so.
But he should
thank us.
They are having a secret relationship.
When we expose their relationship,
Qiao Jingjing will have to admit it.
That may not be the case.
She may refuse to admit
and chose to break up with him
to avoid suspicion.
That's also possible.
Well then,
we are helping him
to end this relationship for good.
We are doing a good deed.
Hi.
Can I add you on WeChat?
I'm sorry.
He's not bad.
He dealt with it calmly.
He's used to this kind of stuff.
What are you doing?
Why are you taking pictures?
I can't help myself.
Look at this.
What do you think?
This will be our token of appreciation
for Qiao Jingjing and her team.
Right?
Does he have a girlfriend?
He looks better than the celebrities.
I have no idea.
He seems to be leaving.
Qiao Jingjing's event
is starting soon.
Let's go.
Hi, everyone.
Good evening to our guests
and the media
that are here to join us tonight.
Welcome to our event
where we admire
the "starlight" together.
First, let's welcome
our brand ambassador,
Qiao Jingjing.
(Jingjing is the best)
Qiao Jingjing is here!
Qiao Jingjing!
Jingjing, I love you!
Darling, I love you!
Hi, I'm Qiao Jingjing.
I'm very glad to be
the brand ambassador for Starlight
and to be able to meet all of you here.
Jingjing, I love you!
(Jingjing is the best)
I'm dying!
My darling looks gorgeous today.
(Jingjing, you're the best!)
Jingjing, you are so pretty!
Jingjing.
Are you one of the media?
You are too far away.
You can't even make out her face.
You won't get any views
if you put up
this kind of picture online.
That's right.
It's fine.
I just take these photos for fun.
Thank you.
No problem.
Please take some nice pictures
for her.
Okay, don't you worry.
Da Mao.
What is it?
The other reporters
are taking her photos only.
But we are taking photos
of both of them.
When we put up
these photos online,
our competitors
will all be flabbergasted.
I think I'm at the
perfect spot.
Look.
The photo, the composition.
It's perfect.
He's really good-looking.
We don't even have to label it.
The readers won't be mistaken.
Take more photos.
This is rare. Hurry up.
(Jingjing, you're the best!)
All right. We will have
the guests
facing the audience
and raise their glasses
in celebration of this event.
With this,
our event has reached the end.
Jingjing
and the media may proceed
to the back of the stage.
Thank you.
Jingjing, Jingjing!
Jingjing, don't go!
I won't go in.
Jingjing, you may get changed first.
I'll go and get dinner.
Ms. Ling wants to have dinner together.
Sure.
It's your first time
seeing me at a live event.
Do I look pretty?
Yes, you do.
You look gorgeous.
I remember Mr. Yu
is quite good at language.
Your descriptions are unimpressive.
Looking from afar,
you are as bright as the sun
as it shines light on the cloud.
Now you're showing off?
But that's acceptable.
It just sounds a little cheesy.
It's my first time going to your event
but I have a problem.
What's with your fans?
The guys and girls
call you "darling".
They just did it for fun.
Are you jealous?
Not really.
In the end,
you come home to me anyway.
Come home to you?
And then?
To watch you translate the thesis?
♪I'm on a distant and quiet land♪
I'm sorry, Jingjing.
I forgot to knock.
I...
I didn't...
interrupt anything, did I?
Jingjing.
Where is she?
I'm done translating.
Today
you're not reading
any interview outline, are you?
I have a script to go through.
You can translate it again.
I have no time.
I need to defend my rights.
I just realized I was scammed.
I'm supposed to have three days to date.
But my date
came back at 7 PM yesterday
and she's leaving at 8 o'clock tomorrow.
So it's actually only a day and a half.
Is this how
mini-apps scams work nowadays?
So what?
Now that I have done it.
I won't return the money.
Usually,
in this case,
the developer
will offer some compensation.
For instance,
open up a new area.
It's surprising to hear this from you.
I didn't know you are such a hooligan.
What are you thinking?
I mean my bedroom.
And that's being decent?
No.
Is it okay?
You have been away for so long.
I can't wait anymore.
Besides the pillow,
what are the other things
that you can't get used to?
You.
There's nothing I can do about that.
You will get used to it.
How is this pillow height?
What do you think?
Don't move.
How do you like it?
What about this?
No.
I'll make it lower.
♪I dreamed of starlight
pulling the sleeves♪
♪A white top
covering the thin shoulders♪
♪I have seen the wounds healed
with each passing year♪
♪There will always be people
running towards eternity♪
♪The bustling intersection♪
♪Looking back all of a sudden
under the dim light♪
♪I loved your eyes
looking at the starry sky♪
♪And I loved the universe in your heart♪
♪Time does not stop, remember the time
that we failed to treasure♪
♪The wind passes by the tall buildings
with no one awaiting it♪
♪I've dreamed of traveling
around the planet♪
♪Seeing the galaxy
pass through the clouds♪
♪I looked at the hills with sorrow♪
♪Will the exit of the dream lead
to the end of the starry sky?♪
♪Looking back all of a sudden♪
♪Which galaxy am I drifting on?♪
♪Looking into the distance,
which of the stars are your eyes?♪
♪It's out of reach,
so dazzling and hard to get♪
♪Time does not hold back, the spring
and autumn in the passing time♪
♪The wind sings the song of freedom
as I listen to the tenderness of time♪