"Golchindl.net"
Since Paris doesn't want us,
we'll just go to the Moon,
just like in Jules Verne's book!
How do you figure you'll breathe
in space, birdbrain?
Come, my dear pigeons!
In space,
no one can hear you coo!
(Gasps) I know how to use
my Lucky Charm!
Let's bring him back to Earth
before he hurts himself!
CAT NOIR: Power up!
ALYA: Oh!
Check out Cosmobug and Astrocat
flying in those new suits!
Yo, Peeps! This is Alya Césaire,
live from Paris,
where our heroes are battling
Mr Pigeon for the 51st time!
They really are miraculous,
aren't they? (Gasps)
‐ There you go!
‐ CAT NOIR: There you go.
Oops! You've said that already.
Cat Noir, I've told you
to stop bringing me flowers!
Yeah, I know. When I tried
to offer you a red rose,
you told me that red symbolizes
"passion," so you refused it.
And I offered you a white rose,
but you said white stood for
"pure love," and refused it too.
So now I'm offering you
a yellow rose.
I've looked it up and yellow
represents friendship.
Here's to a perfect partnership.
Are you sure yellow roses
don't represent jealousy?
Uh... No.
That would be blue roses.
Hang on, no, purple!
Or was it orange?
(Chuckles) You don't
need to give me flowers.
I already know you're
the best partner ever, Cat Noir.
It smells really good anyway.
Thanks, kitty!
(Sighs) She's so amazing.
And so am I, by the way.
I should be
giving myself flowers!
Spots off!
(Chomping)
(Gasps) Oh!
A new poster of Adrien!
Marinette,
you'll be late for school.
Ah! He's so perfect!
I thought you'd stopped
collecting photos of Adrien.
Ah, but it's different
this time, Tikki!
This is... uh, for work!
It's, um, research
for my future designs!
Adrien and I are done!
See?
I can even look into his eyes
without being mesmerized!
‐ Ah...
‐ Marinette!
Yes! Let's get going!
And that's how the friendship
between George Washington
and Frenchman
Marquis de Lafayette was born,
between two men
who believed that freedom
should have no boundaries.
Congratulations, that truly was
a sensational student film!
And completed just in time
for our departure
to French‐American
Friendship Week... in New York!
(Cheering)
Ah! Good thing my parents
aren't letting me go with you!
Not seeing you all for a week
will feel like a vacation!
But, Miss Bourgeois,
your parents
already gave the authorisation.
You are coming along
with everyone!
What? You're gonna
hear from Daddikins!
I, on the other hand,
regret to inform you
that I can't
come with you after all.
‐ Oh, no! But why?
‐ I just have
a few medical exams
I couldn't postpone, because...
I will soon be having a baby!
(Cheering)
Miss Mendeleiev will be
substituting Miss Bustier.
‐ Aw...
‐ She's not cool.
New York with her
will be so lame.
She won't let us do anything!
Something wrong, buddy?
My father isn't going to
let me go. As usual.
I'm stuck in Paris too.
I have obligations
because of my charity work,
but we could see each other,
if you'd like.
‐ Uh, thanks, Lila!
‐ No!
0Uh, I mean... no,
we made that film together,
all of us, which means
Adrien must come with me!
I mean, us! He's our friend
and you don't let a friend down!
Just like in the film,
when sock‐Lafayette
comes and helps his friend
sock‐Washington find freedom.
Adrien,
you're our sock‐Washington!
You're our friend,
and as your friend,
it is my duty
to go and see your father
and convince him
to let you come with us!
Yeah!
And we're coming with you!
Thank you, Marinette.
But my father's
a difficult man to convince.
I will never let a friend down!
‐ Adrien, your friend?
‐ Absolutely!
It was time I moved on!
It was so painful, not being
able to tell him how I felt.
It made me act completely crazy!
(Coughs) No kidding!
Oh! It's so liberating to
finally just be Adrien's friend
instead of "the girl
who's in love with Adrien!"
I no longer get lost
in his beautiful green eyes,
I no longer spray his Adrien n.4
cologne on my pillow,
and I stopped binge‐watching
my montage of his best ads!
What about
your poster collection?
That... that's strictly
for research purposes!
But are you sure you'll be fine
spending a week with him?
Isn't that too romantic?
No! Of course not!
We'll have
a great time as friends!
But first,
I've gotta convince his dad.
Last night the New York Museum
kicked off
French American Friendship Week
with a special exhibition!
Reporter Clara Contard
was there.
That's right, Nadja.
For the first time ever
and only until Sunday,
the museum is putting
Lafayette's sabre on display,
as well as
the eagle‐talon necklace
‐ he gave George Washington.
‐ This is no mere jewel.
Eagle talon is without
a doubt a lost Miraculous.
(Doorbell rings)
Have my plane ready
for take‐off.
That's what makes
our friendship so precious!
And since your son is my friend,
I mean, our friend,
that means he has to come
to New York with us!
‐ Young lady, I ‐‐
‐ I won't leave this place
‐ until you've ‐‐
‐ I've decided to let Adrien go
along with his classmates.
‐ Uh... You have? But usually...
‐ You've convinced me.
You really are
a good friend to my son.
(Cheering)
She just unknowingly offered you
an unexpected opportunity.
Yes. Letting Adrien
go to New York will be simpler
than hiding
my absence here from him.
Besides, this will allow me to
continue keeping an eye on him.
(Grunts)
What's wrong, Adrien?
My whole class is
going to New York tomorrow.
I wish
I could be going with them.
I'm sad for you,
but happy for us.
This'll give us
more time to practise.
When you're as weak
as you were today,
the pleasure of beating you
is lessened.
‐ I'll see you tomorrow.
‐ See you tomorrow, Kagami.
♪ New York, New York,
I'm going to New York...
with Adrien Agreste!
Uh... As friends, of course!
Heh heh!
By the way, Marinette,
who'll protect Paris
while we're
in the US for the week?
All taken care of, my Tikki!
‐ You're going away?
‐ Only for a few days.
It's nothing important,
kittycat!
‐ But I can't tell you more.
‐ To protect our identities.
‐ I know the drill, Milady.
‐ But in case anything happens
in Paris, an akumatised villain,
a sentimonster, anything...
all you have to do
is click here,
and I'll come back
as fast as I can!
For emergencies only, of course!
Of course!
Just go and rest easy.
I'll be Paris'
substitute guardian!
Am I not
the perfect partner after all?
I'm counting on you.
No funny business, OK?
Have I ever struck you
as the funny kind?
I'm as serious as they get!
(Groans)
I... I can go to New York?
Really?
You can thank your friend
Marinette for convincing me.
But, actually,
I hadn't planned on...
What about my fencing lessons?
And Chinese?
Nathalie has already
packed your bags.
Your bodyguard will go with you.
You take off this afternoon.
Uh... yes, very well, Father.
I've been dreaming about this
ever since the Gentlemen's
Cheese came out.
Blue Marble Jack, Cougar Gold,
the legendary Monterrey...
All those wonderful
American cheeses
are just waiting
for us to taste them!
We can't go, Plagg. I promised
Ladybug I'd watch over Paris,
and I don't want
to let her down.
But your father will never let
you stay. You want more freedom,
and, for once, your father
is letting you have fun!
Enjoy! You'll be in New York
with your friends!
She's gonna be so disappointed.
Of course not! She can't be
if she doesn't know!
Besides, she told you not to
call unless a villain shows up.
See any in the house?
What if something happens
while we're gone?
Don't you have
an akuma alert on your phone?
Of course.
In case of emergency
I can transform into Astrocat
‐ to fly back quickly!
‐ Perfect!
And then you can tell Ladybug!
That way,
she'll never be disappointed!
Pound it!
My love, being far away from you
will be
nothing short of torture.
But I may have found a piece
of jewellery in New York,
which might enable me
to beat Ladybug and Cat Noir,
to get their Miraculous
and to make the wish
that will bring you back to me.
Oh, I'm sorry, Luka.
We'll never catch up to the bus!
We will. I know how important
this trip is to you.
You're saying it's important
because of Adrien.
But his being there
isn't important.
I mean,
it's important to Adrien,
because it's an important trip,
but he's just a friend!
(Sighs)
Look! Marinette!
You know what's important?
That this trip
helps you get some clarity.
Thank you, Luka.
Ugh...
Yes, turns out
you're in luck, I'm coming.
But only because I decided to.
Uh, but there is no way I'm
travelling in these conditions.
I'm going to sit down
in first class.
(Groans)
Hey, Marinette!
What's your seat number?
Uh... Baby... BB... 32B.
Oh, great!
You're sitting next to me!
(Gasps)
Awesome, Marinette.
Go and sit next to your friend!
So you can enjoy
a nice flight together.
A very long flight.
Uh, sure! Next to my husban...
my friend... no problem!
He's a friend. Just a friend.
He's a just a friend.
‐ Uh... Everything OK?
‐ Oh, yeah, yeah, great!
Ooh, hoo‐hoo! It's just
a little hot in here, huh?
Here, let me help you.
Whoa!
‐ Oh, sorry!
‐ No, I'm fine!
‐ Are you feeling cooler now?
‐ Gee! No! Not at all!
It must be the seat!
It's a warming seat, right?
Ooh! It's burning hot!
Um... no... it's a regular seat.
But you can have mine if you'd
like. Come on, let's switch!
(Alarm)
Help, Alya!
I can't sit next to him!
I might need more training
to be just his friend.
There's still time
to get off plane.
Because New York is the most
romantic city in the world,
after Paris, obviously.
New York is, like, carriage
rides with pretty white horses,
little dogs and kittens
on your lap,
the sun setting
over Central Park,
‐ the ferry to Liberty Island!
‐ Aaah!
‐ I have to get outta here!
‐ What's going on?
Marinette gets airsick.
It would be better
if she could sit at the centre.
Out of the question.
Each student is to keep the seat
they have been assigned!
Oh, Miss Bustier
would've totally have said yes!
Please, Miss Mendeleiev,
this is a plane,
not a classroom!
Um... All right, fine.
You may have my seat, Marinette.
Guess
I'll see you later, then?
Right, later! Much later!
I mean, see you later!
We are about to take off.
Please fasten your seatbelt.
SOOTHING VOICE:
On a scale of one to ten,
how would you rate
your fear of flying?
Select the relaxation level
you require.
You are a dolphin,
leaping from wave to wave
in an ocean of tranquillity.
(Gasps)
We're about to take off.
Please fasten your seatbelt.
(Snoring)
(Mysterious music)
(Grunts)
(Sighs)
MARINETTE: Whoa! Oh! Shoot!
ADRIEN:
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Aaah! Forry, I... I mean, sorry!
‐ Sorry, Marinette.
‐ (Chuckles)
ADRIEN:
My father told me everything.
The only reason I can enjoy
this beautiful sunset is you.
I thought it'd be impossible,
but you believed in it.
You're always willing to take a
chance on something or someone,
even when no one else is.
You've got something,
Marinette.
Som... something?
‐ Yeah, there. In your hair.
‐ (Gasps)
I can't decide whether they're
the cutest people I know,
‐ or the most embarrassing.
‐ Yep. I love Adrien,
but he's like a baby chick
that's just started
cracking out of his egg.
He has a hard time
understanding signals.
What signals? Marinette isn't
exactly sending them clearly.
I mean, look.
What is she doing with her arms?
Telling him what to do
in case of an emergency landing?
(Indistinct)
(Sighs) If only this trip
could help Adrien
finally come out of his shell.
And if only it could help
Marinette be honest with herself
and clearer about her feelings!
‐ Operation New York?
‐ Operation New York!
‐ Let's help them loosen up!
‐ After all,
isn't the United States
the land of the free?
OK, then... So...
OK.
ADRIEN:
Well, what I meant to say was
thanks for managing
to convince my father.
(Lively music)
Ooh! Sure thing!
Ha, ha! Don't mention it!
That's what friends are for!
For holding each other tightly
in delicious aroma of cologne!
(Hysterical laugh)
Oh, no! That's Techno‐Pirate,
the supervillain
who steals technology!
Don't worry, sweethearts.
We have this under control.
Dear passengers, the United
Heroes are here to protect you.
(Gasps) Uncanny Valley!
The first superhero with AI,
created by Majestia!
(Gasps) Which means...
(Heroic music)
(Alarm)
Wow! Majestia in person!
So cool!
It's time to show
those American superheroes
how French superheroes do it!
Hoo‐hoo!
(Groans)
Techno‐Pirate,
you're under arrest.
Watch and learn!
The legendary
Knight Owl and Sparrow!
Your runaway ends here.
Were you hurt, sweetheart?
I'm 100% operational, Mother!
Welcome to the United States,
and enjoy your stay!
It is now the hour of the owl!
Hoo, hoo!
Duh? Oh...
Wow! That all happened so fast!
I didn't have time
to transform or help out!
Good thing the Americans
superheroes were here.
I couldn't have transformed.
I'm supposed to be in Paris!
Relax! Let the local superheroes
handle their own problems.
So far,
nothing to report from Paris.
(Lively music)
Hey! What's that guy doing?
Oh, it's just Captain Redlight,
organising the traffic.
There's a superhero
for everything here, you know.
So, what happened on the plane
with your "friend" Adrien?
Nothing! We just watched
the clouds and the sunset.
But only as friends!
It's a typical thing to do!
Grr!
Paris is safe
from supervillains!
Have Ladybug and Cat Noir
put an end to Hawk Moth?
‐ A segment by Clara Contard.
‐ Forget about Paris, dude!
You're in New York now!
Your old man's not here,
and when the cat's away,
the mice will play!
Open your eyes,
you know what I mean?
Take it all in!
It is beautiful!
The Little Croissants
are en route.
‐ Good. Don't leave them.
‐ Roger that.
Meet you in the lobby.
‐ Two of them are missing.
‐ (Bang)
Oh! There they are!
(Bang)
Hey! You guys
are the cool French kids
that made that movie! We're from
Armstrong High in Queens!
Baby‐sitting some tourists
and their socks?
I mean, don't they have
anything better for us to do?
Those two
are made for each other.
Seriously, Aeon? Not again!
But I am programmed
to help people, Jess.
Just stop meddling
with people's private lives!
You're right.
Let's just follow the orders
‐ and protect the tourists.
‐ (Clapping) Listen, students!
You'll go to your rooms
by groups of four.
Everyone come
take your itinerary.
And when I come up
in two minutes,
you had better be in your rooms,
with the lights out!
‐ Come on!
‐ Can we stay up a little bit?
Hey! Sock buddies!
We're throwing
a little party on the roof.
Hang with us, but be quiet, OK?
I think there's an American boy
who'd love to see you there.
And you might make... a friend.
(Chuckles)
‐ You... you think so?
‐ A rooftop party in this slum?
You want me to catch lameness
and coodies? That's ridiculous!
Sabrina! Suitcase!
Group D. Awesome!
At least we're in the same room.
(Gasps) As Chloé!
Césaire and Dupain‐Cheng?
That is the last straw!
JESS:
Oh, no, this could go wrong.
What do you think, Aeon?
Should we do something?
‐ You think we should?
‐ No! I was just kidding.
This whole situation
is just plain boring.
(Mysterious music)
MISS MENDELEIEV:
What's that noise?
ADRIEN:
Oh. Sorry. We're so sorry.
Uh... Hi! I'm Marinette and this
is my very good friend, Adrien,
who's just a friend!
See?
They're made for each other.
(Groans) Fine.
If you want to get to the roof
without attracting attention,
there are stairs outside.
Why do that? I thought
we weren't meant to meddle?
If we're going to
watch over them,
there might as well be
something to watch!
Isn't that what you wanted?
(Laughs)
(Lively music)
(Window opens)
‐ Is it a bird?
‐ Is it a plane?
No, it's Hot Dog Dan!
Hey, hey, hey! Hot Dog Dan's
here, so get in the mood!
I'm the hero of picnics
and tasty food!
Hmm. Usually he teams up with
Ketchup Boy and Mustard Justice,
but he's
patrolling solo tonight.
You should hurry if you wanna
try one of his magic hot dogs.
Sorry, guys,
I only have two hotdogs left
‐ for the four of you.
‐ Not a problem.
My girl and I will take one
and you two take the other!
‐ Between friends...
‐ (Chuckles)
It's all yours, Adrien.
My pleasure, as your friend.
No, you take it, Marinette.
Come on now,
one hot dog for two, coming up!
(High‐pitched voice)
Oh, finally!
My chick's wings are growing!
(Laughter)
You were right, they really
seem to be made for each other.
Yeah, no. With those two,
the situation's far from simple.
Hey, you play the guitar!
Maybe you can give them a hand!
Do you know this song?
Oh! That's the song we danced to
at Chloé's party, remember?
Ooh, yes! (Chuckles)
Then, will you?
(Romantic music)
Picture yourself
a beautiful sunflower.
(Lively music)
It was so romantic, you two
dancing in the moonlight,
‐ wasn't it?
‐ Yeah... So, ro...
Friendly! Friendly!
It was a very friendly dance!
Hey, look, that teacher!
That's Dean Gate,
aka "Door Man"!
He can turn a door
into a teleporting passage!
Superheroes don't need to hide
their identity in America!
Amazing! I'm going to ask him
for a quote for the Ladyblog!
(Bang)
Those two seem to exhibit
repetitive behaviours.
Tough luck, right?
We always end up together!
I mean, stuck together.
Ha, ha! (Sighs)
I don't mind being stuck
with a friend like you.
Right! As friends!
It's all good!
I know what to do. If anything's
gonna change between them,
they'll need to find themselves
in a dangerous situation.
What? Are you out of your mind?
Statistically speaking,
humans confronted
with extreme situations
often cause their feelings
to become stronger.
They must believe
they won't see each other again
and it's the last chance they'll
get to say how they feel.
Here's what we'll do.
During the visit,
get them to go
to the Lafayette room alone.
Boom! That's when supervillain
Solitude shows up
and threatens to kidnap
any person that nobody loves.
He threatens Adrien,
and in order to save him...
"No, don't kidnap him,
I love him!"
OK... It's so stupid,
it could actually work.
Wow! Cool impression!
Hey, hold on!
A supervillain? How... ?
(Bang)
‐ Trust us.
‐ (Clapping)
Get them to the room
and we'll take care of the rest.
For someone
who didn't want me to meddle,
you seem deeply involved.
This is more fun
than babysitting socks!
This is the famous sabre
of Marquis de Lafayette.
And the necklace he gave
George Washington as a symbol
of friendship between
their nations.
Careful! The security system
is very sensitive!
You don't want to
set off the alarm.
Let's go to the next room, where
we'll see the Statue of Liberty!
The Marquis de Lafayette was 19
when he participated
in the War of Independence.
So young, and already gifted
with an incredible ability
to galvanize people. He helped
Washington's troops win
the Battle of Yorktown.
Everyone thinks it was all due
to Lafayette's potential.
I think it was also due
to something special.
A Miraculous.
Nathalie,
you take care of Paris,
I'll take care of New York.
Nooroo, dark wings rise!
(Ominous music)
Techlonizer, I am Hawk Moth.
You were robbed of your
technological arsenal
by those heinous superheroes.
I can give you the power to
steal and clone any technology
so you can get
your revenge on them!
In exchange, you will
bring me Lafayette's sabre.
Wouldn't you rather have
an atomic bomb?
HAWK MOTH: No. I want the sabre.
France gave the Statue of
Liberty to America in 1886.
Gustave Eiffel
built the armature
for the inside of the statue!
Could you take a pic
of Lafayette's sabre?
I completely forgot,
and I must film Dean Gate!
Of course!
The real statue
has a hollow stone in its base,
containing
the Declaration of Independence.
I can't find my headphones.
Could you check the other room?
‐ I'll look here.
‐ No problem. I'm on it!
In this hollow stone, there's
also a safe that contains
artefacts left by the people
who unveiled the statue.
No one's opened it since.
I don't know about you all,
but I, for one, would love
to know what's inside that safe.
Uh, excuse me, sir, but, um...
why not use your superpower
to enter the door
that leads there?
Superpowers should never be used
for personal gain,
only for the greater good!
Besides, even if I got inside,
I couldn't open the safe,
because its key is in Paris,
‐ inside the Eiffel Tower.
‐ Wow!
‐ Uh... A‐Adrien?
‐ Marinette?
(Gasps) What's happening?
‐ That's strange.
‐ (Phone alert)
Akumatised villain, Robostus,
is spreading panic in Paris.
And, so far,
no sign of Ladybug and Cat Noir!
Robostus? But Markov can't
have been akumatised in Paris,
he's right here
in New York with us!
‐ What are they doing?
‐ I'm not sure.
But their stress levels are
high enough to engage Phase 2.
OK, go!
I am Solitude,
and I am here to take captive
of those who are
loved by no one!
(Rumbling)
(Ominous music)
(Evil laugh)
Techno‐Pirate! He escaped?
He seems more powerful.
But I can't read fully, as if...
magic was interfering
with my scanning tools!
(Action music)
Hey! I thought your thing
was new technology?
What are you planning to do?
Use the sabre as an antenna?
I don't have time
to play with annoying kids!
Cat Noir should have told me
Robustus is back.
‐ I hope he's not in trouble.
‐ What do we do?
Shouldn't we head back
ASAP to warn Ladybug?
Run, run! Come on!
Sparrow to United Heroes!
Enhanced Techno‐Pirate... Aaah!
This way, kids!
Let the adults handle this!
Your power is mine!
‐ What?
‐ Nobody escapes my sight!
Marinette's in danger!
Plagg, claws out!
(Action music)
Vacation is over!
Tikki, spots on!
(Action music)
Ladybug?
Cat Noir?
BOTH: What are you doing here?
Uh... It's a long story!
Where's Marinette?
I got her to safety. But why
aren't you back in Paris?
I'll explain later!
Nathalie, you can get rid
of the sentimonster.
We will no longer be needing it!
Let's see if I can
absorb you whole!
Aaah!
You've come from Paris
to help us out?
Yeah. We thought it'd be
friendly to give you a hand
in honour of Friendship Week!
See that? They don't need
permission to take action!
That's right.
He never asks for anything.
Do you, Cat Noir?
Sparrow, did you warn
Knight Owl and Majestia?
I couldn't,
but you know what?
We don't need
anyone's permission either!
Sure you want to step out
of the procedure?
It's our chance to prove
we're like these two,
autonomous, bonded together
by trust and super efficient!
"Just go and rest easy!
Leave Paris with me!"
I... I didn't know
I was going to leave!
It was a last‐minute decision,
that's all!
Do you realize there's no one
in Paris to protect the city?
LADYBUG: He's running away!
CAT NOIR:
You sound like Captain Obvious!
Why not tell me
you were leaving?
‐ I was afraid you'd get angry!
‐ And you were right,
because, as you can see,
I am angry!
Autonomous, bonded by trust
and super efficient?
Yeah, I might have
overestimated them.
Surrender, Techno‐Pirate!
There's nowhere to run now!
(Ominous music)
Cataclysm!
(Heroic music)
Lucky charm!
A bicycle pump? What are
you going to do with that?
I may have an idea,
but you wouldn't like it.
Why run away when I can
finally get me revenge
by eliminating the kids of
America's most beloved heroes!
I didn't tell you because
I feared losing your trust.
Well, I can't trust you
any longer, can I?
No!
HAWK MOTH:
That's it for now, Techlonizer.
What... What happened?
Get in. Leave the sabre behind.
What have you done?
It's my fault.
Why didn't you call us? And you,
what are you doing here?
‐ I might be able to help.
‐ Oh, really?
With your magical bicycle pump?
Precisely.
Miraculous Ladybug!
‐ (PC rebooting sound)
‐ Rebooting.
Oh, thank you, Ladybug!
‐ You two are too dangerous.
‐ No, they tried to ‐‐
So are you. You disobeyed me!
You were supposed to call us,
and didn't.
I order you to revert
to your civilian identities
and hand me your powers. We'll
return them when you leave.
We can't do that!
It's true we made a mistake,
but I've fixed everything!
If your power is fixing
his mistakes, we don't need you!
It's better like this.
What would have happened if
Uncanny hadn't been an android?
We can't give them
our Miraculous.
Stop right there!
That's an order!
(Panting)
OK! Let's feed our kwamis
and get back to Paris
to take care of Robostus.
Paris was attacked by a villain
who disappeared on his own.
‐ Clara Contard is on the scene.
‐ Parisians are surprised.
Why didn't
our superheroes step in?
And will Ladybug repair the
damages caused by the villain?
We waited too long
to return to Paris.
There's nothing
I can do any more.
Can't you just do
a lucky charm when we're back?
My power allows me
to create a magical object
that repairs damages
caused by a specific villain.
But the villain is already gone.
Then there's no longer
a chance for repairs?
It's all my fault.
You were perfect, as always.
Knight Owl is right to want
to confiscate my Miraculous.
I left Paris without
telling you.
I ruined everything.
And if Uncanny Valley
hadn't been a robot,
I would have caused
irreparable harm.
Spots off.
Claws in.
Please forgive me, my friend.
‐ No!
‐ I renounce you, Plagg.
What?
I never want to risk harming
anyone again. Least of all you.
Wait!
Cat Noir?
Ah! It's been a long time since
we stretched our wings, Gilbert!
‐ Gilbert? Mr Marquis?
‐ I was right.
The jewel was indeed
the Miraculous of the Eagle!
‐ You're not Gilbert.
‐ I am your new master.
Just like your former one,
I have a great dream to achieve.
And I believe you can help me.
Oh, you know, I'm just Liiri,
the kwami of Freedom.
My power is to free people
from anything
that prevents them
from reaching their potential.
Nothing too powerful!
(Nervous laugh)
Well, that potential
is all I need
to seize Ladybug and Cat Noir's
Miraculous!
‐ Adrien Agreste.
‐ He's not here, ma'am!
Neither is Marinette!
You had one mission... to keep
an eye on the French students!
We did! That's how we discovered
she was unclear about
her relationship with Adrien.
So, we created a villain
‐ to clarify their feelings.
‐ You did what?
‐ Barb. Honey.
‐ Mother, I don't understand.
You always say
that all that is necessary
for the triumph of evil is that
good people do nothing.
What did I do wrong?
My darling,
by trying to help them,
you've put the French students
and yourselves in danger.
Doing good doesn't
necessary mean fighting.
We tried to be helpful, because
we'd nothing better to do!
We're not babysitters,
we're superheroines!
Superheroes, whose mission was
to keep an eye on the students
and you failed!
You're forbidden to take part
in the hunt for Techno‐Pirate.
You're not ready.
How will I ever be ready if you
never let me spread my wings?
No one prohibits them
from fighting villains!
And I almost lost you
because of that.
Come on, Olympia.
We're expected.
(Phone alert)
This is all my fault.
I should've stopped him
from leaving!
He made his choice.
What were we supposed to do?
Mike Rochip,
AKA Techno‐Pirate,
is still on the run!
Until we capture him,
the French‐American friendship
ceremony will be postponed.
President Hombee is right.
Any mass gathering
would be too dangerous.
As long as Techno‐Pirate
roams free, we're asking you,
dear New Yorkers, dear guests,
to stay safe wherever you are!
Meanwhile, we will keep
patrolling the city
and won't rest
until we've captured him!
Release me!
I'm not done with me revenge!
All that anger... Who am I to
stop you from giving into it?
Techlonizer, I'm returning
your powers back to you!
And as a bonus,
to make it up to you
and allow you to fulfil
your fantasies of revenge,
I'll give you another weapon!
To receive your powers,
say, "Liiri, wings of prey."
‐ Marinette?
‐ Adrien?
Get in the car. I shouldn't
have listened to your friend.
This city is much too dangerous.
Dude, no! Stay!
I have to go.
I'm sorry, Marinette.
You fought so hard
for me to be here.
I wouldn't have minded being
stuck here a little longer
with a friend like you.
My father's right. I should have
never come to New York.
What is wrong with you,
Marinette?
Couldn't you see he was waiting
for you to tell him to stay?
What? But I...
He... he made his choice.
‐ What did you expect me to do?
‐ Never mind what I expected!
Who's Adrien to you?
A friend or more than that?
There'll never be
a better time to be clear!
Do you want him to leave
or do you want him to stay?
Adrien! Stay!
I've already lost Cat Noir,
I can't lose Adrien too!
No!
Come back!
You have to stay! Aaah!
Adrien... I... love you.
I wanna surrender!
I never wanted to stop the
French‐American Ceremony!
If I have to lose my freedom for
everyone to celebrate theirs,
then fine, I surrender!
Put me in jail!
I'll go first.
Whatever his powers may be,
I'm the only one he can't harm.
Don't be scared.
I genuinely wish for nothing
but your freedom! Liberation!
Majestia,
you're afraid of your own power.
I release you from your fear!
Ah! All the things
I never dared to try!
Wa‐ha‐ha! Too easy!
Knight Owl! Your morality keeps
you from bringing justice
more swiftly than you wish?
I release you
from your code of ethics!
Why should I show more leniency
than the people who show none?
You don't know how to park, huh?
Victory, you once swore
you would devote your life
to protecting people's freedom.
I release you from that promise!
You'll see who's leader
of the free world!
You will obey me!
No more freedom!
Door Man,
you can go anywhere you want,
but you resist personal
gain for the better good.
I release you from your qualms!
I've always wanted to visit
the Vatican Secret Archives!
No! I know! The Queen
of England's treasure room!
(Hysterical laugh)
Good job, Miraclonizer.
Now hook me up!
Ladybug, Cat Noir,
I'm in New York too!
If you don't want
the party to be ruined,
your only option is to hand
your Miraculous over to me.
‐ We have to go.
‐ They told us not to move,
‐ remember?
‐ Yes, but my mom
told me that being human meant
learning when to bend the rules.
Let's go!
We're the only ones left!
What if we fail?
Incorrect. Ladybug
and Cat Noir are here too!
Are you serious? They almost
deactivated you permanently!
We're dealing with a villain
with extra powers.
We have a zero probability
of success without them.
‐ But they're just teenagers!
‐ And so are we.
OK. You know what? We have to
give ourselves a chance,
because we are the last chance!
Statistically speaking,
that is correct.
But how will we find
Ladybug and Cat Noir?
No one can keep their identity
a secret from me.
OK. On one side there's me,
my basic training,
and zero weaponry.
On the other, an army
of powerful heroes gone insane.
Sounds evenly matched!
You didn't recycle
and you didn't return your book!
‐ You're both going to prison!
‐ That's not how you trained us.
I ordered you
to stay at the hotel!
Respect your leaders!
Marinette Dupain‐Cheng,
New York needs Ladybug.
I'm sorry.
I‐I‐I can't help you.
‐ I don't know her!
‐ Your suit's quantum masking
is meant to confuse humans'
minds, Ladybug. I am not human.
What?
Miraclonizer is an akumatised
Techno‐Pirate.
Which means Hawk Moth
is in New York too.
We cannot defeat them without
the girl who can fix everything.
I don't know if I can do this.
I can't imagine
being Ladybug without him.
This, I can fix!
(Heroic music)
Cat Noir!
New York and Ladybug need you.
I'm no longer Cat Noir.
To err is human, apparently.
My mistakes are unforgivable.
I couldn't bear to see
the disappointment in her eyes.
LADYBUG:
I don't know if I can do this.
I can't imagine
being Ladybug without him.
Your lady is waiting for you.
‐ Glad to see you again, Plagg!
‐ No need to get so cheesy!
‐ Who are you talking to?
‐ My kwami.
Kwamis can't be detected
by technology,
which means your robobuddy
can't see or hear me.
(Makes mocking sounds)
There's no time to lose.
We have to get back!
Plagg, claws out!
(Heroic music)
We've got to break the object
where the akuma is.
I bet it's in his handcuffs.
He had them on, at the museum.
Something else has changed.
He was wearing the necklace
‐ Lafayette gave Washington.
‐ (Gasps) A Miraculous!
That would explain his power
upgrade. Good insight, Milady!
Don't ever do that to me again!
I'm sorry. I was so afraid
to disappoint you
that I didn't dare tell you
the truth. I was so stupid.
Miraclonizer! It's time to
proceed to the next step!
Give me that!
Ladybug, Cat Noir, if the rocket
were to take off because of you,
a world war would be declared!
Unless you give me
your Miraculous, of course!
You have five minutes!
Tick‐tock, tick‐tock...
OK.
The first thing we need to do
is seize
Miraclonizer's Miraculous.
That way, we'll break the spell
and free the adults,
and in turn they'll help us
de‐akumatise him!
But we can't get near him!
Nothing's impossible
for Ladybug.
Lucky Charm!
So we're supposed to defeat
superheroes with a key chain?
‐ Interesting.
‐ Yes. Well...
as soon as I figure out
how to use it.
Four minutes 35...
four minutes 34...
Uncanny, can you show me how
the Statue of Liberty is built?
Look!
There's a ladder inside the arm
‐ that leads to the platform.
‐ Awesome!
But how will we get inside when
there's an army attacking us?
BOTH: Door Man!
Thanks to his tele‐doortation
power, he could get us
inside the statue unnoticed.
But Door Man only uses his power
to satisfy his own curiosity.
‐ He'll never agree to help us.
‐ Besides, how will we find him?
He could be anywhere!
By using his curiosity
to our advantage!
Sparrow, grab a cardboard box
and that newspaper
and make a giftbox!
Uncanny!
Dear sir, we got you
a little gift to thank you
for our day at the museum!
We hope you enjoy the surprise!
Meet you on Liberty Island!
Good luck!
Kids?
(Laughs)
"We know how fascinating
you think keys are,
so we hope you like this."
Signed, Jess and Aeon!
Of course!
That's where
I should have started!
Here it is! The key!
The one that opens the safe
hidden in the statue!
No! At least let me see
what's inside the safe!
Only a few seconds left!
I'll take that!
Sparrow!
Hello, fledgling!
All you have to say is,
"Liiri, Wings of Liberty!"
Liiri, Wings of Liberty!
Cool down!
They can't say
I didn't warn them.
Ladybug, Cat Noir!
This be your last chance
to give me your Miraculous!
BOTH: Never!
(Ominous music)
(Heroic music)
Cataclysm!
No more evildoing for you,
little akuma!
Time to de‐evilise!
Gotcha!
Bye‐bye, little butterfly!
Miraculous Ladybug!
Seriously, what happened?
Keep it.
I know you'll use it well.
I've disobeyed again,
which means...
I'll never get
my weapons back, right?
With the powers
of the Miraculous,
you won't need them anymore.
And I was wrong.
My little sparrow was ready
to become a fearsome eagle.
Thank you, Mom!
I mean, thank you... sir!
It doesn't matter anymore.
With this new suit, everyone
now knows Sparrow is a female,
not a male, and that
the legendary Knight Owl
and Sparrow are long gone.
Maybe it's a sign.
That the time has come
to embrace who we really are!
And even though it still worries
us, the only way for you to grow
is for us
to let you take chances.
Thank you for inspiring them.
And please forgive us
for misjudging you.
ALL: Pound it!
My theory was correct.
There are other lost Miraculous.
And wherever they are
in the world, they will be mine!
Uncanny, what about
our secret identities?
Don't worry.
Once we've said goodbye,
I'll erase this information
from my memory.
Thank you for bringing
us back together.
I'll see you back in Paris,
Milady!
The Mayor's office
has set to work
to repair the damage
Robostus caused in Paris.
We did miss our local heroes,
Ladybug and Cat Noir,
but for good reason.
At the same moment,
they were busy saving New York!
Marinette, everyone's
waiting for you. Remember?
The surprise for Adrien,
your "friend"?
Oh! I don't know, Alya.
We're going back
to Paris tomorrow.
You can ask yourself
the question then. Come on.
HELLO ADRIEN!
Oh, Chloé! I'm so glad to see
you're finally having some fun!
Of course not! I'm only happy
because we're leaving tomorrow!
Now you're a big puffy cloud.
(Heroic music)
Now the Eagle's Miraculous
has been found,
it must return to its box.
I have come a long way,
so give it back with no fuss.
‐ I'm not in the mood.
‐ Negative!
Eagle has proved that she is
a worthy Miraculous holder!
Why not stay here?
We could create a new generation
of heroes together!
"Golchindl.net"