fTiming and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ No longer panicking on the night of the blackout ♫
♫ You're by my side, illuminating a beam of light for me ♫
♫ Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet ♫
♫ Your breath ♫
♫ brushes up against my cheek ♫
♫ With you warming up the stage,
happiness never comes to a close ♫
♫ Boring jokes add some sweetness to the dinner ♫
♫ Daily life is even more like a comic than comics themselves ♫
♫ Happiness and sadness ♫
♫ Make up the moments of life ♫
♫ Rainy days become very special because of you ♫
♫ Picked up a pitiful youngster off the street ♫
♫ No matter when and where, you always appear ♫
♫ Holding me tightly and spinning in circles ♫
♫ Rainy days make me so nostalgic because of you ♫
♫ Becoming some part of the memories ♫
♫ Walking down a street with lights lighting up
one after another ♫
♫ Warming up the whole world ♫
[Please Feel at Ease Mr. Ling]
[Episode 19]
- How come you're back?
- I forgot to bring some materials.
I bought you breakfast on the way back.
I... I'm exercising.
[Cai Niao]
What's unexpected is that that person appeared in your universe.
I don't understand why you won't give yourself a chance to start over.
Must you run into a wall and get covered in bruises before you're willing to turn around?
- Come in.
- President Gu.
These are the fruits and snacks that Mr. Ling Sheng ordered for you.
- Did he order them today?
- Oh, no.
A few days ago, Mr. Ling Sheng bought you an annual subscription to the company's group order service.
It provides you with exclusive snacks and fruits on schedule.
He even drew up a full year's worth of sticky note messages.
[Flower Cookies]
Thank you. You can go now.
I will work hard. See you next time.
Come in.
President Gu, this is yesterday's balance sheet.
Got it.
- Will President Sheng be coming today?
- No.
I was just about to tell you that before he left, President Sheng
asked me to give you this company publicity plan.
[Star Company Plan]
[Part 2 - Project Description]
When were these pictures taken?
These were all taken by President Sheng himself.
In fact, President Sheng specifically told us
not to tell you. He was afraid it would disrupt your work.
Okay, I understand.
Once I've decided on the content, I'll let you know.
Alright, you go ahead.
[New Way]
President Wang, you looked it over quite quickly. This is not a small number.
President Ling, you must be joking. Who in this field doesn't know your capability?
Your interest in collaborating with us is our honor.
I'd be eager to pay even more.
President Ling, when you announce your Lingxiao Plan at an event as grand as the e-commerce summit meeting,
I'm sure it will be the focus of millions.
I look forward to seeing New Way's performance.
Thank you for your trust. Rest assured,
- I will not let you down.
- Of course.
Happy collaboration.
President Ling, I hear New Way has already received financing for its newest project. Is that true?
That's correct. For a project that New Way has not yet announced,
we have already received one billion yuan in the first round of financing.
Included are distribution, property,
Internet, and hundreds of other leading enterprises in different domains.
New Way's new project will promote development in all areas.
I have full confidence that our shareholders will receive  a rich repayment.
Did I wake you up?
Anxin, how come you're here?
I missed you, so I came.
I brought you a bento. Do you want to see it?
You made it so cute, I feel bad eating it.
If you perform well in the future, I'll give you a reward.
Because I have the only secret book.
Where did you learn this from?
When I was little, my brother and I would give each other rewards like this.
Then I want to eat this everyday from now on.
What would be special about it if you ate it everyday?
I didn't put any vinegar in it,
but some people seem to eat a lot of vinegar.
("Eat vinegar" means to be jealous)
Why is that?
Don't be unhappy.
Is this that 5G+ distribution warehouse you spoke of,
the Lingxiao Plan?
It looks so advanced and convenient.
This is the original motive I had in establishing New Way.
I always hoped that one day,
I could use real technology to make people's lives easier.
Your way of thinking is so awesome.
This has always been my dream.
But now that it's going to be released,
I feel a little nervous and uneasy.
Ling Yue, not everyone can find a goal to fight for.
But you've found your goal, and you're fighting for it.
And you've done so well.
You are the star of good fortune itself.
So don't think about anything.
Just bravely go and do it.
At worst, I'll provide for you.
Then I'll count on you to provide for me.
Okay!
President Ling.
Look at this.
Our Gu Group is currently reconsidering B2C (business to consumer) operations.
At the same time, we are in the process of remodeling our distribution value.
We have formed exclusive partnerships with with many famous domestic companies.
We will be the first in the country to register our 5G+ distribution warehouse business.
The Anxing Plan we have advanced
will lead the new structure of the e-commerce era.
This Anxing Plan, whether considering the marketing standpoint or the central technology,
is exactly the same as our Lingxiao Plan.
Has there been any trend on the side of the Lingxiao Plan?
A majority of the investors have already begun to withdraw their capital.
Hold an urgent meeting. Start up the first degree warning plan.
President Gu, after the Plan A was implemented
the Gu stocks have risen aggressively.
The closing rate has grown by 20%, and our Inn can benefit as well.
He's already chosen a dangerous path.
We'll have to see if the following effect can match predictions.
As of yesterday and today, we have lost 20 million.
Of the companies under us, 20 face bankruption.
Our stocks are at its lowest since 2015.
We've just received large amounts of order cancellations from our collaborative businesses, including President Wang.
Many investors have decided to pull out.
Even the Ling Group's stock prices have suffered varying levels of decrease.
The Group's Board of Directors and Board of Supervisors have all arrived. Things are not going well.
That's right. Overnight, our investors have withdrawn more than 100 million in investments.
Stocks are plummeting now. So scary.
As the person managing the company, you made the incorrect decision in your plan against Ling Xiao
and inadequately managed potential dangers, leading to great losses for the company.
The Group's Board of Directors have decided
to temporarily withdraw your authority over New Way.
This unfortunate decision was made in consideration of the company's future development.
After the meeting, the stockholders have the right to limit your company's email,
server, import and export, as well as the mobile information within your work.
New Way has not reached the point of no return.
You want me to throw away New Way to save myself. Was this the old man's orders?
No. This was the entire Board of Director's decision.
This was also after our strict risk assessment.
We all believe this is the best way of decreasing risk at the moment.
President Ling, only by throwing away the small things can the greater good be saved.
Don't hurt the entire Group's benefit for just New Way.
Anxin! Anxin! Come look.
What is it again? Your idol's getting flamed again?
This time it's...your idol.
[Sorry, We Don't Understand New Way]
-Who did this?
-Don't be upset yet.
I'll use my side account to counter for you.
You can't respond to all these attacks one by one.
You'll just end up causing more negative consequences.
Right now, the most important thing is finding the attacker's origin and goal.
That origin could quite possibly be the Gu Group.
After all, if the Ling family falls, they receive the greatest benefit.
Return money! Return money! Return money!
Return money! Return money!
President Ling, let's go back to the company first.
[Give my blood money back!]
Return money!
President Ling! President Ling! Let's go back to the company first!
You've come back. Good work.
You've waited for me this late again?
I haven't seen you in so many days. I wanted to wait and sleep together with you.
I'm sorry. I've been too busy recently.
Has the company run into a problem?
No. I'm just too busy.
There really isn't? You've lost weight.
Don't worry. It's really nothing.
Then go take a bath and sleep early.
Ok.
That origin could quite possibly be Gu Group.
After all, if the Ling family falls, they receive the greatest benefit.
Hi Brother, just at the Evolution Coffee Shop we often go to.
Ok. See you then.
[Evolution]
We...haven't seen each other in a long time.
Brother. Are you really attacking New Way?
You came to see me because of him?
To tell you the truth, yes. I really do want to destroy New Way.
If it wasn't for him, the person standing next to you would be me.
-Why are you doing this?
-Why?
Why do you think I won't do this?
Because I trust that you aren't someone who would do something like this.
Anxin. I don't want such trust.
Your trust has given me pain for too long.
I only want you back by my side. Ok?
Ling Yue cannot hang on for much longer. I will give you everything you want.
Brother...these are two different matters.
Even if Ling Yue has nothing, I will still stay by his side.
Do I not even have a chance?
In my heart, you've always been my closest relative, my brother.
Only that.
Stop fighting with Ling Yue.
Anxin.
There's no regret in each chess piece movement.*(No regret for any action)
Ling Yue's current situation can only be blamed on his incorrect judgment. No one else is to blame.
If that's so,
then I hope you won't act brashly.
And turn into someone you don't even recognize.
I'm leaving.
So no matter how many times this person hurts you!
As long as he needs you, you will run to him without abandon?
Then have you ever thought that
I also need you.
I'm sorry, Brother. I'm a little lost right now.
Let's both calm down...
Why must I always leave the person I love?
I can't give you happiness?
I'm also warning you. Anxin is mine.
I will take care of her.
Brother!
Ling Yue.
New Way's current dilemma is a result of the market's strong suppress weak situation.
I know you don't feel good losing,
but I never thought you would have Anxin come talk to me.
Anxin really went to find you?
You don't need to pretend with me.
Ling Yue, I will use all of my strength to defeat you.
You can't win.
I am Gu Anxin's brother.
What do you want to explain?
Explain how you're wavering between my two sisters?
-Brother!
-Let's go.
Don't-
This President Ling claims he wants to see you.
Is it really nothing or do you have something to hide? You know what it is.
If you let her get hurt one more time,
I will take her back.
Next, we have reached our e-commerce conference's climax.
Let us welcome the founder of Plan An,
the CEO of Gu Group, Mister Gu Ansheng,
to introduce this plan to us.
[Plan An]
Everyone, I believe you have seen all you need to know about our Plan A across all the media platforms.
I won't speak more of our plan's pros and cons.
All I can say now is
the opening for investments is no longer big. Very soon,
the Gu Group will become the largest company in this country's e-commerce business.
President Gu speaks of bold claims.
Ling Yue?
-Why did he come?
-I heard New Way's in danger from recent incidents,
but it doesn't seem so just looking at him.
Is there going to be a turn around?
Young President Gu,
is widely divergent from the Gu Group's
usual boring style. I admire that.
Don't worry. I came today, because I think New Way's innovation ideal
and Gu Group's 5G plan are identical.
Our New Way will wholeheartedly support Gu Group's Plan A.
And will open up collaboration both online and off.
President Ling, do you mean that
New Way will give up on their current 5G proposal
and invest in a similar proposal under the Gu Group?
Earlier, it was rumored that New Way will sue Gu Group,
because Gu Group's Plan A violates the rights of New Way's unannounced project.
Those are all rumors. You media should be most clear about that.
Remember! In the market,
there are no everlasting enemies.
I have high hopes for Gu Group's Plan A. New Way will support it with all out strength.
A plan that even the Ling Group speaks highly of must have unlimited potential.
However, if we want to fight for this fresh piece of meat, we must speed up our steps.
Ling Yue, what tricks are you playing again?
Speaking of tricks...President Gu is the master.
Since you've lost, isn't it better to leave respectably?
Won't this...make it harder for you?
The final result hasn't been released yet, and President Gu has declared himself victor.
I'm afraid it's too early.
Could you have a way to win everything back?
How do you know I can't? Anyways,
even if New Way loses, we lost honorably.
As for you, you only used various excuses and changed your name.
You've announced what was originally New Way's Heaven Reaching Plan.
Even the core technology is identical.
Stealing all these things before New Way's announcement.
President Gu sure has considered everything.
Hey, maintain a smile.
So much media are looking at us.
Don't worry.
As long as you have the will to work with me,
many people will believe your Gu Group.
Steal.
This word is more suitable for you, President Ling.
Don't think there's nothing you, Ling Yue, can't steal.
If at the time I...confessed to Anxin first,
do you think you'd still have a chance?
You have no right to mention Anxin.
If you think Anxin's rejection is because you were late a step,
then you are insulting Anxin.
You have no right to have her.
From today on,
in both work and relationship,
I will not lose to you because I was late a step.
What is mine...I will
take it back bit by bit.
Then you have to speed up,
or else
you might not be able to withstand what's coming.
I'll fight you to the end.
President Liu.
Do you not owe me an explanation?
When you proposed this 5G plus a logistics warehouse to me,
I don't think you mentioned this was New Way's project.
President Ling, why didn't you directly say to the media that the Gu Group stole our plan?
We haven't announced this plan before.
The lawsuit will be hard to win. The Gu Group haven't entered capital yet.
Even if we proved they violated our rights, there won't be any true impact.
Then...it seems you already know how to make a true impact.
Do you remember the Xuefei Technology in charge of Heaven Reaching Plan's video messaging technology?
I remember.
At the time, we wanted to buy their technology at a high price.
But the discussion was never settled.
That's right.
The only reason he wasn't willing to sell us the technology was because he never planned on selling it.
He is someone who views ownership of his own technology as extremely important. He definitely won't sell it to anyone.
So...the Gu Group couldn't have convinced them and implemented the plan so quickly.
Unless...Gu Ansheng doesn't know this technology belongs to Xuefei.
That's right.
If President Liu wants implement Plan An in a short amount of time, then he must withhold Xuefei's situation from Gu Ansheng.
Ling Yue is no threat to us.
You only need to welcome future profits.
Us Gu Group only wants steady development.
Not to draw enemies or invite trouble.
President Gu, I promise you.
The Gu Group will be the greatest winner.
Right now, if New Way supports them, it will definitely peak Xuefei's interest.
Xuefei can then sue Gu Group
saying they stole business secrets. By that time...
By that time, it'll be hard for Gu Group to defend themselves.
Counter someone with their methods.
I just don't want him to have the ability to counterattack.
President Gu, after the e-commerce conference we've received word from many investors.
They all hope to collaborate with us.
So quickly?
They've all seen the future of Plan An.
Alright. Go plan it, and I will see them personally.
Ok.
Hello.
President Gu, bad news.
One of the technologies within Plan A violates rights.
Last night, the related company has sued us.
Also, the media has already reported it this morning, and the internet has related evidence.
It seems like a well planned chain of events.
Technology violation?
How can that be? There shouldn't be a problem with our project implementation.
Where's President Liu right now?
We haven't been able to contact him.
The investors are all trying to withdraw investment, but this batch of investments have already been placed into production.
What should we do now?
Wait until I'm there. I'll head over now.
The Gu Group that obtained endless glory from Plan A
has suffered a plummet in stocks due to reports of fraudulent technology.
And due to various cases of deceiving customers, a loophole in supply,
problems with quality and safety, the Gu Group is endangered.
The opposing company claims Plan A involves a large amount of technology stealing and has revealed related evidence.
They also claim Gu Group has stolen their creation. Can you respond to this?
The Gu Group's stocks has suffered greatly since this morning.
Is this because Gu Group will find it difficult to deal with this situation?
-Then what about the money put in by investors?
-That's right, President Gu!
Please respond, President Gu!
President Gu! Does Gu Group have lawyer statement? President Gu!
President Gu! President Gu, please respond! President Gu!
How will Gu Group face-
Where's my brother?
The media and investors have surrounded the company entrance to ask that Gu Group repay their investments.
Right now, President Gu can only live in a hotel and can't reveal himself publicly.
No pictures! No pictures!
-No pictures!
-Please respond.
No pictures! No pictures!
President Ling, the Gu Group's stocks have been frozen for 5 business days. Should we continue following?
Continue.
I understand.
Let's go and eat!
-Let's go!
-Time to eat...
It's up to you then!
What's wrong? Is there something you forgot again?
Do you have business with me?
Of course I have business with you.
The Gu Group's stocks have been frozen...
What? Something as major as this and you're together with Ling Yue everyday.
You're pretending you don't know?
Ling Yue's been busy recently, and I haven't seen him in many days. What's the situation?
New Way's attacked and completely impacted Gu Group.
My brother's been heavily impacted.
He's like a zombie everyday and can't even return home.
Gu Group's almost over too.
How is it? Are you happy now?
You've had your revenge. Are you satisfied now?
What revenge?
I told you I'm not aware of this matter!
Stop pretending to be a good person.
If it wasn't for you,
would my brother and Ling Yue be fighting like this?
If it wasn't for you rejecting my brother,
would he risk everything to fight with Ling Yue?
Everything is because of you.
Gu Anxin, I advise you.
Don't affect two businesses because of one person's feelings.
The Gu Group's lost so much market value overnight.
How many people's sweat and efforts have gone to waste?
You have no right.
I'm sorry. The user you are contacting is unavailable at the moment.
Please dial again in a moment.
Brother, how are you? Call me when you see this.
What do we do now? People from Gu Group is pursuing me everywhere.
There's no place for me to hide.
Boss wants you to lie low till this has died down.
Didn't we say this was a big slice of cake? How did it turn out this way?
It's definitely a big slice of cake
but it must be eaten slowly so that we don't choke.
Director Liu, you are too anxious.
Boss, what do we do next?
I planned to implicate Gu Ansheng with New Way.
I didn't expect that Ling Yue would avoid the trap and it brought down Gu Group instead.
But it's not without any gains. Don't be lax and keep monitoring.
Understood.
You are back.
I have been too busy lately and didn't come home often.
You won't blame me?
Why have you been so busy lately?
Is there a problem at the company?
It's fine. Work's almost done.
What about your Ling Xiao plan? How is it going?
Not bad. The progress is going without hitches.
That's all?
What's wrong?
What else are you hiding from me?
Gusheng came to see me.
If he didn't tell me,
I wouldn't have known you are so inflexible.
It's common to have competition in the market. Things are not that simple as you think.
But you could have told me.
I didn't want you to worry.
I can worry about you. I'm willing to worry about you.
If every time when you are in a helpless situation and I have to find out from someone else,
who am I to you then?
Because I'm the other side of Gu Ansheng.
I knew you care about this.
How could I not care
about you interrogating me,
being partial to him? How could I not care?
Gu Ansheng brought this upon himself because he messed with me first.
Ling Yue, I think there must be some misunderstanding.
What's your confirmation based on?
Taking into account that I have known him for many years.
Yes.
You have known him for many years.
Yes, I can't be compared to him.
So, you think I'm asking you about this because I'm protecting him?
Isn't that so? Aren't you believing what he said and feel bad about him?
If we have known each other for a long time
and we are now caught in-between by someone,
and you don't have any trust in me at all,
there's nothing to be said then.
If this is what you think, I have nothing to say.
President Ling, Gu Group's shares are now at the lower limit.
The investors withdrew their funds. The company assets have depreciated by around 40 percent.
Our plan to short-sell Gu Group is approaching.
It has always been the patient who doesn't make appointments with the doctor. I have never seen people like you.
You and Ling Yue dragged till now before you are here.
I wouldn't have come if it's not to make the payment.
You are so stark in your public display of affections.
What are you talking about? He hasn't been home for a few days.
You both fought?
We didn't.
He's too busy.
[File : Maria's First Hospital]
Why is the hospital file in your possession?
It's Maria's First Hospital. It's the first hospital where I interned at.
I kept these records after I left.
Why are you asking this?
Many years ago, my father did the paternity test at this hospital.
But I think there's a problem with the paternity test.
Problem with the paternity test?
How is this possible? Tell me who's the unscrupulous doctor. See if I know him.
I heard that
he specialized in hematology.
The specialist in hematology? Could he be...
Jiang Tao?
Yes, it's Jiang Tao. That's him.
How is this possible?
He's my most brilliant teacher,  professional and life mentor.
He has thirty years of work experience.
It could be a problem with the link or you remember incorrectly.
In fact, I thought there was a problem with the link.
Since it's in the past, I should let it go
but my mom passed away because of this.
Hence, I still want to get to the bottom of this.
Let's do this. Tell me the specific details,
date and time of the test.
I will ask my teacher on your behalf.
- Can this be done?
- Yes.
This is very important to me. If it can be done, thank you very much.
Okay. I will call you if I have the results.
[Hospital of Binhai New City, Beilun District]
- Older Sister Xuan.
- Xiao Xiao, here to see Doctor Jiang again?
He's on his rounds. Take a seat in his office now.
Okay, I'm going there.
[Paternity Test Record of Gu Anxin]
[Mp file for 7 October]
[Downloading and saving documents]
[Downloading and saving, 70% completed...]
It's you, Little Rascal. Which wind blew you here?
I'm making an enquiry on behalf of a friend
and ordered some nice food for you at the same time.
Thanks.
Take it that you have a conscience for knowing my taste.
Teacher, were you always working at Maria's First Hospital in the past?
That's right. Isn't there where I first met you, Little Rascal?
You were the intern then and most gifted.
You were also the one who dared to take on hardships.
You taught me well.
Teacher, someone entrusted me to ask you about something.
There's something I would like to ask you.
Speak.
I have a friend, Gu Anxin.
She did a paternity test here
but she feels there's a mistake.
Thus, I would like to ask if you have any impression of this.
Gu Anxin?
That's right.
Generally speaking, if there's was misdiagnosis,
I would have an impression.
Gu Anxin?
I don't seem to have any impression.
Okay. If you recall anything,
please let me know. This is...
very important to her.
Okay.
Teacher, I'm leaving now.
Your fans broke the ten thousand record.
It's time for me to let this agent take the stage. Is anyone secretly shooting?
n
I think this is the charm of a good assistant.
- He doesn't think so.
- Are you both still fighting?
What's up, Doctor Xiao?
Regarding your paternity test,
I have been following up on it
and discovered some doubts. Is Yu Gao your classmate who was injured then?
Yes. Her name is Yu Gao.
[Maria's First Hospital. Results of Patient Yu Guo]
[Conclusion : Exclusive amount of alprazolam in the blood, serious allergy]
What's the meaning of this?
Yu Gao's injury wasn't due to a fall from a high place?
It's part of the reason for the injury
however, the main reason for the disability of the patient
is due to the detection of alprazolam in her blood
which led to severe damage to the nerves in her arm.
Then...this is to say...
This is to say, my teacher falsified Yu Gao's report.
I don't quite understand.
Why did he do this? There's no feud between us.
I didn't understand too.
Hence, when I found this case study of patient's report,
I went to my teacher's office.
He has a habit of recording his patients.
I found this audio file which is related to Yu Guo's report.
Dr Jiang, you must help me regarding Yu Guo.
I can't.
You are involved in forging the report of Gu Anxin's paternity test too.
You forced me to do this.
You were negligent in your final analysis.
If this were to be exposed, you should the consequences.
As long as you help me for this,
regarding Gu Anxin's paternity report,
it will be like a rock sunk into the bottom of the ocean.
Yang Hong.
We are family. No need to be formal.
Your mother is my good friend.
I'm responsible for this too.
It's normal for you to blame me.
Yang Hong and Teacher Jiang Tao were working together in the Department of Hematology.
She knew Teacher Jiang Tao was in-charge of your paternity test.
She secretly dropped this blood sample.
There was a problem with the paternity test.
That's how my mom eventually turned out like that.
Yang Hong's father was Teacher Jiang Tao's mentor.
When Yu Gao had an accident,
Teacher Jiang Tao happened to be promoted to Associate Doctor.
Yang Hong used the error in the paternity test and his promotion to threaten him.
He tampered with Yu Guo's case report
and pushed the reason for her disability to the staircase incident.
Why did he do this to me?
Madam, Miss Anxin's looking for you.
Anxin is here? Let her in.
Anxin is here.
It has been a long time. I miss you.
Come in and take a seat.
Auntie, I don't have any other matters today.
I merely want to verify certain matters with you.
What are they?
Do you still remember Doctor Jiang?
I met Doctor Jiang a long time ago
but we haven't been in contact.
The DNA report that he did for me,
had a problem with it. Do you know about this?
Problem with the paternity report?
I really have no idea.
Because I trust my mother.
She wouldn't do anything to wrong my father.
However, if the paternity report is wrong,
it clearly means that someone forged the report.
Or perhaps, the blood sample was swopped.
This happened a long time ago.
Anxin, I have this piece of advice for you.
Who hasn't been young once? Who hasn't made mistakes?
That's right.
Why should the younger generation be embroiled
with matters that happened in the previous generation?
Your father is just being stubborn
but he's worried about you.
Ever since your mother passed away,
we hope to treat you as our biological daughter
and give you whatever you want.
We hope you will live well.
Auntie Hong, I know
you treated me well for the past years.
Including when you treated me well with Xin'er when we were in school.
I remember this.
By the way, Auntie, do you still remember Yu Guo?
I don't have any impression. Who is she?
My schoolmate who had an accident then.
Ever since she showed up at the Gu family's banquet and disappeared after that,
I found some schoolmates to investigate this.
Some found a video evidence in their cellphones
which can prove that accident
was not related to me.
Of course, it's good to have new evidence.
Moreover,  I have always believed that it was unintentional.
However, this happened a long time ago.
Don't keep dwelling on this.
One should look forward instead.
If we still haven't figured out the past,
how can we look forward?
This is not what I meant.
Aren't you and Ling Yue doing well now?
Of course, Ling Yue and you are free to fall in love with each other. I don't have the rights to interfere
however,
taking into account that you and Xin'er are sisters,
can you not make it hard for her?
Of course, if you have problems,
I can still help.
I like you very much. I will still help you.
It's not easy for a girl to be out there alone.
Auntie, don't worry.
Ling Yue and I are doing well.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Memories are soaked in rain ♫
♫ Fate works bizarrely ♫
♫ The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly beats abnormally ♫
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Obviously, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness, for it has always been you ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Yet the longing has never been able to stop ♫
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Using all of my most beautiful adjectives ♫
♫ Is still not enough to describe your name ♫
♫ Our story is exclusively ours ♫
♫ Our palms hold onto the key to the future ♫
♫ Using love to slowly open up a lifetime ♫