=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 5=
I just saw...
The Ancestral God
was really harsh on you
when you were a kid.
I’m used to it.
I used to be a loner.
And I will still be one in the future.
What are you doing?
Don’t push me away. I have injuries.
Bai Jue.
Not everyone is indifferent
and timid in the world.
The relationship between people
should be kind and warm.
From now on,
I will always be with you.
I’ll accompany you to cultivate,
study and drink.
When the weather is clear,
we can go out to fly a kite.
From now on,
I won’t leave you alone anymore.
♪I can’t help missing the past♪
♪What’s in my hand is
what I can’t get over♪
♪How are we destined to meet♪
♪Tide rushes and the moon rises♪
♪The trip takes a thousand years♪
♪Wake up the clouds♪
♪But can’t wake up the helpless love♪
♪It’s dreamlike♪
♪And it’s also aimless♪
♪For one single glance at you♪
♪I don’t regret cultivating myself♪
♪Even if I have to love alone♪
♪I’ll never stop loving you♪
I’m doomed! I’m doomed!
When Zhiyang comes back tomorrow,
I’m afraid I will be sent to the lower realm
for tens of thousands of years
and can’t come back.
What’s the big deal?
I’ll take the wine to see you.
You know nothing!
Am I afraid of living without drinking?
I’m afraid
I won’t be able to see Shanggu!
Then I won’t pay a visit to you,
so that you don’t even have a drink.
Yuemi, I didn’t mean that.
Of course you are very important to me.
But think about it.
I had an illustrious life,
waiting for ten thousand years.
Now I am about to be together
with Shanggu.
Why it could be messed up by these two?
What do you say?
Sorry.
This is my own trouble.
I will take all the blame tomorrow.
Is that true?
I’m serious.
Good friend!
Then you stay here.
I’m going to see Shanggu.
Little Day, I miss you!
Where are you?
- Little Night!
- Little Day!
Little Night!
Little Day!
- Little Day!
- Little Night!
- Puhua’s Rope of Love…
- Little Day!
- When did it work?
- I miss you!
- Even the True God can’t stand it.
- Little Night!
Yuemi, hold on!
I cannot make it!
- Little Night!
- Little Day!
Why are they so strong?
Little Night!
Come here!
Our God Realm finally has a happy event!
What?
Master Bai Jue, why is that you?
Why are you here?
I didn’t know that
God Puhua has such a wonderful place.
Master, forgive me.
Yesterday, the sun and the moon
went dark together.
I was too far away
to see it clearly.
So it was you
who entered the secret room yesterday?
How’s the lady who followed you in?
Is this place laid for Tianqi?
This joy room…
Yes.
It’s Master Tianqi who asked me
to help arrange it.
But he didn’t come yesterday,
and you came in.
I really don’t know why this happened.
Why did he arrange this?
Well… This is for
his date with Shanggu.
Shanggu and he
had a deep friendship since little.
Now Shanggu has grown up.
Master Tianqi
will ponder their date every day
to marry Shanggu home.
He even let me
play matchmaker.
Did you?
Yes, but it didn’t work.
How can I be a matchmaker
for gods in God Realm?
I just couldn’t let them be together.
That’s weird.
Did the turmoil yesterday…
Did I even get Shanggu wrong?
You even mistook me and Tianqi
who have so many differences.
Not to mention Shanggu.
Yes, yes. It’s all my fault!
You’re not qualified to be a matchmaker
for True Gods.
Don’t mind our business in the future.
As the Chief God, Shanggu
bears the responsibility
of heaven and earth.
How can her love be arranged casually?
Tianqi went a little too much.
You’re right, True God Bai Jue.
This time I was indeed inconsiderate.
I promise that from now on,
I will never arrange any date
for Shanggu.
I’ll let her be single
for 100,000 years!
Master Bai Jue, yesterday…
Oh! Nothing happened yesterday!
I am really old!
I’m really confused.
After the banquet was over yesterday,
I...
I went back to the cave to rest early.
Right?
Just leave.
Yes, yes. I’m leaving.
I’m leaving.
Weren’t I dreaming just now, right?
You were not!
True God Bai Jue really holds a lady!
Oh my goodness!
This…
Who is that lady?
I do not know.
Ancestral God bless us.
Our God Realm is going to gossip!
God of Day and God of Night,
after you two fell in love,
regardless of the rules,
you privately went to the lower realm.
You turned the day and night upside down,
causing a catastrophe.
Do you admit your guilt?
Master, it is all my fault.
Yesterday, I forcibly led the God of Day
to the lower realm.
That’s why we made a big mistake.
Master, no matter
how harsh the punishment is,
I’ll assume to myself all the blame.
Please don’t blame the God of Day.
True God Zhiyang,
I forcibly let the God of Night
go to the lower realm with me.
It’s my fault
and it has nothing to do with him!
Please don’t blame the God of Night.
No, it’s me who couldn’t help
and made a big mistake!
It has nothing to do
with the God of Day.
The God of Night…
God of Day and God of Night,
Puhua has cut off the Rope of Love
for you.
Is the affection between you true?
It begins with a misunderstanding,
stuck in acquaintance,
and becomes loyal to love.
Me, too.
Enough.
Even if you two
have such a reasonable excuse,
you were indeed wrong.
You must be punished severely.
Master, what’s wrong to like someone?
Which rule stipulates
the two of them can’t be together?
Nonsense!
You are also a senior in the God Realm.
Day and night are not allowed
to be at the same time.
It is the law of nature!
It’s known to all three-year-old kids!
It doesn’t need to be written
in the rules!
It’s not their fault anyway.
Yesterday I accidentally threw
Puhua’s Rope of Love on them.
That’s why they went to the lower realm
regardless of their responsibilities.
I am also responsible.
I shouldn’t have set a Dating Event.
Puhua.
You were doing right.
You were just following Tianqi’s orders.
It’s you, Yuemi.
I won’t blame you for messing around
in normal times.
Can’t you tell the importance
of this matter?
Yuemi.
You always blame yourself
for everything.
That’s a bad habit.
When can you change it?
Tianqi.
I am a real man.
One should answer for what he does.
I just drank some wine and
threw a Rope of Love on them.
Just do what’s necessary.
Master Tianqi.
You are the True God.
Why do you want to protect Goddess Yuemi?
And this rope is obviously her…
What hers?
I prepared it for me and Shanggu.
What’s the big deal?
You talk nonsense!
What are you doing?
You can hold the Dating Event
without telling me.
But you even talk nonsense now!
The Rope of Love belongs to you, right?
Alright.
You caused the chaos.
Go lock yourself in the Bright Hall!
You can come out again
only when you recognize your fault.
Why? It’s just a bloody rope!
You are alone for hundreds
of thousands of years.
But you can’t stop others
from finding their happiness!
Shut up!
Come, pull him down for me!
Master Zhiyang!
No need!
I can walk myself!
Was I in the secret room
of Taoyuan Forest?
How did I come back?
Master Bai Jue held you back.
Was I sleeping beautifully?
Was I
snoring or drooling?
A little.
Did anyone see it?
Everyone saw you.
Oh my! It’s horrible! It’s a big mess!
All Goddesses
will definitely hit me
once they see me in the future.
Some might kill me!
Then do I have to pick a time
when nobody else is there
to go to Changyuan Hall
to practice in the future?
Why are you laughing?
Don’t I look good as other Goddess?
Your Grace is the most beautiful.
Go.
Yes.
What should I wear on tomorrow’s class?
My red dress…
Or the green one?
Who was he holding?
Which lady was it?
Come, come, buy away!
Let’s guess
who actually touched the heart
of our Master Bai Jue.
Come, come, come!
Bet all.
How dare you make fun of Master!
Greetings, Master Bai Jue.
What should we do with them?
What’s the situation?
Which type do they think I like?
(Lovely)
They bet on the lovely type most.
Why?
Maybe
yin and yang meridians link each other
in you.
It turns out that I am so indifferent
in your hearts.
Hongri said something wrong.
It’s okay. I’m too serious.
This dress…
It’s her.
Master Bai Jue actually cares about her.
(Temple of Love)
What a day!
I really want to die.
How dare me mind the Gods’ business!
I won’t do that again.
Or…
I’d better close this Temple of Love.
Yes, retreat for two hundred years.
To cool off.
Puhua.
Greetings, Your Grace.
Please get up.
You are in charge of marriage
of the Three Realms.
You should know the best
about love, right?
Since you said so,
do you want to know what love is?
Yeah, what is love?
The storybooks always say that true love
is the promise of life and death.
Then tell me.
If we don’t risk life and death,
isn’t our love true?
Your Grace, you may have worshipped
the wrong temple.
You don’t even know that.
No wonder there are so many foolish
men and women in the lower realm.
No. Well. This…
This word of love is very difficult
to understand.
You don’t know and I don’t know either.
Those who are trapped in love
don’t even know.
So there will be a saying goes like
we don’t know where love starts,
but it goes deeper and deeper.
How can I tell?
Your Grace.
Do you want to tell
who you like in your heart?
Yes.
Your Grace, if you ask like that,
I’m afraid that you’re already touched
and trapped by love.
Stop talking nonsense!
I’m just curious.
Your Grace, if you really want to know
who is the one you like,
you can feel it with your heart.
Feel what?
What you think, what you miss,
and what you expect
is the person you really like.
You are considerate and thoughtful,
gentle and generous,
beautiful and brilliant,
tender and attentive.
You’re the best in the Three Realms.
Your Grace, let me give you a few words.
Love is just like this jug of wine.
The first sip is refreshing.
But if it tastes rich,
it will be entangled
with evil intentions.
Your Grace, you must be careful.
Entanglement?
Does this guy attract a lot of beauties?
I’m not as good as others?
The stars are so bright tonight.
It’s not worse than those
at the Mount Lookout.
How did you come?
I’m afraid you are alone in the temple.
I specially come to visit.
I’ll chat with you.
Did you drink wine?
Today I am in a good mood.
I had a few drinks.
Sit down and I’ll sober you up.
♪Where are you♪
♪Your young face♪
♪Goes with memories♪
♪And is sealed in time♪
♪My thoughts in eyes are now
blocked between my eyebrows♪
♪I can’t see the injuries♪
♪Dreams are imperfect♪
I just kept thinking that
♪I can’t help missing the past♪
is it because you are cold in nature
so that you have a poker face,
or because
you don’t know what expression to show
so that you have no expression at all.
Do you remember that
you asked me
why should I give you the credit alone
on sealing Xuanyi?
You finally want to speak the truth.
Where there is inferiority,
there is conceit.
Your God vessels are smooth now
and you are so powerful.
Those tricks pretending to be
weak and stubborn before.
Don’t play them again in the future.
I feel tired for you.
Still want to talk?
I don’t want to talk anymore.
You’re so good at talking.
Do you want to learn some new moves?
In addition to practice,
can’t we do something else?
What do you mean?
For example…
Stars?
Watch the stars.
The stars in Mount Lookout
are the most beautiful.
But you never bring me to watch them.
If you want to see the stars,
go by yourself.
Why do you want me to bring you there?
You have to take me there!
I know a place
better than Mount Lookout.
This is the Heaven & Earth Platform
where the Ancestral God
released the warning.
It is said that
between heaven and earth,
a calamity will come
every 180,000 years.
Only the Chief God of Chaos
can resist it with God power
to eliminate the catastrophe
and save the common people,
bringing the peace.
Seventy thousand years ago,
the Ancestral God wanted
to pass the throne to Xuanyi.
But Xuanyi lost his mind
and became a demon.
That led to a catastrophe
of heaven and earth.
I know all this.
The Ancestral God passed with the void,
leaving behind a breath of chaos
on this platform.
I was born here
after thousands of years.
I was born to inherit the will
of my Ancestral God.
I’m destined to bring peace
to the world.
So, Shanggu.
You’ll take charge of the world.
Behind the greater power than others,
you have
the most important responsibility.
I will practice hard.
I will work harder than you think
and take charge of the instruction feather
of Chief God as soon as possible
to become the Chief God of Chaos.
Where’s your compliment?
Don’t keep your poker face.
Once your face is cold,
I feel uncomfortable looking at it.
When I feel uncomfortable,
I won’t practice well.
If I don’t practice well,
I can’t serve as the Chief God of Chaos.
Who can I blame?
You are a good speaker.
♪Time disturb my feelings♪
♪Like you do♪
♪Hold tightly with your warm hand♪
♪Look up at the meteor
across the darkness♪
♪Your tall figure♪
♪Is even clear in the haze♪
♪I save some time♪
♪To exchange it for you♪
♪Every second sounds so sweet♪
Is there a painting on my face?
♪Until I meet you♪
We’ll go back when you are sober.
♪To have the next life♪
♪When we meet again♪
♪I’ll travel around with you
without hesitation♪
♪Listen♪
♪We feel each other♪
♪And get close♪
♪For a little talk♪
♪If it’s such a good time
and such a beautiful scenery♪
♪Hope♪
♪Together with you♪
What happened?
Were you having a nightmare?
Or are you suddenly in a bad mood?
It’s okay.
Something happened
in the Nether World again?
No.
Are there any warnings
related to Shanggu released
from the Heaven & Earth Platform
these days?
No.
Since Shanggu was born,
the Ancestral God has failed to warn
for many years.
Shanggu is burdened.
It’s about the power of chaos
and all common people in the lower realm.
There must be no mistakes.
Issue an imperial order tomorrow.
Within 100 meters
of Heaven & Earth Platform,
no God is allowed to take a step close.
Why so strict?
If the Ancestral God
has released some warnings,
all Gods must get informed
at the first time.
Heaven & Earth Platform
is the cornerstone of the God Realm.
Although Xuanyi has been sealed now,
we cannot let our guard down.
In order to prevent the Devils
from coming back,
I will personally guard
the Heaven & Earth Platform in the future.
Alright then. Tianqi has become
more and more absurd recently.
Since you have returned,
before Shanggu takes over
the instruction feather of Chief God,
you can take main control
of some affairs of God Realm,
lest the kind of chaos
God of Day and God of Night
caused destroying the rules
happen again.
I was just asked to come back
to teach Shanggu.
Well.
I have to take main control
of some affairs of God Realm.
Rest assured.
Wait till this is done.
I will send you back to Mount Lookout
and you can enjoy the leisure alone, OK?
Don’t have to.
I accept your arrangement.
True God Bai Jue has a hard mouth
and a soft heart.
You are the most righteous.
Why you look like this?
Isn’t it just a few thunders?
Thunder Punishment from the True God.
Even me
can’t stand it.
How can Zhiyang
treat you this way!
It’s me who made the God of Day
and God of Night fall in love
and broke the rules.
I should be punished.
No, I’m going to find him!
I’m thirsty.
Why don’t you even have water?
I don’t want to drink the water here.
Then wait for me to get you
some spring water.
Fetching spring water
is too troublesome.
You go to Taichu Hall
and bring me a few jars of fine wine.
You are a prisoner of Bright Hall.
According to the rule,
you should not drink alcohol.
Yuemi, I’m really thirsty.
You help me.
OK.
I’ll take some for you now.
It’s okay to break the rules for you.
No matter how many of them.
The more, the better.
OK.
Yuemi, I remember that
I have a few jars of fine wine
of thousands of years.
Go ask Zihan. He knows where they are.
And the batch of tribute from Donghai.
Please also fetch them for me.
Hurry up and go back soon.
I’m waiting for you!
Why are you not weak now?
You just want to drink alcohol!
You…
What happened?
Don’t you want to know
why I throw that Rope of Love away?
Yes.
You asked the Rope of Love for whom?
Do you really fancy someone?
I shouldn’t have asked you that.
Do you really have a crush on a God?
OK.
When I leave the Bright Hall,
I’ll help you check it myself.
I tell you.
In our Gods’ eyes
and your Goddesses’ eyes,
people are different.
You are not uncomfortable?
This is a good thing.
Why am I uncomfortable?
I’m not asking it for myself.
I’m…
Don’t you like Shanggu?
I asked it for you.
Yuemi!
Since you are affectionate
and I am righteous,
from today on,
we become brothers, OK?
From then on,
I will be your big brother.
Or you want to be the big brother?
Is it inappropriate?
Who wants to be your brother?
You haven’t fetched the wine for me yet.
I asked you to give me a suggestion.
Why do you look more worried than me?
Are you feel bored again
practicing with Bai Jue?
Do you want to go to the lower realm
to make trouble again?
No.
Say it. What’s the matter?
I fancy someone.
Fancy?
You fancy a lot of people.
Zhiyang, Tianqi and me.
You fancy us all.
It’s not that kind of fancy.
It’s the kind
that I don’t know what to do
to make him happy.
Anything else?
Do you have any other feelings?
Just his eyes.
His eyes are as bright as
the twinkling stars.
It seems you are really falling in love!
No, my heart is trembling.
But what is good about falling in love
with someone?
Take this dim sum as an example.
When you first started eating it,
it’s as sweet as honey.
But slowly,
you will think
it is sourer than hawthorn.
If this dim sum likes
to be eaten by you, it’s fine.
But if it doesn’t like
to be eaten by you,
it’s as bitter as medicine.
What’s the sour and bitter?
What are you talking about?
If you don’t like this dim sum,
just don’t eat it.
So,
who do you like?
You do not know him.
Not from our God Realm?
No.
Then just go and confess to him.
With your status and beauty,
which God in our God Realm
wants to refuse you?
Let me tell you.
It’s no good to be impatient.
There are too many Goddesses
who rashly confessed love to him.
They all failed one after another.
If you really want to know
if he likes you, I have a way.
What way?
You go kiss him.
Just see how Bai Jue reacts.
Of course.
It’s not the kind of kissing
to redeem your power.
It’s the kind
between men and women.
Forget it.
If I kiss him,
he must have twitched my muscles,
peeled me off
and sent me to purgatory.
You are a coward.
I’m not.
I’m following my heart.
No way.
I didn’t seem to tell you
that it was Bai Jue, right?
How can you guess it right away?
You only listen to him
in the entire God Realm.
If it’s not him, is it Tianqi?
I’m not stupid.
I guessed it a long time ago.
Look at you now.
Humble, shy and nervous.
It’s not like
the free and easy you before.
Is it so obvious?
If you really want to please Bai Jue,
don’t lower your posture deliberately.
Don’t cater to him cautiously.
Facts proved that
Bai Jue doesn’t like it at all.
Look at Xueying. She waits for him
for tens of thousands of years.
You can learn a lesson
drawn from her mistakes.
What should I do?
In the storybooks
if a woman wants to pursue a man,
you can’t be straight.
You should attract his attention.
Attract his attention?
How can I attract his attention?
Don’t ask me that.
If I knew,
then neither do I…
Look at you!
Do you also have someone you like?
You know me.
I think this kind of love affair
is very superficial.
Really?
You read storybooks
more often than I do.
Do you still want me to give you
any suggestion?
Yes, I do!
But,
you have to guarantee
that only you and I know this thing.
Otherwise, your little things…
I promise you!
I won’t say it.
Attract?
You can try to do what he likes.
The thing is that Bai Jue
has no entertainment and hobbies.
What can I do to attract his attention?
I remind you one thing anyway.
He is a heartless man.
He even burned the flowers
that Xueying planted.
Anyway, don’t count on him too much.
I’ve got an idea!
Your Grace.
What are you doing with so many gadgets?
I want to make your Master happy.
He always frowns at normal times.
Your Grace, you have a good heart.
I’m afraid that Master Bai Jue
won’t appreciate it.
Won’t he?
Master.
You came quite early today.
What is this?
The spare time is very boring.
I’ll use these gadgets
to relieve the boredom.
It’s a kite.
Does it look good?
Haven’t you flown it before?
No.
Oh my god. Hongri!
Your Master has never flown a kite!
Is it weird?
Kite, rattle-drum and lantern.
Everyone played them
when we were children.
Yes, there were balls and shuttlecock!
Exactly!
I was not so bored when I was a kid.
I know.
You had been with Taicang Spear
every day when you were a child,
fighting in the South and the North.
If you did want to play,
you didn’t have enough time.
I don’t like these things.
Try it. I’m good at flying kites!
Your Grace, Master won’t appreciate it.
Okay, I will accompany you.
Are you good at flying kites?
There is a lot of knowledge in it.
The kite must fly in the wind
in order to fly high and far.
Come, let me help you.
It’s flying! It’s flying!
It’s flying!
How high is it!
Look!
Phoenix is flying.
It has a great meaning.
Shanggu, if you can choose,
you are willing to be an ordinary God
or a Chief God who shoulders
the lives of the Three Realms?
Why did you ask it suddenly?
You want to test me again?
No.
I just want to hear your sincere answer.
I was born as the Chief God of Chaos.
These lives of the Three Realms
are my responsibilities
for being born into this world.
In that case,
no matter how many responsibilities
I have on my shoulders,
I’m willing to take them.
OK. I will do my best to
help you take over the God Realm
as soon as possible.
Someday,
the place you shine
is the name of Shanggu,
the Chief God of Chaos.
Master, what happened to you?
Did you hurt your waist?
Don’t talk nonsense!
My waist is very good!
The floor in this Bright Hall
is just too hard.
I slept with a sore back.
Oh, yes.
These few days when I was locked up,
what did Zhiyang do to comfort me?
He sent some good wine.
They are all wine of thousands of years.
You’ll definitely appetite them.
Not bad.
By the way, Master.
During your lockdown,
I took time to visit the Demons.
Sen Jian is indeed a creative talent.
I have sent that little tiger demon
to the third heaven to practice.
The Tigers are all brave.
With time, he can be of great use.
You’ve done a good job. Great!
It’s Master who respects him with mercy
and finds a good general for the Demons.
If talking about respecting talents,
you are the greatest Divine Beast
I have picked.
In the war between Pure Dragons
back then,
if it weren’t for Master’s protection,
a little kid like me…
Stop, stop.
If you have the time to repay me,
come in and drink with me.
Go, go, go.
Master, I’m a light drinker.
I’m afraid I’ll make you disappointed.
I won’t.
Is there any news
of Ice Cube these days?
Rumors of the God Realm said that
after the Dating Event,
Master Bai Jue came out holding a lady.
They all said that
there was something wrong.
A lady?
Who is the lady?
There were many witnesses.
So there were many rumors.
Some people said
it’s the Goddess of Snow.
Some said it’s the Goddess of Rain.
And some said
it’s the Goddess of Flower.
The rumors were of everything.
Some people even said it’s Her Grace.
What? Shanggu?
All the ladies
who were alone at the time
had become suspects.
Just for this,
there was a gambling game
at the gate of Changyuan Hall.
Well.
Have the Goddess of Snow,
Goddess of Rain and Goddess of Flower
admitted?
They all admitted
and said they were
the lady who was held by Master Bai Jue.
Isn’t this becoming a mysterious case?
Where did Ice Cube and that lady
come out from?
Were they from the Love Cave?
I don’t know this.
You have to ask Puhua about this.
He knows the best.
Master, Puhua went
to the Immortal Realm.
He’s not in the God Realm.
Why he’s not here
at this moment!
He’s obviously avoiding me!
Master, don’t worry about it.
These are some rumors.
People won’t talk about it
after a few days.
Bring me Zhiyang’s wine.
Yes.
(Endure the Hardship)
Her Grace asked me to
put these things here first.
If she wants to play in her spare time,
it’s convenient for her to fetch.
Master, you haven’t written
the instruction feather for many years.
Who are you going to write to?
Elder Feng Yun from the Feng Clan.
Shanggu’s God vessels are opened now.
It’s time for her to go to the Feng Clan
to choose a Divine Beast.
Why you choose Feng Yan?
That smelly bird is very fancy
and most useless.
Before the Ancestral God shattered the void,
he gave the imperial order.
The Divine Beast must come
from the Feng Clan.
Moreover, most of the Divine Beasts
of heaven and earth are single.
Only the Feng Clan is strong.
If Queen of Phoenix can become
Shanggu’s Divine Beast,
the Feng Clan must be the most loyal
and the most powerful boost to Shanggu.
Master is thoughtful.
But I just heard that
Feng Yan is almost in her nirvana.
After her reborn,
I don’t know whether her temperament
will change drastically.
It’s better to find one like me.
I’m honest and loyal.
I can also chat with Her Grace.
I think it would be nice for me
to find a dumb,
so I don’t have to hear you
talking every day.
It’s annoying.
It’s been 100,000 years…
This is the first time
you joked with me!
Her Grace is so great!
What has it got to do with her?
Yes. Yes.
It has nothing to do with Her Grace.
I’m gonna send preserves to Her Grace.
Open your feet and straighten your arms.
To the right and to the down. Exhale.
Move back.
Arms up. Put your right foot in front.
Exhale.
Move back.
Lift your right foot
and open your hands.
Inhale and stretch.
Relax your body and empty your spirit.
Up and forward.
Try to integrate your body and mind.
Stop.
Your grace, you are a beginner.
Don’t rush it.
Use the strength of your legs.
Don’t focus too much on your posture.
It’s mainly about your mind.
Okay.
Keep still.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪