=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 6=
Up and forward.
Try to integrate your body and mind.
Stop.
Your grace, you are a beginner.
Don’t rush it.
Use the strength of your legs.
Don’t focus too much on your posture.
It’s mainly about your mind.
Okay.
Keep still.
She is much slenderer than before.
Master, Her Grace has
a voracious appetite recently.
Her waist got much thicker.
How did you tell she is slenderer?
Master, we should head for
the training ground now.
I ate too much
and I want to stay here
for a while to digest.
But you said the True God
should abstain from food
and you only had some soup.
Master, wait for me.
(Endure the Hardship)
Bai Jue?
I notice that you like plain colors.
So I put on a plain dress today.
But you are not here.
Your Grace.
Why is it you again?
Don’t you know
other Goddesses are not allowed to
enter Changyuan Hall?
Bai Jue did that to you.
Why do you come here again?
Everyone in the God Realm
knows that Master Bai Jue
treats you differently.
You must be very proud.
Bai Jue and I
are True Gods coming from
the same origin.
It’s natural that he treats me kindly.
You can only fool yourself
with these words.
If you weren’t the Chief God,
if it weren’t for the True God Zhiyang
to select Bai Jue as your mentor,
how would Master Bai Jue
look at you differently
with your temperament and conduct?
Your only advantage
is your identity
as the Chief God.
You broke my kite.
You didn’t apologize but humiliated me.
You got so angry
just because of a kite.
Is it because I’m right about it?
You were born as the God of Chaos.
But you are ignorant and incompetent.
You have little spiritual power.
Do you think you are qualified
to be the Chief God of the Three Realms
and enter Changyuan Hall
as his disciple?
How dare you.
I’m not qualified.
Then are you qualified?
Of course I am.
You only have a higher status than me.
What else are you better than me?
Fine, since you are so confident,
let’s have a competition
fair and square.
If you win,
I will forgive you for
offending your superior.
If you lose...
If I lose,
I’m willing to take punishment.
Good.
Greetings to Your Grace.
Your Grace, you are distinguished.
I dare not hurt you.
Let’s use the lotus leaf
as the criteria.
Whoever falls first loses.
Okay.
Your Grace.
You are too pretentious, aren’t you?
It’s enough to deal with you.
When did Her Grace become so powerful?
Yeah.
They seem to be evenly matched.
Your Grace, you’ve lost.
You played dirty.
But you lost.
As a Chief God,
can’t you afford to lose?
Ancestral Sword!
You promised you won’t
use the Ancestral Sword
before we fought.
But the Ancestral Sword
can smash the sky and the earth.
If you use the Ancestral Sword
to fight with me,
- then…
- Don’t worry.
I will beat you fair and square.
I won’t use a divine weapon
to fight with you.
Now you lost and you vented
your anger on me.
Don’t go too far.
Her Grace is still young and impulsive.
They didn’t say they can’t use
spells before they fight.
Greetings to Master Bai Jue.
Please don’t blame me.
I just want to see
where I’m not as good as Her Grace.
I didn’t expect to win her by luck
and make Her Grace so unhappy.
You won her by luck?
You must be kidding.
If it wasn’t for you to play tricks,
Shanggu would beat you
with no more than ten moves.
You are not as skillful as her,
not as diligent as her,
and not as upright as her.
Do you hear that?
Fortunately, there is someone sensible.
If you plead guilty now,
maybe I will...
Shut up.
The competition ends here.
You should all leave.
Yes.
We are leaving then.
You don’t practice your skills
but horse around in Taoyuan Forest.
She easily set you up
with a spell.
What are you proud of?
Bai Jue.
Don’t show your joy and anger.
Don’t speak your likes and dislikes.
This is what you should
practice the most.
Goddess of Snow only said a few words
to other Gods
and she provoked you into
drawing your sword to fight with her.
How can the Gods of the Three Realms
trust you in the future?
How can the world trust you?
Xueying broke our kite.
It’s just a kite.
We can make a new one if it’s broken.
As the Chief God, you are responsible
for the peace of the God Realm.
You acted rashly today.
What about in the future?
That kite is a little object for you.
But it’s not for me.
Shanggu.
Master!
Master, please stay.
Please don’t be angry with me.
What happened today is my fault.
I’m willing to do everything
to calm your anger.
You should go to apologize to Shanggu
instead of making a show in front of me
if you really learn from your mistakes.
But Her Grace hasn’t calmed down yet.
She won’t forgive me easily.
You are right.
Then I will take a-thousand-year
spiritual power from you
as your punishment.
What?
You don’t want it?
You didn’t mean what you said?
I dare not.
But I’m in charge of the four seasons.
If my spiritual power is damaged,
I’m afraid it will implicate others.
What’s more, I’ve also made
some contributions
in the fight between Gods and Devils.
If you punish me that hard,
I’m afraid others will criticize you.
You have thought a lot.
But you still should be punished.
You are not competent enough.
Instead of practicing harder,
you played dirty tricks.
I remember I said
no Goddess is allowed to
enter the Changyuan Hall.
And it includes you.
Your Grace.
This is the gift from
the Goddess of Snow as an apology.
Just a-thousand-year spiritual power.
It’s far from my power of chaos.
I don’t want it.
You are laughing at me.
You don’t think I can
cultivate my power of chaos,
do you?
I won’t go to Changyuan Hall tomorrow.
My kite is broken.
He didn’t comfort me at all.
It was just a little competition.
And he made a big deal out of it.
He even said the Three Realms
will be subverted.
I think his brain is subverted.
I’m so pissed off.
I lost my temper with Bai Jue.
He must be angry with me now.
I’m not perfect
in his eyes anymore.
But he can’t blame me, right?
He was rude to me first.
So I’m still perfect
in his eyes.
It’s so hard to win someone’s heart.
Yuemi is right.
I can’t get my hope too up, right?
What should I do?
Master, the divine bead has been
sent to Her Grace.
As you ordered,
I said it was from the Goddess of Snow.
I didn’t say anything about you.
Put it away. I won’t need it anymore.
Master, are you not
going to see Her Grace?
No.
Go to tell her
we will learn the ways of
being an emperor tomorrow.
Yes.
Master, I still want to say
that since she came back
from Mount Lookout,
she has been practicing really hard.
She is still young,
and there will be ample time.
(Endure the Hardship)
Are you blaming me
for being too harsh on her?
I dare not.
She doesn’t have much time left.
If I slack off and go easy on her,
that will harm her.
Go ahead.
Yes.
Ice Cube.
Shanggu hasn’t come to your hall
to practice for some time, right?
I heard that Hongri has invited her
several times but she didn’t come once.
Well, I knew you can’t teach her.
Why are you mentioning this?
It requires a tranquil mind to appreciate
the good tea. Don’t ruin the mood.
Zhiyang, I just learned a new move!
I promise you never...
Shanggu.
You came just right.
Come on. Come on.
I heard about what happened
in Taoyuan Forest on that day.
Didn’t Bai Jue take your side?
Why did you get angry with him?
Have a seat. Come on.
The three of us
have a close relationship.
He has taken a-thousand-year
spiritual power from Goddess of Snow
as her punishment.
Really?
Talkative.
Yes.
Never mind.
No matter what tricks Xueying used,
I still lost, right?
Shanggu, you are not angry anymore?
As the saying goes,
the Gods have a glib tongue.
Don’t easily...
Shanggu.
I just got something to tell you.
I’m discussing with Bai Jue and Tianqi
about choosing a beast
at Parasol Forest for you.
When will we go?
We should leave soon.
Shanggu.
How about I go with you?
The Parasol Forest is a good place.
We can travel all the way there
and have fun together.
You are not going with me?
I have something to do.
If you are busy,
we can leave a few days later.
I’ll wait for you.
Why must it be him?
Because he is my righteous master.
Bai Jue!
Do you want to ask me
why I won’t go to
the Feng Clan with you?
I thought about it.
You were right about
my fight with Xueying.
I was too careless.
And I should accept my defeat.
I will find a way to win her.
I don’t care about it anymore.
Then why don’t you go to
the Feng Clan with me?
Shanggu, I can’t solve
everything for you.
It’s about the affairs
of the Feng Clan this time.
And it’s a great chance for you
to tame your beast
and for your self-development.
But I’ve been learning from you.
It’s a big deal to choose my beast.
How can you not come with me?
Master, Your Grace.
Elder Feng Yun presents himself.
Greetings to Your Grace.
Greetings to Master Bai Jue.
Sir, why are you here so suddenly?
Didn’t you receive
my instruction feather?
I came to see you
just because I received
your instruction feather.
What does that mean?
The Feng Clan committed a grave sin.
I’m here to ask for your forgiveness.
What happened?
Before the Ancestral God
broke into the void,
he has selected our queen
as Her Grace’s beast.
Over these years,
Queen Feng Yan has been
cultivating herself
to take on this important task.
Three days ago,
Her Majesty finally reached
the realm of Nirvana.
And your instruction feather
also arrived.
But as she was going to be reborn
in the Parasol Forest,
someone stole her spirit.
Feng Yan’s spirit was stolen?
The Queen of Phoenix will have
Nirvana three times in her life.
After her emotions
and desires are eradicated,
she will become the strongest beast.
The outsiders don’t know these things.
The members of the Feng Clan
are all skilled in martial arts
and you have always been
the head of all clans.
Who is so bold as to break into
the Parasol Forest and steal her spirit?
It’s Wuxi.
He is the ancestor of parasol.
He has guarded the Feng Clan
for tens of thousands of years
and he has been loyal to the Feng Clan.
If he is loyal,
why would he steal Feng Yan’s spirit
during her Nirvana?
There is something you don’t know.
In the end, it’s all about love.
It’s a fatal attraction between them.
The Queen of the Feng Clan
will have Nirvana three times
in her lifetime.
To be born, to become a god and to die.
After Nirvana,
the body, character and memory
will be gone along with the Nirvana.
But the Queen of Phoenix’s
cultivation will not disappear.
Therefore, the Queen of Phoenix
will become stronger
after each death.
I see.
Does it mean that the Queen of Phoenix
has always been the same person?
Yes, and no.
Except for the cultivation,
there is no similarity between
the previous queen and the queen now.
The current Queen of Phoenix and Wuxi
grew up together
and they have fallen for
each other since childhood.
I know they are in love.
But the Ancestral God
has made an order
to select Her Grace’s divine beast
from the Feng Clan.
Queen of Phoenix is the strongest
in the Feng Clan.
Therefore, only she
can be the beast
of the Little Chief God.
But after
Her Majesty fought with the devils,
her spiritual power
was greatly impaired.
Now she only has the power
of an immortal.
Therefore, Her Majesty
decided to have her second Nirvana.
But who knows
Wuxi would actually do that
to stop her Nirvana.
If Feng Yan has her second Nirvana,
there is no difference
from being killed.
Right, Ice Cube?
Everything in the Three Realms
has its own way of living.
There is no right or wrong.
Since Feng Yan has made her decision,
I guess she has made her choice
to give up something.
But Wuxi stepped in
and stopped the Queen of Phoenix
from Nirvana.
He should be killed
according to the law.
Bai Jue.
Rules are rules.
Wuxi goes against the density.
If we disregard Ancestral God’s
order just for him,
then what do we need the rules for?
Sir, please rest assured.
This matter is of great importance.
I will find the spirit back in person.
Didn’t you just ask me to
go through it alone?
Why are you taking it on again?
Wuxi should still be
in the land of the immortals.
But he hid his smell
and it’s hard to find him.
I have an idea.
(Southsea Town)
How is my look?
Give me the Immortal-seeking Bell.
Why?
I asked Yuemi for this treasure.
It can detect the smell of the gods.
Even you have the Immortal-seeking Bell,
do you know what Wuxi
and Feng Yan look like?
I’ve thought about it.
Before we left, I asked Elder Feng Yun
for their portraits.
You’ve made some progress.
It smells so good.
Yeah?
- Yeah, try it later.
- I’m hungry.
Let’s eat something first
before we leave.
A True God doesn’t need to eat.
But I can’t.
I’m still growing.
Maybe I can still grow taller.
You are what you eat.
Wonton is exactly what I need.
Do you forget our task
just because you are hungry?
I mean
I’ll come back to eat it
after we finish our task.
There you go.
They are here somewhere.
Let’s go.
Your Majesty, please forgive me
for my disrespect.
I’ve been with you for years
and I’m deeply in love with you.
It’s killing me to think about
you will forget everything about us
after your Nirvana.
I had to take your spirit away
when you were about to be reborn.
I...
Wuxi.
I’ve told you clearly
before my Nirvana.
I owe you too much in this life.
I don’t deserve
to be with you next life.
Why did you make such a big mistake?
No.
It’s not you, but the Little Chief God
who owes me a lot!
If it wasn’t for her to choose a beast,
you and I wouldn’t have to separate
after your Nirvana.
But the Wuxi who is in love with me
wouldn’t do that.
How can you put the Feng Clan in danger
just to save me?
Our love hasn’t come
to an end this life.
I don’t want a next life.
I regret it.
What?
You regret that I took you out
without permission
or regret being with me?
I regret having Nirvana.
When you stole my spirit
out of the Feng Clan,
I saw your tears.
I thought I could let go of this life.
But I still can’t stand leaving you.
I’ve decided.
Whether we will roam all over the world
or be hunted forever,
I want to be with you.
I won’t fail you.
I will do everything for you
with no regrets.
Now I’ve taken you out of the Feng Clan.
The Gods and the Feng Clan
must be looking for us.
There are many people here.
We can only stay here for a while.
It’s not a long-term solution.
You can put my spirit
in a phoenix flower.
Then
I will be a flower fair.
I think I can hide my identity
in this way.
But I don’t want you
to live that kind of life.
Wait for me here.
I’ll go to find a paradise for us.
And then
we will be a pair of free cranes.
No one will find us.
The Immortal-seeking Bell?
What?
Elder Feng Yun
must have told on us to the God Realm.
They used the Immortal-seeking Bell
to find us through our smell.
I don’t want to leave you.
Don’t worry.
They must think I have your spirit.
I’ll create a diversion.
Wuxi, don’t go.
I’m afraid you will be in danger.
This parasol leaf
has the same root as me.
Your spiritual power is weak right now.
Don’t fight with anyone yet.
You must hide yourself well.
After this is over,
this leaf will lead you to me.
Wait for me here.
I can’t believe Wuxi is still
drinking and having fun here.
But it’s quite fun
with all these immortals.
I’ll bring Yuemi here next time.
Are you here to play or to find them?
I told you I have my own way.
I’m experienced in arresting people
and not being arrested.
I was caught by Zhiyang many times
when I secretly left the God Realm
to have fun.
You can’t rush it.
What’s in the suet? It smells great.
Master.
This is not suet.
This is the famous peach blossom wine
in our Dongfeng Restaurant.
The wine is mellow, and it tastes sweet.
It’s smooth and the aftertaste lingers.
Is there such a good thing
in the Immortal Realm?
Are you sure you are not bragging?
You will know if I’m bragging
after you taste it by yourself.
Try it.
Wuxi?
Wait for me here.
Wuxi knows I have Bai Jue to protect me.
But he still attacked me.
He was creating a diversion.
Maybe Feng Yan’s spirit
is still in the restaurant.
Who is that?
My fair lady, I pass by here
and get lost by accident.
Can you tell me the right direction?
I’m also here for the first time.
You should ask the waiter here.
You are beautiful and kind.
I’ve been finding my way for some time
and I’m really thirsty now.
Can you let me take a rest inside?
I have something important to do.
I can’t let you in.
Maybe it’s because you have
such an outstanding look,
I feel connected to you.
I can’t help but want to
say a few more words.
Are you a flower fairy?
Yes.
You must be careful
if you are going to travel far.
The suburbs are not
very peaceful recently.
How?
There is a flower-picking beast
wandering around
the outskirts of Southsea Town.
His target is exactly
beautiful girls like you.
Really?
You are a flower fairy.
How can you not know that?
I... I heard about it.
Not only this,
I also know a top-secret event
in the Feng Clan.
I love traveling since I was born
and I’m really into gossip.
From the Chief God choosing a beast
to an old turtle marrying a concubine,
there is nothing I don’t know
in the Three Realms.
Forget it, it’s about
the face of the Chief God.
We are little immortals.
Let’s not worry about that.
Since you are going to travel far,
I’ll leave you to it.
Maybe we will meet again.
Hold on!
You just said
Master Bai Jue is secretly investigating
the stolen spirit
of the Queen of Phoenix
in Southsea City?
Has he found out anything?
You are just a flower fairy.
Why do you care so much
about the Feng Clan?
I’m just curious like you.
You don’t have
the Queen of Phoenix’s spirit.
Well.
You really want to go against the Gods?
If it weren’t for these True Gods
to push me so hard,
would I need to do that?
That’s ridiculous.
The immortals and demons know
that the spirit of
the Queen of Phoenix was stolen
and they are coveting it.
The leaders of all clans
want to absorb it
to enhance their spiritual power.
I’m afraid there will be
trouble in Southsea Town.
Handle it with Shanggu
as fast as you can
and hurry back to the God Realm.
The Gods are basically certain
that Wuxi put the spirit
of the Phoenix Queen
in a flower.
It’s a secret. How did the Gods know it?
The fish is on the hook.
Why isn’t Ice Cube coming back?
This peach blossom wine is delicious
but also very intoxicating.
I drank a little too much.
I mean, the spirit of the Phoenix Queen
still belongs to a god.
How can a flower hold it?
After she resides in a flower,
she can’t even protect herself
with her little spiritual power.
I think a lot of people
will come to fight for it.
The Little Chief God thought
it was Wuxi’s own idea.
She didn’t expect that the Phoenix Queen
also wants to leave with him.
How should the two of them end this?
If the Chief God knows
she would put Wuxi
and Feng Yan through this
because of choosing her beast
in the Feng Clan,
she wouldn’t go to the Feng Clan at all.
Now it turns out to be so serious.
Why did Feng Yan
choose such a way
and get some many people implicated?
You have to eradicate your emotions
and give up your memories to be reborn.
Let me ask you.
Without emotions and memories,
will Feng Yan still be herself?
The Phoenix Queen was born
to take on the mission of the Feng Clan.
So she has to be reborn
and part with the love of her life
just because she is the Phoenix Queen?
Don’t you feel sad for her?
She is the prestigious Phoenix Queen,
but she can’t even love and hate
as she wants
like those girls who are dating
in the Immortal Realm.
But there are a lot of
poor people in the world.
No one can disobey the will
of the Ancestral God.
I don’t know
if the superior Chief God knows
that there are many competent people
in the Feng Clan born from
humble backgrounds who can
also take on the mission to be a beast.
Feng Yan has neither the ability
to assist the Chief God
nor the aspiration to help
the Three Realms.
She just wants to be an ordinary woman
and grow old with her lover.
Do you have any other questions?
Chief God, Shanggu.
If...
There is no “if”.
You will understand
what it feels like
to be troubled by love
when you fall for someone one day.
I’m sober now.
Please lead the way.
Never mind.
I wasn’t going to
separate you two anyway.
And now you are firm.
What do you mean?
Just go before I change my mind.
Your Grace.
Hurry.
You won’t be able to leave
if Master Bai Jue comes back.
Thank you for letting us be together.
Wuxi.
Feng Yan.
Why did it take you so long?
I was really worried.
Were you in trouble?
Good.
I was going to look for you
in the restaurant.
But I worried other people
would notice me
and find you out.
The Little Chief God recognized me.
Don’t worry.
She is a reasonable and kind person.
It was her who let me go.
Wuxi, we shouldn’t have blamed her.
This is all because of Shanggu.
You can forgive her, but I can’t.
Ridiculous.
My head hurts a lot.
You still use that tone with me.
When can you stop
being so voracious?
Ice Cube, I feel dizzy.
I mean, can’t you be
a little gentler to me?
Don’t be mad at me all the time, okay?
I really envy Wuxi
and Feng Yan’s relationship.
They are so brave for their love.
They even defied the divine order
and risked their lives for their love.
Wuxi made a big mistake
because of his selfish love.
He is not brave for love.
Stop saying drunken gibberish.
I’m not drunk.
Do I look drunk to you?
Are you listening to me?
I am envious of Wuxi and Feng Yan.
I don’t want to catch them back.
Who were you drinking with?
Feng Yan. Who else could it be?
Where are you going?
Zhiyang sent us a message
that the Three Realms know
the loss of the Phoenix Queen’s spirit.
As the Chief God, you didn’t catch her
and you got yourself drunk.
So what?
Why are you lecturing me again?
Bai Jue, if I am
troubled by love
and break the divine rules one day,
will you also punish me
according to the law?
The divine rules do not
only exist in dogma.
But love has nothing to do with dogma.
♪Time disturb my feelings♪
♪Like you do♪
I mean,
you are only good-looking.
What’s the big deal with you?
You are drunk. Let me help you sober up.
♪Your tall figure♪
Shanggu.
♪Is even clear in the haze♪
♪I save some time♪
♪To exchange it for you♪
This is the Pilgrimage Hall.
No one will come to save you.
What do you want to do?
I’ll do what I’ve always wanted to do.
♪Until I meet you♪
♪I make every attempt♪
♪To have the next life♪
♪When we meet again♪
♪I’ll travel around with you
without hesitation♪
♪Listen♪
Who else did you drink with?
♪We feel each other♪
The God of Flower, the God of Night,
the God of Rain,
Tianqi, Yuemi and Zhiyang.
All right.
Don’t get so drunk with them again.
Do you hear me?
♪If it’s such a good time
and such a beautiful scenery♪
♪May you♪
Why?
You are a woman and I am a man.
You can’t touch the places
covered by clothes.
But there are no clothes on your face.
It’s even more tiring than
fighting with fierce beasts.
Take a good rest here.
Wuxi and Feng Yan are in danger now.
I’ll be right back.
I’ve set a barrier. No one can come in.
The owner of the hut
is a Crane Immortal
who ascended to the God Realm
some time ago.
I guess the Crane Immortal
won’t come back again.
It’s really like a paradise.
Let’s live here for now.
We can make a plan
after everything is over, okay?
It’s really shabby here.
I didn’t think it through.
Yan.
Sorry that you have to live here.
I’m not even afraid of death.
This is no big deal to me.
Wuxi.
We committed a grave sin.
There is no turning back.
From now on, it’s hard
not to hide all the time.
But my spiritual power is weak now.
I’m afraid I will be a burden to you.
Yan.
You know I’m bad at words
and I can’t do the sweet talk.
But I swear to heaven
that I will make you happy
even at the cost of my life.
Will you...
Will you marry me?
Since we are getting married,
we should clean up this place.
Why are you still standing there?
Come here and clean it up.
Okay. Okay.
I will do all the housework.
No!
Someone broke the barrier.
Is that Master Bai Jue?
Let’s go.
Wuxi, get out of here
if you don’t want to die.
What we want is
the spirit of the Queen Phoenix.
I won’t allow that!
How did I fall asleep?
I kissed him?
No way.
It’s definitely impossible.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪