=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 7=
How come I fell asleep?
Did I kiss him?
Impossible.
No way.
Where’s Bai Jue?
It’s still warm.
He looks like an aloof guy.
But he’s actually very nice.
Wuxi.
Bai Jue.
This is a dispute between
our lower realm.
You should uphold justice.
How can you help the Feng Clan?
Talking about justice,
you can just challenge Feng Yan
since her spirit is off her body.
How dare you mention justice
in front of me?
Southsea is where the Immortals inhabit.
You Snake Demons
gave birth to plenty of Gods.
Who’d expect you to be so despicable?
If you try to break in here
and cause chaos in the lower realm.
I don’t mind spending some time
destroying every one of you.
Let’s go.
Well? You still want to fight?
I’ve made my promise.
I have to protect Feng Yan
even if I die.
Wuxi.
You’re helpless.
Why are you here?
I’m the one who let Feng Yan go.
I’m the one to blame.
Free both of them.
You are a Chief God.
You’d only drag the Three Realms down
if you get emotional.
Do you know how dangerous
it might be for them now?
You are not helping them.
You are doing the opposite.
I wonder if there’s another way?
Maybe you can punish Wuxi
without damaging his life.
Indecision invariably leads to trouble.
Feng Yan. You are the leader
of the clan.
I will take your spirit back to home.
As for you.
Such being the case, do you
regret it or not?
Stealing Feng Yan’s spirit
is the most incorrect thing
I’ve ever done.
But I’ve never regretted it.
If I didn’t do it,
I would never know how much love
Yan has for me this life.
If someday,
Your Grace and Bai Jue
are put in the same situation.
I believe
you’d make the same decision.
If you continue to speak recklessly,
I will sentence you to death right now.
Bai Jue. Wuxi has made
such a huge mistake.
He ought to die.
But his inspiration was to save me.
It was me who disobeyed
Ancestral God’s will.
I refused to be a Divine Beast.
It was me who tricked Wuxi
into stealing the spirit
which caused today’s result.
It was all my fault.
I’m the one to blame.
Yan.
I’d pledge loyalty to Your Grace
after my reborn
to make up for my fault.
Please spare Wuxi’s life.
Since Feng Yan has taken
full responsibility,
this can be another pair of shoes.
It’s known to the God Realm
that Bai Jue strictly adheres
to the rules.
He’d make the fairest sentence for sure.
Never mind.
If you can be loyal to Shanggu
after reborn.
I’ll spare your life this time.
Yan.
If I have another chance,
I hope that I’m not the Queen
of Phoenix.
Yan.
But to only be your Feng Yan.
Yan. Yan.
Yan.
Yan. No.
Yan. Yan.
No!
Yan.
Shanggu.
Don’t kill him.
Don’t talk.
I’m taking you to the Feng Clan now.
I heard that Bai Jue took
back Her Grace.
She’s badly damaged.
Now she’s in the guest room.
Well, should we go inside
and take care of her?
It was Wuxi who hurt her.
Now the whole Feng Clan
is deterred by the danger.
The Master may blame us
if we make any mistakes.
You’re right. Let’s just
mind our own business.
We don’t want to put ourselves forward
during this time.
Miss, I’d like to ask
(Wu Huan)
if Her Grace needs someone now.
Wu Huan.
You should be cleaning
the spiritual herbs now.
What are you doing here?
Even if Her Grace needs
someone to take care of her.
It wouldn’t be you.
I’m just worrying about Her Grace.
At a time of this, everyone worries
for themselves.
Why do you pretend to be nice?
I know right?
She’s only a fifth-grade color phoenix,
trying to approach Her Grace.
Why don’t you look at yourself
in the mirror
before you ask for anything?
Let’s go.
Sir.
What’s so mysterious
with Wuxi’s God power?
How come
I can’t heal her wounds?
Wuxi used to be
an ancestral sycamore tree.
His tens of thousands of years
of spiritual essence
all infused to the last strike.
The sword is hidden
with the power of fire.
Your original nature is fire.
Of course you can’t heal Her Grace.
I’ll ask Tianqi...
No.
The power of fire can only
be healed by the Queen of Phoenix.
If Her Grace gets reborn,
she then can deal with it.
But what
should I do now?
I can’t let things happen
to Shanggu.
Don’t worry, Master.
There may be a way to save her.
What’s that?
I know there’s a treasure
in the God Realm
called Water Bead.
It’s the remains of the ancestors
which heals every wound.
I guess
it can clear the fire
in Her Grace’s body.
I know where the bead is.
Let me get it now.
Ice Cube.
It hurts.
It hurts so badly.
Wu Huan.
You’ve got to change your own fate.
Who are you?
I’m Wu Huan.
The Feng Clan is aware of its own crime.
I volunteer to take care of Her Grace.
Ridiculous. Look at this place.
Who are you to be here?
Master.
Her Grace is suffering from the fire,
it must be unbearable.
Apply the water in the Icy Pool
behind the Parasol Forest on body.
It can ease Her Grace’s pain.
Then, take good care of her.
Yes, Master.
I’ll definitely take good care
of Her Grace.
Alright.
Since Master has recognized you.
Take care of her with full heart.
Yes.
I need to borrow your treasure.
I’ll reward you some other day.
It’s my pleasure
to help you.
However, the Water Bead
is given by Master Zhiyang
after the battle between Gods
and Demons.
It’s especially precious to me.
I’d like to know the reason
why you need it.
To save people.
Is it for
Her Grace?
She’s hurt by the parasol fire.
Master and I
have never talked in these many years.
Who’d know you’d ask for a favor
for Her Grace?
I’m curious.
Are you commanding me
as a True God
to give the Water Bead?
Or asking me as an old-time friend
for a favor?
What do you mean?
What do you want me to do
to give out the bead?
I don’t ask for anything.
My only wish is
to be your apprentice
and stay by your side.
Master. You’re back.
My power isn’t strong enough now.
Her Grace’s situation is getting worse.
Have you brought back the Water Bead?
Yes.
Alright. Please cure Her Grace now.
Wu Huan. Let’s go out.
What I want
is your safety.
Ice Cube...
Your Grace.
You’re finally awake.
Who are you?
My name is Wu Huan, I belong
to the Feng Clan.
This is the Parasol Forest.
You were hurt by Wuxi yesterday.
The True God took you back here.
What happened to Wuxi?
The Master sentenced him.
What?
Your Grace.
I only got some skin trauma.
But Wuxi is Feng Yan’s only care.
Why did he have to be killed?
Where’s he now?
I’m not sure.
Your Grace.
You just got better.
Please don’t get angry.
If I know this would happen,
I wouldn’t come to the Feng Clan
to select the beasts.
I teared a couple apart.
I even made Wuxi lost his life.
Your Grace.
Selecting Divine Beasts concerns
both the Gods and the Feng Clan.
It’s a rule made by the Ancestral God.
Please don’t blame yourself too much.
The Ancestral God’s will
is to select Divine Beasts
from the Feng Clan.
But it didn’t have to be Feng Yan.
Bai Jue.
Do you still feel uncomfortable?
We promised Feng Yan
to keep Wuxi alive.
Now you’ve killed him.
How should we tell Feng Yan?
You can go first.
Yes.
Still mad?
Like I’ve said,
I’d only destroy his cultivation.
I stuck to my words.
I knew you wouldn’t do it.
You’re still recovering. Don’t move.
The only thing for you to do
is to make the choice
of the Divine Beast
to settle everything down.
The girl taking care of me, Wu Huan.
She looks like a low-rank phoenix
of the Feng Clan.
I heard the honor of Feng Clan
is usually decided by their ranks.
I think many low-rank phoenixes
may admire Feng Yan who was born
in an honorable family that is
be qualified to be the Divine Beast.
I think Wu Huan does, too.
So, you’d like to choose her
as the Divine Beast?
Yes. If I do,
I mean to let them know
that I treat people
in the Three Realms equally.
I’ll never indulge them with the idea
that family background
decides everything.
By the way,
if I foster
a low-rank phoenix like Wu Huan.
Would the elders of the Feng Clan
be against it?
Some people will.
So, you should come up
with a perfect plan.
To convince the Feng Clan
for their loyalty and help.
This is...
The left is the real one
and the right is fake.
It’s your call to make the decision.
Ice Cube. You’ve already prepared it.
I didn’t expect it.
You are the best ever.
I’m so impressed.
I don’t like you getting
this close to me.
Well... How about when we hugged?
It was much closer.
♪Time disturb my feelings♪
♪Like you do♪
♪Hold tightly with your warm hand♪
♪Look up at the meteor
across the darkness♪
♪Your tall figure♪
♪Is even clear in the haze♪
♪I save some time♪
♪To exchange it for you♪
What’s wrong?
What’s the matter?
What a bad luck.
I had a dream last night
that the cabbage I grow for a long time
got picked by a pig!
There’s no pig in the God Realm.
Even if there is, it’d be
a spiritual pig.
Of course it’s a spiritual pig.
Ice Cube.
Be careful.
Don’t drink too much.
You are right.
I found that
ever since Bai Jue and Shanggu
came back from the Nether World,
the atmosphere between them is weird.
So, I’m a bit worried.
What are you worrying about?
I worry that I may lose Shanggu.
She’s not yours anyway.
What do you mean?
Before Bai Jue came,
Shanggu followed me everywhere
all the time.
But now.
All she talks about is Bai Jue.
What’s so good about him?
If I know this.
I’d definitely not
allow Bai Jue to be her master.
Shanggu can make her own choices.
What is she to you?
A kept wife?
Such a healthy relationship
becomes so weird in your words.
I’m free to say anything I like.
If you don’t want to hear it.
Just go somewhere else.
What’s wrong with you?
The liquor is poisoned, too.
I advise you not to drink it.
What’s wrong with you?
I’ll leave you here to be mad.
I’m going to the lower realm
and replace that Ice Cube.
I can’t let them stay together.
It’s an important matter for them
to chase Feng Yan’s spirit.
Don’t cause troubles for them.
The Feng Clan needs help.
As the True God, it’s my
responsibility as well.
Tianqi.
If Shanggu doesn’t want
to be with Bai Jue,
she’d walk away without your help.
Besides, it’s their own business.
Why do you want to meddle?
Well... Then don’t you meddle
with my business with Shanggu.
I...
Just go if you want.
Don’t come back if you do.
Both good and evil.
It perfectly suits my appreciation
of beauty.
Elder Feng Yun.
Your Grace.
I’m giving back Feng Yan’s spirit.
Please keep it well.
Wait until the Queen of Phoenix
come back after a thousand years.
Yes. As Master commands.
I believe you all know
my trip to the Feng Clan
is to select a Divine Beast for me.
There’s still some time before
the reborn of the Queen of Phoenix.
I’d like to choose one
from the low-rank Phoenixes.
Your Grace.
How can a low-rank phoenix deserve
to be near around you?
If you agree,
I will let go
of the fact that you lost the spirit.
Wu Huan.
Come here.
For the next a thousand years,
would you like to be my Divine Beast
and come back to the God Realm with me?
Your Grace.
Do you mean it?
I don’t think it’s appropriate
to joke in this occasion.
I...
I’d like to do it.
I hope that
from now on,
phoenix of the Feng Clan
can all be appreciated
and put in important positions
as long as they are morally qualified
and work hard.
Your Grace is merciful.
I wish after a thousand years,
no one would find out the spirit
is actually fake.
As for the queen’s true spirit,
put it on the flower.
Wuxi’s body will be transformed
into a sycamore tree.
If give it some time,
there’s still a chance for them to meet.
Great divine water.
I got it. You want to buy me
some wonton.
Take a look.
We’ve traveled for a long time.
- Great divine water.
- I am a bit hungry.
Take a look.
The sweet-smelling divine water.
Sir. Two wonton, please.
Okay.
Wu Huan, don’t you want some?
I’m not hungry.
Besides, wonton to me
is just ordinary food.
I’ll wait at table for you two.
Here’s your wonton.
The God Realm is full of elegant taste.
A simple bowl of food
is called wonton.
I think the best place
for the wonton to go would
be my stomach.
Yum.
Delicious.
No wonder it has an interesting name.
I caught you.
You ate the God of Chaos.
According to the rules in God Realm,
how should I dispose you?
Boring.
Is this the Divine Beast you chose?
Her story went all over the God Realm.
It’s more ridiculous than a drama.
Wu Huan. You are my Divine Beast now.
Since you’re in The Pilgrimage Hall,
you’ve become one of us.
No matter how you used to be bullied
in the Feng Clan.
From now on,
you can straighten up
and focus on cultivating now.
Yes, Your Grace.
In the God Realm,
many look down me as a Chief God.
Many look down on you
as a low-rank phoenix, too.
Let’s train harder
and impress those who are blind.
Isn’t it cool?
Yes, Your Grace.
You two can get along.
Maybe you can really
do something one day.
You’ve neglected training.
You only care about gossip.
Your Immortal-seeking Bell
isn’t working anymore.
I just check it. It’s fine.
Your Grace. Your Grace.
Your Grace.
Xueying broke into the Changyuan Hall.
I couldn’t stop her.
Isn’t she afraid
of Bai Jue’s punishment?
I came to tell you another news.
Bai Jue took Xueying as his apprentice,
it’s all over the God’s Realm now.
That’s impossible.
It’s true.
Xueying said
Bai Jue personally took her.
(Endure the Hardship)
After all these years,
I can finally walk into
the Changyuan Hall justifiably.
I can stay with Master all the time now.
I have to seize this chance.
I still remember
our first met
in the Plum Blossom Garden.
You once said to me,
the plum blossoming on the branch
to wait for me.
Until now,
I’ve not forgotten.
Your Grace.
Master has said
that you’re forbidden
to enter Changyuan Hall.
Hongri. Send her out.
Your Grace doesn’t know yet.
Bai Jue Master has taken me
as his apprentice.
From now on, I’ll be living
in the Changyuan Hall
and cultivate with you.
Living in the Changyuan Hall?
Who said it?
Master’s instruction feather is here.
I doubt if Your Grace don’t
recognize it.
I don’t believe it.
Unless he tells me himself.
Who are you to judge
Master’s apprentices?
Your Grace don’t do any work
but meddling with other’s business
in Changyuan Hall.
You put the cart before the horse.
I’ve heard it before
that Your Grace don’t like cultivating.
It’s a waste of your position
as the Chief God.
Well.
Just travel around
and enjoy the beautiful scenery.
Why would you stay here and suffer?
After all.
Not everyone can be
a disciple of Master Bai Jue.
It’s better for someone who is
not worthy of their position
to leave before it is too late.
Don’t ruin the reputation of the master
and make a fool of yourself.
Then become the mockery
of the Gold Realm.
Xueying, you made me do it.
Ancestral Sword.
Will you go by yourself today,
or I’ll use the Ancestral Sword?
I didn’t expect Your Grace would
have such profound God power
when getting angry.
Your Grace seems to have indeed
fulfilled the tease before
to tear down the Changyuan Hall
after having learned something.
Master.
Bai Jue, explain to me clearly.
Shanggu.
From now on, you and Xueying
will practice together.
There are so many people in God Realm.
Why did you take her as your disciple?
Water Bead.
Master. Xueying was just a little angry
and offended Her Grace.
Goddess of Snow, if you
can use another trick,
maybe Master can think highly of you.
What happened today won’t be repeated.
If anyone dares to stir up trouble
in the future.
I will not spare him.
(Endure the Hardship)
I won’t believe that
if I’m with Master every day.
I can’t be better than you
who are stupid.
Your Grace.
Your Grace. It’s Day of the Chosen
in a few days.
Master Zhiyang has specially
sent a feast robe.
Throw it all out.
Throw all these white clothes out!
Your Grace. Didn’t I choose well?
It’s not your fault.
I get angry
when I see the white clothes.
Master only took a disciple, not a wife.
Why are you so angry?
He knew that I hate Xueying
but took her as a disciple.
It is because of the Water Bead.
I should pay back what I owe.
Master must have treated you
as his own family.
Who wants to be
a sibling kind of relative with him?
She likes to learn skills
from Master, right?
Then I’ll satisfy her.
Yesterday, Her Grace left in anger.
I guess she won’t come today.
Your Grace.
You are so beautiful today!
Of course.
I am beautiful every day.
Don’t be late tomorrow.
Plus,
it’s cold in spring.
Wear more clothes next time.
Don’t just talk about me.
Do you see what your disciple
is wearing?
It’s not summer yet, is it?
Goddess of Snow, you put on
too little clothes.
I can’t tolerate the heat.
Your Grace are joking.
I have thought about it.
Goddess of Snow didn’t hesitate
to use Water Bead
to become a disciple of Bai Jue.
I think you must be dedicated
to learning
and hungry for practice, right?
All these ancient books were sent
to me by Zhiyang.
Today.
I’ll give you all of them
to pay back what I owe you.
Thank you for your generosity.
Your Grace.
Reading requires meditation.
You also know the nature of me.
If you stay in the Changyuan Hall.
I’m sure I’m going to bother you.
I suggest that you should
take these books back.
Close the door and learn.
Tell me when you finish.
I have everything that you need.
Don’t be so polite.
But I’ve read all these books.
Is that so?
Your Grace don’t believe me.
Well, to you.
It’s difficult for you to finish
reading them all.
Don’t underestimate me.
I have read all these books.
Since you have read it all.
I won’t lend them to you.
Wait.
(The Classic of Mountains and Rivers)
The Classic of Mountains and Rivers.
The classic of the God Realm.
Although it has access
to the world’s mountains and rivers.
It’s difficult to understand.
This book looks brand new.
Did Your Grace really read it?
Of course.
Just The Classic
of Mountains and Rivers.
When do we start the class?
(Endure the Hardship)
Since you two have both studied
The Classic of Mountains and Rivers.
Then I will give you a test.
Xueying.
Yes.
It is said in the book that there is
a thing born on the Western Sea.
The area is filled with spices and gold.
Its shape is like leek,
and its flower is cyan.
What’s its name?
This is a kind of grass called Zhu Yu.
What is its use?
You won’t go hungry if you eat it.
The head of the Northern Mountain
is called the Mount Shanhu.
Another 250 miles north.
A Mountain called Qiuru.
It is full of jade, no grass and trees.
Good.
Shanggu.
Just ask.
I know this book backwards
and forwards.
I understand all of them.
The head of the Northern Mountain
is called the Mount Shanhu.
And 300 miles north, called...
What’s next?
Luckily I was prepared.
And 300 miles north, called...
The Classic of Mountains and Rivers...
Go, go, go!
Here it is. Here it is.
Can’t you answer it?
(The Classic of Mountains and Rivers)
Your Grace.
Mount Dai with jade on it
and a lot of green jade under it.
Goddess, my answer is not right?
Absolutely right.
Hongri. Go get two cups of hot tea
Okay, I’ll go get it for Your Grace.
A beast born in the West Sea.
It looks like Yu with white ears.
And it can crawl on all fours
and walk like a man, what is its name?
And it can Crawl on all fours
and walk like a man, called...
W... Where is it?
I can’t find it!
Your Grace.
This is the content of the first
volume of the book.
You just said that you
can recite it backwards.
Now you don’t know it.
Well.
- Can you answer?
- The first volume...
Shanggu.
It’s called Xingxing. If you eat it
and you will walk fast.
Your Grace is really knowledgeable!
Even these earrings are extraordinary.
Lying and deception
are worse than uneducated.
Okay, I know.
The Classic of Mountains and Rivers
is difficult to read.
If you want to memorize it,
you need to work hard.
Shanggu,
I will test you again in a few days.
Understood.
The next question I would like to ask
is the matter involving
the management of the Three Realms.
You should study it well as a Chief God.
The issues involving
the management of the Three Realms.
There is nothing more superficial
than the customs and traditions,
astronomy and geography
So that you can adapt
to the local conditions.
And deal with all the problems.
My next topic is
The Tiger Demons live all year
round in the Red Blood Forest.
This area is barren.
In what ways do they practice?
The Tiger Demons are savage,
cruel and murderous by nature
They must have obtained the spiritual power
by eating their own kind
to improve themselves.
I didn’t realize that Goddess of Snow
is just an armchair strategist.
Sitting and talking.
The Tiger Demons are an
extremely united group.
All of them got the spiritual
power from God of Demons.
Then mastered the basic power
to practice.
They rely on generations
of inheritance and accumulation
to have strong spiritual power.
Red blood Forest is hot in all seasons.
I have never been there
to perform a spell.
So I don’t know the cause and effect.
Please punish me, Master.
Punishment is not necessary.
But there is no end of learning.
Don’t be someone who is
strong in appearance
but weak in reality.
Yes, I will remember the teachings
of Master.
Your Grace.
Look at me.
I forgot about Goddess of Snow.
But you are made of ice.
I don’t think it’s necessary to have
hot tea to drive away the cold.
Shanggu.
You are the Chief God.
You are closely related to
the Three Realms and you just recovered.
Take more care of yourself
in the future.
Okay.
Really?
When did Ice Cube become so warm?
You didn’t make it up, did you?
Look at my charm.
Look at you.
Do you have confidence
to attract Bai Jue?
Pretty close.
It’s like 80%.
80%?
Not that confident.
I think you are really into this.
Completely fallen into this.
This is not useful for me.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Ice Cube was on my side.
Maybe he also likes me, right?
But why doesn’t he tell me?
(Bai Jue)
I see.
Ice Cube. Don’t be afraid
I’ll help you out of your misery.
(Xueying)
Xueying.
I’ll see how you can pursue
Bai Jue in the future.
Ancestral God, bless me
to be successful.
Otherwise.
My years of being single would be
in vain.
Created by nature,
You called me here in a hurry.
What happened?
When I begged you to come here,
I was worried that
Shanggu won’t take over
the position of the Chief God.
The speed of the collapse of the Power
of Chaos in the lower Realm
is faster than we can imagine.
The power of chaos collapses everywhere.
Then barriers everywhere
and seals must have been damaged.
You should send someone
to repair the barrier
as soon as possible.
Of course I know this.
But tomorrow is the Day of the Chosen.
The Immortals in the lower Realm
who just cultivated to the top
will enter the God Realm for practice.
I am determined to
select an outstanding disciple
for Shanggu
to help her practice.
I called you to ask you.
How many more days does
Shanggu need to become Chief God?
She learns fast, but it’s
still a short time.
I’m afraid it will take
ten thousand years longer.
Ten Thousand Years?
No.
The later she becomes Chief God,
more dangerous the lower Realm will be.
Master Bai Jue.
You guys guard here every day.
Is there anything strange?
I did not find any strange.
I would like to ask Master to explain.
Never mind.
Guard this place, I will personally
go in to have a look.
Yes.
The spiritual power is thin here,
so the seal should be damaged.
But the God-holding lock
is not weakened in any way.
It’s chaos.
Could it be the Deicide Flower?
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪