=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 8=
The spiritual power is low here.
The seal should have been damaged,
but the God-holding Lock
hasn’t weakened by any bit.
It’s the air of chaos.
Could it be the Deicide Flower?
When Deicide Flower blooms,
it releases the air of chaos,
which can only be absorbed by
the Chief Gods of the Three Realms.
It is most conductive to practice
the mightiest the Power of Chaos.
Bai Jue,
the little Chief Goddess
that you care so much about
can learn it from you.
Why don’t you hand her to me?
Within a thousand years,
I’ll train her into
a Chief Goddess of Chaos.
The old man Qingtian set me up
so I’m tied here
on the God-Holding Platform,
how do I harm her, right?
Why should you be worried?
My proposal
benefits you
or me
or the Three Realms.
Maybe only by becoming
the Chief Goddess of Chaos
can you change the predestination.
(Ning, a girl born by a snake, lying on
a bed anxiously was seen by her family)
(Even though you’re a demon snake)
Even though you’re the Chief Goddess,
my heart doesn’t change.
I, Bai Jue, won’t fail you.
The story is good.
It’s about the knowledge of
the nine-headed serpent.
I’ll excerpt some.
I’ve heard that
Master Bai Jue was going to
wine and dine you alone, Your Grace.
Is the red rope already working?
Your Grace, let’s go
make some preparations.
Of what?
Having a bath
and getting some new clothes.
Since Bai Jue sincerely invited me,
I can’t rudely reject him, right?
But you and I must
put the practice in highest priority.
We can’t be distracted by fun.
(Wish we’re together forever)
If someday, Master Bai Jue
tells you how he feels about you,
you should handle it properly
as a dignified Chief Goddess.
How dare you.
You’ve only served me for days,
and you’re already mocking me.
Sorry.
Your Grace,
my master has something important
to speak to you.
Please come to Changyuan Hall.
Go back and tell your master that
I’ll be right there.
Yes.
It’s just an average dinner,
you didn’t have to dress so grandly.
When Hongri went to me,
Wu Huan and I were selecting
a robe for the Day of the Chosen.
I didn’t want you to wait too long,
so I just came with the robe on.
Please, these are all your favorites.
You eat a lot normally.
What? You don’t have an appetite today?
Idiot, no appetite?
I’m just trying to be elegant.
Try this sour bamboo. It’s appetizing.
See?
The bracelet is so shiny
after I polished it.
I take so good care of the gift
that you gave me.
The wonton is still warm.
It tastes the best right now.
My lip makeup.
You don’t like it?
How is it?
Slow down. Don’t choke on it.
Shanggu,
I have something to tell you.
This is it! This is it!
Ice Cube is pouring me some wine.
Is he...
Going to tell me how he feels about me?
I’ve got a good plan
which may help you get the
instruction feather of Chief God sooner.
Great!
There are too many magics
for us to learn.
Let’s go together.
I’m afraid you’ll have to go
on your own.
I’m going alone?
Where?
Fighting is the quickest way to
improve your God power.
I’ll have to
head to the Nether World on your own.
The Nether World?
For how long?
A thousand years.
A thousand years...
Shanggu,
you’ve been practicing hard ever since
your God veins got unblocked.
It’s just time is pressed.
I don’t have other choices.
It’s not that I don’t want
to go with you.
You practice the Power of Chaos,
Neither me nor Tianqi nor Zhiyang
can help you.
You’re on your own.
I’ve started to recite
the Classic of Mountains and Seas.
I’ll study hard.
Don’t scare me with the Nether World.
The decision has been made.
No more discussion.
I don’t understand.
Why do you kick me away
all of a sudden?
Did I do anything wrong?
The Nether World is dangerous.
There will be no one there
protecting or spoiling you,
or making plans for you.
So you must be good.
Think twice before you act. Got it?
I won’t go!
Unless you go with me.
♪Wait for years♪
This is the elixir that I made for you.
You may take it if necessary.
I won’t go!
♪Existing afar♪
♪Love shines upon mountains
And seas like the moon♪
I know that I’m willful,
that I’m lazy and that I don’t practice
or read enough.
But I’m trying to change myself.
I’ll strive to meet your expectations.
Just don’t send me to
the Nether World. Please.
As a True Goddess, you are to
lead the Three Realms.
We don’t get to choose our fate.
In the Heavenly Realm, we call
it the last meal before execution.
Fine.
I’ll go.
♪Expect migrant birds to return
Wait for years♪
♪No regret after despair♪
No one is irreplaceable♪
♪Wish that wake up someday♪
♪With a clean slate♪
♪My heart confesses to you♪
He’s a heartless man all along.
It’s your own fault
that you were too optimistic.
You looked for trouble yourself.
What did Bai Jue do again?
He said
I’ll be sent to the Nether World.
On my own.
A thousand years.
He’s lost his mind.
The Nether World is full of Devils.
I can’t believe he has
the heart to do so.
No. I must reason with him.
Tell me,
is he not going to be satisfied with me
before I become a Chief Goddess?
Silly girl.
I really don’t want you
to experience all these.
I don’t want to go.
I don’t want to go to the Nether World.
What am I supposed to do
to make him revoke the decision.
No matter what happens,
I’ll be on your side.
If you don’t want to go,
let’s figure something out.
It’s no big deal.
We’ll fight him if we have to.
Tomorrow is the Day of the Chosen.
Please rest early, master.
Go to the lower realm tomorrow.
Give Wuxi some spiritual power
to facilitate his
transformation into human.
What?
It’s nothing.
At the thought of Wuxi and Feng Yan,
my heart softens.
Your heart softens?
They have parted with
each other for a thousand years.
It’s too much pain.
Muguang.
Thanks.
You’re welcome.
We promised that we’d look after
each other in the God Realm.
The Day of the Chosen
is the day the disciples are chosen
in the God Realm.
These four immortals
are the best in recent years.
Please make your choice prudently
to reinforce the foundation
of the God Realm.
Yes, Your Grace.
Arise.
You’re the best candidates.
You’ve passed the Chosen Test
and are ranked.
Tell us where you are from.
I’m Zhong Li from Mount Kunlun.
I’m Xia Hui from Daohe Clan of Shanzhou.
(Muguang)
I’m Muguang from the Golden Dragon Clan on Mount Tianci.
He’s from the Golden Dragon Clan.
Muguang has strong spiritual power
and is very gifted.
He ranked No. 1 in the test.
And he practices the soothing
techniques of the Golden Dragon Clan.
I think
Muguang is the most ideal
assistant of Shanggu.
I’m Gu Jun
from the Sea Dragon Clan
of Yuanling Swamp.
Sea Dragon? Sea Dragon?
Why is the savage land sending
anyone up here?
(Gu Jun)
The Day of the Chosen is solemn.
If the lower realm
doesn’t have four candidates,
just let us know.
Why is an inferior demon sent here?
Goddess of Snow,
are you belittling the Demons?
Sorry.
I heard that
other than the four True Gods,
other gods do their jobs
equally.
If I was lowly,
then what would you be, Goddess?
If the God Realm hierarchizes
the lower realm based on regions,
then maybe the God Realm
is too snobbish for you.
Insolent!
How dare you!
Kid, you’ve got an attitude.
Step forward.
Let me have a look at you.
You do like him.
No wonder
your temper is like that person.
Zhiyang,
I like the kid’s attitude.
You choose from the rest.
He
will be the disciple
of the Pilgrimage Hall.
Whatever you say.
Hail, ma’am.
No.
Master Bai Jue, you can’t interfere with
the decision of the Pilgrimage Hall.
Lady Shanggu makes the choice.
Is Master Bai Jue choosing a disciple
or the Pilgrimage Hall?
The lower realm complains that
because Wu Huan is at your side,
so you got a good deal.
I’m afraid Gu Jun is admitted because
of his appearance, right?
How can she say this?
Right.
What did you say?
How can you say this?
You can insult me,
but not my master.
What are you going to do with me,
lowly demon?
He’s weak now but he will grow.
The life of God is long.
No one predicts the future.
Goddess of Snow, I book a duel with you
as the master of Gu Jun.
A month later, you two duel.
I promise that
if Gu Jun fails,
I’ll head to the Nether World
right away.
Before I master the Power of Chaos
and take over the
instruction feather of Chief God,
I won’t come back to the God Realm.
If you lose,
are you willing to
detach yourself from the God Realm?
Deal.
Lift your hands.
Thank you, master.
I won’t fail you.
I can’t believe
I was so lucky on the Day of the Chosen
to have you.
Don’t worry.
Although I’m not a True God,
I still have the good stuff for you.
I’ll train you into
a God as quickly as I can.
I, Muguang of the Golden Dragon
on Mount Tianci,
kneel before my master,
the Goddess of Moon & Stars.
I respect my master like parents.
I won’t fail you. I’ll practice hard.
Arise. Don’t be so formal with me.
You’re gifted.
But you’re rigid. Just like Zhiyang.
Please don’t make fun of me.
But...
I haven’t given you the
disciple’s entrance letter.
I’ll go home
and get it for you.
That’s unnecessary.
I know that Golden Dragon Clan
is courteous and cultured.
Ever since Moon House was built,
it only has a board but no couplet.
Can I task you to write the couplet?
Sure.
I have the confidence to
complete the task.
But remember,
don’t make it highbrow. Make it grand.
Come to see me in the Taoyuan Forest
once you’re done.
Yes.
(The Pilgrimage Hall)
Sir Gu Jun, this is the Pilgrimage Hall.
Your Grace is inside the room.
Please wait here.
Thank you.
Hail, master.
Look at you, all tensed up.
Just like when I just came to
the Pilgrimage Hall.
Get up. No strangers here.
I’m here to see my master
and officially bow to her.
Please let her know.
Her Grace is reading in there.
She is not to be disturbed.
She ordered me to tell you something.
Please tell.
The competition is upon you.
You must practice hard.
The formality isn’t essential.
Formality isn’t needed here
in the Pilgrimage Hall.
Don’t worry, Your Grace is kind.
And she is nice to others.
Just do what she tells you to do.
Yes, I will.
All right, straighten your spine.
From now on,
the Pilgrimage Hall is your home.
You’re from Yuanling Swamp.
Where did you practice before?
Sea Dragon Pool of Yuanling Swamp.
Sea Dragon Pool?
What a coincidence!
I, too, practiced in Sea Dragon Pool
for a hundred years before.
Did you.
I always think
Sea Dragon Pool is a desolated place
and the spiritual power is thin
in Yuanling Swamp.
Why did you practice there, my lady?
The earth deity of Sea Dragon Pool
is generous
and loves to teach knowledge.
I was fortunate to study a lot from him.
I passed the Chosen Test
because the earth deity enlightened me.
How is he doing?
He still drinks three jugs
of booze every day.
That’s what he likes.
When did you practice in Yuanling Swamp?
Three thousand years ago.
I was there, too.
Were you?
Why didn’t I see you?
I was a lower demon back then.
I always practiced in self-seclusion.
That’s why you didn’t see me, my lady.
It makes sense.
It’s only been three thousand years
and you’ve improved so much.
I’m not gifted.
But I was more diligent than others.
Her Grace chose you for a reason.
You’re different from the rest.
Please don’t make fun of me.
Please don’t call me “my lady” anymore.
Call me Wu Huan.
I didn’t know
we practiced at the same spot.
as the divine beast of the
Chief Goddess of the Three Realms,
you’d practice in rigor and cold.
I thought
only a lesser demon like me
would go to Yuanling Swamp.
You’re right.
I was one of the lesser
ones of Parasol Forest.
The Five-colored Phoenix.
No.
I didn’t mean you were lesser.
For real.
Birth means nothing.
As long as we don’t
look down on ourselves,
no one else can.
Don’t waste time here. Go to practice.
I’m off, then.
(The Pilgrimage Hall)
Gu Jun.
If you need anything,
just come to me.
Thank you, Lady Wu Huan.
He has the backbone.
He’s more pleasant than
those patronizing high disciples.
(Taichu Hall)
God Zihan. Master Zhiyang has assigned
Muguang to learn from Goddess Yuemi.
The two of us are gonna learn
from Master Tianqi.
Is that possible for you
to take us to meet our master?
Stop.
Master Tianqi has said,
all people in his hall look pretty.
You guys are too ugly to join us.
He didn’t want you.
Well, then,
you gotta find us another shelter
in this God’s world, right?
Yeah.
(Accommodate Yourself)
Fine.
Here you go with
two 10000-year-old snow lotus seeds.
Take those back.
They’ll nourish your skin.
Probably in the next Day of the Chosen,
you’ll get favored by Master Tianqi.
God Zi…
He’s nothing but a beast.
How dare he crack the whip at me!
So embarrassing.
Now I’m a little envious of Muguang.
Since Goddess Yuemi took him in,
she has treated him so well
and nurtured him
as one of the 12 Star Messengers.
That’s for sure.
You and I are no match for Muguang.
But that Gu Jun of low origin
should take away our halo.
I swear I will find a chance
to teach this demon beast a good lesson.
Let’s go.
- Goddess Xueying.
Relax. I didn’t hear anything.
It’s just that
the Nine-Clawed Lotus of the East Pond
of Changyuan Hall are blooming.
I heard it’s intensely poisonous,
which shouldn’t be underestimated.
Many fairy fishes
in the pond have been poisoned.
You gotta find a way
to solve the problem.
Yes.
(Ning, a girl born by a snake, lying on
a bed anxiously was seen by her family)
Your Grace.
It’s been a few days
for you haven’t visited Changyuan Hall.
Hongri has come
for several times to check.
What did he say?
Both Hongri and I worry about your bet.
Xueying is a Goddess.
It’s truly hard for Gu Jun
to win over her.
Gu Jun could break into the Chosen Test
all the way from Abyssal Ridge Swamp.
It means that he
has the perseverance
to grasp the nettle.
Over time,
I’ll get better as well.
When the time comes, our hall
will definitely become the top one hall
in the God Realm.
Your Grace. Work hard.
I’ll make sure Pilgrimage Hall
is always ready
and won’t distract you and Gu Jun.
Gu Jun. You owe us a favor.
Thanks to the fairy water,
or you’d have to burn yourself!
Demon beast is a demon beast.
You really think
you can acquire God Power?
If I were you, I’d go home
before losing face
of the Chief God in a month.
Bullshit.
What the hell is this?
It’s on my handsome face.
Go.
- Master.
- Go.
What happened to you, Master?
You…
Your Grace. Your Grace.
Bad news! The Taichu Hall is flooded!
Zihan detained Gu Jun
and claimed that he has intended
to assassinate Master Tianqi.
(Taichu Hall)
Your Grace.
How did you hurt so badly?
Slow down. Slow down.
Shanggu.
I was too careless
to be hurt by some immortals.
I’m afraid I won’t live long.
It’s just a Nine-Clawed Lotus.
You are a true god.
How could this happen?
You have no idea.
A few days ago, I was practicing.
Suddenly,
I was like possessed by the devil.
My heart got hurt severely.
And the Nine Claw Lotus
attacked my heart as well
and caused an old injury recrudescence.
I’m afraid that this time,
I can’t hold out for too long.
Seriously?
Shanggu.
I hope in my last moments,
you’ll be by my side.
Don’t worry.
You definitely will make it through.
Why?
Because coincidentally, I just learned
a set of pointing techniques
in the lower realm.
It won’t work.
A drowning man will catch at a straw.
See?
I was right.
You definitely will make it through.
Since when did you find out?
When I walked in the door.
Am I that bad at acting?
Just a little worse than me.
I remember when I was young,
I was injured by Taotie.
You took me to the lower realm
to seek medical treatment.
The treatment takes more
than a hundred years.
Actually, I’ve realized
I was totally fine.
You were using me as a cover
so as to facilitate your own travels
down the lower realm.
Holy crap.
At that time, you were naughty
and mischievous,
just like a boy.
Zhiyang got frustrated about you.
I’m the only one willing
to clean up your mess.
I learned nothing
but cleverness in trivial matters
from you.
It was Yuemi who taught you that.
You’ve got the wrong person.
It’s definitely not me.
Although
Devil God is now being suppressed
by the God binding Lock,
in the Nether World,
there’re still many free Devils
out there.
This is a dangerous trip.
I really don’t want you to go.
I know.
Your willfulness and stubbornness
are all pretend.
You’re the most self-driven person
I’ve ever met.
You grew up amidst criticism, Shanggu.
As for the nonsense they talked,
when you hear it,
you’d only fight it back
with pranks.
Only when you return to the hall
will you secretly wipe your tears.
The position
of Chief God seems to be glorious,
but in fact it’s too hard to take.
That day in the hall,
I could tell that
Zhiyang and Bai Jue
must have discussed it.
Neither of them stopped you to go
to the Nether World.
But don’t worry. As long as I’m here,
no one can force you to do
what you don’t want to do.
Isn’t it just a trip?
It only takes a thousand years.
It will pass in a blink of an eye.
A piece of cake.
Your acting skills aren’t any better
than mine.
As long as I can inherit
the instruction feather of Chief God,
I am willing to suffer as much as I can.
Our naughty little Goddess Shanggu
has finally grown up.
It’s heartbreaking to see you
to think like an adult.
Sorry. Sorry.
Who are you?
I’m Muguang. I’m so sorry, Goddess.
It’s you.
I’m not Goddess.
Just an Attendant God of Her Grace.
You don’t have to bow for me, Muguang.
You’re Wu Huan,
the Divine Beast of Shanggu?
I was too reckless just now.
Sorry about that.
I will pay for your dress
next time we meet.
Don’t worry. It was just an accident.
Oops. I’ve smudged your masterpiece.
It’s okay.
The light and shadow comes and goes.
There is no limit to the boundaries.
I’ll always be there with no regrets.
That’s fabulous!
Affectionate
and Magnificent.
Here you go.
Goddess Yuemi asked me to write
a few couplets for the Moon House.
I wrote many of them
with which I wasn’t so satisfied.
I was contented
until I came to these two.
So, I wanted to show them to my master
as soon as possible.
That’s why I knocked into you.
I’m really sorry for that.
It’s okay.
You’ve already apologized.
No need to say it again.
I’m still in a hurry to get back
and wait for news from Gu Jun.
Let’s talk later.
Gu Jun?
What happened to him?
He got into trouble in Taichu Hall.
I don’t know if he’ll be alright.
Her Grace is there.
He’s gonna be okay.
What if he doesn’t have the protection
of the Goddess?
You were born with a golden key.
I guess you don’t know
how difficult the path upward is
for us lower people.
Gu Jun treads on eggs.
I guess you won’t understand.
I don’t quite understand.
We just don’t want to be looked down
upon by others.
How come you two
are even uglier than before?
It was Gu Jun who beat us up.
Please trust me, Master.
Don’t call me Master.
Taichu Hall doesn’t accept apprentices
who lost in fights.
Fighting isn’t a big deal.
It’s a big deal
if it hurts Master Tianqi,
especially for his precious face.
A leaf from a 2000-year-old tree
accidentally fallen on his face
has been banished to the lower realm
to clean the pond.
Tell me.
Who put out the Nine-Clawed Lotus?
- It was him.
What the hell is that Nine-Clawed Lotus?
I’ve never heard of it.
Gu Jun. Although you’re the apprentice
from my hall,
I won’t show any favor toward you.
Tell us the truth.
Did you put the Nine-Clawed Lotus there?
No.
Okay, I believe you.
Your Grace.
The Nine Claw Lotus is originally
from the Demons.
Both of us are Immortals.
It’s impossible for us to have it.
Nevertheless,
in the God Realm, it also exists…
Right in the East Pond
of Changyuan Hall.
If it wasn’t brought by Gu Jun
from the lower realm,
could it be brought by Bai…?
Never mind.
I don’t care to look into this matter.
You two.
Go take three lightning strikes each.
- Yes.
As for you…
None of my business.
I’ll leave you to Shanggu.
Go. Go.
I don’t wanna see your face.
Why don’t you bow down and thank Master?
Thanks. Master.
I’ve just checked
Gu Jun’s cultivation level.
He was born with cold veins
and his spiritual power is disordered.
I’m afraid he can only compete
with Xueying after he’s promoted to God.
Otherwise, he’ll definitely lose.
I came to check on you.
I heard that you got into trouble.
Zhong Li and Xia Hui
tried to set me up,
and they got hurt instead.
I’m glad you’re okay.
Her Grace took you as her apprentice.
There must be plenty of people
who are jealous.
In the future,
you should be more careful.
I know.
But I worry that I can’t make a progress
in such a short time,
and lose the match with Xueying,
giving shame to my master.
From now on, I’ll practice with you.
With an opponent,
you’ll get to know where to improve.
Thanks, brother.
What are you holding?
This is a couplet I wrote for my master.
By the way,
do you usually practice your sword
in the Pilgrimage Hall?
Not really.
Sometimes, I’ll practice as I walk
when I got fascinated.
Come on. Let’s go practicing.
Go.
Is Wu Huan always
in the Pilgrimage Hall?
Yes.
How is she?
She’s nice.
One, two, three, four...
…Five, six, seven, eight.
Oh no. What Zihan said is true.
One is missing.
In that case,
the Nine-Clawed Lotus appeared
in the Taichu Hall
was taken from the East Pond.
Since the Goddess of Snow came here,
the East Pond has been taken care
of by her.
Shall we bring her here and ask?
Master. Where’re you going?
To the Pilgrimage Hall.
I’m gonna tell Shanggu the truth
and prove Gu Jun’s innocence.
Master is really getting more and more
concerned about her Grace.
If she really goes to the Nether World,
will he regret it?
How come Shanggu isn’t back yet?
Doesn’t she want to discuss
how to help Gu Jun advance to God?
It’s been a whole night.
What was she doing at Tianqi’s place?
Stop watching. Mind your business.
Goddess Yuemi. Please enjoy the tea.
I heard
there is a dark place in the God Realm
that is most suitable for Gu Jun
to be promoted to the upper gods.
That is the treasure of the Ice Cube,
which he never lend out.
But Gu Jun’s business
is Her Grace’s business.
Master Bai wouldn’t be so cold, right?
He couldn’t wait
to see Gu Jun fail.
In this case, Shanggu
can go to the Nether World
without any excuse.
(The Pilgrimage Hall)
Such a small matter,
how come True God Bai Jue was alerted?
Master Bai Jue.
Where’s Shanggu?
She’s where she likes to be.
It’s none of your business.
Master Bai Jue.
Her Grace went to the Chaos Hall.
Where’re you going?
The Nine-Clawed Lotus was taken out
of Changyuan Hall.
I gotta go apologize to Tianqi.
Apologize?
You are more like going to fight.
Shanggu.
Look, I’m in so much pain that
I can’t even hold my chopsticks.
Why don’t you feed me?
Enough.
How much pain
can a Nine-Clawed Lotus cause?
Back in the day, wasn’t you
who stepped on a Nine-headed snake
and took down a roc bird
with your fists?
How come you’re this weak now?
When have I ever been so brave?
You’re getting old
and your brain isn’t working well.
Just feed me one. Shanggu.
Who allowed you to stand here?
I didn’t invite you.
You came for me?
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪