(Lovers of the Red Sky)
(This drama is fictional and people or stories are not tied to reality.)
Long, long ago,
there was a time when humans lived in harmony...
with nature alongside beings that were not visible to the human eye.
One such being was three deities dwelling in one body.
They were called Samsin.
The eldest presided over birth.
The second presided over death.
The third presided over the balance between the two.
One day, the deity of death that craved more blood...
ate up the deity that managed balance.
The balance of life and death fell,
and the world was overcome with fear and unrest.
Around this time, the Demon broke off from Samsin's body...
and lived off the evil greed of the humans.
A woman who had lost her lover...
because of the Demon's reckless madness...
completed a drawing.
Old lady Samsin responded to her plea...
and took possession of the painting,
and the Devil who had brought havoc on the world...
became sealed within that very painting.
And then that woman disappeared.
(Episode 1: The Red Sky)
(Dan Dynasty, First year of King Seongjo)
(King Yeongjong ruled the world through the Demon in his body,)
(but he was afraid of the bloodbath caused by the untrollable Demon...)
(that he passed down his throne to his son, Seongjo,)
(and decides to do a ritual of sealing his own portrait...)
(in order to get rid of the Demon.)
Eun O, have you heard?
That this portrait is meant to be used to contain something?
They extracted something devastating from the king's body,
and are going to seal it in here.
I pray to you, oh deities.
May my husband's painting...
be completed without any problems.
I pray to you, oh deities.
This will do. Step aside.
But as a Seongjucheong shaman...
The Sealing Ceremony is held by Jokyeokjeon.
I understand.
(Hong Eun O, Gohwawon painter)
How can a painting be this powerful?
It is truly amazing.
Now it is all...
up to the will of the heavens.
Baby.
My baby.
Darling.
Dear Buddha.
Dear deities.
Dear Samsin. If anyone can hear me,
please protect my baby.
Samsin.
Please protect my baby.
Please protect...
Cheon Gi.
(Old lady Samsin: Gave life since the beginning of time)
Dear Cheon Gi, you were afraid, were you?
What is wrong? What is the matter?
Sir.
Father.
Is it truly possible to seal the Demon...
in a portrait of you?
That is the only way to banish the Demon from this world.
Too much blood was shed in the long war against the Demon,
and I will end it today.
Begin.
Om mani padme hum.
(The Demon: Caused death since the beginning of time)
Who dare awaken me?
Did you dare wake me up?
You fool!
He is our King!
The Demon must show his respect!
Do not look into his eyes. Do not make eye contact!
King. Step closer to me.
Take me in.
You can never escape me.
Hello?
Is anyone there?
(Hwacha: A goblin that lives on the energy of paintings)
Samsin.
Samsin, how dare you?
From now on, you shall all suffer from droughts and famine.
Your offspring shall endlessly wander in the darkness.
Your offspring shall never be able to paint again.
To think that he made you blind.
Then again, the Demon has always been mean.
Baby,
I cannot lift your curse,
but I will match you with someone who will protect you from the curse.
My Lady, you gave birth to a boy.
Baby, your name is Ram.
You are the eldest son of the noble Ha family,
Ha Ram.
That is a beautiful name.
Is something wrong?
Will this really bring peace to the world?
I am afraid the Demon will break free.
You do not have to worry.
Your kingdom will enjoy an age of peace.
The curse bothers me.
I mean the one about droughts and famine.
Giddy up.
What do you think you're doing?
Do you think you can get away with this?
Once the former king finds out...
The former king chose Seongjucheong.
You may step down now.
Slay!
Scatter!
To boil the hound once it has caught the rabbit.
I did what I did...
for the safety...
of the royal family and the people.
(9 years later, the 9th year of Seongjo's reign)
(The ritual was a success, but due to the curse of the Demon,)
(Dan Dynasty suffered 9 years of famine and drought.)
(the head priestess, Mi Su, looks for a helper...)
(to sacrifice for the rainmaking ritual.)
What does it say?
I can't read either. I have no idea.
- The king lacks virtue? - The drought is getting worse.
- I'm sure His Majesty has a plan. - Don't be ridiculous.
That's why it doesn't rain!
The drought has been going on for years!
- Coming through! - Father!
- Father! - Honey!
Not a single grain can leave the house.
Do you understand?
- Yes, Master. - Yes, Master.
- Oh, no. - Please.
- There's no water left. - Give us rain.
That boy has a marvelous ability.
- It's here. - Are you sure there's water here?
- Let's dig! - Dig!
The boy says there's water here. Hurry up and dig.
- Water... It's water! - It's water!
That boy must possess...
the energy of water.
We found water!
Father!
Hi, Ram.
Did it go well?
- Isn't that man... - Yes, Father.
Master Ha Sung Jin?
Let's go inside. Come.
So he was alive.
It's been a long time, Master Ha.
How dare you show up here?
Even after all these years,
I'm sure your resentment is beyond words.
You haven't the slightest idea.
I was under the orders of the former king.
Tell me why you're here right now,
or I'll kill you with my own hands.
I'm here for your son.
You little...
I'm sure you're aware that he was born with the energy of water.
I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
Master Ha.
This kingdom has been suffering from droughts for nine years now.
We need him at the next dragon rainmaking ritual.
Shut your mouth! I don't want to hear any more. Leave right now!
Your powers have become stronger.
I'm the royal shaman now.
(Royal shaman: A shaman who performs royal rituals)
I'm taking your son as a helper for the ritual.
It's not a matter of choice.
Get prepared.
We shall leave early in the morning.
What's the most important thing when it comes to portraits?
It's not the eyes that you see,
but the eyes that see you.
Guys, it's the blind ghost and her father.
My mom says they're possessed.
Possessed? Really?
Guys, do you believe that?
That makes no sense!
Watch this.
- Come and take it! - Come and take it!
- Give it back! - Come and take it!
- Come and take it! - Give it back! It's my father's!
Go away, ghost!
You beggar.
You're filthy. Get lost!
Leave my daughter, Cheon Gi, alone.
- Leave her alone. - What's wrong?
Father, don't do that.
I'm fine. Father!
Father, please.
I'm fine.
Father!
Hey, let's go!
Let's run. Hurry!
Let's run!
Move out of the way!
Don't look him in the eye.
- Never look him in the eye. - Father?
Don't look him in the eye, never.
I sense the Demon's energy.
Don't look him in the eye.
Stop. Please stop, okay?
What's this energy?
My father isn't in his right mind.
Where am I?
Father, are you okay?
- Cheon Gi. - Father, do you recognize me?
- Cheon Gi. - Father.
My dear Cheon Gi.
Eun O. Hong Eun O.
Is that really you?
Were you...
alive?
Master Ha?
I'm delighted to see you again.
(Seongjucheong: An institution in charge of royal shamanic rituals)
Are you all right?
You seemed to throw a fit earlier.
My fits started after that day.
Now I am getting more forgetful by the day.
I am worried sick about my young daughter, Cheon Gi.
She was born in the Shinchuk Year. On that very day.
So was my son.
Is he all right?
Ram, why don't you go and play in the yard?
Yes, Father.
Cheon Gi, you should go out too.
Then can I stop by at the Baekyu Painters Society?
Please, father.
What a smart little girl.
- Ram, why don't you accompany her? - Yes, Father.
I'm used to going there alone.
I'm not following you.
Does this area belong to you or what?
(Baekyu Painters Society)
- What's this place? - Goodness!
You really followed me?
I walked ahead of you.
Is that a joke?
I said, what's this place?
It's the Baekyu Painters Society.
It's a private painting group.
A private painting group?
It means they sell their paintings.
The painting we're going to copy today is not an old one.
(Copying: One of the six ways to learn how to paint)
This is a painting I made at Gohwawon...
of some men I saw at the market who gambled on a cockfight.
- Oh... Chun Bok. - Yes?
You'll have to take over.
Master Choi.
Master Choi, where are you going?
All right. There are a few things you can learn from this painting.
By the way, why are we here?
You wouldn't understand even if I explained.
Just tell me.
Stop prying without giving me anything in return.
Do you want me to pay?
Nothing in the world is free.
Forget it.
I don't want to know.
Fine.
Try closing your eyes.
I don't want to.
Once you close your eyes,
you hear sounds.
Do you hear that?
I hear the brush moving on the paper.
Swish.
Swash.
Goodness, now you're bragging.
As I listen to the sounds,
images arise in my mind.
And when that happens,
I feel good.
I see the world through sounds.
Please.
Ms. Gyeonju.
Master Choi.
Cheon Gi.
I've run out of paints at home.
Can I take some leftover paints home?
Sure, go ahead.
Okay. Thank you.
Master Choi.
What? What is it now?
Have you seen Ms. Gyeonju?
She said she had something for me,
but I can't find her in the kitchen.
There's a bundle in the shed.
A bundle in the shed.
He says there's a bundle in the shed.
Yes, there's a bundle in the shed.
What a smart boy. Will you help her find it?
Sure. Let's go, Cheon Gi.
Ms. Gyeonju.
Master Choi, the class is...
- I give up! - Oh, my.
- Fine, I give up! - Master Choi!
Why are you so thick?
I shouldn't have taken you in.
By the way,
how did you know there was a bundle in the shed?
Well...
That's...
Cheon Gi, you're here.
Ms. Gyeonju.
I thought you were away.
Well, the thing is...
Hold on a second.
Your jeogori is torn.
Give me a second. I'll go and mend it right away.
Wait here.
Why didn't you tell me?
I get holes in my clothes all the time.
I thought you were the same.
Don't you have a mother either?
I do.
Why? Don't you?
She passed away...
on the day I was born.
What are you drawing, all of a sudden?
A star.
That looks more like a full moon to me.
To me, this is a star.
What are you doing?
Let's draw together.
Is this a star?
Yes.
The Big Dipper.
Are you hungry?
No, I'm not.
Follow me.
You two.
Come over here.
Us?
Yes. You two. Come here.
Let me see you.
Here. Tomorrow,
you will need this.
No, it is okay. I cannot accept something like this.
What do you mean?
Oh?
What's wrong?
What is it?
Nothing.
I think I was mistaken.
Let's go.
Keep your hands held tight.
They finally met.
(Seongjucheong)
What brought you to Guanyang?
Fate can be so cruel.
At the next rainmaking ritual,
my son was selected to be the helper.
My son Ha Ram was born with the energy of water.
Then he is going to the Palace?
He must not.
What?
You found a helper for the dragon rainmaking ritual?
Yes, Your Majesty.
We are keeping him in Seongjucheong.
Who is he?
He's the son of Ha Sung Jin who was Lord of Jokyeokjeon,
and he is a special child with the energy of the water deity.
The man who sealed the Demon nine years ago?
He is still alive?
Yes, Your Majesty.
He seems to have cheated death and moved to Yangzhou.
What a relief.
However,
this time, I must sacrifice his son?
You must withstand the pain and make the decision
for your starving people.
Are you saying we must sacrifice a human being?
Your Majesty.
One century ago, a life was taken at a rainmaking ritual,
and the deities swallowed their fury to give us rain.
How dare you say such things?
We follow Confucius' and Mencius' teachings,
and we cannot do such terrible things.
My lords. Have you already forgotten what happened nine years ago?
Droughts and famine have plagued us for years.
Sacrificing a life is the only way to lift the Demon's curse.
How dare a mere shaman speak her mind in this great hall?
What do you think?
The heavens' will not change whatever we humans do.
It is unthinkable that they would even accept a human sacrifice.
I agree with you.
The dragon rainmaking ritual will be held with dignity,
but without a human sacrifice. Do you understand?
- Yes, Your Majesty. - Yes, Your Majesty.
There will be no rain without a human sacrifice, Your Majesty.
Even if you all disapprove, I must go through with it.
As the royal shaman.
Hey.
What are you doing? This is what thieves do.
Quiet.
Hey.
There's someone here.
Don't you hear her snore?
Not bad.
Do you see the stick over there?
Yes.
Climb the tree.
Can't you just tell your father you're hungry?
There's a famine. Do you want to cause them trouble?
Okay, fine.
Be quiet.
Everyone here knows peach orchard's Ms. Anseong.
Why?
She has a fiery temper that makes grown men tremble in their shoes.
That means she's dangerous.
If she catches you, you'll never walk again.
What?
I won't do this, then. I'm coming down.
I want a peach.
I can't pick any because I can't see.
Okay.
Are you okay?
Who's there?
Oh?
Hey, run.
Okay.
She's coming. Run faster.
Are you okay? Let's go.
You fools. Don't you dare come back!
It's all your fault. If not for you,
we wouldn't have had to run from someone that scary.
Where are you going?
I hate you.
I never said wanted to steal someone else's peaches.
You're just the same.
Because I can't see,
because my dad's not right in his head,
because my mom died while giving birth to me,
I have no friends.
Everyone ridicules me for no reason.
They say I'm cursed.
I just wanted to share some peaches.
I'm sorry.
Whatever.
But...
your mom dying after you were born,
you not being able to see,
and your dad not being right in his head...
isn't your fault.
So why...
Why? What?
You don't know anything.
You're right.
I don't know anything,
but it couldn't be helped.
All that happened to you were out of everyone's control.
It wasn't your fault.
So don't blame yourself over...
what wasn't your fault.
I ran so much that I'm even more hungry now.
This is definitely your fault.
Here.
Darn it. It's not yet ripe.
It's sweet. It tastes just fine.
Oh?
What are you doing?
It'll be okay now.
Where is your bundle?
Oh, no. The bundle Ms. Gyeonju gave me.
I must've lost it while we were running away.
Here it is.
You really have it?
That's great.
Why did you tease me?
My heart almost sank.
You are merciless.
I can't even tease you.
There are so many stars tonight.
There's the Big Dipper.
Really?
Oh, right.
Oh, right, what?
Do you feel bad I can't see the stars?
I'm sorry.
I was inconsiderate.
How many stars are there?
About one hundred million?
How many is one hundred million?
Lots and lots.
Get down now. We're back.
Wait.
Here. You need it back.
No.
I'll come for it after the rainmaking ritual.
Isn't this very precious?
This? It's nothing much.
it's just...
an one-and-only handkerchief my mom gave me.
Is that lie true?
Okay. Come back tomorrow.
I'll wait for you.
Okay.
Then...
I'll get you more peaches while Ms. Anseong's back is turned.
Give me your hand.
My hand?
Here. Take this.
Take it.
You'll go to pick peaches with me tomorrow, right?
Of course I will.
Good. You promised.
Yes.
Let's go.
His Majesty the King.
You must be Ha Ram.
I lack in virtue and must rely on your help.
I owe your family a great debt.
Thank you.
Drawings are all about the eyes.
Your soul must be clean!
Darn you!
My goodness.
What is wrong with you?
Save me. Don't kill me.
Dad. This time,
a really good medicine came in.
Hang in there. Give me a little more time.
His Highness the Crown Prince.
Lee Hoo. It has been a while.
(Lee Kang: King Seongjo's first son)
Why haven't you visited in so long?
Your Highness, don't speak to me so politely.
There are people watching.
Who cares about that?
We are brothers from the same mother.
I am so pleased to see all my younger brothers.
Your Highness.
Our nation's in great distress caused by...
the long drought and famine.
Rather than focus on pleasure,
please think more of the meaning of the upcoming rainmaking ritual.
Hoo.
The day I become king, I will remember your advice.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Do you have to be so stiff?
Yul, I did not remind the Crown Prince...
because he doesn't know the meaning.
That's enough, Yul.
Hoo spoke out of concern for me.
(Lee Yul, Prince Yangmyeong: King Seongjo's third son)
I understand, Your Highness.
Hoo.
Why do you walk so fast?
Leave me alone.
Did what I say upset you?
Let it go, Hoo.
Yul, do you not feel anything?
About what?
We're like a guelder rose.
We can flower but we'll never bear fruit.
A flower with no life.
Each time I meet the Crown Prince,
I get frustrated.
Even though it can't be helped.
Hoo.
A guelder rose is light green when it first blooms.
It's white when in full bloom, then turns yellow before it wilts.
How can you say it has no life...
when it lives one so colorful?
Come with me, Hoo.
I will cheer you up.
What are you talking about?
I will show you something fantastic.
(Gyeongwon Pavilion: Late kings' portraits were kept and honored)
Your sacred turtle talisman fell off.
(Sacred turtle: Said to live 10,000 years and chase away evil)
Talisman are said to chase evil.
Father told us to keep one close at all times.
Put it in a deep pocket.
It's a bad omen.
Why did it fall off?
Forget about that, Hoo.
When will we ever get to see this if not now?
This place has a really strange energy.
(Tablet of the First King)
(Tablet of King Gwangjo)
He who is to be king.
He who is to be king of this land.
He who is to be king. He who is to be king of this land.
Come to me.
All rise for His Majesty.
He who is to be king. He who is to be king of this land.
Come to me.
My brother, what are you doing? You aren't supposed to touch that.
He who is to be king.
Come to me.
Doesn't Grandfather's portrait...
look as if he's still alive?
He who is to be king.
He who is to be king of this land.
"Oration."
"Oh, the bright and shining spirit."
"This great drought is harsher on our people than ever."
"Our people cry out..."
"as they are tormented in this neverending dry spell."
"It's all due to my lack of discretion."
"Please take mercy upon this ritual..."
"and allow heavy rain to fall."
Begin.
Salamander, oh salamander
Raise the clouds
And spurt out fogs
Salamander, oh salamander
Raise the clouds
And spurt out fogs
Come to me.
He who is to be king.
We must go now. Hurry.
I shall be with you.
He who is to be king. He who is to be king of this land.
Salamander, oh salamander
Raise the clouds
And spurt out fogs
Salamander, oh salamander
Raise the clouds
And spurt out fogs
If you let sweet rain fall
I will let you go
Is it you...
who woke me up?
Wait, this is...
human sacrifice?
Om mani padme hum!
Om mani padme hum.
Where are you?
Is it that way?
Ha Ram.
My goodness, look.
- Goodness! - Goodness!
Ha Ram.
Oh no.
Father.
Father!
A kid just fell.
- Go get him. - He just fell in the water.
Will you go get that kid out?
- What are we going to do? - He just fell in.
- Will someone get him? - Ha Ram...
Someone save him.
Father.
Your Highness!
Escort His Highness out.
Your Highness.
- Your Highness. - You must leave.
That was my position.
Escort the Prince out now.
It was truly...
my seat!
Father.
- This way! - Go!
Escort His Highness this way!
- This way! - Hurry up and evacuate!
Father...
Rain! It's raining!
It's raining.
Ha Ram!
It's raining!
It's really raining!
It was mine.
The King's throne was mine.
Ha Ram.
You have sacrificed your life...
for the lives of thousands, tens of thousands of people.
Did you use the kid as bait...
to lure me in?
Demon.
Reside in this child's body.
I'll take away the source of your energy, your eyes.
You won't be able to use your power...
until the day you retrieve your eyes.
Cheon Gi.
The promised child who will save this world.
I will leave these eyes to you for a moment.
Make the pottery of fate.
(Gyeonghoeru)
Look at him!
Ram.
- My lord. - Move aside!
Ram!
Arrest the shaman now!
Your Majesty.
I'm falsely blamed, Your Majesty.
Please give me a chance to explain, Your Majesty!
Ram.
- Father. - Ram.
I... I can't see anything.
Father.
Nothing.
I can't see anything, Father.
In the distant future,
when the two of you are reunited,
everything will fall into its place.
(Special thanks to Jeon Kook Hwan, Han Sang Jin and Kim Pub Lae)
(Lovers of the Red Sky)
(Every necessary precaution was taken when filming the water scene.)
The only painter in this city.
The sole lady of our studio.
There is no use in drawing everything identically.
I mean that you must reflect people's hopes in the painting.
You're here, Lord Ha.
It'll soon be 3am. We'll begin with Vermilion Bird of the South.
How are you going to explain this blind man studying astrology?
She has no pride as a painter.
What's the charm of imitated work?
In a nutshell, it has to look identical.
It must be that person who only wants Cheon Gi's paintings.
Find that copycat painter and get more information.
I don't know who you are, but please turn a blind eye for a moment.
Wait, is this woman...
(Lovers of the Red Sky)