Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ No longer panicking on the night of the blackout ♫
♫ You're by my side, illuminating a beam of light for me ♫
♫ Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet ♫
♫ Your breath ♫
♫ brushes up against my cheek ♫
♫ With you warming up the stage,
happiness never comes to a close ♫
♫ Boring jokes add some sweetness to the dinner ♫
♫ Daily life is even more like a comic than comics themselves ♫
♫ Happiness and sadness ♫
♫ Make up the moments of life ♫
♫ Rainy days become very special because of you ♫
♫ Picked up a pitiful youngster off the street ♫
♫ No matter when and where, you always appear ♫
♫ Holding me tightly and spinning in circles ♫
♫ Rainy days make me so nostalgic because of you ♫
♫ Becoming some part of the memories ♫
♫ Walking down a street with lights lighting up
one after another ♫
♫ Warming up the whole world ♫
[Please Feel at Ease Mr. Ling]
[Episode 24]
'your asset transfer is illegal'
'If I take this risk and let you become the highest share holder'
'will you keep your word and put the promised shares under my name?'
'of course'
'then sign a legit shares transfer'
my feelings to you are sincere
'as long as she disappear, then our Xiner's past would not resurface'
baby, mom does this for your good
good for me?
are you doing this for me or for you?
you hid this from me for so many years
until today do I find out I was the abuser
give us an explanation
what was that recording?
did you really transfer Lingyue's shares?
was it all for Miss Gu
Quiet! the recording is fake
it was all nonsense
till now do you still lie?
whats the situation?
I think everyone is really curious why I am here
this is my engagement. you irrelevant person just had to show up at the perfect time
irrelevent? I'm afraid not.
I'm just here to reveal the truth
just casually asking all the shareholders
a person promoted from despicable means
can you all really entrust the company to
despicable? whats more jaw dropping is that you brother would fake our own death
a person who wish to kill to keep a secret...
kill? accuse me of such a big crime. where's the evidence? rumors need evidence
things have developed to this point
you still want to cover up?
Lingyue, this recording, even I could forge
father is in a critical state
he has already said he wished that I would control the company shares
everyone here is wise
and know my father's regards
all support me as the company heir
as you? what do you have
what will you use to contend against me
'President Ling'
father
'hurry quick! let's go over there'
Dad? you are awake?
if i'm not awake, my most treasured and spoiled baby son, would have ruined the rest of his life
with the burden of destroying my hard earned business
most treasured?
you mean the most despised and most useless
Dad, it's been 20 years, for what? and for what?
you trust Lingyue to take care of your business
me, Lingsheng would be the one to ruin your house and home
why you trust Lingyue has right to inherit the company and me, Lingsheng
is only like a pet dog has to rely on you all to survive
you unfilial child
if you keep speaking badly then I won't polite
alright
you can all treat me badly but you must get this straight...
in this company I have the most shares
this company is mine no one can remove me from this spot
Lingsheng,
you are the youngest in our family
so everyone spoils you
but I wouldn't think it spoiled you like this
cause you to not know right from wrong and for selfishness
hurt your siblings
how can you do this, child?
everyone...
I, Lingtian today will announce
the current 20% in my hands
without conditions transfer to Lingyue
although it's not as much as the shares in the hands of this unfilial child
but through the heart
we don't value the quantity but the quality
I also have 10% transfer it all to Lingyue
now Lingyue has 30%
brother, are you crazy?
you going to give your money to a adoptee
Lingsheng! he is like you, both my younger brothers
let's go back
let me tell you, from the start I was not going to let this go
fine, now we have equal amount of shares
dad, you are already getting older
and have a weak body. you can entrust the company to me
you who is so ambitious
I would never entrust you with the company
fine
then all the shareholders here today will vote
who goes and who stays
as naturally goes
no need
Gu Anxin, you are not apart of this you don't get to speak
I have company shares, I also count as a shareholder
I have 5% that Uncle Ling gave my mother
plus my 5% we have more right to speak
a measly 5%
all shareholders combined is equal to 20%
not to mention we already reached a consensus
for Lingshi we have made better of plans
you don't need to feel remorse
Lingshi under you would only be slowly ruined
leaving it to me is the best option
Lingyue, help me up
to all shareholders
I, Lingtian have a few things to say
everyone here has been with me through thick and thin
from startup and coworkers
to friends
I pulled you all into this mess
I deeply apologize
today, Linshi Company
was not build be just me
was from everyone's participation
and built together
I believe every shareholder here
passion towards Lingshi
can even go past my own
so everyone knows at this climax
Lingshi most needs...
what?
hope everyone will be able to make the most wise decision
for everyone's collaborative effort
I, Lingtian thank you
I support Ling Yue!
I also support Ling Yue.
- Me too.
- I also support Ling Yue.
I support Ling Yue.
I also support Ling Yue.
- I support Ling Yue.
I support President Ling Yue!
Me too!
I also support Ling Yue.
- Me too.
Me too.
- I support Ling Yue.
Me too. I support Ling Yue.
- I also support Ling Yue.
- Me too.
- I also support him.
- I support Ling Yue.
What a good performance.
You prepared this long ago, didn't you?
You had to bring ruin upon me to be content?
Ling Yue, you're ruthless indeed. I lost.
Why couldn't it have been me?
Child, turn back.
Xiao Sheng, we already reported your previous actions
to the police. If you admit your crime, there's still time.
[Beilun District Hospital]
Brother! How is he?
Dad's CT scan showed a brain tumor.
They're now giving emergency treatment inside.
Brain tumor? How can that be?
It's all my fault. I was always worrying about Xin'er and Mom.
I didn't even notice that Dad...
It's all my fault.
Brother, don't blame yourself.
No one wants something like this to happen.
Then what about Xin'er?
Xin'er is currently being investigated by the police.
My mom... she couldn't take all this news at once. She is also being hospitalized now.
The police said that once she is more stable, they will continue the investigation.
Doctor, how is he?
Mr. Gu's surgery was very successful. However, he will experience after-effects.
It's because this brain tumor was pressing against his cranial nerve for a long time.
Mr. Gu's hippocampus and sebum
have atrophied. To be precise, Mr. Gu has developed Alzheimer's.
It's what we commonly call senile dementia.
- Thank you, Doctor.
- Of course.
Don't worry. It's okay.
We'll find a way together, okay?
I never even got to tell him the truth.
Now he won't have me in his memories anymore.
Then we'll spend time with him so that his present memories are all good ones.
Mom, I came to see you.
I talked with the doctor. Dad has recovered very well.
He'll be able to leave the hospital at the end of the month.
Mom, the police will come soon.
They hope that we will cooperate in their investigation.
Mom.
I don't know where you started to go wrong.
But from now on, let's return to the right path,
okay?
Okay?
The food has gotten cold.
I'll go heat it for you.
I've heard that in life, there are two kinds of people that you must never forget.
One kind is those who have helped me.
The other is those who have pushed me into dire straits.
But I don't know why I met these two kinds of people
in the same person.
How much I hate you is how quickly I hope you get better.
I want to hear you explain to me why you treated me like this.
If it's so hard to think of a reason to hurt someone,
then why did you make the decision so quickly back then?
I shouldn't have to tell you
where to go next, right?
Why don't you just punish me directly?
The police and the law will punish you.
But it's a waste of your talent.
Are you not afraid I'll run?
Up to now, my Brother Wu has never misjudged anyone.
[Long Wu]
When you come out, call me.
Barring unforeseen circumstances, I'll still be here in 80 years.
I just hope that your skills will be used on the right path.
[Long Wu]
Dad's memories are all from his youth.
Oh right, I've already put in the request to defer my studies.
In a few days, the approval will be issued.
Right now, my family needs me, and the Gu Group needs me.
I can't have both my career and my education after all.
Actually, I can take care of Dad.
Right now, I only care that Dad's lifelong effort and career will be carried on.
My mom's situation isn't too optimistic either.
I want to spend more time with her.
To be honest, if you asked me to forgive her now,
I don't think I could.
But it's all passed now.
I hope she can start over.
Oh right. Your room has already been rearranged to how you liked it when you lived there.
You will always have a home here.
I will fulfill my duties as your brother to the end.
Xin'er.
Sister.
I'll go get you both something to drink.
How are you?
Pretty good.
I've explained everything.
What happened with Yu Guo was my fault. I will take responsibility.
I'm sorry.
In truth, I should have said that long ago.
It's just that I always relied on my parents spoiling me.
I took it for granted.
My sense of infallibility
and narrow-minded selfishness
hurt you and Yu Guo
in ways that can never be remedied,
no matter how much I apologize or how remorseful I feel.
From now on, each time you call me 'sister',
it will cancel out 10 apologies. That takes immediate effect.
I hope that we can live as we each would like to live.
Okay.
Sister.
Dad.
You're back.
Dad, how's your health?
Why don't we go to the hospital and check it out?
My body...
I know my body well.
It's fine.
I'm sorry, Dad.
Since he was young, Ling Sheng
has been pampered by everyone in the family.
He surely was spoiled rotten.
If he had  only succeeded in getting the family estate,
I wouldn't begrudge that.
But, these outrageous acts [Ch: offense against Heaven and reason],
like this plot to murder members of the family,
I can't forgive him for that.
Dad, I think my little brother is still young.
As long as he is truly remorseful,
there's still time for everything.
I always thought
that the men in the Ling family could be raised like wolves teach their young.
Raise them with an awareness of how to compete and think of danger in times of safety.
But the result? The opposite of what I wanted.
To him, I really wasn't fair and square when it came to children education.
All of this
is the result of my incompetence as a father.
Dad.
In my heart,
you're a great father.
You've always been that.
Do you see? All these things are arranged in style.
I designed it. The old man's office should take on an entirely new look.
Look here. I chose these photographs.
Aren't they interesting?
I don't think they'll do.
No. You haven't even assumed your position formally yet,
and you're putting on airs.
What I mean is that this doesn't belong to me.
What are you saying?
Brother, I'll give this to you.
Dad already said that the Group is yours to manage.
Again, the tickets for touring the world are already reserved.
This is just disturbing my natural rhythms.
The person that Ling Shi Group needs most is you.
Dad just gave this to me to handle. But I'm the one who can decide how to handle it.
So, I'll leave Ling Shi Group to you.
What about you?
Establish a 5G logistics business. Realize Ling Xiao's plan.
Create a New Way that can change people's lives for the better.
That's my thinking and my objective.
- I regret this.  - Regret what?
You should have said this earlier; I changed the style in here to what you like.
Look at those photographs behind you. I'll be facing them every day as I work.
Where will I get my inspiration?
From my style.
What beauty is there to appreciate there?
Welcome to our Milky Way cartoon office.
There are a few requirements I need to make clear to you at the beginning.
This is a very fashionable company.
And it's a very strict company.
- A culture of overtime work.
- A wolf-character philosophy.
- No days off.
- On call 24 hours a day.
- No procrastination on drawings.
- Unlimited revisions.
A soulless punch card machine.
Anything like lax discipline is not allowed.
Did we scare you?
All that was just in fun.
We actually have a relaxed atmosphere in our work.
Our mission is to work and create joyfully.
Okay, you're off work for today.
When you come to work tomorrow, you'll understand the feeling.
[Ling Yue]
[Gu Ansheng]
I will very quickly  develop the
purpose and plans for this collaboration.
I'm actually quite curious about the plans you and Anxin have.
Is this your concern as my brother?
As a brother who once loved her and will continue to love her.
That makes me feel quite threatened.
A little sense of danger isn't a bad thing.
Don't worry. Anxin is the person I love.
And she's my family.
What are you doing?
Acting so respectable and polite is so exhausting. And I can't do it.
Besides the family already has a boss. Isn't good enough that l just draw my cartoons?
You'll get used to it over time: being the artist, Anxin.
My ancient style comic, I Accidentally Picked Up a Prince,
the separate edition is already in process.
But you have to change the name. The market already has illegal copies with that name.
Disgusting.
Okay. Boss. Ms. Boss.
Let this hard-worker think about it, okay?
Good luck.
Young Miss Boss, time to go home?
Although I'm one of the bosses here,
based on reason, you should be the young Miss Boss.
We're dating, not doing some business to accomplish a mission.
I'm used to this profession.
Actually,
you could call this an intense date.
But I think it makes up for the previous time we've lost.
There are still a lot of things that we haven't said;
a lot of things we haven't done.
Since it's like that, let's take it slowly.
After all, we still have a lot of time ahead.
In my current state,
you must be very disappointed in me.
Very disappointed.
But I'm also very worried
and wondering.
Everything has fallen apart.
It's peaceful.
For all of this I have only myself to blame.
You can begin a new life for yourself.
I won't let you be tangled up and dragged down by this.
These days...
I keep thinking back
to things that happened when we were young.
Those things
were all for completing homework
and worries over exams.
pure and wonderful
I would also think
if we could restart
to the first time I met you
would everything be different
i'm sorry
i can finally understand you
how you felt at that time
you won't understand
how would I not know
haven't I also been waiting for someone
waking up every morning
I have things to do
and places to go
and have someone who needs me waiting for me
how is it you show up when I was feeling down
I want to know if he is well
and help him heal
and hope he doesn't worry
or be afraid
and hope everyday he
is simply happy
and can smile genuinely
do you know?
these things now
is my happiness
I don't deserve you
and I don't want
you to see my ugly past
and still willing to stand with me
well...
our time together
i'm already really happy
Linghseng
look
i am prepared
all those days you waited alone...
i will spend the rest of my life to repay you
i hope one day you would look back at me
as long you nod
i can without reason run to you
Xiner is like the moon in the sky
beautiful and bright
to get closer to her
i prepared for so many years
now I can finally stand next to her
and hold her hand
to accompany her with laughter
and tears and growing old
when I think about this
I am the happiest man in the world
and I will also make the the happiest
so don't make me wait too long
did you sign in today?
I did sign?
the iron law I told you yesterday do you remember?
yeah I memorized...
you are so talented
stop looking you already look so good
i'm not, just checking for something on my teeth
although I am a public figure now. check out my smile
of Miss Celebrity
today's work is to sign everything here
for signed copy is not discounted for non signed copy is discounted
every additional signed copy we earn $9.63
I got it, though no food or sleep I will sign them all
Sister
Xiner
congratulations on your new publication
also congratulations to you, I saw the news
Cai Niao Station has officially opened for business
and got the new logistic technology award
I have to think Lingyue
what can he help you with
your stations is now blossoming everywhere
is because of your ability
oh yeah have you read? any comments?
I read all your ManHua
did you model a character after me?
thank you, you gave her such a lovely ending
in real life you deserve to be loved as well
wait for me
take one with you
Anxin, President Ling got to the airport and disapeared
he has a business meeting but we can't get in contact
do you know any place to find him
I know now, I will take a look
I have an emergency, you guys stay here
Lingyue are you home?
Lingyue
Okay
You better be alright or your going to be in so much trouble
Miss, our supermarket has a promotional event
here take one
oh no thanks, I'm really busy
try it out
okay, thank you
here we go
Congratulations on becoming rich!
okay, okay thank you
congratulations you just won our grand prize
it is a coupon for $888
888?
such a coincidence
I actually do have an emergency, I got to go
oh thats great
there was a gentlemen that said if you won't come with me then to
give you this package
what package
my bike
♫ When I first met you, I never believed ♫
♫ that we would be so intimate someday ♫
♫ You were so cold ♫
'please deliver yourself to the arranged destination'
what destination?
♫ Follow me right now to fill in this gap ♫
♫ And travel among the sea of people ♫
♫ I accidentally encountered love ♫
♫ Waited at the intersection ♫
♫ Because you are here ♫
♫ Everything is worth looking forward to ♫
♫ Waited at the intersection ♫
♫ What a beautiful encounter ♫
♫ What I accidentally found was love ♫
♫ Waited at the intersection ♫
♫ What a beautiful encounter ♫
♫ What I accidentally found was love ♫
Ling Yue!
Gu Anxin.
Where did you run off to?
I was so worried.
I have something I want to tell you.
What is it?
I want to tell you that I'm not someone who likes unforeseen circumstances.
So I always take every precaution when doing anything.
Just like you said, I'm like an armadillo.
All of a sudden,
the first person in my life who made me feel
so unprepared,
is you.
When we were little, we brushed past each other because of an unforeseen circumstance.
Go!
Little Bean, I will come back to find you.
When we grew up, we met again because of an unforeseen circumstance.
Wake up!
But I really treasure these unforeseen circumstances.
I think that perhaps all of my preparations
were so that I could meet you again.
After I got together with you,
I did some things that I've never done before.
In the future, can you research some more food?
Then in the future, I'll cook for you everyday.
Your so-called dignity
neglected all of my efforts.
Everything I did was for your sake. Do you have to get so mad at me?
I shouldn't have interfered with your affairs. I failed to respect your actions.
I thought I was doing it all for your sake.
But I never asked you what you needed.
I won't interfere with your affairs in the future.
I will love you in the way you want me to.
Are you willing to give me some more time to learn how?
No matter what difficulties I face,
as long as it's to protect you, I am filled with courage.
If it's okay, I'm willing to use all of my life
to protect you.
Are you okay? Don't worry.
Ling Yue, be careful!
You, the you who says "No problem!" in any circumstance, gave me this courage.
Because as long as I have you by my side, I feel at ease.
Then again, after a while, this angry chicken look of yours
seems pretty cute.
Shut up.
So,
Miss Gu Anxin,
will you marry me?
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Memories are soaked in rain ♫
♫ Fate works bizarrely ♫
♫ The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response ♫
No problem!
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Obviously, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness, for it has always been you ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Yet the longing has never been able to stop ♫
Hello, Mr. Ling.
Hello, Mrs. Ling.
♫ Our story seems familiar ♫
♫ Fate has given so many hints ♫
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
♫ Our story seems familiar ♫
You're done kissing?
- Kiss again!
Kiss again! Kiss again!
Kiss again!
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
There are fireworks!
♫ Using all of my most beautiful adjectives ♫
♫ Is still not enough to describe your name ♫
♫ Our story is exclusively ours ♫
♫ Our palms hold onto the key to the future ♫
♫ Using love to slowly open up a lifetime ♫
Xiao Ji, let Mom see!
Go down a little.
Try this side.
That's right.
This is greater than or equal to.
This one is here, got it?
My goodness, you're too good at drawing!
Who taught you this? Was it Dad?
Yes.
Xiao Ji, Xiao Li?
Why do you want to choose such basic names?
How are they basic?
When Xiao Ji and Xiao Li grow up, they will become Da Ji, Da Li.
["Da" means big, "Da Ji, Da Li" is an idiom that means good luck and prosperity]
It has such a good meaning.
I am already starting to worry about our kids.
What if their intelligence takes after you?
They have to take after me, thank you very much.
- They'll take after you.
- They'll take after me.
[I Accidentally Picked Up Love]
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Memories are soaked in rain ♫
♫ Fate works bizarrely ♫
♫ The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly beats abnormally ♫
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Obviously, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness, for it has always been you ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Yet the longing has never been able to stop ♫
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Using all of my most beautiful adjectives ♫
♫ Is still not enough to describe your name ♫
♫ Our story is exclusively ours ♫
♫ Our palms hold onto the key to the future ♫
♫ Using love to slowly open up a lifetime ♫