♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
=The Eternal Love S3=
=Episode 04=
What's bothering you, Brother?
Since when did you and the princess...
become this close?
You were absent, Brother,
so you might have misunderstood it.
What the princess said yesterday
wasn't utter nonsense.
She said that men shouldn't rely on women.
They should live their own life.
Careless talk leads to trouble, Eighth Brother.
But don't you think that
this princess is quite different
from the one you used to know?
Tan Er almost drowned,
and shortly after, she survived an assassination.
After these back-to-back traumas,
it's only normal that her personality changed.
Please stop second-guessing.
Still,
be wary of the princess, Brother.
I knew Tan Er since I was a child.
Don't say what you said again.
Don't get blinded by love, Brother.
Official Su has arrived.
As per Her Majesty's request,
the eighth young master of the Mo family,
Mo Lian Cheng is to enter the palace.
Please, Eighth Young Master.
Behave yourself. Do not bring shame
to the Mo family.
What's wrong with Mo Lian Cheng?
He dares to disrespect me?
Once you remember everything,
I'll make you suffer!
I'm different now.
I'm a princess.
You have to obey me.
Your Highness.
The eldest princess has sent an invitation,
asking you to visit her.
(Invitation)
Why does she want to see me?
Ill-intentioned.
I'm not going.
Not going.
Noted. I shall take my leave now.
Wait!
Jing Xin.
Do you have something to say to me?
Your Highness, I have thought hard about it,
but I can't understand one thing.
Are you like this because
you were too traumatized by the
drowning incident?
I am more than willing to travel far
to find you a medicine, Your Highness.
Jing Xin.
I know you've been
loyal to me.
I also know that
you must be thinking I've changed a lot.
Sometimes, I'll even start rambling.
It's just that at this moment,
I can't find a good explanation.
Just believe that
whether if it's in the past, the present,
or the future,
regardless of the timeline,
regardless of which Dongyue,
you are forever my best sister.
If someone ever bullies you,
I'll be first to defend you.
I'm glad you're safe.
I might not know the words you used,
but I'll try to understand the context.
You're a princess after all.
You can't call your guard your sister.
Not to mention I said those harsh words earlier.
And you still...
It's okay, Jing Xin.
I know you care about me.
By the way, when we're alone,
don't call me Princess.
It sounds weird.
Just call me Tan
like you used to.
Tan?
Like I used to?
Your previous life.
I'm forever your Tan.
Come on, say it out loud.
We're sisters, forever and ever?
Tan.
No! No! No!
I should just call you Your Highness.
I really...
Stop it.
Listen to me. No ifs or buts.
Don't get mad at me anymore, okay?
Yes.
Father.
The Bachelor School will start in three days.
All of you are to study there.
You represent the Mo family,
so watch your demeanor when school starts.
Behave properly.
Yes.
Both of you can leave now.
I have something to tell Lian Cheng.
Let's go.
How are things going on the palace?
Her Majesty was trying to see
if I harbor ill will.
Perhaps she never trusted me.
It's not worth continuing further.
I see.
It seems like we can't proceed according to plan.
Be patient, Father.
It can be a blessing in disguise too.
You want to use the princess?
It's a possible route.
What she said yesterday leaves an opening for us.
You can rest assured, Father.
It is also my wish to free
the citizens from suffering.
Since it's my wish, I shall do my best.
Good.
(Jingyi Pavilion)
As per the royal decree,
the Bachelor School will start today.
You are expected to behave yourself
and be a good husband.
In your future marital life,
you are to bring forth offspring and to
work hard without complaining.
Please open the first page now, everyone.
Read every word carefully.
(What else should I do)
(to make Qu Tan Er ask for my hand?)
What are you writing, Eighth Young Master?
I am merely taking note of
what you said, Official Su.
Just a few scribbles. Nothing of concern.
So you're saying that you were
listening to the lecture
with that preoccupied expression of yours?
As per the royal decree,
the Bachelor School will start today.
You are expected to behave yourself
and be a good husband.
In your future marital life, you are to bring forth
offspring and to work hard without complaining.
If I remember it correctly,
Official Su shall continue your lecture.
We're all eager to learn here.
Good.
Read carefully.
(Jingyi Pavilion)
(Moral Codes for Men)
Please study every word carefully.
I will come back and check after two hours.
Fourteenth, if you have trouble
understanding the lecture,
feel free to ask me.
I...
I knew you weren't paying attention.
Let's start with Humility.
The third day after the birth of a boy,
you should place the baby below the bed,
give him a potsherd with which to play,
announce his birth to his ancestors
by an offering.
To lay the baby below the bed
shows that you are lowly and weak,
which means you should be...
Intimate contact with another bachelor.
Sent an expensive gift to a bachelor.
Eighth Brother, who's this bachelor?
Eighth Brother, what are you planning?
They sound...
Do not overthink this, Brother.
Princess is here!
Mo Lian Cheng.
Come out.
Eighth Brother...
(Fine then.)
(Now that you've done it in the public,)
(you'll have to marry me.)
What can I help you, Your Highness?
I know you must be tired from studying
so I came to cheer you up.
That's all?
Yes.
Well...
I came here to see you after class in person.
I even brought you some snacks.
Do you feel extra honored now?
Stay there!
I know the school starts today,
so I waited for the entire afternoon.
Is this your textbook?
Let me see what men
learn in this matriarchal Dongyue.
(Intimate contact with another bachelor.
Sent an expensive gift to a bachelor.)
(Peeking a bachelor.)
Aren't these what I did to you?
Your Highness kept disrespecting
the boundaries.
And now, my reputation is tarnished.
I'd like to know how Your Highness
will make it up for me?
So what I did to you
really bothers you then?
You want me to make it up for you.
So you want me to marry you?
What do you think, Your Highness?
Is this the real you, Cheng Cheng?
Who else do you think I am, Your Highness?
(Your Highness again? Seems like
he's not Cheng Cheng.)
(The eighth young master asked me to marry him.)
(If the real Cheng Cheng knows...)
Why? Are you reluctant to do so?
(Whatever. I just have to get this man first.)
Of course, I do.
I'm very much
willing to so.
Read the next page.
(Three Orders and Three Rules)
Three Orders and Three Rules again?
How repetitive!
First order, no spilling secrets.
Second order, non-interference.
Third order, be honest.
Three Rules.
For daily interaction,
stay further than a one-arm distance.
For the bedroom,
a folding screen will be between us.
Lastly, no lovey-dovey
interaction.
Can you do them, Your Highness?
All see and no touch then?
Well...
No problem.
Shocked? Surprised?
As long as you marry me,
I'll agree to anything.
Do you really like me that much?
Of course!
A strong man is afraid of an obsessive woman.
What comes around goes around.
I'm your karma.
In that case,
I shall visit you at night
to discuss our marriage at length.
Don't need to worry about dowry.
Just wait for the bridal carriage
like you're supposed to.
Jing Xin, does this look good on me?
Should I wear something lighter?
You look good in anything, Tan.
Really?
You don't look feminine enough.
What about...
Come.
I, the makeup guru, shall dress you up!
No thanks!
Come here!
Let's... not use this.
I'm going to give you
the most stylish hairstyle of the year.
Come on! Stay still.
Now you look cute.
Really?
Can't you knock, Cheng Cheng?
Make some noise at least.
Are you trying to scare me to death?
I'm meeting you at late night, Your Highness.
I cannot risk letting anyone know.
I'll take my leave.
Don't worry.
From now onwards,
as long as I'm here, no one can harm you.
After school, Her Majesty asked for my presence.
She was curious about the changes
in your personality
after the drowning incident.
Why are you staring at me?
What's so bad about the changes?
Isn't now much better?
Don't change the subject.
I think Her Majesty simply wished to see you.
You're a playboy!
It's fine that you attract other women,
but you attract an empress this time.
How am I supposed to win?
Such trouble!
Well, we can sever ties.
No!
That's not what I meant.
I meant to say that
you're as fine as wine
and...
as dashing as the Prince Charming.
I do have literary talent.
(Look at how quick my reflexes are.)
(Every man)
(should learn from me.)
Since the empress is suspicious of you,
if you propose to marry me now,
it won't be easy.
I am the second princess of Dongyue.
I am allowed to marry whoever I want.
If you want me, then we need to work together.
Sure.
Mo Lian Cheng, you wish to file a complaint
against the second princess?
Yes.
When Her Highness was recuperating
in the Mo Residence,
she molested me and...
Dirtied my body and
reputation.
I demand a fair judgment, Your Majesty.
This is nothing but a seduction attempt from
Mo Lian Cheng since he wasn't chosen
during the harem selection.
It was just a ruse from him.
He wanted to blame everything on me,
so I have to marry him.
He is after the prince consort position.
You...
But several days ago,
you asked me to meet you outside of the school.
Everyone saw that.
What excuses can you make this time?
I...
(Oh, no! I forgot my line.)
Since the princess is not willing to admit it,
Your Majesty, I implore you to exact swift justice.
(Even though we skipped several parts)
(that we discussed earlier,)
(but I still remember this part.)
(I can follow up.)
You just want me to take responsibility, don't you?
I know I've fallen for your trick.
Arrange a marriage then, Your Majesty.
We wouldn't want him to spout nonsense
and risk having Your Majesty's reputation
be tarnished.
Whether Mo Lian Cheng has planned
all these or not,
have you really done something intimate to him?
(We didn't anticipate this question at all.)
(I have no idea what she's trying to achieve.)
(How should I answer?)
It seems like
the princess still refuses to
bear the consequences.
I was first accused of seducing Your Majesty,
and now, my chastity was called into question
by the princess.
I see no place for me in this world,
perhaps...
Perhaps I should just commit suicide.
Stop!
Like I said, I'll marry you.
Look at this mess you've caused.
You have indeed dirtied him,
but marriage is no trivial matter.
I shall issue a decree
to announce that the second princess
is free to choose her own spouse.
(That's a trap!)
(If I pick Mo Lian Cheng,)
(it means I really like him.)
(So this show we put up will be in vain.)
(What a pro! A cunning pro.)
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Dismiss.
- I'll take my leave.
Let's see who she'll pick.
Everyone knows that the second princess
and Chen Er love each other.
If she didn't pick you,
wouldn't your plan be in vain?
You don't need to worry, Father.
The eldest brother seems to be upset
when learning this news.
Indeed. He is ready to get married,
but the second princess never requested
Her Majesty to arrange a marriage.
Instead, she is now asked to select her own spouse.
Of course, Chen Er will be upset.
What the second princess said might hold true,
but her disrespectful disposition will only do
more harm than good to my eldest brother.
But I know he is
loving the second princess
with his soul and heart.
They have feelings for each other since young.
If the second princess did not choose Chen Er,
I'm afraid he'd spend
the rest of his life as a monk.
Don't worry, Father.
I will not make things difficult for him.
Nice move.
Your Go skills have improved.
But Tan,
are you really going to pick the eighth
young master as your husband?
I believe that the eldest brother
is the best candidate.
You won't understand this, Jing Xin.
Love is a merciless one-way street.
On this street,
I see only Mo Lian Cheng.
Mo Yan Chen is a sweet guy,
but he's not what I want.
Let's go.
Cheng Cheng!
All right. One-arm distance.
Everyone else, please wait outside.
I want to have a private moment with him.
Your Highness seems to have noticed that
the decree of Her Majesty hides
an ulterior motive.
So what?
I will still pick you.
What is she going to do? back out?
An empress will never renege on her promise.
However, more troubles might come in the future.
So you want to call everything off?
Are you regretting your decision now,
Mo Lian Cheng?
I have a strategy
to solve our current predicament.
Would you like to hear it, Your Highness?
Speak.
As long as you can be my husband,
if you ask for the stars, I'll never give you the moon.
Then marry my eldest brother too.
What?
Are you crazy or did I mishear?
This sounds ridiculous!
You did not mishear me.
If you wish to marry me,
you'd need to marry my eldest brother too.
He's so going to regret this when he
got his memory back.
He might even kill himself.
I refuse. You will regret this.
I am a man of his word.
(As expected from a nutjob.)
(I know his craziness is incurable,)
(but I still need to do something.)
(Or else, when he turns into the real Cheng Cheng,)
(he'll not need to wait for lightning to strike him.)
(He can just kill himself.)
Nothing in this world
can escape from this axiom:
What a tsundere says will always backfire.
When you install a flagpole,
it will eventually fall.
Today, you give me your word.
Tomorrow, you'll wish to take them back.
If Your Highness is reluctant to do so,
then let's nullify our previous agreement.
We are strangers now.
I did this for you, okay?
Can't you see it?
And your final decision is...?
I'll count to three.
One, two,
three.
Fine.
Karma will come back and bite you.
Don't blame me when the time comes.
Deal!
Such decisiveness, Your Highness.
I believe we'll form a great team.
Mo Yan Chen is handsome.
If I ever fall for him,
don't you regret it.
Whoever regrets first is a dummy!
Promised.
Whoever regrets first
is a... dummy.
(Congji Hall)
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Yan Chen.
You're the most considerate one
in the Mo family.
I'd like to arrange for you to be married
to the second princess.
What do you think?
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I shall devote my life to the second princess
and shoulder her burden.
I've also decided that
Lian Cheng will be wed to her too.
Both of you can look after each other
and also the household.
(I suppose this is)
(to cease Lian Cheng's obsession
towards Her Majesty.)
(I'm fine with it,)
(but Tan Er took the short end of the stick.)
As you wish, Your Majesty.
(I'm surrounded by two men.)
(Why does it feel like)
(I have peaked?)
(Seems like it's all thanks to Mo Lian Cheng.)
(Might as well enjoy it.)
Both the prince and the eighth lord
bear the same intention,\.
What do you think?
(What's happening?)
Why aren't you taking my decree, Mo Lian Cheng?
(Tan Er! How dare you marry Mo Yan Chen!)
Marriage is no trivial matter.
Only if you follow your heart that
everything will end well.
I implore Your Majesty and Your Highness
to think twice.
(Mo Lian Cheng!)
(Why are you playing hard-to-get
all of a sudden?)
Once issued, the royal decree cannot be revoked.
(Oh, no! He's still in love with the empress.)
(If this carries on, it will end badly.)
I shall work with my eighth brother
to serve the princess,
to be the princess's right-hand men.
Now that this is settled.
Who should be the first husband?
(The empress is still trying to gauge
our reaction until now.)
(Now that we're here, might as well
go with her wishes.)
My brother is the eldest son.
He should be the first husband.
Tan Er.
What do you think?
(Mo Lian Cheng as my second husband?)
(Sounds exciting.)
As you wish, Your Majesty.
(Seems like Tan Er loves me after all.)
In this case,
proceed as you wish.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I can't believe
I get to enjoy two husbands one day.
Never see this coming.
Indeed.
A decade-long dream has finally come true.
Thank heaven!
Tan Er, I...
Tan Er?
Eighth Brother?
What?
You're my second husband and now
you can't wait to exert dominance?
In the great hall,
I said only if you followed your heart that
everything would end well.
Did you not get what I said?
You churn out different drama every day.
Who knows what's in your mind?
Do you think I'd joke with my heart?
I once said that whoever we are,
regardless of the time and the distance,
I will find you, love you,
and marry you a thousand times.
Never separate in an eternity.
Cheng Cheng!
♪Yet I still bet with this life♪
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪The flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪the love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter what
hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have to
travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter what
hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have to
travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪