Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ No longer panicking on the night of the blackout ♫
♫ You're by my side, illuminating a beam of light for me ♫
♫ Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet ♫
♫ Your breath ♫
♫ brushes up against my cheek ♫
♫ With you warming up the stage,
happiness never comes to a close ♫
♫ Boring jokes add some sweetness to the dinner ♫
♫ Daily life is even more like a comic than comics themselves ♫
♫ Happiness and sadness ♫
♫ Make up the moments of life ♫
♫ Rainy days become very special because of you ♫
♫ Picked up a pitiful youngster off the street ♫
♫ No matter when and where, you always appear ♫
♫ Holding me tightly and spinning in circles ♫
♫ Rainy days make me so nostalgic because of you ♫
♫ Becoming some part of the memories ♫
♫ Walking down a street with lights lighting up
one after another ♫
♫ Warming up the whole world ♫
[Please Feel At Ease Mr. Ling]
[Episode 11]
I thought about it a lot these past few days.
I shouldn't have interfered with your issues. I forgot to think about how you felt
These are all actions of not respecting you.
I thought that doing these was for your own good, but I never asked what you needed.
Are you willing to give me more time to learn?
I'll try my best to understand you in the future.
We have to communicate when anything happens
and be honest with each other, okay?
Okay.
You said that you wouldn't do anything.
If I don't hug my entire world, then how can I sleep?
Good morning.
If your clothes are in the blanket and your not wearing it, do you need me to help you?
No need, I can do it myself.
You really don't need me to.
Really.
You really don't?
See, it's all your fault.
Then I apologize.
Your trying to murder your husband?
I will blow it for you.
Perfect timing. Just as I was about to go find you, you came.
That man is looking for you.
Where is Anxin?
She is changing her clothes.
Do you not understand?
I have to tell you one last time.
If you do anything to Anxin, I will make you suffer.
I am also warning you, know your position.
Anxin is my women, I will be responsible for her.
Your women? Anxin is my sister.
That's not up to you.
Brother?
Why are you here?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Why do you look this like?
Yesterday, I kept calling you all night. You scared me to death.
Sorry! My phone didn't have any service.
Did he do anything to you?
He didn't do anything.
Let's go home.
I can walk myself.
-Ai Li.
-Give that to me.
Thank you.
President Ling.
Brother.
Gu Ansheng, do you not have a car?
My car broke, you won't mind right?
Anxin, let's go.
I'm leaving.
Your just going to leave like that?
Goodbye. I'm leaving now. Get some rest.
What's wrong?
You're my person. Don't get too close to other men.
When did I become your person.
Last night-
Anxin.
You two? Last night?
Even though I don't like you.
But you are an important person to Anxin.
Don't worry, I will treat her well.
I don't agree.
President Ling, do you think Gu Ansheng will continue to block you and Miss Anxin?
I trust Anxin.
Brother, it's been dry recently. You should drink more water.
What's going on?
Yesterday, you didn't really... with him...
Brother, do you really want to talk about these 18+ things?
- It's so awk—
- Anxin.
Sorry.
Did he take advantage of you?
It's not what you think.
So it was of your own free will?
Brother, in truth,
in truth you should try to get to know Ling Yue.
I'm telling you, I can't.
Why not? Don't be so biased against him.
Just try to get to know him. Besides,
it's not like it's either him or you.
If I tell you that it is either him or me,
who would you choose?
- No, Brother—
- It's fine.
I'm sure you didn't rest well yesterday. Go and rest a little more.
I'll leave now.
Hi.
Come, come.
- Sit.
- There's this too.
Oh, thank you.
- Xixi, look. Pour it to here, got it?
- Oh, okay.
Look at this line.
It's easy to get drunk if you drink alone. If you get drunk, who will send you home?
Anxin?
You're so good-looking, how could I feel at ease?
(Anxin literally means "feel at ease")
Anxin.
I'm sorry, I thought you were someone else.
These things, you have to learn yourself, okay?
I remember now.
Excuse me, can I have a glass of water?
Hello?
What's wrong?
Right now?
Okay, okay. Then I'll come over now.
Thank you! Let's go.
You told me to come just so I could pay for you?
M-my bank card was locked a couple days ago.
I didn't have any money in my WeChat either, so I could only...
If you'd told me earlier, I could've just transferred some money to you over WeChat.
How come you're both good-looking and smart?
It was such a simple problem, how come I didn't think of that?
God is really too unfair to me.
Is there anything else you need?
Why do you smell so heavily of alcohol?
My friend took me out for drinks.
I hadn't seen him in a long time, so I drank a little too much.
And you still came as soon as I called? You're too kind.
After you sent me home last time, I didn't even have a chance to thank you.
Now I've bothered you again. I'm really sorry.
How about this, as repayment,
I'll take you to see a movie.
Don't you not have money?
I don't have money.
But I have a movie card.
The kind where if I report my name, I can see the movie.
You're Anxin's friend, so you're my friend.
- You don't have to bother about this.
- That won't do.
I, Xu Youyou, am very particular about fairness.
You buy me snacks, I pay for your movie. That way, it's fair.
I love this movie!
Thank you.
Oh right, what kind of movie does your brother like?
My brother likes
The Notebook.
These two have been separated for so long, but the male lead is still looking for the female lead.
Can't this female lead take a little more initiative?
This is too painful.
Perhaps when waiting becomes a habit,
it's not so painful anymore.
How do you know?
Perhaps I'm waiting for someone too.
What do I do? Is he giving me a hint?
What do I do? How should I respond?
"Me too." No, that's too direct.
"I can."
That doesn't work either.
Do you like someone?
For a long time.
What is this? Didn't we just meet?
Or is it that even though we've just met, it's like we've known each other for a long time?
My God! It's so romantic!
Then why don't you tell her?
I thought it would be enough for me to always watch over her quietly.
I never thought one day someone would take her away.
What do you mean? Of course you have to tell her.
God has already put true love right in front of you.
If you don't say anything, and I don't say anything, when will sweet love
come to us?
You're right.
I'm ready!
I'll think carefully about it.
Thanks, Youyou.
Of course.
This is a new beginning.
You've got this, Gu Anxin.
President Ling, Miss Anxin has already begun to send out her resume.
The first round usually looks at educational background.
I'm afraid her job applications won't go so smoothly.
That's true. Do you need me to make arrangements?
No need. I promised Anxin to respect her choice.
- Hello?
- Have you eatetn?
Yes. I just ate
a really big hamburger. I'm so full right now.
Then... is the job search going smoothly?
Yes, of course it's going smoothly.
You don't need to worry about me.
Be at ease.
I have to go to an interview. Bye!
Bye. Good luck.
[Careful Hot]
♫ Walking down dark streets together ♫
♫ Watching streetlights flick on and off ♫
♫ The future can be seen with a turn of the head ♫
♫ We've yet to part but longing has begun ♫
♫ Hugging you is like holding the entire world ♫
♫ So beautiful that I'm afraid of a time limit ♫
♫ Promises are too shallow, not worth a thousandth of you ♫
♫ Countless forevers wouldn't be enough ♫
♫ Let me love you, let me use my true heart ♫
♫ and learn to warm  ♫
Why does he have a pot on his head?
But it's still cute! Thank you.
You've worked hard. Good luck.
Good night~
The project everyone sees here comes from the Cai Niao Inn.
According to Cai Niao Inn's logo designer,
his inspiration actually came from himself.
Because sometimes he gets off work late, and once there are many deposits,
there is no place to save and record them.
-Later, once we-
-You always have to go so far to pick up deliveries?
Because I get off work too late, so I can only leave the deliveries with the property manager.
But I can only leave it for a little while, and can't leave it for too long.
If picking up deliveries were like the bank
with unscheduled pickups, wouldn't that be great?
So they created this idea of an "inn".
In every neighborhood, they would-
President Ling, this company was just established.
It primarily focuses on neighborhood deliveries.
Although it looks small, but it's progression is rapid.
A company like this must have someone powerful behind it.
Since they've come to the venture capital conference,
-then they are looking for another path.
-Understood.
Alright. Next, let us welcome Ms.Gu Xin'er!
Can we speak alone?
Brother Yue, thank you so much.
Who knew you would support our company so much?
It's collaboration. This is the result of your abilities.
I'm really curious. What part of Cai Niao Inn attracted you?
After all, there are actually many small startups like ours on the market.
Although the Ling Group is financially capable,
however according to my knowledge, you aren't someone who wastes money randomly.
I've obviously taken a liking to the project's value and potential.
Your Cai Niao Inn took care of worker's inconvenience in delivery pick ups.
You've matched the life style of young people, and met the market's needs.
Most importantly, you've utilized the newest technology.
You've gathered middle class workers, alongside laundromats, group shopping,
and recycling agencies.
The neighborhood service inn is the center of everyday life.
This matches with New Way's business direction quite well.
So collaboration is only expected.
Brother Yue really understands me, so...
glad to be working with you?
Glad to work with you.
Oh, right. You have something on your hair.
Let me help you.
Alright.
Thank you.
There's no need to be so polite between you and I.
It's best to separate work and life.
But work and life
will definitely have connections.
I look forward to seeing you next time.
Don't be in a hurry. You'll find a job suitable for you sooner or later.
It's too hard, brother.
But thank you for finding time today to come job search with me.
Why so polite with me?
[New Way President Ling and Daughter of Gu family Caught on Camera in a Car]
The user you are calling is unavailable. Please call back in a moment.
Let's go to the venture capital conference right now. They should still be there.
There's no need to go, brother.
It's nothing. I believe in him.
Anxin, I will help you.
Eat fish!
-He's allergic to corainder.
-They were the closest in high school.
I've taken out the coriander for you.
Brother,
Xin'er and Ling Yue knew each other before?
So they knew each other before, right?
They...
were together before.
[New Way President Ling and Daughter of Gu family Caught on Camera in a Car]
Ling Yue, he...didn't tell me.
Brother! Anxin!
You've also come to attend the venture capital conference?
Xin'er.
What's going on?
Those boring media people have started writing stories again.
Don't think too much about it.
-Where's Ling Yue?
-He just left a little while ago.
You guys didn't meet him on the way?
Just left?
-You two stayed in the car for that long?
-It wasn't that long.
We just caught up with each other.
Xin'er, you clearly know Ling Yue and Anxin are together right now.
Why aren't you clearing your own suspicion?
Anxin, don't take it personally.
Brother Yue only has you.
Before he put in a lot of effort to give you a gift.
He puts in a lot of effort to a girl he likes.
Your perfume is nice.
It's Layered Fragrance.
Do you like it too? I can't believe our interest is very similiar.
But girls like a unique perfume.
Do you want me to recommend you something?
Ling Yue gave it to you?
Is that important?
It is very important, I am his girlfriend.
Today is a coincidence.
Do you know, a lot of coincidences
are destined to happen.
Anxin. Let's go.
Goodbye, Brother.
Hello?
Boss, I arranged everything. Once the news comes out, I think we can use it to our advantage.
Okay. I understand.
Brother, where are we going?
Didn't you always want to go to see the ocean? I'm going to take you right now.
Do you want to take a short nap? I'll wake you up later.
The user you dialed is temporarily unavailable
Please call again later.
President Ling, we already deleted the photo. We will also gradually delete any related articles.
But a lot of partners has asked, are you and the Gu family
planning on having a marriage?
This news has greater positive impact compared to a negative impact for the company.
I advise that we can't confirm the external statements but we can't not deny too.
Since it is fake news, of course, we have to refute it.
President Ling, but Miss Gu's image has always been good.
She is also a daughter of the Gu family, and we also have a partnership with her family.
We can use this chance to build more publicity.
Is this your idea or Cai Niao Station's idea?
It's both of our ideas.
When did New Way needs media gossips to build momentum?
In 10 minutes, I don't want to see any more news related to this.
Okay, I will take care of it right now.
Also, immediately deny the rumors.
There can't be anything shady.
Yes.
After you are done, you can also hand in your resignation.
Yes...
President Ling, I know where Miss Anxin is at.
Enjoy the nice sunshine. Let's go out to the sea together.
Cai Niao Station
Hi President Gu.
President Gu.
What are you thinking about?
The chances of you appearing have been pretty high.
I can't have a spot in your heart so I can only have a spot in your memory.
I just came by to ask,
last night when you promised me to go to the art gallery, does that still count?
If you are willing to wait for me to finish these documents, then-
Of course I am!
But... do you need me to take care of the reporters?
You can ignore the rumors, it's fine.
Rumors?
Then that means my chance is still here.
You brat. What are you thinking?
Xin'er, I am at the age of getting married.
[Media Advisory by New Way clarifying that President Ling and Gu Xin'er are just business partners]
Sorry, I don't want to go today.
You don't want to go?
That's fine. We can go next time.
When you were younger, you always said you wanted to see the ocean.
I didn't have time to spend with you.
Since you were young, you were excelling in morals and studies.
You would always go to violin lessons once you were on break.
They wouldn't bring me along so I would stay at home alone and wait for you.
Is it okay if I make it up to you now?
It's okay, Brother.
You don't need to say these things to me.
From now on, I won't ever let you get hurt again.
Actually it's okay Brother.
When I calm down
I will go find him to talk to him.
Let's not talk about others today.
It's just us two, with a calm quiet day.
Okay!
Anxin!
Why are you here?
Aren't you scared of the water? Go back, don't come here.
I have to explain it to you.
What do you want to explain?
Are you going to explain how you're wavering non-stop between my younger sisters?
-Brother!
-Let's go.
Don't-
Ling Yue!
-President Ling!
-Ling Yue!
You're awake?
Slow down.
How do you feel?
I'm fine. Why am I at the hospital?
Ai Li and my brother brought you here.
Why do you have to act so strong?
You scared me to death.
Are you worried about me?
I'm not.
Anxin, Gu Xin'er, and I aren't like what the news has reported.
Then why did you give me the same perfume as her?
The perfume was my mistake.
That day I was talking to Ai Li about it, and she was right next to us and suggested it.
I didn't think she was that scheming.
So, you two were together?
Absolutely not!
We are just classmates, nothing more.
-Also about the picture-
-I know about the picture.
It's very obvious it was just a pretext.
I am so smart, how can I not tell.
[Diagnosis of what happened, results and medications of Ling Yue]
Oh yeah,
have you always been taking that medication?
This is a medicine that lowers the heart rate. I've been eating it for many years.
Every time I think I am in danger, my heart rate will increase
I can only use this medication to control it.
So...
is it the same with your fear of water?
It's all thanks to my brother that I have a fear of water.
Why did you tell dad?
I didn't.
Why are you still lying?
♫ It's not that it doesn't really matter ♫
Silly, what's wrong?
I didn't know this.
I also said before that you were coward.
After being with you, I stopped taking those medications.
As long as I have you by my side, I will feel at calm.
♫ No need for right and wrong in a relationship,  ♫
♫  how dull ♫
♫ Gaze at me, don't avoid me ♫
♫ Give me the last of yourself ♫
♫ Let me try to touch your hard shell ♫
♫ Hold me gently ♫
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Memories are soaked in rain ♫
♫ Fate works bizarrely ♫
♫ The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly beats abnormally ♫
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Obviously, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness, for it has always been you ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Yet the longing has never been able to stop ♫
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Using all of my most beautiful adjectives ♫
♫ Is still not enough to describe your name ♫
♫ Our story is exclusively ours ♫
♫ Our palms hold onto the key to the future ♫
♫ Using love to slowly open up a lifetime ♫