♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
Do you think you could offend me
just because
you finished transforming into a dragon,?
I will let you live one last time
for the sake of your cultivation.
I hope that this time,
I won't be disappointed again.
Thank you for saving me.
I owe you my life.
It's done.
My soul power
is at level 67 now.
Your method requires soul power
but I was born with none.
What if
I can increase your soul power?
You...
What did you say?
[Episode 166]
You...
What did you say?
I can teach you a cultivation method
that might help you become a soul master.
But I can't impart it to just anyone.
Are you willing to take me as your teacher?
I am!
Good.
Teacher.
From now on,
you are a part of Tang's Clan.
Tang's Clan?
Here.
Eat it.
Ten Thousand Year Ginseng?
This is a priceless treasure!
It can help build your foundation.
This Ten Thousand Year Ginseng
we gathered from the Ice Fire Mouth Spring
is less valuable
than the Crystal Bloody Dragon Ginseng
and the Decade Millennium Grade Nine Ginseng King,
but it's perfect
for Ji Xiang.
Sit down.
Concentrate on your core
and feel the soul power
I'm transferring into your body.
Remember where it passes through.
Teacher.
Look!
Very good.
You are very talented.
But
you must practice hard
if you want to be successful.
Yes,
I will.
Thank you.
Ji Xiang.
What kind of a person is the head
of the Purple Pearl Pirates?
I'm familiar with her.
She's a good person.
She often gives money
to the poor fishing villages.
Do you know who Haider is?
What is his relationship
with the Purple Pearl Pirates?
I do.
Back then, he brought a bunch of
soul masters to join the Purple Pearl
so he was quite arrogant to other members.
Really...?
If I want to hire them
to find my friends,
can you connect us up?
Sure.
No problem.
I'll take you over tomorrow morning.
Teacher.
There are roughly 3,000 people
in the Purple Pearl Pirates,
200 of which are soul masters.
The strongest is the leader, Purple Pearl.
She is a level 68 soul emperor.
She has about 40 ships,
and is very well known in the waters nearby.
Doctor Ji Xiang.
Hello, Doctor Ji Xiang.
Let's drink tonight!
Okay.
That is where the leader lives.
Teacher,
you...!
Brother San.
Rong Rong.
San...
Thank goodness, you're alright.
We were worried about you.
Where is Wu?
Who tied you up here?
Teacher!
Ex...excuse me.
Wu!
Brother San.
Don't...don't misunderstand it!
Die!
Who is it?
A woman?
You're brave to be making trouble
in the turf of Purple Pearl Pirates!
Let go of Wu,
or you die today.
I'd like to see
how you're going to kill me.
Fourth Skill,
Viper in a Thundering Sea!
I can't let Wu get hurt.
I need to get rid of her quickly.
Fifth Skill,
Blue Silver Emperor Tyrant Spear!
Brother Dai!
How did he suddenly get over here?
Teacher, don't kill her!
If you dare to attack our leader,
we will fight you to our last breath!
She hurt my friends.
She deserves to die!
Brother San.
Leader Pearl didn't hurt us.
Fatty.
What happened to them?
We are suffering from the Chill Poison.
She tied us outside
to use the sunlight to detoxify the poison.
She was trying to save us.
Nonsense!
I wasn't.
I just wanted to torture you!
Let's keep fighting!
I'm not scared of you!
What actually happened?
After we were separated,
we floated in the ocean for long.
We later met another
decade millennium soul beast.
[Soul Land]
Xiang!
Be careful! In the water!
Rong Rong, hold onto my hand!
White Tiger Intense Light Wave!
Careful!
His attacks contain poison.
Rong Rong, careful!
Mirror Copy Sausage!
Phoenix Meteor Shower!
Flame Right Arm's Soul Bone Skill!
Bursting Phoenix!
This chill...
Brother Dai!
Ao!
Don't come over here!
We fought a hard fight to kill it
but we were all intoxicated
by its Chill Poison.
Even my Phoenix Flames couldn't melt it.
It was Leader Pearl who saved us.
Fatty.
The decade millennium soul beast
they ran into
is the same as our leader's martial soul,
Ocean Viper.
But even our leader
couldn't treat the poison directly.
We had to...
You're using the sun
to treat this petty Chill Poison?
The Ten-headed Burning Sun Serpent
is the king of all snakes
and its core is pure heat.
Its neidan
can heal the Ocean Viper's Chill Poison
in an instant.
Since it was a misunderstanding,
can you let our leader go now?
Since you rescued them,
I won't kill you
if you give me Wu.
Why should I give you Wu?
What is her relationship with you?
She is my fiance.
What?
So what if she's your fiance?
Judging from her state right now,
you definitely didn't protect her well.
How about this? Let's make a bet.
Let's fight again.
If you win,
I'll give Wu back to you.
If I win,
Wu stays with us.
I would never bet on Wu.
How about this?
I'll take a step back.
I'm letting you go now
and
I won't use my soul skills
while you can use whichever skill of yours.
If I catch you again
within half an hour,
then I win
and you have to recognize me
as your leader.
Otherwise,
you can punish me however you want.
How about that?
In your dreams.
You think you can catch me
without using soul skills?
Fine.
I'll take that bet.
Let's start.
Leader!
We will protect you!
Brothers,
good job!
If I win, I'll treat you all
to drinks and meat!
Tang's Clan 100 Hidden Weapons,
Heavenly Flower Rain!
Heavenly Flower Rain
is one of the basic hidden weapons of Tang's Clan.
It's not very strong
but is easy to control
and just enough to hit your numbing acupoint.
I don't believe I can't hide from you
on my own island.
Spiritual Cohesion Wisdom Skull.
The Blue Silver Domain
has already located you.
You won't be able to escape.
Soul sects?
Want to catch me?
You're too naive.
Really?
Let me see
where you can go now.
Here's the ocean.
He's a land soul master.
As long as I hide in the ocean,
he definitely won't find me.
It seems like
you caught something extra.
As you wish.
How did he know the route I planned?
Purple God Light!
You cheater!
I didn't say I wouldn't use soul bone skills.
Surrender.
Go to hell!
Sixth Skill, Demon Snake Ghost!
Boy, you lost.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 166 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1543 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2509]
[Total scene: 61396]
[Total CGI: 28312]
[Total plan of action scene: 12678]
[Total scene model: nearly 572]
[Total character model: nearly 1043]
[Total props model: 13400]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
♪ I'm faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods ♪
♪ Who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching ♪
♪ Any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven't told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
When someone's power
is stronger than which of all others,
he can be called God.
Everyone, go back and rest.
Who cares if she's your fiance?
It looks like you found something extra.
Just tell me what you want, boss.
Thank you for hosting us
these past few days.
It's a century millennium soul beast
that guards the island.
How do we leave Haishen Island?
Teacher, you're finally back!
I understand your good intentions.
Wait!
Brothers, I'll treat you to wine
and meat once I win!
I believe that the God of the Ocean you said
does exist.