PREVIOUSLY ON PENTHOUSE...
(Episode 13)
(Number Withheld)
(Speaker)
Shim Su Ryeon.
You look even more beautiful today.
Logan beside you
looks pretty good too.
Come to the penthouse right now.
I'll give you five minutes.
But you have to come alone.
If you don't listen,
I might just blow Hera Palace up.
I set up some bombs here and there.
I miss you, so come quickly.
Ring the emergency bell!
It's an emergency.
Evacuate all residents. Now!
Ring the emergency bell. Quickly.
Attention all residents.
There is a bomb in Hera Palace.
Please evacuate promptly.
If the elevator's full,
take the stairs.
Be careful not to get hurt.
Take the emergency stairs!
This way! Be careful!
Move! A person fell!
Easy. Let's go!
This way!
Are you okay?
- A bomb will set off!
- Run!
- Hurry!
- This way!
No! Are you okay?
Wait!
Go now!
Get in the elevator!
Seok Kyung!
Why are you standing there?
Let's go.
Mom, please don't die.
You better make it out alive!
- First floor.
- Get in!
Hurry.
- Go quickly.
- Stop.
What are you waiting for? Let's go!
Someone's still in there.
Seok Kyung!
Are you crazy?
It's dangerous! We don't have time!
Let me go. I can't let her die.
- No! Wait!
- Gosh.
Guys, no!
No! Wait!
- Are you okay?
- Thank you.
They'll be back soon.
Just a second.
Jenny!
Please wait just a second.
Hurry.
(Max capacity)
- Get in!
- No!
No!
- The emergency stairs!
- Let's run.
Thank you for coming
to my engagement party, Joo Dan Tae.
You finally showed up.
At last,
I can kill you with my own hands.
Do you really think that can happen?
Congratulations on your
engagement to Logan.
I prepared a last-minute present.
I wonder if you'll like it.
If I press this button,
it will set off the bombs in
the fountain and the penthouse.
They're much stronger than the ones
I set up in Logan's car last time.
You can look forward to them.
Boom.
You crazy jerk.
If you want to die, die alone.
Why should I be the only one to die?
What did I do wrong?
Do you know that it was your dad...
who killed my mom and sister?
Your father of Simoon Construction...
took away my house.
What's so wrong with taking back...
what was taken from me?
Lot 27 of Cheonsoo District
always belonged to my dad.
It was your parents who lived on
that land without permission.
The demolition accident was all
Baek Joon Ki's father.
My dad knew nothing.
Don't make excuses!
The noble Shim Su Ryeon...
never admits to doing anything wrong
even until the end.
Don't move.
How dare you defile my Hera Palace?
Only I can have this place.
Only I can destroy it.
If I can't have it, no one can.
You understand?
Dying alone felt lonely.
It comforts me to know that
it will be with you.
Nice dress.
That's the perfect outfit
for you to wear to the fiery pit.
Drop the remote.
You think you can shoot me?
I will press the button
the moment you pull the trigger.
Then Hera Palace will disappear
in the blink of an eye.
Come on. Shoot me!
I said, drop the remote!
And I said you'll die
if you keep challenging me.
Just like your ex-husband.
Just like Min Seol A.
Just like Oh Yoon Hee!
Shoot me!
This is for...
all the innocent lives
you took away!
You're crazy!
How dare you shoot at me,
the mighty Joo Dan Tae?
Are you still obsessed
with that name?
This is you paying...
for all the crimes you've committed.
Drop the remote!
Shim Su Ryeon,
let's go together...
to the fiery pit.
Stop it!
Stop it, Joo Dan Tae!
Seok Kyung, Seok Hoon.
I love you so much.
Su Ryeon!
Are you okay?
Why did you come here?
We have to get out of here. Hurry.
A little more.
I killed Dan Tae.
You did nothing wrong.
It's all good now. It's over.
What about the others?
We evacuated everyone.
They're all safe.
Are you okay?
I'll let you live like
Shim Su Ryeon.
I'll make so much money
that you can get buried under it.
We can buy a house in Gangnam
and build a building.
I'll make everyone in the world
kneel at my feet.
And we'll have kids?
Of course.
A son and a daughter.
Our kids will live in
the most expensive...
and the highest home in the country.
The closest to paradise.
Wow. I'm so happy just imagining it.
Hera Palace, the most expensive
apartment in Korea...
and the symbol of Seoul
has collapsed.
Hera Palace, which had led
the domestic real estate market...
with its property value
that skyrocketed year after year,
was completed demolished yesterday...
after bombs set by
Chairman Joo Dan Tae,
who personally designed Hera Palace,
exploded.
The 100-story apartment building
with a shelter...
that could house 200 people
during a nuclear war...
and boasted infrastructure
that could withstand earthquakes...
was destroyed
by a suicide bomber.
Chairman Joo Dan Tae obtained
illegal homemade bombs...
through Cho,
who used to be his secretary.
Cho's body was found this morning.
The cause of death
has not been determined.
More than 90 percent
of the residents...
had already moved out of
Hera Palace.
And thanks to the quick response
of the residents,
there was not a single casualty.
However, since the residents were
mostly from the upper class,
the damage is expected
to be astronomical.
People who are angry
with Joo Dan Tae's many deeds...
that threatened
innocent people's lives...
gathered in front of
the Blue House...
to oppose Joo Dan Tae's funeral.
Joo Dan Tae...
threatened me and said...
he had hidden bombs
all over Hera Palace.
He said they were much stronger
than the ones in Logan's car.
He confessed all of that to me.
In other words,
it was Joo Dan Tae...
who tried to kill Logan.
These are photos from the scene.
He wore an old man's disguise,
but it's definitely Dan Tae.
Since the suspect is deceased,
we cannot investigate.
Also, we found a laptop
in Mr. Cho's mother's home.
We've obtained a lot of evidence
of the many crimes...
Joo Dan Tae had committed.
It's tragic that all of this
finally surfaced...
only after his death.
Dan Tae and I were divorced,
but he's the father of my children.
Since this happened
during my engagement ceremony,
I feel partly responsible.
(Hera Palace Compensation
Press Conference)
We plan to compensate
the residents of Hera Palace...
for the damages suffered
due to Joo Dan Tae's bombing...
from our personal funds.
Thus, I will donate
ten billion dollars...
to establish a foundation
for the victims.
Moreover, Logan Lee Corporation
will acquire Cheong A Group,
which went bankrupt
due to its owner's improper acts...
to minimize the loss suffered
by shareholders and employees.
I will also donate
my personal funds...
and do my best to help the victims...
and with the disaster relief efforts.
To the people who suffered...
psychologically and financially
in this accident,
I sincerely apologize.
(Shim Su Ryeon, Logan Lee)
(Hera Palace Compensation
Press Conference)
Korean-American
businessman Logan Lee...
who announced the takeover of
bankrupt Cheong A Group...
stated he'll donate
ten billion dollars...
to compensate Hera Palace residents.
- Oh Ha Young has the story.
- Ten billion dollars?
- CEO Logan Lee said...
- That's where the ten billion goes?
The residents will be compensated.
He's gone at last.
Joo Dan Tae.
The death suit you very well.
I brought the medicine
from the hospital.
Good.
Shim Su Ryeon will be watching
my every move.
I shouldn't do anything
to make her suspicious.
Whenever my appointment's set,
get my medicine from the hospital.
I'll do that.
Also, congratulations.
With Joo Dan Tae's death,
you no longer have to
repay his debt.
You'll be allowed to travel too.
Submit a renunciation
of inheritance today.
Is this how the heavens
are helping me?
- Eun Byeol hasn't noticed, right?
- Not at all.
Keep your wits about you
and don't mess up around her.
She's a sensitive kid.
If she realizes
I didn't take the medicine,
she might feel betrayed
and who knows what she'll do then?
Mom.
I'll erase all your bad memories...
so you can always be happy.
I've been saving all my pills...
just for you.
My goodness.
You did a beautiful job.
- Do you like it?
- Of course, I love it.
I can't believe this.
Mom, shall we drink?
Sounds good.
Who's that?
I'll go and see.
Mom, it's our photo.
Don't we look lovely?
Eun Byeol, how come
you're so pretty?
Her testimony
is my only way out now.
If Su Ryeon releases the evidence
that I killed Yoon Hee,
Eun Byeol has to say I have
drug-induced early onset dementia.
Is that possible?
The police...
will make you take tests
when you're under their supervision.
Your current diagnosis
won't be enough.
That's why I need Eun Byeol.
I'm unlike
any other dementia patient.
My dementia is
a side effect of a medicine.
No doctor can be sure
of my condition.
More than the opinion
of ten psychiatrists,
Eun Byeol's statement
will have more weight.
What will you do now?
First, I need
to send Eun Byeol abroad.
I can join her
once my travel ban is lifted.
Once I can prove
I'm too mentally unstable...
and my mind won't allow
a normal life,
not even the law can tie me down.
Sir. Are you awake?
Do you hear my voice?
If you can hear me, nod your head.
Good.
Sir. Can you say your name?
Ha...
Yoon Chul.
It seems like he recovered
his consciousness.
I thought he'd never wake up.
It looks like his determination
created a miracle.
Thank you. You did a great job.
- Logan.
- Yes.
It's me, Dr. Ha.
Well done.
Good for you. I knew you'd wake up.
Eun Byeol!
Come on! Eun Byeol!
Ro Na. Was she badly hurt?
Thanks to you, she wasn't.
She was treated as an outpatient.
She's just fine now.
That's great.
Thank you.
Thanks so much.
I'll let you talk.
Joo Dan Tae. What happened to him?
He died. In Hera Palace.
He got blown up by a bomb
he set himself.
Is he really dead? Are you sure?
It'll be hard to find his body.
It was the world's
most dreadful and pathetic death.
Now only Cheon Seo Jin's left.
Cheon Seo Jin.
She put Ro Na in danger.
How dare she still...
She wasn't badly hurt,
so she was discharged.
She's staying in a small apartment.
Now that Dan Tae's dead,
the loan sharks
are no longer after her.
Other than her secretary
who gets her dementia medication,
she herself doesn't do much.
Dementia medication?
She's showing signs
of acute dementia.
She can't recognize people,
and she lost whole chunks of memory.
Dementia, just like that?
It'll be a lie. It can't be.
I don't believe her.
She knows we have her
killing Yoon Hee on tape,
so she's trying to avoid a trial.
You cannot believe her.
We have our suspicions,
but no proof.
We're watching her 24 hours a day,
and we have nothing.
Eun Byeol.
Is she still with her mom?
We're offering a 30-percent discount
to celebrate the grand opening.
Come inside and have a look.
We're offering
a 30-percent discount.
Come inside and have a look.
We're offering...
We're offering a 30-percent discount
to celebrate the grand opening.
Come inside and have a look.
We just opened
and everything is on...
You do it.
Is that all you can do?
Are you trying to ruin my business?
I'm sorry. I really am.
I don't care. Just quit.
You begged,
so I even paid you in advance.
You're a complete fraud.
Hey. You better pay the money back.
No. I'll work harder from now on.
Please let me work.
Please. I really need the money.
Hey. Pay the money back.
Please, sir. I beg you.
Come in and try using this model.
Everything is 30 percent off.
Come inside.
Everything is on sale.
Mr. Ma!
I heard the rumors.
Your family went broke.
Director Cheon Seo Jin...
I mean your mom...
is being chased by loan sharks
and is suffering from bad credit.
Looking at you, it seems like
you went super broke.
I thought rich people could live by
for three years after.
Maybe that doesn't
apply to criminals, though.
Then are you a young female
head of the house, now?
I'm leaving.
Don't you need money?
When I think about
how your mom used to be,
I really don't want to help you.
But I feel so bad for you right now.
You know I have a warm heart.
No, that's okay.
Your words are enough.
Thank you.
Even if it's 1,000 dollars a day?
What's the job?
Are you really going to give me
1,000 dollars?
You have to pass the test first.
I know I can do this well.
But you have to pay me in cash.
Okay.
You should know you're lucky
to have met me today.
If you follow what I say,
you can both make use of your major
and make money.
Here.
Sing it from the top.
Trot is all about your delivery.
Can you do it?
(Ppongjjak Medley)
(Jin Sung - "At Andong Station"
Kim Yeon Ja - "Amor Fati")
Was it an empty oath
Blown Away
By the wind?
On the first snow day
In front of Andong Station
The person who promised to meet
Don't be disappointed
You can't be good at everything
As long as tomorrow
is better than today
Life is all about the now
Mom, shall we drink?
This is...
the happiest day of my life.
Who are you?
Mom.
Yes.
Mom became this way because of me.
I must earn money and protect her.
Fill me up with love
I am the head of the house now.
The battery of love has run out
Oh my goodness
Don't do this
A woman's heart is like a reed
One day, you suddenly leave
And only a brown light remains
A lonely teacup
In a cold teacup
A faint brown memory
(Top 100 songs for the road)
No wonder you're an SNU student.
The high notes are the same pitch,
and you deliver it with such sorrow.
Kind of like a maschera-ringing
minari-like voice.
We can start recording tomorrow.
Already? I haven't even rehearsed.
You don't need to rehearse.
You're not a real singer.
You're just pretending
to be a singer.
Our job requires you to record
as many songs as possible.
Prepare songs with quick tempos,
not ones that drag along.
The ones that can wake you up...
when you're falling asleep
on the road.
I'll pay you well, so work hard.
Understood. Thank you, Mr. Ma.
Ha Eun Byeol.
- Yes?
- Life is so funny, don't you think?
I'll see you tomorrow.
(Dad)
(Cheong A Medical Center)
Dad!
When did you wake up?
Why did you wake up only now?
Why are you also making it hard?
I thought something was
going to go wrong.
I'm sorry, Eun Byeol.
You must have been so worried.
I'm okay now.
Why haven't you been answering
my calls?
Where have you been this late?
How about school?
I'm taking a gap year.
I need to earn money
to feed Mom and myself.
Why are you worrying about money?
Then who will?
We don't even have money
for Mom's medications.
Is it true your mom's sick?
What do you mean?
Is it true she has dementia?
She's lying so that she doesn't
get punished, isn't she?
Are you playing along although you
know it, or have you been duped too?
Dad! You've crossed the line.
Even if you hate Mom,
how can you say that?
Is dementia a joke to you?
You think Mom is making a joke
out of being sick?
Mom does have dementia.
She has dementia because of me.
I fed her drugs...
Drugs?
The drugs I got from Ms. Jin.
I fed them to Mom.
To help her forget.
What are you saying?
Why did you do such a thing?
I thought only then
she would stop doing bad things!
I can't see her commit crimes
for me anymore.
So I fed her the drugs so that
she wouldn't remember anything.
But I didn't know she would
even forget about me.
I feel so sorry for Mom.
Every day, things are getting
deleted from her brain.
She can't do anything
on her own anymore.
It's all my fault.
I made her stupid.
Eun Byeol.
Dad...
I'm going to take care of Mom.
I'm not going to ask for help.
I'm going to earn money
and take care of her.
So please tell Su Ryeon
to forgive Mom.
She won't do bad things anymore.
I beg of you, Dad. Please?
I'm begging you.
Please don't bully Mom anymore.
Just let it go. Just this once.
You saw with your own eyes
what your dad did.
I can't just let it go.
That's why I'm giving you to Ro Na!
I feel bad for Ro Na's mom.
Do you think it was easy
for me to let you go?
- But I'm giving it up!
- Ha Eun Byeol!
Mom has already paid for her sins.
What is a bigger punishment
than not being able to remember me?
Mom is nervous throughout the day
that she can't even sleep.
Isn't that enough?
Mom and I...
are going to start from the bottom.
Even if we starve to death,
I won't ask for your help.
That's not the point here.
I don't want to see you anymore.
Don't call
and don't come to find me.
Let Mom and I live by ourselves.
You can be Ro Na's dad
until the day you die!
Eun Byeol.
Eun Byeol...
(Cheong A Medical Center)
What about the thing I asked for?
Cheon Seo Jin's hospital records.
Based on the brain wrinkles,
it looks like her dementia
has advanced.
Not only is there severe
hippocampal atrophy,
but there are also multiple infarcts
in the white matter of the brain.
So it's true she has
early onset dementia?
Possibility of it being fake?
Doctors talk based on test results.
She really took those drugs.
At this level, she must have had
a hard time in her daily life.
The dosage of the drug she is taking
right now is quite high,
so she must be sleeping all day.
Mom is nervous throughout the day
that she can't even sleep.
Hold on. Just one more favor.
Seo Jin did an MRI
after a car accident five years ago.
Can you find it for me?
What do you think?
Something's not right.
Her recent scan doesn't show
any signs of her surgery.
The two scans look
completely different.
They're not the same person.
I knew something was off.
The test results have been
tampered with.
Why did you let him see her chart?
There's nothing I can do to stop
a fellow doctor from seeing it.
You can't tell anyone
she doesn't have dementia.
If you do, I'll reveal
all the bribes you've taken...
from pharmaceutical companies.
Worry about yourself.
If this gets out, my career is over.
I have a lot to lose.
Who is he to lecture me?
You must've been shocked.
Why didn't you stay
in the hospital for a few days?
I'd rather be home.
I'm worried about the kids too.
You don't have to worry about them.
Logan booked the entire hotel
so they could rest.
All Hera Palace residents
are staying there.
Thank you.
I guess this is
the end of Joo Dan Tae.
Dr. Ha woke up too. I'm so relieved.
Even the doctors were unsure.
It really is a miracle.
How is he doing?
Will there be
any long-term effects?
When can he leave the hospital?
I'm not sure.
He needs rest.
Let's visit him together soon.
Sure, let's do that.
All we have left is Cheon Seo Jin,
the worst of the worst.
Her condition has deteriorated,
so she'll be given stronger drugs.
She's getting more
and more desperate.
She must feel impatient.
Let's reveal the dashcam footage
and put her behind bars.
She'll be sent
to the Institute of Forensic Psychiatry...
and undergo a psychiatric evaluation.
That's her goal.
Getting away with murder
using her mental condition.
At this rate,
even with clear evidence,
her sentence will be reduced...
or the execution will be suspended,
releasing her within three years.
We can't let her get away
with killing Yoon Hee.
No way.
She killed a person,
and Ro Na lost her mom.
Three years is not enough!
We can't just sit back.
We should find out ourselves.
She threw away all her pills.
Cheon Seo Jin
has been putting on an act.
Eun Byeol is working until late
to make money.
How could she pretend to have
lost her memory in front of her kid?
She has no conscience whatsoever.
She doesn't deserve to be a mom.
We'll have to ask the hospital
to test her again.
If someone tampered with
the test results for money,
they should be punished as well.
Let's reveal the dashcam footage
immediately.
I wanted to keep it a secret
for Ro Na and Eun Byeol's sake.
But there's no reason to anymore.
As soon as Ro Na leaves,
I'll send the footage to the press.
Ro Na was very worried about you.
She visited you in the ICU
every day.
She did?
Yes.
You may not remember it,
but you must've heard her voice
while you were unconscious.
I'm sure that's why you woke up.
I didn't know that.
I thought she resented me.
Ro Na is leaving for the US
to study.
She got into the Juilliard School.
When is she leaving?
Tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
We wanted to bring her with us,
but she seemed busy
with preparations.
Still, she must be relieved
to know that you woke up...
before she leaves.
Logan, do me a favor.
Please get me out of here.
I want to see Ro Na.
This time, I need your help.
("The Temperature of Language")
Welcome.
It's been a while, Ro Na.
I did hear that you woke up.
Did you already get discharged?
Yes. I recovered fast.
Ro Na, let me pour you one.
Is it okay to drink?
How's your injury?
It's fine. The surgery went well.
The wound healed completely.
I just have to finish my treatment.
Ro Na, your hair has grown so long.
The dress looks great on you.
You look really good in white.
You...
take after your mom.
Big eyes, a beautiful voice...
You're brave too.
But she said I got
my stubbornness from my dad.
My semi-curly hair too.
I'm moving abroad to study tomorrow.
I got into the Juilliard School.
Good job, Ro Na.
I'm so happy for you.
How long will you be there?
I'm not sure.
It might take a while.
I might even settle there.
Why are you sweating so much?
I haven't been outside in a while.
It makes me nervous.
You must be busy.
Thanks for your time.
I just wanted to make sure
you're doing all right.
Let's say goodbye here.
Take care.
Why...
did you do that?
Why did you try to protect me?
Did you think I'd be grateful?
That's not it, Ro Na.
I hate you.
I hate you so much.
Do you know how scared I was?
That something would happen to you.
That you'd die because of me.
What was I supposed to do?
How was I supposed to live?
I'm sorry, Ro Na.
I keep doing things
I have to apologize for.
But I didn't mean to upset you.
I just didn't...
want you to get hurt.
I'm really fine.
So...
work hard in the US.
Forget everything...
and live happily, Ro Na.
It seems like he recovered
his consciousness.
Logan?
Yes, it's me, Dr. Ha.
Why is it so dark?
Please turn on the lights.
Can't you...
see anything?
No, I can't.
Everything's blurry.
I can see outlines, that's all.
Doctor. Please be honest with me.
I can handle it.
Well...
Your optic nerve was damaged,
so you've lost your eyesight.
We did our best,
but it was in a very dangerous spot.
There was just so much we could do
during surgery.
I'm sorry.
Then...
will I die?
You'll have extreme migraines.
He'll require...
the strongest pain killers
during the time he has left.
I don't want to waste
what precious time I have left...
staring at the ceiling
in a hospital.
We're here.
Ro Na is sitting in the middle
by the window.
What is she wearing?
A white dress.
She looks pretty with her hair down.
I want her to remember me
when I was healthy.
You can do this.
I've been here often,
so don't worry.
(Fate)
(Neurosurgeon Ha Yoon Chul)
Goodbye,
Dad.
Bye.
(Neurosurgeon Ha Yoon Chul)
(Cheong A Group)
The Cheong A Group that was created
by Cheon Seo Jin and Joo Dan Tae...
no longer exists.
However, I do not want
to discard the efforts...
of the executives and employees.
Therefore, we will retain
every single employee...
without any conditions.
Cheong A Group will be reborn
and Simoon Group.
Simoon Construction will make sure...
that Cheonsoo District
is the best town in which to live.
Please forget the past...
and do your best for this company.
(Cheong A Group)
(CEO Joo Dan Tae)
Father.
(Simoon Construction)
I got back the name Simoon...
that Dan Tae had stolen.
(Ha Yoon Chul)
Dr. Ha.
Su Ryeon.
This place...
(Rose Mansion)
This is where Seo Jin is living, right?
Yes, it is.
I came for Eun Byeol.
How did you get there by yourself
in your condition?
I have a favor to ask.
Let me tell Eun Byeol myself.
(Rose Mansion)
It's about her mom.
It will be too shocking
if she hears about it on the news.
I plan to take Eun Byeol far away
for the time being.
I don't have much time left.
I want to spend it alone with her.
I'll be right there.
Yoon Chul, do you hear me?
Wait. Don't do anything
until I get there.
Okay?
(Rose 304)
Eun Byeol?
Were you waiting for me?
Eun Byeol, let's go.
You can't stay here.
Your mom's lying to you.
Her MRI scan is a fake.
She didn't take that drug.
I already checked.
Let's hurry before your mom comes.
Eun Byeol. What's wrong?
Don't you believe me?
I never imagined
you'd lose your eyesight.
You really can't see?
Stay away.
Where's my daughter?
Eun Byeol.
What's wrong? Do I scare you?
Stop it.
Just how low must you stoop?
You're still Eun Byeol's mom.
How could you use your own child?
You didn't take that drug.
I have to live
for Eun Byeol to live!
Don't use her as an excuse.
It's all for you.
You did it to save yourself.
It doesn't change the fact
that she tried to feed it to me.
I just acted the way
she wanted me to be.
You did it to hide the fact
that you killed Yoon Hee.
It was all an act.
You have absolutely no shame.
You used
Eun Byeol's guilty conscience...
and you're putting the blame on me.
I'm going to take her.
I'll tell her everything.
Who else knows
that I don't have dementia?
Did you tell Su Ryeon?
Does that jerk Logan know too?
You're done for now.
Just accept your punishment.
I'm fine
if you keep your mouth shut.
Eun Byeol and I are moving abroad.
We'll never come back to Korea.
That will do.
I'm begging you.
Please, Seo Jin. Stop.
How did this happen to you?
Please.
Please snap out of it. Please.
Please let it slide...
for Eun Byeol's sake.
This is my last request.
- Let go.
- Seo Jin.
- Let go!
- Seo Jin!
No! No way!
No!
Yoon Chul.
No...
You can't die.
I won't forgive you if you do.
I have to go now.
I never...
forgot about you.
I loved you.
Yoon Hee.
You...
made me the bad one to the end.
Even until the moment you died,
you abandoned me.
Eun Byeol, why are you here?
Where's your dad?
I bought fruit
because he said he'd visit.
And your mom?
At the hospital.
Ms. Shim!
Eun Byeol, come this way.
What's wrong?
Get out of here
and call an ambulance. Now!
(Public Toilet)
It's all done.
It can't be turned back.
I have to go forward. Because...
I'm Cheon Seo Jin.
(Secretary Do)
It's me.
Ha Yoon Chul's dead.
Arrange for me to go abroad.
Eun Byeol and I have to go
to whatever country possible.
Hurry.
(Mortuary)
(May you rest in peace.)
Dad.
Why are you lying here?
It's me.
Wake up and look at me.
Dad!
Dad. I'm sorry.
I won't tell you
not to visit anymore.
Dad. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for everything.
I won't tell you
not to visit anymore!
So get up, please!
Dad.
Get up.
I was so mean to you.
I'm sorry for that, Dad.
Dad.
Dad...
- Dad.
- What happened?
- Why is he dead?
- I'm here now.
Seo Jin did it.
Cheon Seo Jin left him to die.
Dad.
(Neurosurgeon Ha Yoon Chul)
I didn't get to pass the gift
Ro Na got for him.
I'm sorry, Dad.
Seo Jin will try to flee overseas.
I must put a travel ban on her.
No.
Let's let her have her way.
What do you mean?
What if we lose her forever?
Then we play our final card.
We should deceive her too.
So she confesses her crimes.
Are you all right?
Let go of me.
If you want to talk nonsense,
just go.
I won't listen to what you say.
Do you still not believe me?
Why would someone who can't
remember anything kill Dad?
Mom wasn't even home at the time.
She was. She ran away.
Your mom remembers everything.
She's lying to you.
That's impossible.
I fed her the drug myself.
The drug that erases your memory.
That's why she doesn't
recognize me either.
I don't know what's going on,
but your mom
didn't take the drug.
Her MRI was faked.
No!
Eun Byeol.
Ro Na's mom is dead
and now so is your dad.
Don't you feel bad for them?
How many more must sacrifice
for you to believe me?
Until I see it for myself,
I won't believe anything.
Dr. Ha was blind,
so it looks like the police
will conclude he lost his footing.
And Shim Su Ryeon?
She isn't doing anything.
Then I'll have no problem
going abroad.
Eun Byeol.
Is she still at the funeral?
Yes. I'll bring her
to the airport on time.
You should leave first.
So that no one suspects you,
I think you should
travel on separate flights.
Let's go.
(Eun Byeol)
Hello?
Mom!
Hello? What sound is that?
Quit the act, Cheon Seo Jin.
If you want to save your daughter,
get over here now.
To where you killed Yoon Hee.
If you're not here within an hour,
you'll never see Eun Byeol again.
Shim Su Ryeon has Eun Byeol.
- What?
- Didn't you hear me?
Shim Su Ryeon took Eun Byeol.
I have to go.
You can't. It'll be a trap.
Leave this to me
and leave the country.
You must leave now if you're
to make the flight. There's no time.
Su Ryeon killed Dan Tae.
She's capable of anything.
She might kill Eun Byeol too.
I have to go.
You can't.
You need to save yourself first.
If you lose this chance,
you might not get another one.
I will save Eun Byeol.
Eun Byeol is my daughter!
I will save her.
Shim Su Ryeon.
This will end today.
Give me the car keys!
Ms. Cheon!
Eun Byeol.
Eun Byeol, I'm coming.
Shim Su Ryeon, you...
Shim Su Ryeon!
Eun Byeol!
Don't come close.
Or your daughter dies here.
What are you doing?
Eun Byeol did nothing wrong!
I'm the one you want!
No!
No! Eun Byeol!
Eun Byeol! No!
No!
Eun Byeol.
Kudos to your acting...
when you're this clear-minded.
Shim Su Ryeon!
Why are you interfering
with my life every step of the way?
Did you think killing Yoon Hee
will solve everything?
Did you think you could
keep it a secret till the end...
as long as you could
blame Joo Dan Tae for it?
Oh Yoon Hee died because of you.
I had to cut your right-hand woman
off to deal with you.
So now you're confessing.
Don't act all high and mighty,
as if you're better than us.
If only you hadn't acted
like you were on a high horse...
by forgiving the murderer
who killed Min Seol A,
Oh Yoon Hee would have
stayed in prison,
and she wouldn't have died.
Did you live all your life...
always rationalizing
your sins like this?
- Shut up!
- You should pray.
I'll make your daughter pay
for all of your sins.
Where's Eun Byeol?
Where is she?
Eun Byeol!
Where is Eun Byeol?
Where is my daughter?
What did you do to her?
Why did you kill Ha Yoon Chul?
Because he found out
you didn't have dementia?
Because you were afraid your lies
were going to get exposed?
So you killed a man?
Bring me Eun Byeol.
I don't hear anything you're saying!
Depending on how you behave,
Eun Byeol may die...
or live.
What do you want?
You want me to turn myself in?
No way. That's never happening.
If only you hadn't left me
with no other options,
Ha Yoon Chul wouldn't have died.
He shouldn't have abandoned me
for his daughter's sake!
Mom was really the one
who killed Dad?
After all I've done for Mom...
how is she still a monster?
Now, do you believe?
I'm sorry...
you had to see that.
Is this the police?
I'm reporting a murderer.
I know who really
killed Oh Yoon Hee.
I saw it.
My mom killing Oh Yoon Hee.
It's over, Cheon Seo Jin.
You finally made
the foolish choice...
of being abandoned even
by your own daughter.
What?
Eun Byeol has been watching.
Your lies.
Your dirty wrongdoings. All of them.
It was Eun Byeol who reported you
to the police.
Shim Su Ryeon.
Without you,
my life would have been perfect.
If only you hadn't
shown up in my life!
My family would have
remained intact.
I wouldn't have gotten involved
with someone like Joo Dan Tae.
Eun Byeol and I,
including Yoon Chul,
my family could have been happy.
Happy?
You don't deserve that.
That will never happen
in your life now.
I can't die like this.
I can't die alone!
Cheon Seo Jin. Don't do this.
- Don't move!
- No!
No!
No, Mom!
Su Ryeon!
Shim Su Ryeon!
No.
I held on to her.
I swear.
Let's go!
Eun Byeol!
Someone has gone over Gimpo cliff.
The suspect has been arrested.
Stop! You can't go that way.
- Su Ryeon!
- You can't go that way.
Su Ryeon!
- It's dangerous.
- Su Ryeon!
Calm down. It's dangerous.
- Calm down.
- Stop this.
Su Ryeon!
Eun Byeol!
(The Penthouse 3)
What do you mean there's no signal?
- We have to find her.
- I didn't do it!
The tragedy started with me.
I don't know who that person is.
Congratulations on your
first performance.
You said you'd buy me pasta.
I've missed you, Ro Na.
Don't kill Seo Jin.
I want to end everything now.
I have people I have to meet.
Will you come with me, Logan?