Watch on kisskh.me
LOKI: So, you're part of the TVA's
courageous and dedicated workforce?
Yes.
You were created by the Time-Keepers?
Correct.
(LAUGHS)
RAVONNA: You're not the only analyst
working for me.
But, would you say,
maybe, I'm your favorite one?
LOKI: Enchantment is a clever trick.
SYLVIE: I have to create a fantasy
from their memories.
That young soldier from the TVA,
she was just a regular person on Earth.
Of all of the apocalypses
saved on that TemPad, this is the worst!
No one makes it off here!
LOKI: How long do we have?
SYLVIE: Twelve hours or so.
Things down here are only gonna get worse.
To the end of the world.
- Sync and corrections by explosiveskull - www.opensubtitles.org -
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44
(WIND BLOWING)
Dragon swoops towards the palace,
the Valkyrie flies over,
defeats the dragon, and saves Asgard.
(DEVICE BEEPING)
There's our Variant.
On the authority of the Time-Keepers,
I hereby arrest you for crimes
against the Sacred Timeline.
Reset it.
Wait!
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
MAN: No! No!
(GRUNTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTS)
Help him!
Next case!
(GRUNTS)
- Next case!
- Right here!
(DEVICE BEEPING)
(GASPS)
(INHALES AND EXHALES)
(OPENING THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
What'd they say? Are you okay?
No, no, Mobius. I'm not.
Under the best of circumstances,
it's jarring to stand
before the Time-Keepers.
And this is not the best of circumstances.
Yeah, but they can't blame you.
They can and do.
The Variant was right here.
What if she got to the Time-Keepers?
I know. But she didn't.
No. But she got away.
Along with the Variant that
I got you permission to bring in here.
Do you have any idea how impossible it is
to keep the timeline stable?
The Time-Keepers are all that stand
between us and full-scale calamity.
And I'm glad they're on our side.
But if they want me
to find Loki and the Variant,
(WHISPERS) I need access to Hunter C-20.
I'm sorry, but that's impossible.
Look, when we found her,
she kept saying, "It's real. It's real."
Over and over.
I need to find out what that meant
and what else she saw
when she was with the Variant.
Look, I know there's protocol,
but she could have information...
She's dead, Mobius!
What? How?
The Variant, she enchanted C-20,
scrambled her mind.
I don't get it. She seemed okay.
She seemed fine.
RAVONNA: At first, yes.
But by the time she got in here,
she could barely speak.
The decline was steeper after that.
- I didn't know. What...
- Nobody does.
We don't want people to panic.
Can I trust you to keep that between us?
Of course. Yes.
I'm sorry.
Every moment those Variants are out there,
we're all in danger.
Find them!
(PEOPLE YELLING)
(EXPLOSIONS)
I'm sorry.
I remember Asgard.
Not much, but I remember.
My home, my people, my life.
The universe wants to break free,
so it manifests chaos.
Like me being born
the Goddess of Mischief.
And as soon as that created a big enough
detour from the Sacred Timeline,
the TVA showed up, erased my reality,
and took me prisoner.
I was just a child.
I escaped.
Stole a TemPad and I ran for a long,
long time, which really sucked.
Everywhere and every-when I went,
it caused a nexus event.
Sent up a smoke flare.
Because I'm not supposed to exist.
Until, eventually,
I figured out where to hide.
And so that's where I grew up,
the ends of a thousand worlds.
(SCOFFS)
Now...
...that's where I'll die.
ANALYST 1: There's nothing, sir.
MOBIUS: Even with
the magnified nexus threshold?
That one should be setting off alarms
if somebody steps on the wrong leaf.
ANALYST 2: Wherever they are,
I'm not sure anything survives.
Yeah. Don't underestimate them.
You see anything down at Roxxcart?
They're gone.
Leaping across time,
plotting their next massacre.
(COMPUTER WHIRRING)
Any news on C-20?
No.
We need to find them.
We will.
SYLVIE: Not long now.
Do you think that what makes a Loki a Loki
is the fact that we're destined to lose?
LOKI: No.
We may lose.
Sometimes painfully.
But we don't die.
We survive.
I mean, you did.
You were just a child
when the TVA took you,
but you nearly took down the organization
that claims to govern the order of time.
You did it on your own.
You ran rings around them. You're amazing!
We've got something.
ANALYST 1: Temporal lock.
(RUMBLING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Okay, that's not someone
stepping on the wrong leaf.
You ever seen a branch like that?
No.
(COMPUTER WHIRRING)
MOBIUS: Well?
LOKI: Well, what?
I know you got some quip
you're dyin' to say.
I don't have a quip.
I've got nothing to say.
Come on.
By the way, I should have an equal amount
of security. This is insulting!
You just can't help yourself.
- You betrayed me!
- Grow up!
- You grow up.
MOBIUS: You know, it occurred to me that
you're not really the God of Mischief.
LOKI: Oh, here it comes.
The folksy, dopey insult
from the folksy dope.
What am I? The God of Self-Sabotage, yeah?
The God of Back-Stabbing?
Just kind of an asshole and a bad friend.
Yeah, chew on that for a little bit.
All right. It's ready.
What is this?
You'll see.
- Mobius!
- Okay. No, no, no, let him,
one last desperate trick
from the desperate trickster. Go ahead.
(PANTING) The TVA is lying to you.
Put him in.
No. (GRUNTS)
What?
(CHUCKLES)
Seriously?
You.
Sif.
You conniving, craven, pathetic worm.
- You did this.
- What?
LOKI: Ow.
I hope you know you deserve to be alone
and you always will be.
All right.
A bad memory prison? How quaint.
LOKI: Ow!
Some punishment. (GRUNTS)
I remember exactly what I did after that.
I went and had a nice, hot bath
and a glass of wine,
and I never thought about it again,
because it was just a bit of fun.
- SIF: You.
- Huh?
You conniving, craven, pathetic worm.
You did this.
Hang on. Ow.
I hope you know you deserve to be alone
and you always will be.
Just...
(GROANING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Time loops. How lovely.
You.
You conniving, craven, pathetic worm.
Okay. Okay, Sif. Hang on.
No, you hear this.
You deserve to be alone...
And I always will be.
All right, I get it.
Listen. You are a reconstruction
of a past event
created by the organization
that controls all of time.
So you need to trust me
and you need to help me escape. Yeah?
Okay, good.
Pathetic.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Hey.
(CHUCKLES)
Shouldn't you be interrogating
the Loki Variant?
He's softening in the Time Cell,
but while he marinates, I thought
maybe I'd interview the other Variant.
Oh, no. Just stick with your Loki
and figure out what that nexus spike was.
I know, but I think I can get there faster
if I work 'em both together.
You said we have a part to play,
and the part I play...
Absolutely not. She's just too dangerous.
Too dangerous? Come on, Ravonna.
This is what I do.
And this is what I do.
Nobody speaks with that Variant.
I mean, if there's a mastermind here,
I don't think it's Loki.
Good.
Then he should be the easiest to break.
Work your Loki and figure out
what caused that spike.
Time-Keepers are watching, Mobius.
They're always watching.
"Work your Loki, work your Loki."
That ought to be my mantra.
You all right?
- Is she in there?
- Mm-hmm.
(SCOFFS)
They don't go gently, do they?
Aren't you supposed to be
interrogating your Variant pet?
Just stretching my legs.
You know, we brought in Kree,
Titans, vampires.
Why is it the two orphan demigods
are such a pain in the ass?
And yet it was your idea
to bring in another one.
I'm happy to share credit for that idea.
Mobius?
Did Loki say anything
while you were in there?
Yeah. He said the TVA is lying to me.
Why?
Just doing my job.
- SIF: You.
- (SIGHS)
You conniving, craven...
- Sif. Sif.
- ...pathetic worm.
Please, please, no more.
Please, I beg you.
I'm a horrible person.
I get it. I really am.
I cut off your hair
because I thought it'd be funny.
And it's not.
Uh...
I crave attention...
because I'm...
(SIGHS)
I'm a... I'm a narcissist.
And I suppose it's...
It's because I'm scared of being alone.
You are alone and you always will be.
Okay, Loki.
You ready to talk?
Fancy technology.
Threatening interrogation tactics.
Seems you and I are in a loop of our own.
Well, there's been a lot of water
under the bridge since then.
LOKI: Certainly has.
Okay, you said the TVA is lying to me.
Go ahead.
Or is that just a cockroach's
survival mechanism kicking in?
Let me out of this place,
stop beating me up, and I'll tell you.
Cockroach. Got it.
How long have you been
working for the Variant?
Me? Working for her? Please.
If you're not working for the Variant,
what is it? You're partners?
Absolutely not.
She's difficult and irritating,
and she tries to hit me all the time.
No. Not partners, no.
Yeah, I guess you don't do partners.
Unless, of course, it benefits you,
and you intend to betray them
at some point.
It was a means to an end, Mobius.
Welcome to the real world.
Down there, we're awful
to get what we want.
Now I gotta have a prince tell me
how the real world works?
Why don't you just tell me what caused
the nexus event on Lamentis?
Let me say this again.
I'm not going to tell you
just so you can turn around
immediately afterwards and prune me.
I guess we've reached a dead end then.
Okay, it's over.
I'm going to miss
these little tete-a-tetes.
LOKI: Me, too.
One guy playing checkers, you,
old Mobius playing chess,
but, yeah, give my regards to Lady Sif.
What... No. What? No, no, no.
Please, not...
Well, just wait, wait, wait.
Yeah?
Of course it was me
pulling the strings all along.
She came to me on Asgard a long time ago
and then she took me
to one of her apocalypses
and that's where
we hatched our plan together.
Which is?
Coming along very nicely, thank you.
MOBIUS: And the Variant?
Doesn't matter. She's a pawn.
Something very, very big is gonna happen.
And when it does, I'll dispose of her.
Well, we saved you the trouble there.
She's already been pruned.
- So assume I do set you free.
- Hang on, wait.
- What'd you just say?
- What? Assume I do set you free.
LOKI: The Variant. She's gone?
Yeah. Not before she took out two of ours.
Yeah, she was going
to her Time Cell, broke free.
Hunter B-15 stepped in, popped her.
So you might want to fire off
a thank you note to Hunter B-15,
because it looks like
you're the superior Loki.
I would've bet on her,
but that's what makes a horse race.
Good riddance.
(CHUCKLING)
- What's so funny?
- Come on.
Look at your eyes. You like her.
- What?
- You like her. Does she like you?
- LOKI: Was she pruned?
- No wonder you have no clue
what caused the nexus event
on Lamentis.
Both of you are swooning over each other.
- LOKI: Tell me the truth.
- It's the apocalypse.
Two Variants of the same being,
especially you, forming this kind of sick,
twisted romantic relationship.
That's pure chaos.
That could break reality.
It's breaking my reality right now.
What a incredible seismic narcissist.
You fell for yourself.
Her name was Sylvie.
Ah, Sylvie.
Lovely.
How do you spell that?
Is that with an I-E or just an I?
Is she alive?
For now.
(SIGHS)
And was infiltrating the TVA,
was that always sort of the grand plan?
Our interests are aligned.
- MOBIUS: Overthrowing the Time-Keepers?
- Maybe they need to be overthrown.
- I ought to box your ears.
- LOKI: Mobius, listen.
If what Sylvie told me about this place
is true, it affects all of us.
Here we go. Now, you've already told me
about 50 lies in the past 10 minutes.
- I'm not lying.
- Now, I'm supposed
- to believe your girlfriend.
- It's the truth.
- She's not my girlfriend.
- Whatever you want to call her.
What, your female self that
you have some demented crush on...
You're all Variants!
Everyone who works at the TVA.
The Time-Keepers didn't create you.
They kidnapped you from the timeline,
and erased your memories.
Memories she can access
through enchantment.
So before this, you had a past,
maybe you had a family, a life.
Nice try.
That was good. You two, what a pair!
Gosh! Unbelievable. Wherever you go,
it's just death, destruction,
the literal ends of worlds.
Well, I'm gonna have
to close this case now,
'cause I don't need you anymore.
Yeah, or as you might say,
our interests are no longer aligned.
You know, of all the liars in this place,
and there are a great many,
you're the biggest.
Why? 'Cause I lied about your girlfriend?
Oh, no. That I can respect.
I mean, the lies you tell yourself.
(EXHALES)
Open the door.
Hello... Oh, I don't know.
Your name's a number.
Can't read it from here.
(DEVICE BEEPING)
Come with me.
(THEREMIN MUSIC PLAYING)
Mobius?
Oh, yeah.
- You okay?
- Yep, I'm good.
- Case closed.
- Yes.
Cheers.
- Cheers.
- To putting all this behind us.
(SIGHS)
Amen.
If you could go anywhere, anytime,
where would it be?
I can go anywhere, anytime.
You know what I mean.
Why wouldn't you let me
interrogate Sylvie?
- Sylvie?
- The Variant, that's what Loki calls her.
Why wouldn't you let me,
you know, question her?
I told you,
we couldn't risk her escaping again.
She wouldn't have escaped.
The other Variant got away during
your first interrogation, didn't he?
Ouch. (CHUCKLES)
Come on. Anywhere and anytime
on the timeline. Where'd you go?
I like being here now, with you,
doing the work.
Fine.
I received word from the Time-Keepers.
They want to personally oversee
the Variant's pruning.
And they want you there, too.
It's about time. Great.
When... When did you first notice
what was going on with C-20?
Mobius, what is going on with you?
- Nothing.
- We did it.
- I know.
- The Time-Keepers are happy.
- It's great.
- Mission accomplished.
Mission accomplished.
It was just that she seemed fine when I...
When I saw her.
I mean, a little freaked, but fine.
Well, she quickly wasn't fine.
- Okay.
C-20? The Variant?
All these questions,
what are you getting at?
I don't know. I...
Something just seems a little off.
Fine. You want the truth?
I'm trying to protect you.
Would you normally interview
someone like that? Yeah.
But the Variant scares the hell out of me,
and I didn't want to see
anything happen to you.
C-20 lost her mind.
She couldn't even form words by the end.
I just couldn't deal with that
happening to you or anyone else.
Is that what you wanted to hear?
Yeah, if it's the truth.
You've been spending
too much time with Lokis.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
I definitely have been
spending too much time with Lokis.
What we do here matters.
I know.
When we're out there fighting
for the fate of the Sacred Timeline
we're also fighting for this. For us.
Friends against time, allies to the end.
You've seen all of existence, same as me.
So, you know,
friendship like ours is uncommon.
And worth fighting for.
Same as the Sacred Timeline.
It was a good speech.
Thank you.
I knew I was your favorite analyst.
Was that so hard to admit?
What are you gonna do with that trophy?
- Oh!
- Where's that gonna go?
You're right.
Let's see.
RAVONNA: Uh...
How's that?
Looks perfect.
You're running out of room there.
All right, I will see you later on.
One drink?
- MOBIUS: I had two, didn't I?
- Mobius!
This is a career case.
You sure you're okay?
I'm just exhausted,
dealing with all these Lokis.
Fair enough.
Let's finish this.
For all time.
Always.
I'll see you up there.
Thanks for the drink.
Fine. You wanted a fair fight.
I respect that.
When you were in my head, I saw something.
What did you do to me?
I showed you your life before the TVA.
That's a trick. It's a deception.
- No, it's not.
- I was created by the Time-Keepers.
No. I can't create memories.
I can only use what's already there.
The Time-Keepers took your lives from you.
From all of you.
You're Variants.
We're the same.
Show me.
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
(GASPS)
I looked happy.
What now?
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(DEVICE BEEPS)
You're not hearing me. I was there.
This was real, what I saw.
This is a place that I've been.
This wasn't the TVA. This was a memory.
I lived down there. I went to that bar.
I had friends.
I had a whole life on the Sacred Timeline.
- INTERROGATOR: Calm down.
- "Calm down"? I'm a Variant.
So are you.
So is every single person in this place.
I'm ending this.
I've heard it once,
I've heard it a thousand times.
"You. You conniving, craven,
pathetic worm. You did this."
Right?
- What are you doing?
- Passing the time.
Do you care about her?
Sylvie? I'm not sure
if it's the right word.
- We've covered this back in there.
- Shut up!
Do you really think
you deserve to be alone?
- Loki!
- You told me to shut up.
Do you believe
you deserve to be alone?
- I don't know.
- You better figure it out quick,
because the nexus event
the two of you caused,
whatever that connection is,
can bring this whole place down.
- So we better understand...
- "We"?
Do you swear she didn't implant
those memories in Hunter C-20?
Mobius, no. I believe her.
So, I just have to trust
the word of two Lokis?
How about the word of a friend?
You were right, about the TVA.
You were right from the beginning.
And if you wanna save her,
you need to trust me.
Can we do that?
- Yes.
- MOBIUS: Okay.
You could be whoever,
whatever you wanna be,
even someone good.
I mean, just in case
anyone ever told you different.
I think you have something of mine.
Yeah, I got all the way down there
before I even realized I picked up yours.
What's going on?
What's the problem, Ravonna?
You know where I'd go
if I could go anywhere?
Wherever it is I'm really from.
Yeah, wherever I had a life
before the TVA came along.
Maybe I had a jet ski.
That's what I'd like to do.
- Just riding around on my jet ski.
- Prune him.
(GROANS)
(GASPS)
Wait for me at the elevator.
Who was in here with her?
Sorry, ma'am, B-15 insisted.
Put out an alert for Hunter B-15.
She too has been compromised
by the Variant.
(WHISPERS) You okay?
I've got them from here.
(DOOR OPENS)
Do you remember me?
I do.
What do you wanna say to me, Variant?
What was my nexus event?
Why did you bring me in?
What does it matter?
It was enough to take my life from me,
lead to all of this.
Must have been important.
So, what was it?
I don't remember.
RAVONNA: Gracious Time-Keepers,
as promised, the Variants.
After all your struggle,
at last, you've arrived before us.
What do you have to say for yourselves
before you meet your end, Variants?
Is that the only reason
you brought us here?
To kill us?
I've lost track of the number of times
I've been killed, so go ahead.
Do your worst.
You and your bravado
are no threat to us, Variant.
Oh, no, I don't think you believe that.
- I think...
- (STATIC)
I think you're scared.
No, Variant. You're nothing
but a cosmic disappointment.
- Delete them.
- No, I'm not done with you yet.
(STATIC)
(BEEPS)
For all time.
Always.
Protect the Time-Keepers!
LOKI: A little help here?
Here.
Come on.
This time I finish the job.
(GASPS)
You're a child
of the Time-Keepers too, Sylvie.
- We can talk.
- SYLVIE: Oh, yeah?
(TIME-KEEPERS LAUGHING)
Wait.
(POWERING DOWN)
Don't.
Fake.
Mindless androids.
It never stops.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Then who created the TVA?
I thought this was it.
Sylvie...
Not another pep talk, please.
No, I have to tell you something.
We will figure this out.
How do you know that?
Because, uh...
Well, back on Lamentis...
This is new for me. Um...
What?
What is it?
Do it.
No.
You're gonna tell me everything.
- Sync and corrections by explosiveskull - www.opensubtitles.org -
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44
(SLOW ROCK SONG PLAYING)
If the sun
Should tumble from the sky
If the sea
Should suddenly run dry
If you love me
Really love me
Let it happen
I won't care
If it seems
That everything is lost
I will smile
And never count the cost
If you love me
Really love me
Let it happen
Darling, I
Won't care
Shall I catch a shooting star?
Shall I bring it where you are?
If you want me to, I will
You can set me any task
I'll do anything you ask
If you'll only say you love me still
When at last
Our life on earth is through
I will share
Eternity with you
If you love me
Really love me
Let it happen
I won't care
I you love me
Really love me
Let it happen
Darling, I...
(GASPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Is this Hel?
Am I dead?
VOICE: Not yet.
But you will be unless you come with us.
(GRUNTS)
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
- Sync and corrections by explosiveskull - www.opensubtitles.org -
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44