[Imitation]
[Episode 5]
["Nangrangbihwa"]
[Rand Hotel]
[We have arrived at the hotel.]
["Nangrangbihwa"]
[History-changing love of a swordsman]
Found it.
["Nangrangbihwa"]
Here you go.
I'll pick you up at 6:30 a.m.
I still feel bad about
being the only one having a fancy room.
The film company is paying for it,
so don't feel guilty and enjoy it.
You earned it.
Sure thing, sir.
Get a good night's rest too.
Got it. Sleep tight.
Good night.
What is this?
[Fins Mouthwash, for Ryoc's fresh breath]
[Be a hit, "Nangrangbihwa"!]
No!
-Hurry!
-Get in!
-My gosh.
-Wait for us!
Unbelievable.
Stop right there!
What's going on?
Stalker fans are in the house. See you.
[Going up.]
Jeez.
Director Ji-hak?
It really is you.
Now you're the CEO of JH Entertainment.
Do I know you?
We met once during SHAX's interview.
I'm Byun Jeong-hui with "Fact Check".
I see.
The girls must be in the spotlight now
[Fact Check, Byun Jeong-hui]
for "Fact Check" to take interest in them.
Tea Party was at the heart of some issues,
but the group isn't on that level yet.
Let's grab some coffee.
I doubt we'll have anything to talk about.
The girl whom Eun-jo dated.
I hear it was you who saw her last,
CEO Ji.
Is that worth a cup of coffee?
My gosh, Dae-gwon. Please.
Why does he always do this?
Why didn't you take the key?
You're my manager.
He's in room 1425, right?
I'm sure this is the floor they got off.
[Executive Suite]
Could they already be inside?
-Ryoc!
-Are you all right?
-Stop it.
Get away from there.
Not you guys as well.
It's our job to protect Ryoc.
Stop this. Keep order, will you?
Doing this makes you
just like the stalker fans.
Seriously? Who are you comparing us to?
I'll stand guard here,
so you go downstairs
and see if the stalkers left.
You, check the staircase.
Move!
Don't glare at me like that.
Ryoc.
In there. Hurry!
I don't know how they found out,
but the stalkers haven't been caught,
so don't open the door for anyone.
-No one came by, right?
-No.
-Dae-gwon.
-Yes?
What's going on, and why are you smirking?
-Dae-gwon!
-My gosh.
-You know I love you, right?
-What?
I love you a great deal.
-Jeez.
-You look distressed.
What you need for sure is rest.
-Have you been drinking?
-No.
Fine. All right.
Anyway...
Why did the lights suddenly go on?
Dae-gwon!
-What now?
-I'm exhausted
and would like some time alone to rest.
I came by with your mouthwash.
Mouthwash? Hand them over.
I'll put them on the shelf.
I can do a good job.
I can do it.
Why not purchase it yourself too then?
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Go and get some much-needed rest.
-Don't open the door for anyone.
-Got it.
I hear you.
-I'll get going.
-Sure. Good night.
Interesting, isn't it?
I don't know why,
but Eun-jo's girlfriend...
Well, that was never verified, but still.
Anyway, she committed suicide
after talking to you
and Eun-jo disappeared.
Shortly after,
you left the entertainment industry.
A few years went by,
and you made a comeback
by producing Tea Party.
It turns out though that Tea Party
used to be OMEGA-3,
which was the group the dead girl was in.
Stop beating around the bushes.
-What do you want to know?
-It's about Eun-jo.
You see, I've been a true fan of SHAX
since the very beginning
and a founding member of Fins.
I'm curious about Eun-jo as a fan.
He's already been forgotten.
I guess. But you know how it goes.
Anyone who's ever been in this industry
doesn't have a right to be forgotten.
They have no right to be forgotten?
Traces of the past remain everywhere.
Then use those traces to locate him.
I have an early day tomorrow,
so I'm clocking out.
But...
I knew it was a long shot,
and I was right.
What?
Why don't you sit down and relax?
No, I'm good.
-I'm sorry about this.
-Why were you here?
Because of this.
["Nangrangbihwa"]
The fans made it especially for you.
There was the padded jacket incident,
so...
Take a seat over there. It'll be a while.
["Nangrangbihwa"]
I wouldn't have had the guts.
It was cool what you did on that stage.
I wanted to tell you that.
But I see you slept through my words.
It's nothing. I was just... You know...
[I'll pick you up at 6:30 a.m.]
[6:02 a.m.]
-It's 6 a.m.!
-Keep it down.
-What's wrong?
-6:30 a.m.
It's my pick-up time.
6:30 a.m.?
Darn.
Darn it.
An SOS call at dawn? This can't be good.
-What's wrong?
-Nothing's wrong.
I just got a call. Are you going to stay?
-He's ours to protect.
It's sunrise soon, so get some shuteye.
[Executive Suite]
What on earth? Seriously?
Why is Lee Ma-ha here?
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
That's enough.
Lift your chin up.
You don't need to apologize.
I'm the one who pulled you in.
Are you insane?
You can't pull her into your room!
Especially when there are people
stationed outside!
-Quiet.
-What?
[Ma-ha]
[CEO Ji-hak]
[Executive Suite]
Ryoc, what's wrong?
Dae-gwon, stay with me!
Let's go.
-Ryoc!
[13F]
Dae-gwon!
[12F]
[13F]
Darn it.
I can't believe this just happened.
You can put me down now.
I can manage from here.
I'm a faster runner.
I'm quite heavy, aren't I?
You are.
Darn it!
I'm sorry.
I was in the shower after working out
when you called.
Hurry. We're already late.
-Get ready.
-Got it.
Ryoc!
It was an acute hemorrhoidal crisis,
but he's good now.
Hemorrhoids?
-What was it?
-Hemorrhoids.
Have you lost your mind?
You have hemorrhoids.
What? Hemorrhoids?
What have you been telling people?
["Nangrangbihwa"]
Now I'm really mad.
I can't believe you gave me hemorrhoids!
Explain yourself!
CEO Park will fire me if he finds out.
["Nangrangbihwa"]
I...
I guess I can survive the fallout.
I'll find work elsewhere,
but Ryoc...
["Nangrangbihwa"]
Did your fans see you?
I'm talking to you, darn it!
Give me my clothes back. Where are they?
[Stupid fool]
Are you zoning me out?
Is this fun for you?
[Be a hit, "Nangrangbihwa"!]
I'm sorry. Sorry I'm late.
-Ma-ha, it's okay.
-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Ms. Lee--
One should be punctual.
You kept the senior actors
and staff members waiting.
-I'm sorry.
-Have basic manners.
Face that way.
You, that way.
["Nangrangbihwa"]
[History-changing love of a swordsman]
It only took me five minutes
to park the van and follow you up here.
You sure are sleeping deeply
for someone who has insomnia.
How can you sleep so well?
My day started early too.
Maybe I should sneak in a nap.
What? What is it?
What do you want to know?
You, look straight into my eyes.
Are you sure nothing happened?
Dae-gwon,
you asked me that 516,999 times
on our way home.
That's the number of fans in Fins.
While we're on the subject of Fins,
let me remind you what we went through
to remedy the jacket situation.
What happened last night
is like a nuclear bomb!
Dae-gwon, I promise you.
Nothing happened. Don't you trust me?
Your SOS signal almost melted my bones.
You know I'm weak-hearted.
-It's still pounding.
-Whatever.
Take the beverages from my suitcase.
I saw that you were running low.
That's sweet of you.
Just remember this.
If by any chance,
even if something did happen,
you have to
act like nothing happened, okay?
They say many a little makes a mickle.
I know you'll handle it well,
but with your looks,
she can't help but fall for you.
Don't give her even the slightest chance.
Okay, okay. You can go already.
Wash up and get some rest!
Thanks, Dae-gwon.
Just stick to one thing.
Don't be nice to me
if you'll keep acting crazy.
Take the beverages.
You jerk.
I'll take two. Get some sleep now!
[I'm home.]
Ma-ha. It must've been exhausting.
It was really deep.
She's been like this
ever since we went to see your movie.
-You saw it?
-You didn't even show us the script.
And you didn't even invite us
to the preview.
Lee Ma-ha. Your eyes were
totally sparkling.
Stop it, Ri-a.
Are you sure you've never dated anyone?
It was so realistic.
Hey, it's all acting.
You're a genius then, Ma-ha.
When we were shooting the scene,
Ryoc and everyone else
made it comfortable for me,
so it came out naturally.
Who made what comfortable?
You mean that rude Kwon Ryoc
who finds everything unsatisfying?
He's not that rude.
Hey, SHAX earned their title for a reason.
I hear they're really evil and rude.
Especially Kwon Ryoc.
He's the rudest one among them.
He doesn't even lift a finger
and drives his manager hard.
They said he's really cold and picky,
so I thought that's why he seemed so,
-but he's actually rude.
-He really is.
He's just plain rude.
And other rumors say...
No, rumors are just rumors.
He was really considerate of me
and made things comfortable.
He took care of me
so our scene could turn out nice.
So don't think of him so badly.
-What?
-You were like this last time too.
-Why do you keep siding with him?
-No, I didn't.
I think Ri-a is right on that one.
-That's because...
-Anyway, be careful.
I almost tore into the screen
when you kissed Ryoc in the movie.
So that I can shake you off of him.
-Why would you do that?
-In case Fins take it out on you
and get attacked by them.
You should've seen how they reacted
when they saw the kissing scene.
They screamed so loudly
that I asked Yu-jin
what the lines were many times.
What? Yu-jin tagged along too?
What did he say?
[Music Holic]
The lights were off,
so I thought you went home.
-You're still practicing?
-Yes, Tae-geun.
You should get some rest
when you're not working.
Sure.
Tae-geun.
I want to try acting in dramas or movies.
You?
-Yes.
-I thought you weren't interested.
I suddenly want to.
I want to try everything
and do well in all of them.
Hey, she's back.
It has been a month already.
What's wrong?
You were laughing on your own.
It's creepy.
What about it?
It's weird.
It's weird to see you laugh.
-Did something good happen?
-As if.
-Get out of here.
-Nothing happened?
I don't know what to do.
The gift pack.
He couldn't have seen it, could he?
[H Cafe]
[Welcome.]
[NOG Entertainment]
They're done with the tour,
and they're only left
with promotions on radio shows.
-Nothing happened, right?
-Sorry?
No, nothing happened, sir.
Tell Ryoc to decide
which dramas and movies
he wants to star in as soon as possible.
Yes, sir.
Don't give him any time to rest.
Got it, sir.
Ma-ha, you did well with the movie.
Well done.
Thank you. You went through a lot
because you had to drive me
back and forth to the set.
It's nothing.
I wouldn't mind doing it every day.
That means you guys are growing.
Right?
And we were asked to do a photo shoot.
-Are you up for it, Hyun-ji?
-Me?
It's a fashion magazine called "V".
Eun-jin called for you herself.
I'm your boss,
but I respect your opinions.
I won't force you to do anything.
That's not the reason.
I'm not sure if I can pull it off.
You're the goddess of Tea Party.
What's wrong?
Our goddess needs to show
how one can pull off a style.
Like this.
Gosh, why are you going overboard
early in the morning?
I'm just upbeat
because Mr. Ji brewed the coffee for us.
What is this unsettling feeling
I'm having since yesterday?
I'll do it.
I'll give it a try.
Okay.
Oh, right.
Ha-seok wanted to see you, Ri-a.
I mean,
you want me to read all these
within this week?
You should read them fast
and decide already.
Isn't this too much?
I don't like forcing you either.
Mr. Park wants you to
start the next work fast.
Dae-gwon.
[♫ I love this, but don't faint,
this is a magical adventure ♫]
Don't get any ideas.
-What? What do you mean?
-Whatever it is!
-Turn it back on!
-Just keep reading the scripts.
♫ I'm your Tea Party ♫
Could you excuse us?
["The Return of the King"]
You kissed her for real
in the kissing scene.
You must've loved it.
Thank you for contributing
to the number of viewers.
I haven't seen it. I didn't want to
watch it after seeing the stills.
That's why I turned down the OST offer.
Did you think it was me
while shooting the scene?
Didn't you think of me
while shooting the scene with my copycat?
Stop it already.
This isn't any fun.
You keep calling her copycat.
Will you stop calling her that?
She's totally different.
Ma-ha is different
from you.
Should I
be happy with what you just said?
Yes, come in.
-Hello.
-Hi, Yu-jin.
-Hey, Hyun-ji.
-Yu-jin.
What? You guys know each other?
That's great.
Okay, we'll shoot your solo shots first,
-and you'll go next, Yu-jin.
-Okay.
Okay.
I love her movements.
All right!
Hyun-ji, change your outfit.
Yu-jin, get ready!
Hyun-ji, you look great.
Are you sure
this is your first photo shoot?
You were really good for a first-timer.
You're being too nice.
I like pretty girls, that's why.
It's Yu-jin's first time too,
and he's really good.
He's nice and well-mannered.
He has a nice personality too.
He takes good care of his friends.
I don't think
he's all that nice.
Seeing how he lashed out at Kwon Ryoc.
What? To Kwon Ryoc?
Did something happen to him?
I don't know either.
Who could've woken up the sleeping lion?
But then again, we'll have to see
who's the real lion.
Are you disappointed
that I called you to sing a guide?
It's not like that.
I'm willing to help you with anything.
-Don't think it's someone else's song.
-Sorry?
I don't ask just anyone to sing a guide.
You're giving life to the song
that hasn't been released into the world.
So that it could live long
with your voice.
I'd like to ask you to do mine.
I ended up hearing your private talk.
-When did you come?
-Just now.
Could you do mine too?
Really?
I-hyeon of SHAX wanted to work with you?
What did you say?
"So I guess SHAX is making
a girls' song too."
You're the best, Ri-a.
He must've been flustered.
Flustered, my foot.
He was flirting with me.
How dare he make a pass at me.
Anyway, you can't get involved with SHAX.
-It is them!
-No way.
It's them!
You're Tea Party, right?
-I was right!
-They're Tea Party.
We have no makeup on at all.
Could you turn around?
-Their faces are so small.
-They're so pretty.
You guys are so cool!
I've never seen a celebrity
in this town. This is incredible.
Celebrity?
You're Hyun-ji, right? And you're Ma-ha.
You're such a good singer!
You know all of our names too?
Thank you so much.
Could we take a photo with you?
-Photo?
-I don't think we can...
-Let's take one!
-Let's take it!
1, 2, 3!
We've totally become your fan
after watching your performance.
1, 2, 3!
My gosh, I can't believe
we're getting paid after three years.
I'm getting teary.
What should I buy? What should I get?
Should I get a new car
with 350 horsepower?
That's possible if you buy it
with 360 month-installment.
Why not? I could do that.
-Let's go out.
-To where?
-Today's our cheating day!
-Shall we?
Yu-jin, aren't you coming?
-Where's Hyeon-o?
-He's already out.
Let's go.
Bye, guys.
-Yes.
-Yes!
They called us a celebrity. Gosh.
We're a celebrity?
This is incredible.
We should've
put on some lipstick, at least.
Let's put it on and come back.
Yes, let's go get some cosmetics.
Hey, Yu-jin.
[What are you guys doing tonight?]
["Dancing You"]
On a dark street,
"his heart skips a beat
after seeing her in the distance."
[At the three-way intersection]
He can hear her heart beating.
[Inside a cafe with live singing]
She smiles as she dances.
"He wipes her tears,
and when they're about to kiss..."
[At the corner of a palace]
Slow down.
Did you forget? You're no match for me.
Block it! Go get the ball again.
-It's coming back again.
-That's mine.
-No, it's not.
-No.
-There you go!
-But you scored your own goal.
-That's a skill too.
-That's it.
-I'm blocking it.
Jae-u would say...
Ryoc, I'm saying this
as your team leader. Don't do it.
Don't do anything, and...
Yes! It's 2 to 0. Oh, is it 1 to 0?
-It's 1 to 1.
-I'm almost done. Let's do it.
-One...
-One more time.
Hyuk would say...
Fins! Hey, Fins!
You see, Ryoc...
-Yes, I'm very happy.
-Ryoc.
I can never share it with him.
Never in my life.
Why are you all up and down?
[I-hyeon?]
What? What do you want from me?
You take care of it.
Nice! It's 2 to 1.
One more point to go, Jae-u.
I can soon talk informally to you.
Look at you being cheeky.
Okay. I'm going to tell you something.
A keeps saying sorry to B and runs away.
And B pretends not to recognize who A is.
But A keeps appearing again.
B is annoyed by A,
but he can't help but care for A.
So A is B, and B is A.
Is this a math problem?
Do-jin, you're my only hope.
Please focus, and listen to me again.
-Okay?
-Okay.
Okay.
There's a close friend of mine.
He's my best friend. A really close one.
Your best friend?
But you don't have any friends except us.
Why you...
I do.
I have friends too.
Anyway, so what?
There's this girl he's known
for a long time.
She's like his younger sister to him.
But he met her again recently.
And she keeps appearing
in front of him whenever she wants.
So he's bothered by that.
He must like her!
No, it's not like that.
If he can't stop thinking about her,
that means he likes her.
No, that's not it.
He's just concerned about her.
Oh, right. He has something
to return to her too.
-Then call her.
-He doesn't know her number.
Oh, my gosh.
What's with him?
Tell him to get her number first.
Or wait, he can make use
of her social media account.
Socio medium.
-Social media.
Okay, thank you.
[Enter your keyword: Lee Ma-ha]
Lee Ma-ha.
[Results for Lee Ma-ha]
Why are there so many accounts?
Okay.
It won't fit.
Excuse me.
Do you have chargers for old phones?
Right in front of you.
That'll be 5,500 won.
Wait, are you Kwon Ryoc?
-Thank you.
-My gosh!
Can we walk slowly? Where are we going?
-Get your expectations up.
-What?
Ta-da.
Why are we eating dinner
at a place like this?
This place isn't for us.
It's a sudden boost in our social status.
It's not on me.
The tab is on someone else!
One second.
I don't know this number.
[Messages]
[Is this Lee Ma-ha's phone?]
Is this a spam message?
Really?
I heard many haters these days
contact you directly with your number.
Be careful.
I deleted it.
-Let's go!
-Let's do this.
[Is this Lee Ma-ha's phone?]
[Crow-tit]
Isn't this the right number?
I sent her this message ages ago.
Why won't she respond?
It has only been two minutes.
-Gosh.
-Look, a chandelier.
-It's pretty.
-Hello.
Hey.
-What's going on?
-Yu-jin!
What's going on? Your birthday?
It's not your birthday yet.
But celebrate as if it is.
I wanted to celebrate with you.
Celebrate what?
Wait, did you...
I balanced my account, then got paid.
-Really?
-Hey, Yu-jin.
The 1st payment in 3 years?
-Congrats, really.
-Thanks.
Everything is on me tonight.
You can order everything you want.
But still, you can't buy us dinner
at such an expensive place.
I'll save when I have to,
but I owe you something like this, right?
Hey, I'm touched.
If this is your first payment,
why are you celebrating with us,
not with your members?
Wait, in your group,
are you an outcast?
Ri-a, don't say that.
Come to think about it,
has my priority changed?
But I come before them
if you consider our trainee days.
Yes, I'm very proud of you.
And Yu-jin is a nice kid,
so everyone likes him.
Thanks.
When you insert expensive food,
you get compliments in return.
Do you see how hollow my cheeks are?
-Let's order already.
-Sorry.
Let's see.
May I order everything
in alphabetical order?
You better not regret this.
Why aren't you picking up?
It's the strange number from before.
It keeps calling me.
Is someone making a prank call?
Whatever.
-Let's order.
-Yes, let's order already.
My gosh!
This is so annoying.
Do I really have the wrong number?
[Is this Lee Ma-ha's phone?]
Right, how was the first shoot?
It was the first time
Hyun-ji and I were on set,
but we were at ease,
and I think it's because we're friends.
I must've been at ease too.
Time flew by
even though we were on set all day.
I'm glad.
Great work.
[You don't want the gift pack?]
I need to use the restroom.
I knew it.
Don't be impatient, Ryoc.
Stay cool.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Four?
No way.
Ma-ha.
I'm sorry, Ryoc.
-I thought it was a spam message.
-Spam?
But
how did you get my number?
It's the same as before.
[-Your number.]
-Right.
Ryoc, I'd like to have
the gift pack returned to me.
Where are you?
Tell me where you are.
I'll bring it to you.
No, you can have it delivered to me.
Right.
A delivery service.
Fine.
By any chance,
did you open
that gift pack?
Hey.
Do you think I'm someone who opens
and looks at other people's stuff?
No, never. That's not what I meant.
Forget it.
-Give me your address.
-Sorry?
You wanted it delivered.
Yes, I'll text it to you.
Okay.
[It's 6-2 Jeonghyun-ro 82-gil...]
How did she know?
[It's 6-2 Jeonghyun-ro 82-gil,
Gwangdong-gu, Seoul.]
[Crow-tit]
Crow-tit.
[Kwon Ryoc]
[Save number]
[When are we going to meet?]
[NOG Entertainment]
You always say that.
One second.
-Is she dating someone?
-My gosh.
That used to be unimaginable.
Date while you can.
You'll soon miss those days.
-Jealous?
-Jealous of what?
If you wanted to date anybody,
you should've done it as a trainee.
I was in the practice room
around the clock.
Right? You were like a zombie. Gosh.
So? Do you regret it?
No.
If I did that, SHAX wouldn't be here.
Exactly!
That's what I, Dae-gwon, want to say
as the manager of SHAX.
You and I both
have never dated anyone anyway,
so let's just keep running.
Let's date after you retire.
That again?
Don't put us in the same category.
Okay. I'll retire as a manager
when you retire.
So you can date then. Okay, Ryoc?
Let me go.
It must be tough to read
the scenarios and scripts,
so sweat it out!
Stay relentless, Dae-gwon. Gu Dae-gwon!
Yes, it's on me.
[Really?]
Of course.
I'll meet you at the same place.
[Okay.]
Bye, then.
[Search for: Crow-tit]
[Results for Crow-tit]
[Search for: Lee Ma-ha]
[Results for Lee Ma-ha]
["Tea Party's Lee Ma-ha
cast for 'Nangrangbihwa'!"]
[Crow-tit]
[What are you up to?]
What is this? Why won't she respond?
[Are you working today?]
["Nangrangbihwa"]
[What about tomorrow?
What's on your schedule?]
[Any plans?]
[Kwon Ryoc]
[No promotions?]
Why is he suddenly doing this?
Just send me the parcel already.
[Kwon Ryoc]
Should I at least respond?
Could he... No, right?
["Nangrangbihwa"]
What? I thought you went back
to your dorm to get some rest.
I guess I'm not the type who can rest.
Sounds great.
I need to talk to you.
All right. What's up?
The math problem isn't finished?
-Well, B got in touch with A.
-And?
-But A has been ghosting B.
-What?
What's that?
Goodness. What are A and B?
Well.
-A is some girl.
-Some girl?
And B is
-Ryoc's friend.
-What?
You have a friend?
Well, it's...
Ryoc, you like someone, don't you?
Are you crazy? Me? Like someone?
Calm down.
So what's the problem with this "friend"?
He worked with my advice
and found her number,
but she only responded back once.
I don't know how I should...
He doesn't.
It's tough.
This is why images are far from reality.
At times like these,
I can tell how bad you're at dating.
You don't even know how you feel.
Stop it already with A and B.
-Did you talk to her on the phone?
-Yes.
Yes?
-He did.
-Then what's the problem?
-Get started.
-How? What now?
-I have nothing to say to her.
-What do you mean?
Show her how you feel.
-How I feel?
-Ryoc.
When Do-jin plays soccer games,
he only dribbles the ball.
When did I do that?
I'm a total striker. Shoot, shoot, shoot.
When will you shoot
instead of dribbling all the time?
You have to shoot to score.
Hey!
Ryoc is going to sleep tight tonight.
I need to take him back to his dorm.
What? The car key.
Where's the car key? The key.
Where's the car key? Darn it.
[You have arrived at your destination.]
[-Road navigation completed.]
-What?
Where does she live?
Why can't I drive any further?
Hey.
Ma-ha!
[Epilogue]
[NOG Entertainment, Ji-hak]
I don't want to be an idol star.
Not interested.
It's your chance
to do something you like for life
without worrying.
-Hello.
He's a new member.
Say hi to him. And be nice.
Hello.
What is this?
He didn't even say goodbye.