[Episode 7]
One, two, three.
-Let's do it!
-Okay!
-We're all ready.
Let's go.
Go all the way back.
Ryoc!
-He's here! Down here!
-Ryoc!
-Get an ambulance!
-Hurry up.
-Call 119!
Ryoc, wake up!
-Ryoc, wake up!
-Ryoc!
-Get him out of there.
-Ryoc?
-Somebody call an ambulance!
-Ryoc!
-Get an ambulance!
Call 119!
-Please wake up.
-Ryoc, wake up!
-Oh, no!
-Ryoc!
Please wake up.
-Over here.
-Please hurry.
Please hurry over.
-Just a second.
-Ryoc!
-Ryoc?
[Ambulance]
Ryoc, stay with me.
Please wake up.
Ryoc, wake up.
Ryoc...
Ryoc, please wake up.
Stay with me.
[Caution, Fall Hazard]
Please wake up.
[Waiting Room]
Ryoc...
Ryoc, please wake up.
[Caution, Fall Hazard]
Ryoc...
Oh, no.
Please stay with me.
[Emergency Medical Center]
Why aren't they coming out?
-Can you see anything?
-No.
It hasn't been reported yet.
This is frustrating.
It's not like we can go in there.
What if it's bad?
Although I'm sure that won't be the case.
Ma-ha, if anything happens,
it'll blow up online first.
I see you lead a double life.
I doubt you came all this way for coffee.
Before, you told me
to follow the traces lying around.
I did and they led me here.
How am I doing?
Eun-jo's back in Korea, isn't he?
-Where is he right now?
-You're barking up the wrong tree.
To know about Eun-jo,
you'll have better luck
with NOG's CEO Park.
Don't be like that.
CEO Park only cared about
the revenue SHAX brought in.
Back then, you were the man
who knew everything about the boys' lives.
Seriously?
[Reporter Nam Joo-tae]
I'm busy, can't this wait--
[Byun, Kwon Ryoc of SHAX
was in an accident.]
[His car flipped while filming.]
-What?
[-I thought you should]
[be the first to know.]
Is it serious?
[I don't know.
NOG is trying to put a lid on it.]
Darn it.
That'll be all for today.
I have somewhere to be.
Which hospital is it?
[H Cafe]
A hospital?
[Breaking News:
"Kwon Ryoc's Car Flips on Set"]
[H Cafe]
[Incoming Call, Unknown Number]
This is Ji-hak.
[Sir.]
Eun-jo?
A stunt double was on standby.
So why did he do something unnecessary?
It wasn't a difficult scene,
so Ryoc volunteered to--
Seriously?
-Does he look like Tom Cruise to you?
-I'm sorry, sir.
Don't you know
how much he brings in for us?
What will you do
if he gets a scar on his face?
I'm sorry, sir.
Do your job better, darn it.
Yes, sir.
Keep a tight lid on it until tomorrow
and come up with a decent press release.
His passion and love for the movie.
-You know the drill.
-Yes, sir.
And you...
[Ji-hak]
Mr. Ji?
Mr. Park, wait!
How's Ryoc doing?
I'm Byun Jeong-hui with "Fact Check".
Fact Check?
That sure was fast.
I don't know the details yet though.
-Let's go.
-Yes, sir.
But...
I guess it's not that serious.
-Why isn't he waking up?
-The doctor said he's fine.
There isn't anything wrong
with him physically.
That's what the doctor said,
so he'll be fine.
-We should give him some space.
-Sure.
How's Ryoc?
His injuries aren't severe.
Still, anything can happen
with car accidents.
Darn those trash journalists.
How packed was his schedule?
He's not one to make mistakes,
so the reason is obvious.
How many hours...
Did you even let him sleep?
-Well--
-At least be humane.
Anyway, I'm glad I got to see him.
[Nchicks Chicken]
Here you go.
Let me see.
-That'll be 135,000 won.
-Thank you.
Enjoy!
[Breaking News:
"Kwon Ryoc's Car Flips on Set"]
Are you really taking a pass?
Eat your fill, guys.
We'll eat quickly to minimize the smell.
Yu-jin's filming all night.
Tae-geun won't be back for hours.
Okay.
-Where's Tae-geun?
-He dropped me off and left.
So much for Mr. Movie Star
filming all night.
You're home early.
Because of Kwon Ryoc's accident, right?
-Accident?
He must've thought he could do the stunt.
It's always all or nothing with him.
How can you say that when a man's injured?
Unbelievable.
I'm just saying
you should watch your mouth.
Didn't you get in his face once?
I get it now. Working on set with him
must've formed a camaraderie.
That's enough.
Yu-jin's probably shocked about it.
I'm glad it wasn't you.
Let's not waste energy over this.
-Ryoc!
-Call 119!
Hey, Ma-ha.
Didn't you hear any news from the staff?
If you do, please let me know.
What did he say?
Ma-ha, there's nothing you can do here.
The entrance is crawling with his fans.
Do you have it in you
to march boldly in there like La Ri-ma?
I want to stay until he wakes up though.
You guys can leave.
Your ears are red
and your lips are blue from the cold.
You'll end up in the hospital yourself.
Ma-ha, it's the first day of filming
for the sitcom tomorrow.
Let's head home.
If you stay, we'll have to stay too.
We won't leave you here alone,
so what will it be?
It's La Ri-ma!
-La Ri-ma!
-La Ri-ma, what did you see?
-La Ri-ma, did you hear anything?
What on earth is she doing here?
La Ri-ma!
-Wait!
-La Ri-ma!
[Jangyeon University Hospital]
I-hyeon.
Right. I must've dozed off.
-The others?
-They already left for work.
How's Ryoc doing?
The doctor says he's fine,
so we'll have to wait and see.
I'm glad.
-We should go too.
-Sure.
Dae-gwon, we're leaving too.
I'm sorry, Ryoc.
I shouldn't have
sent you to the countryside.
I shouldn't have pushed this movie on you.
That was a rash decision on my end.
You wanted some time to think,
but I forced it upon you.
I caused this accident.
I'll do anything you ask of me now,
so please wake up.
You promised.
Yes, I'll do anything for you.
Promise?
What?
You promised to let me do anything.
I slept like a log.
Making up for lost sleep
made me a new man.
Hold on.
-Were you crying?
-As if.
I could've picked you up.
Why? Is something up?
-No.
-Of course not.
We're here to wish her luck
on the new sitcom.
Ma-ha, good luck on your first day.
Good luck.
You look...
Didn't you get much sleep?
I got nervous
about the first day of filming today.
You need to watch your health.
I'm sorry.
Get some shut-eye on the way there.
Sure.
[KBC]
All right. Ma-ha will dance,
and you'll look at her as if she's a joke.
Let's try that.
No, not like that. Make it look funny.
How else can they react to it?
Okay. Good, right?
That's the end of rehearsal.
Filming will start at 2 p.m. after lunch.
I can't believe
they just changed up the scene.
Whatever. Let's go.
Wait.
Is he all right?
Yes, I'm always good. No problem.
I think she's asking about Ryoc.
Is it bad? How is he doing?
You don't need to worry.
Read the articles later.
How can I not worry?
How can I not worry when he's injured?
Okay, okay.
Dae-gwon? Why are you here?
-How's Ryoc?
-He's awake.
What a relief.
Wait. Are you looking for someone?
Is Lee Ma-ha done for the day?
Ma-ha? Why are you asking?
Get out of the way. Ji-hak!
Hey, Dae-gwon.
Oh, hi.
I'm sorry to ask, but I need two hours.
What do you mean?
The articles say
that he's still unconscious,
but his teammates say he's fine.
I want to see if he's all right
with my own eyes.
We just found Person A, right?
Uh-huh.
Go ahead.
Peekaboo.
Dae-gwon, what's the plan?
-What are you doing here?
-Off we go to the hospital.
-They're here.
-Over there!
-There.
-They're here.
The door's opening!
-Look.
-Over there!
Over here!
-Any news?
-How's Ryoc?
-Wait!
-Do you have any news?
-Seriously?
-Come on!
You have ten minutes
to check on his well-being.
How should I be when she gets here?
I'll lie in bed,
look like I'm in pain,
and get up slowly.
She'll then ask if I'm all right.
"My injuries are minor
despite the severity of the accident."
You were worried, weren't you?
Thank you for being here.
Ryoc...
You said you weren't badly hurt!
Why are you lying on the bed like this?
I didn't even get to say what I want.
Actually, I've been your fan
for a long time.
When my manager ditched me,
I wasn't cold at all
because you walked with me!
When you asked me
if the only thing I could do
is copying La Ri-ma,
I didn't feel resentful.
You were the one who held my hand.
You danced with me.
So please get up soon.
You need to give me my gift pack.
I wanted to see you again,
so I hoped our kissing scene
would be picked as the best scene.
I like you.
I really like you.
Do you really mean it?
-Do you mean it?
-Ryoc.
What I mean is...
I meant...
Take a deep breath.
You just need to hold your breath
and block your ears.
Just as you wanted to
return my padded jacket yourself,
I wanted to return
the gift package myself.
I like you too, Lee Ma-ha.
I also wanted this scene
to be picked as the best one.
During the shoot,
he got into a car accident.
He was sent to the emergency room
and proper care was given.
We, the SHAX members,
will be with him as he recovers.
So please refrain from writing
speculative articles
so that he can rest and fully recover.
How is his condition?
-Did he wake up?
-Is he conscious?
We'll wrap up the interview here.
-Please tell us more!
-Thank you.
-Wait!
-Hey!
-Don't go!
[Incoming Call, Unknown Number]
-Hello?
-Did you get home safely?
Yes... Yes.
I miss you already.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Hello?
Hello? Ma-ha.
I said I miss you.
Me too.
It's so late already.
You should get some rest!
So cute.
Ri-a.
-Why are you still up?
-Lee Ma-ha.
I thought you'd drop dead,
but now you're full of energy.
What do you mean?
I can tell from your blushed face.
What do you mean? Don't be ridiculous.
You met him, didn't you?
-I'm sorry.
-You did? Why?
Why did you meet him alone?
My gosh. Are you out of your mind?
It's not like that.
-We...
-"We"?
We as in you and Kwon Ryoc?
We?
I mean, I...
I mean, he...
How are you going to handle this alone?
There's definitely something going on
with you and Kwon Ryoc.
That's not true. We're just...
Are you going to tell Hyun-ji?
Ri-a, your eyes are bloodshot.
You must be tired.
It must be really late right now.
-Hey.
-What?
What's this smell?
I bought a new jacket, that's what.
Go to bed now!
Lie down already! I'm going to wash up.
You should sleep first.
Mission complete. I kept my word, Ryoc.
I don't think I can ever do it again.
-It should end with Ryoc.
-Of course.
Don't look at him.
We can never be caught by Mr. Park.
This all depends on you, okay?
We should keep this to ourselves.
The more people know,
the faster the story spreads.
Gather up.
Don't look!
Good morning!
Welcome.
Excuse me. Who are you?
I'm a part-timer.
Oh, he finally hired one.
-It's nice to meet you. I'm...
-Would you like to order?
One vanilla latte, please.
-That'd be 5,900 won.
-Pardon?
Oh, I'm a member of Tea Party.
We are JH Entertainment's artists.
Tea Party.
I'm a part-timer of Cafe H.
I don't know what Tea Party is.
The vanilla latte of Cafe H is 5,900 won.
Would you like to have it?
Ma-ha.
She won't budge.
-Mr. Ji.
You need to pay.
I did too.
Can you put it on my tab?
All right. Now that we have
a reliable part-timer,
I'll get back to my work.
I'm going home.
-No!
-Why not?
There's an order to everything.
I'm fine. I'm totally fine.
I'm worried about the movie schedule,
and I feel heavy lying in bed all day.
I feel like I have to get back to work.
I can see through you.
Do you think I don't know
why you're doing this?
We released articles about you,
so you need to stay right here.
Come on.
You should get some rest
when you have a chance.
I'm getting out of here!
Darn it.
No.
Let go.
I can't let you go!
Do not get in my way.
-Please!
-I am not going back!
There's an order to everything,
you crazy punk!
I know accidents can't be prevented,
but you need to take better care
of your team.
Of course. I'm sorry, Mr. Park.
Dae-gwon is managing him,
but he's too softhearted.
So I can't trust him entirely.
Of course.
[CEO Park Jin-man]
Jae-u, you're not in the same position
as Ryoc.
You know that, right?
Yes, I know it very well.
Okay.
Make sure to do your job
as the leader of the team.
If anything happens, report it right away.
I'll make sure
you'll have nothing to worry about.
Okay.
Hold on.
[Gu Dae-gwon]
[CEO Park Jin-man]
Hey.
He can't get back to work
just within a day!
Get your head straight,
and keep him in the hospital, got it?
I can't believe
I'm working with these people.
How did it go?
I've arranged it.
[Crow-tit]
[What are you doing?]
[They told me I need to rest,
so I'm still at the hospital.]
[Don't worry.
I'm being discharged in two days.]
[Ma-ha, just hang in there
for two more days.]
[I'm on my way to work.
You must be suffocated there.]
[Star Is Born]
[Just think that you're getting rested
and hang in there.]
[Cheer up!]
Did you memorize the lines?
Yes, I memorized every single line.
How about the dance?
I'm going to give it my all.
You're thoroughly prepared,
but I'm worried.
I just hope you won't show it.
There are many eyes on you.
I'll make sure to be careful.
Ma-ha.
I don't intend on meddling in.
But
make sure to keep this in mind.
You're the most precious person.
Don't forget that no matter what happens.
You should care for yourself
more than your feelings toward him.
Yes, I will.
Gosh, you're so mean. Fine! I won't look.
Isn't it cute?
[Cheer up!]
You're showing off to me
when I've never dated anyone?
How should I reply to her?
What's the issue?
I'm frustrated because
you're the only one in this room.
Here. She sent a heart emoji.
What should I send her?
Aren't they all the same?
They all look the same to me.
I was a fool for asking your advice.
-Just send her this
-What are you doing?
There. You sent it.
Gosh. No wonder he's never dated anyone.
Hey!
What do I do?
[Star Is Born]
Ma-ha.
That was from Ryoc, right?
You guys are moving really fast.
Don't forget what we did for you. Okay?
Of course not.
Thank you.
From now, if you find
anything about him frustrating,
you can look for us anytime.
Knock on our door.
He's rather child--
He's a romantic.
Yes, he is. That's right.
-Right? A romantic.
-Yes.
Okay. Then I will
knock on your door from time to time.
Sure. Anytime.
He's a romantic.
[Byun Jeong-hui]
He's getting released today.
[Press release]
NOG wants us to release this
at the right time.
I knew he was fine all along.
[Press release]
["Ryoc Shows Great Acting
Despite His Injury"]
Let's go inside. We're home.
Guys!
-Hi.
-Good work today.
Thanks.
Why that... Gosh.
He nearly died from the accident.
You brats.
It's okay. They must be tired too.
Okay. You should go inside and rest.
Gosh, that startled me!
[Welcome back home!]
[From Do-jin]
[From I-hyeon]
[Stop making us worry. Welcome back home.]
When did they prepare all this?
[Don't get sick!]
[From Hyuk]
[From Jae-u]
[Don't get hurt anymore.
I'm sorry for everything.]
[Always take good care of yourself.]
I take my word back!
-It's Ryoc.
-Ryoc!
[Ryoc! We wish the best for you!]
Ryoc...
-Ryoc!
-Ryoc, are you okay?
Are you hurt?
-Ryoc! This is for you!
-Thank you.
What's this? He really got hurt!
Guys, step back! Line up now.
Well...
It's...
Thank you so much for worrying about me,
but I'm actually
fine.
I'm okay.
So... Let's do this!
Let's do this, everyone.
Let's do this.
-What was that?
-Was he badly hurt in the head?
What about his head?
Darn it. What's this unsettling feeling?
Let's do this?
Say that for yourself.
You look like a crazy man.
I told you to keep a poker face.
Okay, I'm sorry. Please stop nagging.
-It's driving me crazy.
-Fine.
Are you feeling better?
Yes, I'm fine.
Hey, congrats!
I don't think you can do as you wish
just because you're our senior.
Hold on, Dae-gwon.
Wait.
Do you like Ma-ha?
No, I used to like her.
Ma-ha and I are old friends.
Friends?
I've also known her for a long time.
I'm just a friend to her.
Although that wasn't the case for me.
That's why I'm trying to forget her.
But
I'm planning to stay next to her
as a friend for a long time.
What?
I'm saying
you shouldn't let your guard down.
You looked too relaxed, so...
Wow, it's great.
Hey.
Did you think about what I said last time?
-No.
-Why not?
I thought I wouldn't need to.
So what's the reason?
I thought I already said
I don't want to get involved with SHAX.
Let's call it a day.
Okay, sure.
Wait.
Then think of it
as doing it with me alone, not SHAX.
What?
Just give it some thought.
She won't let her guard down.
Ha-seok.
Something that feels like this moment.
You know, it's...
You have no idea.
Careful, Ryoc.
You must be tired. Get some sleep.
-Dae-gwon.
-What now?
Fine.
I'd rather let you borrow my wife
before I let you drive my car.
You aren't married.
Ryoc, be gentle.
Don't let it get scratched, okay?
Be gentle.
Buckle up.
Okay.
Let's go.
It's our first date.
This is it. An unoccupied and quiet place.
Yes, it's quiet.
But
they take photos from across the river.
The river?
From across the river?
Crow-tit.
It's time for us to kiss.
Goodness.
I'd love to.
What?
No.
This is it.
This is supposed to be
the most popular dating spot.
Yes, it does look quite popular.
Isn't it great to drive around?
Yes, but the view is the same.
[-Aren't I a great driver?
-You're great at turning corners.]
[Ryoc, do you have any medicine
for motion sickness?]
You jumped out in excitement,
so why did you return depressed?
You're so unpredictable.
You have an ad shooting, so get rested.
I'll be back at 6 a.m.
Okay.
Be on time. Make yourself presentable.
I won't let you off twice for being sick.
Bye.
Gosh.
It's not easy, is it?
No, it can't be that easy.
Dae-gwon has his eyes on you,
and you got nowhere to go and no time.
You get all excited,
then your bubble gets popped.
We had nowhere to go,
so I drove for two hours.
Did you go to the Han River?
Don't ever go there. No way.
You know that people wait there
around the clock, right?
I do, so I didn't go there.
How about an arboretum?
-It's quiet and...
-No.
An actor couple was
filmed there last week.
People know about it already.
Wait, so you just went round and round
on your first date?
Round and round?
-Want some tips?
-Want some?
Do you want help from the experts?
March forward, my man.
-March forward.
-Yes.
-What are you so happy about?
-My gosh.
What's going on?
-What?
-Is something troubling you?
Tell me. I'm ready to hear you out.
Well, the thing is this.
There are A and B.
-One second.
-What?
-Go with C and D.
-Why?
A and B already had a happy ending.
Go with C and D.
Okay, fine.
Now, there are C and D.
But C keeps getting angry
and annoyed at D.
But D doesn't hate it.
Things don't work out, right?
D gets concerned.
Yes. You're right.
So what now?
Hey, Dae-gwon.
Can you pick me up at 5 a.m. tomorrow?
Be here on time.
[What? Why 5 a.m.?]
No, never mind. Make it 4.
See you at 4 a.m.
[Is this some kind of show?]
You have to come. Be here on time!
[You crazy punk!]
[Star Is Born]
Hello?
Why did you
suddenly call me out at this hour?
What if someone sees us?
Like who?
Did you put makeup on?
I thought someone might see us.
Gosh, you might start rolling
once I tap on you.
Right?
I'm glad I got to see you.
I need to go now.
-What?
-I have a shoot.
We have to go. We'll be late.
Bye, then.
I get it.
Hurry up and go. Just go.
We're late. Just go.
We have to go. We're late. Go.
Gosh, one second, please.
I can't seem to get excited.
Hey.
[Nchicks Chicken]
-He's not here yet?
-No, not yet.
I thought I was in this with Ryoc.
Hello.
I know you were hospitalized,
but you should still be on time.
What should I say?
Miss you. I miss you.
-What's going on?
-What is?
Who changed you like this?
Are you dating someone?
Silence means yes, right?
-You're right.
-Who is she?
I couldn't tell you that.
Ryoc. Goodness.
Since when has he been dating Ma-ha?
Sorry?
Hey, I told you not to tell her.
-Do you think I did?
-Bingo.
My gut feelings are always right.
Oh.
Well, please keep this a secret. Please.
I thought you'd come and be with me.
This is pretty shocking.
If I wait, will you come to me?
-I'm not just playing.
-I'm not playing either.
Please keep this a secret.
Please don't tell anybody.
Okay.
Ryoc.
Erase that smile.
You obviously seem like you're dating.
-Hey, that was my fault, right?
-No, I think it was mine.
Was it that obvious?
What's wrong?
I don't want to be in a shoot today.
Let's get started.
[Tea Party]
If I act more like Ma-ha,
will he show me a smile too?
[Star Is Born]
[What time do you get off?
I'm still on set.]
[I guess we can't meet today.]
-Ma-ha, they're ready for the next scene.
-Okay.
Now, eat up.
You should eat.
You're on a diet anyway,
so just eat and continue.
Use this as a motivation.
-Take a seat.
-Ri-ma.
Thank you for the thought,
but what if the agency finds out?
It's fine as long as I bought these.
They aren't going to get mad. Take a seat.
Then I'll sit.
I've been starving all day.
Ri-ma, aren't you going to eat?
I'm not in your position.
-Then thank you for the food.
-Thank you.
Ma-ha!
It's way too late.
I miss him.
Then you can see me.
How did you know...
Hyuk said you were done shooting,
so I knew you'd come home.
This time, don't run away.
What do you think?
Wait, you aren't
taking a big breath anymore.
You sounded very shy on the phone.
You'll have to take many big breaths
in the days to come.
Where are we?
Just follow me.
Mask up.
Really?
That's Kim Ji-min.
Ignore everyone you see.
It smells good and tastes good.
I'm having coffee
with Kwon Ryoc of SHAX this late at night.
[The star that shined brightly
far off in the darkness]
[sat next to me and shined by the dawn.]
[To Lee Ma-ha]
[Epilogue]
Gosh, it's so hot.
Where did he hide it?
Goodness, it's so dirty.
["Nangrangbihwa"]
Found it. It's your heart, Crow-tit.
[Star Is Born]
[My star, Kwon Ryoc.]
[Be a hit, "Nangrangbihwa"!]