(Lovers of the Red Sky)
Due to the Demon's temptation,
so many people had to shed their blood.
I gained more power as the king,
but karma was always there to haunt me.
I will take on all the karma.
I want you to seal the Demon
and do your best to avoid...
the consequences.
I will do as you say, Father.
Have you found traces of the Demon?
It has disappeared.
The Demon...
never dies.
Sealing it is the only way...
Father!
Restore the king's portrait as soon as possible...
so that we can seal the Demon once again.
Yes, Your Majesty.
But before we do that,
we must find an artist who can restore the portrait.
An artist who can portray divinity...
so that the spirit of the Demon can be sealed.
I am talking about artists like Gan Yong Guk and Hong Eun O.
Find me an artist...
no matter what.
Yes, Your Majesty.
(Episode 2: The Divine Artist)
(Baekyu Painters Society)
(19 years later, 31st year of King Seongjo)
- Look. - Goodness.
Let us go see.
How beautiful.
Gosh, my heart is fluttering.
My heart beats so fast just by watching.
If your heart beats that fast just by looking at a painting,
you should go see a doctor.
- Hello. - I am sorry.
Hurry.
Among many different types of Sehwa paintings,
let us learn about "The Old Man of the South Pole."
What is most important when it comes to Sehwa paintings?
Obviously to finish it by the due date.
Otherwise, no one will buy it.
- She is right. - That is correct.
She has a point.
Finishing it quickly...
is not the most important thing when it comes to Sehwa paintings.
How short this man is. The deer he is riding.
The protruding head.
You must portray these exact characteristics.
That is how you form a lucky omen.
You made an excellent choice by hiring him...
as today's lecturer.
Choi Jung, a painter from Gohwawon,
came here to teach them himself.
No lecture would be better for the painters.
My goodness.
You fool.
You need to do more than just copy the paintings.
When it comes to Sehwa paintings, it is most important...
to use clear colours and portray joy in the paintings.
In other words, you must portray people's longing desire...
to be blessed with luck, joy,
happiness, and beauty.
She really is something.
Painter Hong, if you are done,
stop causing trouble and just leave.
I was going to leave.
- Master Choi. - Gosh, you startled me.
Uncle Chun Bok, here you go.
I need to go somewhere. I will be right back.
Where are you going at this hour, young lady?
Where is she going every night?
Probably to the market to meet Hong Eun O.
Chun Bok, do you know something?
Do you know how long she has been taking care of her father?
Yes, 20 years.
You already told me dozens of times.
So you do not need to remind me...
She was just a little girl...
who couldn't see a thing.
One rainy day, her vision returned...
and told me she needs to make money to take care of her father.
She asked me to teach her how to paint...
and said she will chop firewood and do the dishes.
The skies must have been touched by her filial devotion...
and gave her sight back.
And just like her father,
she not only quickly learned how to paint,
but she was also very talented.
I could not help but care for...
her.
Look at how handsome he is.
There is more to him than that. He is also a gentleman.
I heard he is favoured by His Majesty.
Look at him glow.
What is going on? What is all the fuss about?
You know why.
Scholar Ha is on duty tonight.
But then again, even I think...
he is as handsome as I am.
At the end of the day, he is blind. They are unbelievable.
- By the way, - Yes?
I heard Scholar Ha was the helper...
of the rain making ritual that took place 19 years ago.
Yes.
Did he really lose his sight that day?
Yes, that is correct.
That was when it finally rained in nine years.
Is that why he is called the guarding spirit of this place?
What are you talking about?
He is nothing but a freak.
Scholar Ha is here.
Hello, Scholar Ha.
- Hello. - Hello.
Let us begin the observation.
We will begin with the Vermilion Bird of the South.
- Yes. - Yes.
Let us begin the observation.
The fifth star is extremely bright today.
Someone special will come from the east.
Who are you people?
You are here.
They are my pals. Come on in.
- What took you so long? - I am sorry.
The swirling clouds surrounding the peak of the mountain.
The pointy pine tree branches.
Is this...
the original painting?
You really do have an eye for art.
I guess Wolseongdang really does buy and sell rare artwork.
What would happen if it gets torn...
Stop.
Do not even touch it. It is worth four houses.
What? Four houses?
I am finally done.
Hey, take a look. What do you think?
You really are talented.
You actually copied that.
You made it look just like the original copy.
What are the virtues of making imitations?
First, copy the techniques.
Second, portray the energy in the original work.
Third, it needs to be exactly the same.
Will you stop being so arrogant?
Okay, fine.
I bet you my precious brush...
that not even Prince Yangmyeong, the lover of arts,
will not be able to notice that mine is an imitation.
Really?
My gosh, why did they have to build the storage here?
I will never come back here again.
Did you guys ever hear about...
the owner of Wolseongdang?
Ilwolseong?
He is known to be the richest man in Guanyang.
The most famous merchant in this country.
That makes sense seeing that he was able to buy "Sochundo."
That is not all.
There are tons of original artworks in Wolseongdang.
You are right.
There is another big secret.
If you write a question...
and put it inside the box in front of Wolseongdang,
Ilwolseong writes you back...
saying you will have to pay a price for the answer.
In other words, Ilwolseong is an informant...
who knows everything.
But you must be careful.
Apparently, no one has ever seen his face.
He speaks from an adjoining room,
and you can only hear his voice...
that does not sound like it belongs to a human.
And they say whoever sees his face...
will get beheaded.
You and that darn mouth of yours.
Do not believe him. Half of what he says is a lie.
What? Does that mean you believe me half of the time?
Unfortunately, I am not even interested in the other half.
Ilwolseong?
Hey, wait up.
Yoo Si Hong, the younger brother of Yeon's emperor,
is coming here as a messenger?
That is unusual.
Is there a special reason why...
you chose to work at Jangwangjang today?
According to the stars last night,
someone special will come today from the east.
The entrance of Jangwangjang is facing the east.
Can you guess whom it might be?
I am not sure.
I wonder whom that special person will be.
Hello.
Jung, are you there?
Goodness, look who is here. It is Painter Hong.
I would like to get paid first.
First, let me take a look at the painting.
It is hard to tell which one is the original copy.
This is why I like you.
How should I put it? You have no pride as a painter.
They both look exactly the same.
Is that a compliment?
It is a great compliment.
Most painters who draw imitations...
try very hard to leave a trace of their identity.
They are not even an aristocrat.
Those painters also think of imitations as their work.
I did not know that.
Here you go.
Let me check.
It is the right amount.
What is this?
It is my gesture of gratitude.
Gosh, why are you acting like you are going to quit?
That is right. I have earned enough money for my father's medicine.
Thus, that is going to be my last imitation.
Keep quiet about all my works as you have promised.
You are quitting?
Well, okay.
Painter Hong.
Drawing imitations is very hard to quit.
It is like a drug.
What is with you guys?
What is with us?
Do you really not know?
We favoured you and treated you like a real painter,
and that must have caused you to become arrogant.
Let me see.
I cannot hurt your wrist.
Are you threatening me?
Have you forgotten who I am?
Of course not. You are the only female painter in this city.
The only female of the Baekyu Painters Society.
What do you think this will do to the reputation of Wolseongdang...
that is known to be the best art studio?
What? Are you going to cut me with that?
Go ahead.
Wait.
Here is my wrist.
You are bolder than most men.
You are wiser than most men.
Leave before I change my mind.
You had better not change your mind.
What are you doing?
Is there someone here?
What is with you? I told you to leave.
Do not talk nonsense and just go.
Okay.
I will be off now. Thank you for everything.
Goodbye to you too.
Are you really going to let her leave?
Just get ready to go to the capital city.
The lord in Bukchon-Ri is waiting for us.
Do not get it mixed with the original artwork.
Goodness, the colour is so beautiful.
Do you see that?
This colour comes from a turtle that lived for 10,000 years.
A turtle with a gold shell and a yellow neck.
It is a medicine that was made with a 10,000-year-old ingredient.
Unless it's a real 10,000-year gold turtle pill,
it can't be this colour.
Okay.
I like it.
If you take just one of these pills,
from the moment you take it, its effects...
slowly start to show.
Is that true? That's it, then.
I can finally cure my dad's madness.
No, it's fine. No discounts.
You'll jinx the medicine.
I won't haggle. 50 Yang.
Fights should be stopped and deals should be made.
No, I want to take this pill with its effects and everything.
Here you go.
Fifty Yang of silver.
You can check.
- I'll go, then. - Sure.
Thank you.
- Come and take a look! - Take a look!
Dad, it's me, Cheon Gi.
Cheon Gi?
My Cheon Gi's still a baby.
Today's work looks pretty good.
Can you draw me?
Of course.
Mister, since yesterday,
you only made hoes, sickles, and plows, didn't you?
I hear round, low sounds like my hands.
Do you know how much I looked for you?
I told you where I'd be.
Did you forget again, Dad?
What?
Your drawings are really nice.
To pay you for the drawing,
I will give you this.
Open your mouth.
What are you doing?
My Cheon Gi will be hungry too.
I didn't give her much for breakfast.
I brought more than enough food.
You can eat it all.
Dad.
I also have...
something very precious.
What's that?
Eat this too.
When you eat this, you must smell it first,
and then taste it when it's in your mouth.
You must savour it twice.
Here.
What is this?
It's my everything.
I hope you can say, "Hong Cheon Gi, my daughter,"
and hold my brush with me like before.
And scold me not to paint copies again.
I'd like you to tell me that painting without heart...
is of no use.
What a smell.
She didn't catch on, did she?
She's a very bright kid.
We made sure she didn't notice a thing.
Here.
- Let's go. - Wait.
Please, can I have the deeds to my home back?
The house was in my family for three generations.
Who told you to offer a human sacrifice?
I did it on my own.
Kill me if you must, Your Majesty.
It wouldn't have rained if not for the human sacrifice.
The public would've resented it even more,
and the government would've been in distress.
Am I wrong, Your Majesty?
It rained,
so I will spare you your life.
As soon as day breaks,
you are to leave the Palace.
And...
never return even in death.
Your Majesty, I pray for your health.
The Prince has come to see you.
It seems like it was just yesterday...
that you came to me after Father sent you away.
That was 20 years ago already.
You haven't forgotten your vow, have you?
How could I?
That day,
I said I did not find you.
I said the heavens had picked you.
Yes. When will that time come?
The undying.
When you accept the power of the Demon who presides over death,
then your time will come.
How many years have you been saying that?
Compared to the deities, humans live just for a moment.
Their time flows unlike ours.
Try not to be so impatient.
Isn't that a white crow?
A good omen that comes every 1,000 years.
It was found dead in a mountain not long ago.
In the near future, a huge mishap will come upon us.
A mishap?
Father.
Will I really be able to see again?
Yes. Don't worry at all.
Om Mani padme hum.
Om...
It has been a while.
You're...
Investigator Kim Gong Rae?
Investigator?
If you had died when you went over that cliff,
I would not have had to do this.
Why are you doing this?
Over ten years have passed since the late king's command.
Even if 100 years have passed, it must be carried out.
The king's command?
I risked my life to seal the Demon,
and my son lost his sight to bring us rain!
Is this what we get in return?
Father!
No!
- Father! - No!
- You can't take them! - Father!
- Father! - Son!
You're taking my husband's body...
and my son as well?
It's the King's command.
- Mother! - Ha Ram!
Do you wish to die too?
No. Mother!
That day,
you killed three people.
I will make you...
pay for the price of bloodshed.
I swear.
You're late, Moo Young.
We got a pigeon from the Palace.
- Is it about the Crown Prince? - Yes.
He was travelling to a hot spring...
when he was attacked by assassins.
Who's behind it?
Wolseongdang sent out their informants.
We should hear soon.
But then,
the King has been sick for a while.
The Crown Prince is sickly,
so it's the perfect timing for those who want to take power.
It seems that...
the time has come for me too.
We're about to have an important guest tonight.
I'm sorry for the trouble, Moo Young.
Yes, my lord.
My lord, it's another bull's eye.
I hear that the Crown Prince was attacked...
during his trip to the hot spring.
Was it done by a treasonous group...
that wish to overturn the royal authority?
I can't seem to go to sleep.
It's too early to jump to a conclusion.
However, if you're still worried,
it might not be a bad idea to meet with Ilwolseong.
Ilwolseong?
Yes, he's a man with wisdom and information of Zhuge Liang.
Why haven't I heard of this man...
until today?
I apologize, my lord.
He's a very careful and secretive man,
so no one has heard his voice or seen his face to this day.
So you weren't lying.
No, I wasn't. How would I dare to lie before you?
If what you said is true,
then don't we need him even if we must ask him three times or more?
Where can I meet him?
You'll find his request box in the middle of the city.
My name is Moo Young of Wolseongdang.
I came to take the request.
Lead us to your master.
I'm here with a nobleman. Do delay this any further.
I apologize, but my master does not show himself to anybody.
How dare you speak like that before him?
However, he already expected to meet the Prince tonight.
If you do not pry into his identity,
- you'll get the answer you want... - How dare you?
I understand.
Your Highness.
It's all right. I completely understand...
the wish of Ilwolseong.
In 7 days, 23rd period, at Simcheonggak.
From Ilwolseong.
Ilwolseong.
- Come and take a look. - Come and get what you need!
No, I asked you to draw me something to put up on my gates.
What on earth are you drawing? What is this?
Darn it, what a fraud. Darn it.
Hey, did you get anything done?
You're here.
Did you get that medicine you were talking about?
Yes, I did.
So how was it?
Can't you tell?
Her eyes look completely empty,
so she must've been scammed again.
Hey! Didn't I always tell you that you'd better watch your mouth?
I'll take this drawing.
I can't.
Don't be like that. Give me this drawing.
No.
I'll give you a good price, so just give it to me.
No, I can't.
Give it to me. You're going to rip it.
- Old lady, what's wrong? - Let go. It'll get ripped.
I'll have it.
Doesn't it look nice?
- Goodness. - Give it to me.
Anyway, it looks like you might get on a litter soon.
Sorry?
Don't worry about it. It's for a great occasion.
Wait, old lady!
Dad.
It's me, Dad. Your daughter, Cheon Gi.
Do you want me to draw you something?
Oh no.
Don't stand there in the rain. Get in here.
Right, my daughter.
Dad.
This is just a shower. It'll stop soon.
Let me go. My daughter can't even see.
She probably can't avoid the rain in this cold weather.
Then I'll bring her, so wait here.
All right, then.
She's about this tall.
And she has a stick, right?
Yes.
All right.
Don't go anywhere. Sit here and wait for me.
I'll bring her.
About Cheon Gi.
I don't feel so comfortable...
about deceiving that poor girl.
Watch your mouth. Our lives are at stake too.
We just need to turn a blind eye to this.
Goodness, you foolish man. Why did you get into gambling?
Even if she realizes that she bought fake medicine,
we cannot be the ones who spill the truth of the matter.
Cheon Gi.
What did you just say? Deceiving me?
What do you mean by that?
I'm sorry, Cheon Gi.
What in the world are you talking about?
My lord, you're here.
Why did you drink so much?
My love, my precious.
Darn it, you shameless man.
My gosh!
Where's the exit?
Stop right there!
Hey! Stop right there!
- Hey! - I have no idea!
Stop right there!
Hey! You shameless jerk!
- Hey! - Move aside!
Goodness!
Do you know what that money is worth?
I wanted to help my dad, so I saved up that money...
without eating, spending, and even getting criticized!
Did you wish to live after doing something like this?
Give me my money back!
Stop right there!
Give me my money!
My gosh, she's one feisty woman.
Stop right there, you jerk!
Wait, move aside.
My money!
What's going on?
It looks like there is a ruckus here.
Goodness, Hoo.
It's great to run into you in a place like this.
Yes, Yul.
Were you writing poems with other scholars here?
Yes.
Nice to meet you. My name is Mae Hyang.
You're Mae Hyang, the flower of Simcheonggak.
You must be Prince Joohyang. I've heard so much about you.
You can all meet later.
I'm glad you came. You should join us.
I'll have to postpone it.
I have an urgent engagement.
You're always so serious. We never have any fun.
How do you always remain the same?
People say they'll die if they suddenly change.
Goodness, this isn't the only day for us.
You'll be holding a painting contest soon.
The two of us can spend...
all night drinking together.
What?
Will you really come, Hoo?
It looks like this contest will go down in history.
Then I hope you all have fun.
Goodbye, Hoo.
Are you Ilwolseong?
Yes, my lord. Please take a seat.
Sure.
Did you read through the request?
"There was a precious jade in green in a place beyond anyone's reach."
"Recently, a night prowler has come and tried to steal the jade."
"Was it just a petty thief who was blinded by the jade?"
"Or was it a big thief who put out his life..."
"because he knew its worth?"
Yes. Do you understand...
my concern?
The green jade must be a jade marble.
In other words, it's your brother, the Crown Prince's realm.
The unreachable place must be the sky.
In a nutshell, this means the Crown Prince's palace.
And?
If this was a petty thief,
you wouldn't have stepped up yourself.
I'm sure it's a big thief.
Such a thief believes he's a big, nobleman.
And a man like that...
reached out to the unreachable sky,
it can only mean treason.
What's your ground for that conclusion?
I heard the Crown Prince...
came across an assassin during his trip to the hot spring.
Was this found on the paper?
If that's not a sign of treason,
what else could it mean?
Are you saying...
the incident of that assassin was an act of treason?
Do you...
truly wish to know?
Speak!
In that case,
you shouldn't be here talking to me.
You should look into a mirror.
Wasn't it you, Prince Joohyang,
who sent that assassin his way?
Do you really wish...
to die in my hands?
If...
the power behind this incident comes out to the light,
then you, Prince Joohyang, who tested me with this paper,
wouldn't be able to survive.
You.
No.
Have you forgotten?
You promised not to pry into...
my identity.
What persuaded Zhuge Liang...
wasn't a sword.
I do not believe you're an impatient man,
because you still...
let the current king live in peace and safety.
You will...
meet me again in good time.
This was my test.
Your wisdom and boldness are...
as great as I've heard, Ilwolseong.
I look forward to the day we meet again.
Should I track him?
No.
He's not a man who'll kneel before my sword.
- Let's go. - Yes, Your Highness.
You! You fraud!
Give me my money. Give me my money back!
I don't know anything!
I just did as Jung asked!
What? Jung?
Is Wolseongdang a part of this too?
It was an organized crime, wasn't it?
I don't know anything.
Stop right there, you scammer of Wolseongdang!
Did I just hear that right?
Yes, she clearly said, "You scammer..."
"of Wolseongdang!"
Tell Moo Young to find out everything that happened...
in Wolseongdang to this day.
Yes, my lord.
Let's go, that's it.
Yes, did I keep you waiting?
Don't mention it, Your Highness.
It's not like the sun has come up.
What did you say?
Are you saying I become wasted every single day?
Anyway,
don't you think you stop by the gisaeng house too often?
What can I do? I get conscious of what people think of me.
You do?
They say my power has grown tremendously big.
What power, Your Highness?
The problem is that I only associate with the nobleman.
I mean, it's not easy for a prince of a nation...
to look this handsome and to have excellent calligraphy.
If this handsome prince must live with a misunderstanding...
because of my love for literature and arts,
then I do not mind living my life like this.
I shouldn't have said that.
No, you can say that once again.
And start over at my handsome looks.
The handsome prince...
This is why I like you.
Jung...
Wolseongdang.
Hey, what is this?
Anyway, what's with your face?
I need your help. Gather round.
What happened is...
Now, this is a painting of a bamboo by Wun Dong of Qing.
I hear this place has the biggest collection...
and that you sell the paintings...
at a handsome price, so I decided to come by.
You're at the right place.
That costs over 100 Yang of silver.
Be careful. Be very careful with it.
I'll contact you once the painting is sold.
You can relax and wait.
Roll it up. Careful.
To the left. That's it.
Is anybody here?
What is it?
We heard you copy the paintings people leave here...
and sell them back as if it's the genuine piece.
Search through.
- Yes. - Yes.
Search for what? What are you doing?
What is this? Who's trying to frame me like this?
This isn't an imitation. It's the real one.
Painter Choi.
He's a painter of junior eighth rank at Gohwawon.
He's here to evaluate this to tell us if this is a copy.
It was copied.
What kind of nonsense is this?
This isn't a copy!
Why is there an insect in a bamboo painting by Wun Dong?
- What? - That's impossible.
Also, this paper came from Moonsung, right across the street.
Look.
There's the mark for Moonsung.
This can't be.
This can't be right!
- Arrest him. - Yes.
This is unfair. I've been framed!
I don't know anything about this.
I'm not like that!
It's not a big deal.
I was just there to talk.
- I can't believe that man. - What a shame.
Hong Cheon Gi, you brat. It was you, wasn't it?
Are you out of your mind?
You'll pay for this! You're just an insect!
I will crush you!
That made me feel so much better.
Is that good enough?
You should be able to handle most thugs now.
Did you ask about the gisaeng house incident?
Vice-chief Jung Seon Rye had been making a profit selling copies.
A painter who provided the copies wanted to quit,
so he deceived her and took her money.
And she found out.
Yes, and because of that, Jung Seon Rye was arrested today.
Was he?
It seems he got caught selling forgeries.
Do you mean he was arrested because of the copycat painter?
Yes.
Close Wolseongdang...
and find the copycat painter to find out more.
My lord, it is time to go to the Palace.
If this was not treason,
would anyone have attacked the Crown Prince?
Dozens of soldiers failed to catch the assassin.
I find that hard to believe.
Of the Five Polar Stars within...
the Small Purple Custer indicating the palace,
the Crown Prince's star is bright and strong,
so you need not worry about his safety.
Is that so?
What I wonder is, shouldn't we find out who's threatening us...
and punish them for it?
I heard that when a king causes bloodshed,
it stays with the family for a thousand years.
You are still concerned about the blood your late father shed.
Times like this is when you must be even more resolute.
Yes.
I should.
Come closer.
From now on, out of the Five Polar Stars,
keep a close eye on the second and third stars that represent...
Joohyang and Yangmyeong.
That is my special and secret command to you.
I will do as commanded.
Do you still have no memory of the past?
I do not.
I still remember nothing right after the rain making ritual 19 years ago.
However,
sometimes, bits and pieces of my memory return.
It's a relief to hear you're making progress.
Yes.
It's a great relief.
Your Majesty.
I may have no memory of that day,
but how could I forget absolutely everything?
Until those who killed my father...
and ruined my family and my life pay the price,
I can never forget...
or stop what I'm doing.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
Boss.
What took you so long?
They demanded triple the amount this time.
They took triple the bribe and treated me like this?
He said you should be grateful they're letting you go.
Don't.
Hong Cheon Gi.
Where is she?
Good riddance, Jung Seon Rye.
The jerk.
Getting revenge doesn't mean I'll get the money back.
My gosh.
All that happened to you were out of everyone's control.
It wasn't your fault.
That random comment...
still offers some comfort.
Yes.
Hey, Nuisance.
What do you want now?
Wolseongdang Jung Seon Rye conned me out of 50 Yang.
His master Ilwolseong must give me 100 Yang.
My gosh.
You've been quite busy, Painter Hong.
What do you want from...
me?
What do you think?
You sent me to rot in prison for a while, but I didn't stay long.
Oh?
What, 100 Yang?
You cheeky thing.
- Shoot. - Darn it. Get her!
- After her! - Get her!
- Darn. - Stop!
Oh, no.
Boss! Boss!
- Boss! - Get up!
Where is she?
Go that way!
Okay.
What a brat.
Scholar Ha, we reached the gate.
I'll show the guard our night time travel permit.
Okay.
What? Jung? Is Wolseongdang a part of this too?
How did I get involved?
I don't know who you are, but please ignore me for now.
But...
- Who are you? - Be quiet.
You lost her?
It's past curfew, so she can't have left the Capital.
Find her at all cost.
- Yes, Boss. - Yes, Boss.
Just wait until I get you.
I'll break your wrist so you never draw again.
Can this woman be...
Who are you?
Let me ask you something. Did you see a girl run by?
A girl?
May I look inside the litter?
Let's go, Man Soo.
Yes, sir. Let's go!
Okay. One, two.
Wait.
What do you want?
I need to see the face of the person inside.
Do you know who this is?
What's going on?
It's nothing, sir.
- You should just... - Sir.
I don't know who you are,
but I'm looking for a servant girl who ran off.
I'm sure she went this way.
I looked all around...
I'm the only one inside.
I cannot let you go until I see for myself.
You can't...
Open at your own peril.
Red eyes?
This litter belongs to His Majesty the King.
Do you know what that means?
It was ignorant of me to disturb you.
You got lucky.
If you had opened the window,
you would have lost your life.
Let's go, Man Soo.
Let's go.
Step aside.
Thank you. You saved me.
Were you very startled?
My heart almost stopped.
My heart almost stopped too when I saw a man in a litter...
when I expected a woman.
I only ride litters because I cannot see.
Pardon?
I see.
Why did you help me?
What if I really were a servant girl on the run?
You smell of ink,
so you can't be a servant.
A servant wouldn't have thought of jumping into someone else's litter.
I thought you must've had a reason.
You're right. I'm a painter.
You're truly impressive.
Not at all.
I cannot see, so I observe with smells and sounds.
Were you waiting for someone?
It's very late.
Actually,
they were chasing me from the start.
What happened that made you so desperate?
That fool conned me.
He's the worst.
Have you heard of Wolseongdang on Woonjong Street?
I'm not sure.
It's an art studio known for selling expensive paintings,
but the truth is, they're a rotten bunch...
that sell copies for the real deal to make a profit.
He conned me and took my money,
and I got back at him for it.
I saw him get arrested and taken away.
He got out so soon.
Oh, right.
Ilwolseong. He must've gotten him out.
I heard he was dangerous.
- Ilwolseong? - Yes.
He's the worst of them all, and very dangerous too.
Anyone who knows his identity ends up getting killed off.
I think I heard of him,
but isn't he knowledgeable and virtuous...
What?
That sounds as preposterous...
as a date getting struck by lightning on a clear day.
That's not true at all.
Are you...
Ilwolseong...
I mean, you're not his friend, are you?
- As if I would be. - Good.
Why would you tease me? My heart almost stopped.
Here it is.
That's great. Why did you tease me?
My heart almost sank.
Why does she remind me of her?
The road's uneven from here.
- Okay. - Okay.
Your eyes...
are really beautiful.
They're like red jewels.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
No one has said that to me before.
People see my eyes...
and call me a freak.
What?
About such beautiful eyes?
They're the prettiest eyes I've ever seen.
I mean it.
- Oh, dear. - Gosh.
Are you all right? It's so rocky.
Sir?
What's wrong?
Do you feel unwell?
I need you to get out.
Pardon?
Just like that?
Man Soo, stop the litter.
Pardon?
Yes, sir. Put down the litter.
Sir.
Sir, can you tell me your name?
- Let's go now, Man Soo. - Yes, Sir Scholar.
"Scholar"?
Get back safely.
Let's go.
One, two, three.
Wait, sir! Can I know your name?
Sir...
She'll be okay on her own at night, won't she?
The Capital's very close, but still.
What?
How could he tell me to get out just like that?
I wonder what happened to Nuisance and Frown.
Why is he moving so much?
Will you hold on tight? The road's rough as it is.
The litter's shaking.
This is a bit serious.
Stand still.
Put down the litter.
Do it, now!
Sir, you're okay, aren't you?
Sir.
What is that?
It's a ghost.
No, it's a freak! The freak!
Sir.
He's gone?
Run!
Go. Get out of here!
You made a mistake, Ha Ram.
On the Winter Solstice when Yin prevails,
you crossed the boundary.
I found my eyes.
(Lovers of the Red Sky)
Something happened on Mount Inwang.
He fell from the sky...
and passed out.
What do you mean the soldiers died overnight?
The bodies are all listless.
It's very strange.
It's a mark of the Demon.
Is this truly a copy?
Find the cheeky copycat painter for me.
- Lock her up this instant! - No!
What's the delay when it's Hong Cheon Gi?
Her mad father is always outside.
Get her right now!
Memories of the girl from the peach orchard...
keep overlapping with her.
Who are you?