[English subtitles are available]
[Moonlight]
[Episode 15]
When you told me to
quit the publishing house
and focus on surviving,
I didn't listen to you as well.
Yeah, since when have you
ever listened to me?
[Oh no.]
[That's what Mr Fox had said before.]
Since when have I told you that?
We were strangers
before you came into the industry, right?
If we knew each other before,
I would've told you to give up
being an editor.
Look at you right now.
You can't even afford to pay a fine.
Who would've thought that
the wealthy Mr Zhou Chuan
would hold it against me
for a meagre fine?
There's hot water in the pot.
Why are you drinking cold water?
Hello, Sister?
You've returned home?
We can talk about Huang Quan Inn later.
You can go and annoy your Jiang Yu Cheng.
I'll hang up now. Goodbye.
You should return now.
It's been tough on you.
I've wasted two hours
of your writing time.
How could it be a waste of my time
when I'm together with you?
I read the ending you wrote
while I was on the plane.
You need to change it according to
what we've discussed.
Let me carry it.
Sister, I know now.
After I'm done helping you out,
I'll return and write immediately.
Don't worry, I won't lose.
♫ They say strange things
and keep rapport ♫
[Our life isn't comprised of
our previous burdens.]
[Our journey ends here.]
♫ Guileless adults are reduced to a joke ♫
Sister,
I've put your things into your room.
♫ Unceasingly, here to stay ♫
♫ No dancing on the roof, but rain ♫
♫ The loneliness has found
a place and moved out ♫
♫ Guests sillier than me
argue and exaggerate ♫
♫ The moon is
outrageously beautiful tonight ♫
Here you go.
We used them as our bookmarks
when we were young, right?
That's what a girl would do.
♫ Lend me the light on your face ♫
You don't like it?
Forget about it then. I thought
it could serve as a memento.
♫ I've been giddy from drifting
in a sea of people ♫
Just throw it away if you don't like it.
I do like it.
♫ Unwilling to admit my anticipation
of getting submitted to gentleness ♫
What do you like?
I like ginkgos.
♫ I want to be led by you,
albeit a meager freedom ♫
I like ginkgos as well.
I like you as well.
♫ The Hand of the Creator
has finally seen to ♫
♫ I'm drifting in a sea of people.
And will frequently look back♫
♫ Scared to reach out my hand
that no one will save me ♫
♫ How rich can concrete skyscrapers be ♫
Sister.
Sister, what's wrong with you?
♫ You are a rare shining oasis ♫
♫ Exactly what I want ♫
Do you know the meaning of
love comes upon once in your life?
I've thought about it many times.
One day, when I'm old,
there's someone who would
still hold my hand.
We would take a walk in the park together.
As the breeze passes by us,
the sun
will shine on us.
Birds will chirp on the trees.
No matter how many times I think about it,
Jiang Yu Cheng was always
the one on my mind.
He will still make you sad.
I know that.
But I don't know how to give up
on that idealistic image of mine.
Sister.
Go back now.
I want to be alone.
I have something to discuss with you.
We need to determine who will cook
and who will do the work.
Why don't you determine who will cook
and who will eat the food?
You're the one eating.
That's a given.
Do you think this is enough?
That's too much.
You can wash
all of our cooking utensils
with that amount.
Do you even know how to wash dishes?
Use this.
The metal sponge is used to clean pots.
Isn't all of it the same?
Mr Zhou Chuan,
do you have a smurf account?
[Here she comes again.]
What smurf account?
I don't even have enough time
to handle my main account.
I haven't told you what kind of
smurf account I'm talking about.
I don't have any smurf account.
Weibo, WeChat, QQ, none of them.
Why are you asking me this?
Nothing. It's just a random question.
Mr Zhou Chuan,
I discovered something interesting.
What is it?
For every ending of your story,
you'll put five ellipses at the back.
Is that a habit of yours?
Can't I do so?
Of course you can. It's just that
one of my online friend
has the same habit as you.
Plenty of people
have the same habit, you know?
So, are all of them your online friends?
But even the tone you're using
is the same as him.
Especially when
you're criticizing Mr Jiang.
He's bothering Jiang Yu Cheng as well?
You can introduce him to me then.
What exactly are you trying to say?
Mr Zhou Chuan,
you're Mr Fox, right?
Mr Fox?
Who is it?
It's the Little Zhou Chuan
I've told you about.
You mean the one who's just like me?
You must be delusional.
You're saying that I'm Mr Fox
just because of the way I write?
Not just that,
the way you criticize people
is exactly the same as him.
You two are curious about
the same thing as well.
Just like
the entries for the
Interactive Cultural Festival.
Now, you're using the tone
of my writing as evidence?
You should listen to yourself.
It's absurd.
I'm one of the authors for
the Interactive Cultural Festival.
Isn't it normal for me
to care about the amount of entries?
As for that Mr Fox,
I think he's curious because
he's one of my readers.
You can call Mr Fox right now.
Ask him if he is me.
[Please don't make the call.]
[Please.]
Mr Zhou Chuan,
are you not Mr Fox?
Didn't I give you a chance
to prove it to me?
Forget about it.
I'll take it as a no then.
I won't dwell on this anymore.
[What a relief.]
I have to endure this every day?
My heart won't be able to take it
any longer.
Why are you staring at me?
Of course I can't admit that I'm Mr Fox.
I wasn't honest with her from the start.
What should I do if she knew that
I was trying to get information from her?
Mr Fox is me at my geekiest moment.
If she knew that I was Mr Fox,
what if she threatens me
and wants me
to hand over my copyright to her?
Enough already.
I know she won't resort to this.
But I'm sure she'll tease me for it.
I can imagine her face
when she teases me.
"Mr Zhou Chuan."
"I didn't expect you
to be such an emotional teen in the past."
What if she threatens me with that
and doesn't want to cook for us?
I'm fine with that.
But can you change from
eating freshly made dishes
to dried dog food?
That's why.
I can't admit it for your sake.
Let's not dwell on it anymore.
I will never admit that I'm Mr Fox.
Let's go.
[Moonlight]
Good morning, Mr Jiang.
Morning.
Are you here for the latest issue
of Moonlight Magazine?
Yes.
Count this as my present for you.
Thank you.
Compared with the fan fictions
on Xin Dun Creative Exchange,
seems like this issue's
Interactive Cultural Festival
focuses more on
promoting new authors.
I guess all of the articles
are specially chosen.
That's what Mr Xia thought of.
He wants to guide the newcomers
as a veteran.
He wants more people to know about
the new authors.
By the way,
all of your articles
were specially picked by me.
What do you think?
I did a good job, right?
I have nothing to fear when you're here.
By the way,
I've rewritten the ending for
The Disappearing Amusement Park.
Are you free tomorrow night?
I wish to discuss it with you.
Of course. You wrote another ending to it?
Mr Jiang, you're really amazing.
So, am I the first reader
of this new ending?
Please remember to send the location
and time to me.
I need to leave now.
I have a meeting to attend to.
Alright.
-Goodbye.
Hello?
Please reserve two spots
with the best view for me.
For two.
For the Interactive Cultural Festival,
no matter it's from the entries
or the response of the readers,
they're the best we've achieved
for the past two years.
We need to thank our leader for this.
He has been fully supporting us for this.
But, there are some problems
regarding the festival as well.
For the authors,
their popularity vary greatly.
Everyone knows that
the current publishing field
isn't doing too well.
I think we can use this chance
to cut down on our number of authors.
All of the authors included
have a sturdy fanbase.
Their popularity
is largely determined by the situation.
For example, for Mr Zhou Chuan
and Mr Jiang Yu Cheng
Their fans are more active
on social media.
That's why they may seem more popular.
But for some authors,
their readers are more mature.
They keep a low profile as well.
Although they may not express themselves
on social media,
it doesn't mean that the authors
are not popular.
You're saying that they're popular?
If that's so, why are people
faking data for them
behind the scenes?
Chief Editor Yu,
I'm sure you know who I'm talking about.
It's Suo Heng.
Everyone knows the amount of letter
Suo Heng had received this time,
am I right?
Five letters in total.
According to our data,
why is the second section
keeping an unpopular author like her?
Do you think she's our mascot?
Mr Liang,
Ms Suo Heng has been writing
for Moonlight Magazine for a decade.
You can't just judge her capability
based on an activity like this.
Actually, the managing editor
has been reminding
Ms Suo Heng of her situation.
It's just that the results
aren't that positive.
You guys are seeing it for yourselves.
I was the one who brought Suo Heng
to our publishing house.
It's heartbreaking
for me to say this,
but I have to say it
for the sake of the publishing house.
In my opinion,
we should fire
unpopular authors like her.
We should leave spaces
for authors who are more worthy.
This is a publishing house.
We aren't doing charity over here.
There's no need for us to support
the losers in life,
am I right?
Losers?
Miao,
you think this has
nothing to do with you at all?
Chief Editor Yu,
we are in a meeting, you know?
There's no need for you to
confront me directly.
Unpopular authors like Suo Heng
should've been
eliminated long ago.
It's been so many years, you know?
Do you think other publishing houses
are still publishing her works?
If it weren't for your support,
she wouldn't have been able to stay with
Yuan Yue Publishing House
for so many years.
Miao.
Chief Editor Yu,
I know you've been asking other people
to write Suo Heng's stories for her.
Director Yang was unhappy
when he found out about it.
I tried my best to defend you, you know?
Yet, you're still unwilling to give up?
That's it. It's decided then.
If anyone has objections,
you can complain to Director Yang.
Sir,
I've prepared steam rice rolls with
BBQ pork for your lunch.
Steam rice rolls with BBQ pork?
Where is it?
Er Gou!
You're complaining to me about Er Gou?
Come back home immediately
and prepare another set
of steamed rice rolls for me.
Brother, can't you
please call for deliveries
using your phone?
Why do you sound so down?
I'll hang up now. Bye.
Chu Li, Ms Suo Heng
looks pale.
I feel like she's going
to faint at any time.
Fine.
Both of you are trying to
make me angry, huh?
You won't get to eat your favourite
chicken meatballs,
you hear me?
Don't tell me she realized that
I was Mr Fox after last night?
Mr Fox didn't reply her the entire night.
That won't do.
How should I reply her?
[The Navy Hired by the Monkey]
What are you doing?
No.
This sounds just like me.
[The Navy Hired by the Monkey]
Good morning.
Today will be a great day.
Let's see if you still suspect me
as Mr Fox after this.
Deputy Editor Miao.
You must be kidding me, right?
Yuan Yue Publishing House and I
have been working together
for so many years.
How could you terminate
my contract just like that?
We had no choice.
We tried to fight for you,
but
this is a decision made by the higher-ups.
We didn't want this to happen either.
Deputy Editor Miao, look.
I still have more than
10 types of novels with me.
I've completed everything
you asked of me.
I was always trying to be creative.
I'm not lying.
I tried my best to be creative.
Please take a look at them.
Or I can write anything
you guys ask of me.
As long as you guys don't give up on me.
Suo Heng,
didn't I tell you already?
Regarding these scripts,
since we've worked together
for so many years,
let me
be honest with you.
You're not suitable
for writing.
It's better for you to find another job.
He said he's being honest with her?
He's stabbing Ms Suo Heng's gentle heart
with a spear.
I've spent the most precious decade
of my life
on writing.
I try my best
to write every day.
I was thinking that even if
I wasn't talented as a writer,
my hard work will be able to
compensate for my lack of talent.
I don't want my career to end like this.
I can't accept this.
You can't accept this?
Even so, you can't just let
Yuan Yue Publishing House
incur losses because of your stubbornness.
I understand now.
I understand everything.
Great, I'm glad that you understood me.
Let's part with a smile then.
Just sign
on this contract.
And that'll be all.
I can't accept this!
Miao, you better don't be too much!
Aren't you being too anxious?
Why are you here?
You have no say in this matter!
Ms Suo Heng's novels
were great.
Every writer has their own style
and themes they're good at.
Things wouldn't have ended like this
if you didn't force her
to change her style.
I forced her to change her style?
Tell me, should all writers
stay in their comfort zone then?
I just wanted her to make a breakthrough.
But she couldn't make it.
How could you blame this on me?
Is asking her to write something
she isn't good at
an attempt for her to make a breakthrough?
If you love to help her out so much,
why don't you write it for her then?
Enough!
[Party B's signature]
[Yuan Yue Publishing House's
Termination Agreement]
Actually, I know everything
that's been going on.
I do read the private messages as well.
"Ms Suo Heng."
"Your writing is getting lousier."
"I miss the touching words
you've written before."
I know all of that.
I knew what was going on.
I don't need you guys to take pity on me!
I don't need you guys to kick me around
like a ball.
Changing my editors
one after another.
Suo Heng,
you can take back your scripts.
Just throw them away.
Ms Suo Heng.
Suo Heng!
Suo Heng.
Listen to me.
You don't need to say anything.
I don't want to hear
how unpopular I am anymore.
Wait for me.
I'm sure there's a solution to this.
You've already forsaken me.
What's the meaning of this conversation?
I can only say that
I really had no choice back then.
That's why I told you
to find other editors.
That's why I chose Miao.
I've signed the contract
of termination just now.
From now on,
you don't need to care about me.
[The Best New Writer Award]
"This year's most unforgettable novel,
Golden Spears and Armoured Horses,
a fantastic novel about the female gender,
its author
is a relatively unknown
and young female author."
Is she referring to me?
-Yeah.
-Let me take a look!
Wait, there's more.
Look.
"This novel is just like a black horse,
crowning itself as
the top-selling novel of the year!"
"Crowned as the best novel of the year,
readers can expect great things
from this up-and-coming author."
We've made it.
Yeah.
We've made it!
Hello?
[Are you Su Heng?]
I am. Do you need anything from me?
[It's really you?]
[I'm Xu Chao from the literature club.]
[I've been trying to contact you
for a long time.]
[Yu Yao did tell you that]
[the literature club will
have a gathering tonight, right?]
[You will attend the gathering, right?]
Mr Zhou Chuan?
Why are you so childish?
You're pulling my braids just like
a primary student would.
Do you know how long
I've been waiting for you?
I thought your lunch break is at 12 noon?
It's 1 p.m. now, you know?
Do we have an appointment
in the afternoon?
Why don't I remember anything?
I want steamed rice rolls with BBQ pork.
And I had to wait for you.
You'll foot the bill later.
You look so down.
What's wrong?
It's all because of Ms Suo Heng.
She received too less replies from
the Interactive Cultural Festival.
That's why Director Yang
is terminating her contract.
Even if Suo Heng couldn't make it,
Yu Yao is still there for her.
Why are you worried about her?
Even you know her relationship
with Chief Editor Yu?
I know a little bit.
Isn't Ms Suo Heng pitiful
if Chief Editor Yu
were to ignore her as well?
So, what has this got to do with you?
Why has it got nothing to do with me?
Miao said so before.
Even you are saying the same thing.
But I'm an editor.
As an editor,
how could I watch and do nothing
as a talented writer
fades away?
This concerns my professionalism.
If I failed after I've done my best,
I won't say anything.
But if I keep quiet about it
and pretend to be ignorant
because it doesn't concern me,
I will never be able to forgive myself.
As long as I'm working as an editor,
I will never give up on any author.
That's why I became an editor
in the first place.
What if, one day,
I run out of ideas?
I will never give up on you as well.
Incorrect. You should've said,
"Mr Zhou Chuan, it's impossible for you
to run out of ideas?"
So,
the talented, handsome,
and resourceful Mr Zhou Chuan,
do you know where
Ms Suo Heng is staying at?
You think I'm the paparazzi?
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Are you removing the BBQ pork
because you want to give them to me?
You said you love BBQ pork, right?
I'm giving them to you just in case
you want more.
You're doing all of this
just because you want to
find out her address?
Waiter,
give me another set of BBQ pork.
Alright.
How could you say that about me?
Do you think I'm being nice to you
just because of that?
Ever since I came to know you,
I've been serving you every day, you know?
Where can you find another
cute and bubbly editor like me?
I've sent Suo Heng's address to you.
Thank you, Mr Zhou Chuan.
I'll go and find her tonight.
I hope you still remember that
you're my editor.
Eat up.
-Sorry for being late.
-You became prettier.
Come.
I saw that your daughter has
given birth to a girl.
Congratulations.
Yeah, congratulations.
Not bad at all.
You were a tomboy in the past.
Yet you got married the fastest
among all of us.
Now,
I'm a housewife who had just given birth
to my second daughter.
I was so busy that
I can't even finish a book.
I wanted to be a writer
in the past, you know?
But, I realized that
I can't make a living
with just writing novels.
That's why
I joined the sales industry.
This is a rich wife's life.
Yeah, no one can compare to her.
Suo Heng,
I heard that you've written
several novels.
Share them with us.
Yeah, the hottest novel right now
is The Fierce West Wind.
Did you write it?
-The Fierce West Wind?
-Yeah.
It's quite good.
You'll earn a lot if
you turn novels into movies.
Suo Heng, tell us about it.
How much do you earn from
selling your novels?
I don't earn that much.
-Just tell us about it.
-That can't be.
Why are you asking about her income
when we're here to have a meal?
Why do I feel like you have some
ulterior motives?
Not at all. I'm just trying to
show concern for her.
Come, it's been a long time
since we've met.
Let's have a toast.
-Come on.
That person who's been
enjoying himself abroad,
you have to drink three cups.
Bottoms up.
He's living his life right now.
Ms Suo Heng!
Are you okay?
Why are you here?
Did you drink?
I've terminated my contract
with Yuan Yue Publishing House.
I have no ties with your company anymore.
Don't come and look for me anymore.
What about your pills?
Ms Suo Heng,
you mustn't give up on
writing just like that.
Don't you think
you're being sarcastic
when you're working for
Yuan Yue Publishing House?
Chu Li, I've seen everything
you've done for me.
Thank you for everything.
Director Yang.
Director Yang, I need to speak with you.
Chief Editor Yu?
What a coincidence.
Do you need anything?
I have something to
report to Director Yang.
Director Yang and I had
a happy time tonight.
He drank a lot.
He has fallen asleep.
Why don't you try to wake him up?
Come.
Director Yang,
Suo Heng...
As long as she regains confidence,
as long as she returns to her expertise,
I'm sure she can write
another great novel like
Golden Spears and Armoured Horses
She isn't worthless.
Yeah.
You do have a point.
Chief Editor Yu,
the weather is quite cold.
Have a piece of chocolate.
Director Yang.
Director Yang, please give
Suo Heng another chance.
Director Yang.
Director Yang,
please give Suo Heng another chance!
Hello?
Dear?
I'm sorry.
I might not be able to
attend Mum's birthday dinner later.
Please apologize to her for me.
Wish her happy birthday for me.
I'll surely apologize to her personally
in the future.
Mum, let's proceed.
She's busy tonight.
She won't be coming.
She was already busy with her work.
She had never brought Qiu Qiu
to visit us.
Now, she was finally
transferred back here.
I thought our family
can have a happy meal together.
Coincidentally,
today is my 60th birthday.
We waited until now,
yet she's telling us that
she won't be coming?
I'm sure Yao Yao has an emergency
to attend to.
I'll apologize to you on behalf of her.
Qiu Qiu,
let's sing the birthday song
for Grandma later.
Is your phone a decoration?
You didn't answer my calls at all.
I thought someone kidnapped you, you know?
We're out of fruits.
Let's go and buy some fruits.
What are we having for breakfast tomorrow?
I'm talking to you, you know?
Hello, do you sell
Estazolam pills here?
Estazolam pills?
That's a restricted medication.
You need to get them from the hospitals.
What kind of medication is this?
It's a strong sleeping pill.
Who are you buying it for?
Sir, please send me
to Ms Suo Heng's house.
[The number you have dialled
is unavailable.]
[Sorry, the number you have dialled...]
What should we do? She isn't picking up.
Hello, Chief Editor Yu?
I found some strong sleeping pills
in Ms Suo Heng's handbag.
And she went out to drink just now.
I'm afraid something might happen to her.
I'm on my way to her house.
Calm down. Don't be anxious.
Okay.
Ms Suo Heng, are you at home?
[The Best Original Novel,
Golden Spears and Armoured Horses]
Ms Suo Heng, please open the door!
[The Best Original Novel,
Golden Spears and Armoured Horses]
-Ms Suo Heng,
-Chu Li.
please open the door!
Chu Li.
Her awards?
Chief Editor Yu,
Ms Suo Heng wasn't willing
to open the door.
And she doesn't answer my calls.
I have her keys.
[Estazolam Pills]
Suo Heng.
Suo Heng!
-Call the ambulance.
-Suo Heng!
Alright.
Get up.
-Why are you guys here?
-Suo Heng.
How could you do such a silly thing?
What should I do
if anything happens to you?
Ms Suo Heng,
you're still young.
Don't be silly, okay?
What are you guys saying?
[Estazolam Pills]
I'm not trying to kill myself.
It's just that I couldn't sleep lately.
That's why I'm taking the sleeping pills.
I didn't expect myself to
fall into a deep sleep.
Did you drink just now?
Alcohol might strengthen the effects
of sleeping pills.
I'm glad that you're fine.
How did you guys come in?
Chief Editor Yu...
I've always kept your keys with me.
I was the one who opened the door.
So,
since she's fine,
I'll wait for you outside.
Do you still find it hard
to sleep lately?
Your body will be damaged
if you keep taking sleeping pills.
You need to see a doctor.
I know a great doctor.
I don't need you to care for me.
Even doctors won't be able to save me.
I know my own condition the best.
I'm fine right now.
Please leave.
Ms Suo Heng,
Chief Editor Yu has always
been concerned for you.
So,
I think we'll leave now.
If you need anything,
you can call Chu Li.
Take good care of yourself.
Ms Suo Heng,
we didn't give up on you.
If you're willing,
I can be your editor...
Even Yuan Yue Publishing House
won't be able to save me.
Stop worrying about me.
You guys should leave.
-Let's go.
-Wait.
Leave the keys here.
Is there anything else?
Tearing your own scripts into pieces,
I've done that before.
But, it's useless.
Because every word that you've written
will be imprinted in your mind.
If you can't even accept your past self,
you have no right
to talk about the future.
Do you think I still can
expect something from my future?
No matter for what reason,
you didn't take the entire bottle tonight.
That means you're still
expecting something.
What's the use of expectations?
This is just my last struggle.
Why don't you have a try?
Today, my editor told me that
as long as she's working as an editor,
she won't give up on any author.
That's why she became an editor
in the first place.
She can accept it when she fails
after trying her best,
but she can't accept it when
she submits to fate without even trying.
That's because you're lucky.
You got yourself a great editor.
That's precisely why
you should give her
and yourself another chance.
It's all because of me.
I was the one
who pushed her into this plight.
I was the reason
she couldn't sleep without taking
sleeping pills.
Do you know
why she ended up like this?
It's because I gave up on her before.
It'll be inconvenient for me
to visit you from now on.
You can take the keys first.
You're not visiting me anymore?
Even you are giving up on me?
It's not that. I...
I need to take a long break.
In the future, I'll ask
the other editors
to take care of you.
What do you mean by that?
Are you saying that you're abandoning me?
Is it because no one is buying my book?
Is that why you're abandoning me as well?
I don't know how to
explain it to you right now,
but,
Suo Heng, I'm sorry.
I didn't expect you
to deviate from your original style
after you did your research
on how to write better.
Maybe it's my fault.
Sis Yao Yao,
can you please trust me one last time?
Please trust me one last time, okay?
Fine.
I understand now.
Thank you for caring for me
all these years.
From now on,
we'll be on our separate ways.
We are even now.
I was so naive that I thought
the dreams you told me before
were your true dreams.
Just throw away the keys.
Chief Editor Yu,
why didn't you tell her that...
Because
I was pregnant back then.
The doctor said
it'll be hard for the child to survive
if I didn't rest well.
Why didn't you tell her then?
Even if I had told her,
that wouldn't have changed anything.
Even if I had told tell her that
I didn't want to give up on her,
what would have that changed?
It won't change anything.
I'm sorry, Chief Editor Yu.
Stop it.
You're not the one
who should apologize here.
Sorry for that.
I have things to attend to.
I'll leave now.
Chu Li,
let's go.
It's fine as long as she's alive.
If you want her to pull herself together,
you'll have plenty of time to do so
in the future.
I watched Ms Suo Heng
as she couldn't say anything
or do anything about her circumstances.
She worked so hard,
even the ink of her keyboard has faded.
In this world,
there are many helpless situations.
Your effort might not be repaid.
But, if you can move on bravely
even after realizing the truth,
these difficulties you've faced
won't become ordeals to you.
They'll become a meaningful experience
to you.
Sir, I'm sorry.
Did I mention your sad past by accident?
I'm different from you.
I'm a genius.
Geniuses don't need to put in effort.
Your confidence is what I like about you.
Let's go.