=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 1=
When the world appeared,
Ancestral God created the God Realm,
the Immortal Realm and the Demon Realm.
He passed on the cultivation
of spiritual power
before he broke the space and left.
The God Realm is supreme
where Four True Gods command
all the other Gods.
(Temple of Love)
Look.
Yuemi,
Qionghua Banquet is held every year.
What’s the fun of that?
But look at the Temple of Love.
Puhua holds the Dating Event
every thousand years.
Everyone in the Three Realms
wants to find their love in this event.
It’s the funniest place.
Here.
What for?
Look at them.
How bustling!
I’m looking forward to it.
I don’t need to cover my face.
(Shanggu)
I come to the lower realm
to enjoy the beautiful scenery.
Who just begged me
(Yuemi)
to cover her for coming here
and promised she would be obedient?
Soon you forgot it?
All right. I’ll cover my face, then.
Your portrait has been hung
in the middle of the Supreme God Temple.
If someone recognizes you
and tells on you to Zhiyang,
we’ll be in trouble.
Yuemi, don’t worry.
If there’s trouble, I’ll take the blame.
Look at Puhua.
He only drinks in the God Realm.
He’s holding up so many immortals.
Now the world is in peace.
Instead of cultivating themselves,
those in the lower realm
simply want love.
How boring and superficial!
Come on, Goddess of Moon & Stars.
You feel bored?
Let’s go somewhere else.
- Go.
- Don’t.
We’ve come already. Don’t leave.
Are you keeping something from me?
Don’t be absurd.
I was wondering on my way here
why you wanted to come
to the Temple of Love.
Turns out you have love for someone.
Give it back to me.
Tell me. Who’s he?
I won’t tell you.
If you like someone,
go ask Puhua.
If you’re too shy to go,
I can ask him for you.
You don’t understand.
Life is too long.
I also want someone
to divert me from boredom.
But over the past ten thousand years,
not even a single immortal
has chased me.
In story books,
love lasts ten thousand years.
But to us,
it’s merely a passing moment.
I don’t think it’s a big deal.
When you fall in love,
you won’t sound you don’t care.
Fall in love?
I’ve learnt a new spell.
I’d like to help them.
I picked her first.
You!
What?
Let go of me!
Rogue!
Why did you touch me?
How impolite!
What?
Puhua taught me the spell personally.
Why did I use it so poorly?
You have little spiritual power.
You certainly used it poorly.
Let go of me!
What are you doing?
What do you want?
Do something!
Zhiyang will know!
Girl. Girl. Girl.
Girl, you look so beautiful.
How do I look?
Wait for me.
Girl.
Girl, here I am.
Shanggu.
Girl? Girl?
Where’s she?
Where’s she gone?
Girl.
When the primordial world
came into being,
Ancestral God created the God Realm,
and generated spirits
with the Power of Chaos.
Spirits fell in the lower realm,
the Heavenly Realm emerged
after a hundred thousand years.
- Master.
(Bai Jue)
What did I say
in the first class?
Be sincere in study and don’t be late.
Gods and immortals can do as they like.
But they can’t break rules.
Master, we didn’t mean to be late.
Today, a girl jostled
in the Milky Way.
Instead of reflecting on yourselves,
you blamed others.
How can you be immortals?
You were held up,
but I taught you Riding with Sword
three months ago.
Why didn’t you use it?
Sorry, but I’m a little rusty.
Then why didn’t you practice it?
Follow up.
Are you scared?
Yes.
Practice more
and you’ll no longer be scared.
Yes.
Go reflect on yourselves.
Now that you’ve come,
why bother to hide?
I had thought
teaching little immortals
could make you gentler.
(Tianqi)
But you still have the same temper.
Be quick.
What can an uncommunicative man
teach you?
When cultivating to be a God,
you should enjoy yourselves
like I do.
Today,
I’d like to show you.
Watch carefully!
What are you laughing at?
I’m simply thirsty.
Bai Jue,
fight me after I drink enough wine.
Master Tianqi, we fight with hands,
but only boast with the mouth.
Yeah!
Yeah.
Fire Beast, you’re quite talkative.
I’m not the Fire Beast! I’m Kylin!
Come on. Heat the wine for me.
Master, look.
Master Tianqi...
Class is over.
Hongri, take them back for some rest.
Yes.
Ice Cube.
It’s the fur of the Nine-tailed Fox.
It was a kind of fierce beast
when Ancestral God created
the Heavenly Realm. You hunted it?
I just did some exercise
in my spare time.
Why did you only
prepare gifts for Zhiyang?
Help yourself to the wine.
I knew it.
You must be missing us
over the past ten thousand years.
If you come to see how I’m doing,
you can leave.
I can’t.
I come to bring you back.
I’ve sent you
countless instruction feathers
over the past years,
but you gave me the cold shoulder.
It’s Shanggu’s ten thousandth birthday
next month.
Since she was born
on the Heaven & Earth Platform,
you have never seen her.
In this world,
only we four are True Gods
who were born by the world itself.
It’s time for you to come back.
She’s still young,
considering her life span.
We’ll meet sooner or later.
No rush.
It’s not up to you.
(Bai Jue, you have to come back
for Shanggu’s birthday, Zhiyang.)
This is the order from Zhiyang.
He summoned you
to the ten thousandth birthday
of Chief God of Chaos.
Anyway,
she’s the future Chief God of Chaos.
If you don’t go,
those old Gods will think
you disrespect her.
Besides, Shanggu is...
I’m not finished yet.
Listen.
If you dare to help her
hoodwink me again,
leave the God Realm
and start over your cultivation!
Yes, Master.
Looks like Zhiyang is really angry.
Do you remember you were punished
with three thunder strikes
for making wrong comments on reports.
I never forget!
I laid in bed for a month.
As far as I see,
you’ll lie in bed
for two months this time.
Don’t be scared.
You’ve got a good idea?
I don’t.
But I can go to the lower realm
and get you some story books
to divert you from boredom
when you lie in bed for recovery.
Don’t be sarcastic.
You think I’m really afraid of Zhiyang?
Punishment isn’t a problem,
but I’ll feel disgraced.
Now that you went
to the Temple of Love with me,
I’ll remain faithful.
I’ll take the thunder strikes for you.
No.
I answer for my own fault.
Shall I go out and hide for a moment?
After Zhiyang calms down,
the punishment
will be cut half, at least.
My girl,
everyone in the God Realm
is looking for you.
Where do you think you can hide?
There’s an empty hall over there.
Changyuan Hall?
That’s where Bai Jue lives.
He’s not a man to mess with.
You can’t go.
Don’t be scared!
He’s been in the lower realm
for ten thousand years
and he won’t be back soon.
It’s an empty hall, anyway.
Ancestral God, bless us.
Don’t let Bai Jue come back.
Zhiyang!
Have you found Shanggu?
Bai Jue?
(Zhiyang)
Hope you’re all well.
Don’t get yourself embarrassed.
He’s greatly improved his cultivation
and fought me when he first saw me.
He’s still so competitive.
It’s the birthday gift
for the Chief God of Chaos.
Let me have a look.
A birthday peach?
You grew the peach tree?
There’re peach trees on Mount Lookout.
You simply picked one?
What’s the difference?
I have something else to do
in the Heavenly Realm. See you.
Bai Jue.
I know you don’t like to socialize.
I didn’t simply
summon you
for Shanggu’s birthday.
Not for her birthday?
Then why did you get him back?
Shanggu was born
with blocked God vessels
and little spiritual power.
She can’t cultivate
the unique Power of Chaos.
I want you to stay in the God Realm
and teach her personally.
Why...? Why do you want that?
Bai Jue is so stubborn.
How can Shanggu bear with that?
Besides,
I watched Shanggu grow up.
I should teach her!
Tianqi is naughty,
but he’s good enough
to teach a ten-thousand-year-old girl.
Bai Jue made sense.
Bai Jue,
if Shanggu learns from Tianqi
to be so arrogant,
the God Realm will be in danger
even before the invasion of Demons.
Danger? Why would that happen?
Can I break the God Realm?
Shut up!
Bai Jue,
among us three,
only you can make her vessels
no longer blocked.
Not interested.
I’m interested.
Shut up!
Bai Jue.
All right.
There’s something
you’ll know sooner or later.
Come with me.
Since when did the barrier
of the Nether World split?
Since last month,
the Power of Chaos has begun to vanish.
Do you know?
The barrier of the Nether World contains
the Power of Chaos of the Ancestral God.
When the Power of Chaos began to vanish,
the barrier will be totally split
sooner or later.
Once the Nether World is open,
there’ll be a great disturbance.
Maybe it’s the destiny
that Shanggu didn't have unblocked God vessels.
Even if you don’t want
to bother about Demons,
don’t you remember
the Tribulation of Chaos?
It’s coming in a thousand years.
Only the Chief God of Chaos
can fight it.
But we don’t even know
what the Tribulation of Chaos is.
How can a young girl like her fight it?
That’s why I want you to teach her.
It’s about the peace of the God Realm.
For the sake
of Ancestral God’s last wish.
If the Tribulation of Chaos comes,
I’ll fight with my life
to defend the God Realm.
The disaster is coming to the God Realm.
It reminds me of the old years!
Tianqi,
do you remember the first time
the Ancestral God took us
to the battlefield?
It’s still vivid in my mind.
Bai Jue even...
Zhiyang,
we’re no longer young.
Don’t bring it up again.
If immortals of the low class know it,
he’ll be laughed at in the Three Realms.
How humiliated he’ll be!
You swore you wouldn’t bring it up.
Sorry, sorry.
It’s my fault.
We didn’t mean that. Never mind.
What’s Shanggu like?
Shanggu?
She’s submissive and hardworking.
She’s also smart
and never makes trouble.
If she didn't have unblocked God vessels,
she would have taken control
of the instruction feather of Chief God.
Seriously?
Yes.
I’m used to quietness
in the past ten thousand years.
All right.
I promise to keep your hall
from being disturbed,
especially by Goddesses.
I can’t help her much.
It mostly depends on her.
It’s a deal, then.
You mustn’t regret!
Why didn’t you tell him
Shanggu’s real temper?
What were you laughing at?
You kept making trouble!
It’s you who spoilt Shanggu!
I laughed?
Shanggu,
you always make trouble
though you mean good.
When you tried to help Zhiyang,
you made wrong comments on the reports.
When you wanted to be a matchmaker
for immortals,
you made trouble again.
Is there something wrong with your mind?
Isn’t that the Goddess of Snow?
Why is she coming to Changyuan Hall?
Try hard to be in full bloom.
(Xueying)
When Master Bai Jue comes back,
he’ll be happy to see you in full bloom.
It’s been ten thousand years
since Bai Jue left,
but the Goddess of Snow
is still waiting.
What a touching affection!
Who’s there?
Master Bai Jue?
Greetings, Master.
He’s Bai Jue?
It’s been ten thousand years,
and you still look the same.
Why are you here?
Master, I know you like Blue Flowers.
When you were away,
I was taking care of them here,
so that you can see the same scene
when you come back.
Master.
I said that
without permission,
no one is allowed in my hall.
You broke my rule deliberately.
Go take three thunder strikes.
How merciless he is!
Does it hurt?
No.
Looks like I need
to grow the tree taller
in case someone peeps again.
I peeped you?
I don’t want to know who you are.
Please leave.
And you.
Wait.
The Goddess of Snow made great efforts
to grow the flowers,
and you just fired them?
How impersonal you are!
I’m a God. Why must I be personal?
You!
This is my hall.
I can fire anything as I wish.
What does it concern you?
I, Shanggu, concern about everything
in the God Realm.
Shanggu?
Greetings, Your Grace.
Don’t worry, Goddess of Snow.
I’ll bring you justice.
Tomorrow morning, I’ll degrade him
to the lower realm.
You think you can?
Yes!
Let go of me! What are you doing?
Let go of me!
Rogue!
Why are you so rude?
What’s going on?
Shouldn’t you be degraded?
I was trying to bring love
to the Heavenly Realm.
I just didn’t expect some accidents.
You abused your spiritual power
and disturbed the Heavenly Realm.
You’re not only weak,
but also irresponsible.
Do you think you’re better?
You have a good appearance,
but you’re indeed merciless.
What bad luck
does the Goddess of Snow have
to like you?
You knew yourself well enough
so that you didn’t come back.
Even when a God like you breathes
in front of me,
I’m afraid you’ll stain the air.
What are you doing?
I’m the future Chief God of Chaos.
Tianqi brought you up, didn’t he?
Yes, so what?
You’ve only learned bad habits.
Put me down!
What are you doing?
Today,
you were absent from Qionghua Banquet
and disturbed the Temple of Love.
You should be punished
with ten thunder strikes.
How dare you! Put me down!
Zhiyang deceived me to be your teacher.
He even told me
you were submissive and hardworking.
I hope
you won’t let him down.
Go tell Zhiyang
I punished you for him.
And he’s welcome.
Bai Jue, wait and see!
I’ll let you know
who reigns the God Realm!
I don’t know
why those Goddesses like Bai Jue.
For his long face?
For his reprimand?
Or for his frequent punishment?
The Goddess of Snow is so beautiful,
but he turns her down.
In story books,
love once begun, will never end.
If I fall in love with such a bad man,
I’ll be screwed.
Yeah. Bai Jue is so cold.
He can’t be as popular
as Tianqi.
Let alone Tianqi...
Think about Zhiyang.
The Ancestral God is our father.
And we were all bred
between the heaven and earth.
I’m the only loser.
They’re all powerful.
Is the Ancestral God not my real father?
My poor girl,
you have poor power, but a noble status.
You’re underestimated.
Yuemi, you’re the best to me.
You never want me to suffer, right?
Are you done?
Get to the point.
How do you want me to help again?
Help me to pull down Changyuan Hall.
- I’ve got something else to do.
- Yuemi!
Dear girl,
he’s Bai Jue,
the most powerful True God.
I can’t fight him,
even if I had tenfold power.
You can’t see me
be annoyed to death, can you?
Shall we ask Zhiyang
for some advice?
What happened?
I was reviewing the reports.
Why did you get me here
from Chaos Hall?
Look at her.
She was annoyed for the whole night
and had nothing to eat.
She even threatened to kill herself.
Who did that?
Who else could it be?
The God you got back.
Dear girl,
why are you eating nothing?
Yuemi, go get her
the Sweet Juice.
All right.
Don’t bother. I won’t eat anything.
I’m fine.
I’m alright. Alright.
Who bullied you?
Tell me and I’ll defend you.
Bai Jue, or who else?
He did something wrong first.
I reprimanded him a little.
Guess what?
In the face of Xueying,
he kicked me out of Changyuan Hall.
Expel him
from the God Realm immediately.
If he isn’t expelled,
I’ll starve myself to death.
Bai Jue?
You don’t want to?
I don’t mean that.
But it’s kind of a tough job.
Tough?
What makes it tough?
Everyone in the God Realm obeys you!
Are you partial to him, instead of me?
My little girl,
I’m certainly partial to you, right?
Shanggu, I don’t mean not to help you.
But Bai Jue is also the True God.
He’s as noble as me in the God Realm.
I can’t win if he fights me.
Unless the God Realm collapses,
I can’t expel him.
Don’t you...?
Don’t you have another option?
There is.
What is it?
Shanggu, you can improve yourself,
master the Power of Chaos,
take control of the instruction feather
of Chief God
and be the Chief God of Chaos.
When you’re the Chief God of Chaos,
you can not only expel him,
but also make him do whatever you want.
Good idea.
Zhiyang, it’s a good idea.
But...
I can’t do it in a short time, can I?
It’s not hard.
Learn all his skills.
After you succeed,
let’s fight him together
and expel him immediately.
Yeah.
When you come back
after completing your study,
no one dares to bully you again.
How could I learn from him?
Who am I? The Chief God of Chaos.
If I call him Master,
how disgraced I’ll be!
Shanggu!
Forget it.
Bai Jue was really out of line.
I’ll go to Changyuan Hall with you
and fight him.
If we fail,
I’ll run away with you.
Even if we have to
be unidentified immortals,
I will not let you suffer
in Changyuan Hall.
Be unidentified immortals?
How can you be unidentified immortals?
Considering Shanggu’s temper,
if she becomes an unidentified immortal,
she’ll be bullied, won’t she?
Hurry. Get packed for her
and send her to Puhua Cave
to be a matchmaker.
After you go to the lower realm,
it won’t be long
before you become
a respectable immortal.
I...
But...
But what?
You’re totally incompatible
with Bai Jue.
I won’t let you suffer.
I...
I what?
To live a comfortable life,
work for Puhua
and be an Immortal of Love.
I...
Yuemi, this is my home.
I’m not going anywhere.
It’s a deal, then.
I won’t let you meet Bai Jue again.
I won’t let you suffer at all.
Yuemi, get packed for her
and send her to Puhua Cave.
Wait, wait. I’ll go.
Go what?
I’ll go to Changyuan Hall
for cultivation.
In such a long life,
I believe I’ll learn all his skills
and expel him from the God Realm.
All right. Put on your shoes.
My girl, just sit down.
Be careful not to catch a cold.
(Changyuan Hall)
Look how naughty you are.
You come to see your teacher.
It’s my first day for classes,
I must be respected.
Last time, he kicked me out.
This time,
he must invite me in respectfully.
Greetings, Master Bai Jue.
Why are you bowing? Raise your heads.
Stop. Are you coming to be a disciple
or to screw the place?
Go. Be quick.
I’m here to learn skills from you,
Master Bai Jue.
Please kindly teach me.
Zhiyang told me that
you promised to teach me.
You’re the True God.
You won’t break your promise, will you?
I can teach you,
but you must promise three things.
Specifically?
I’ll even accept thirty things.
Take off your cloak.
Yuemi, did you hear that?
He asked me to take off my cloak.
How impolite!
Dear, bear with it.
In my place,
there’s no Chief God or Her Grace.
Take off your cloak of the Chief God
and wear plain dresses.
Until you leave my place,
you’re still an Attendant God
in Changyuan Hall.
Are you alright with it?
Bai Jue,
- Shanggu is...
- All right.
I will take it off.
I haven’t had the Power of Chaos yet
and I’m not the real Chief God.
Now that I’ve never enjoyed the status,
what’s the problem with taking it off?
What are you doing?
When you cultivate yourself here,
you mustn’t be distracted.
Destroy them and never touch them again.
Can you do that?
I’ve been carrying them
since I was little.
I can stop carrying them.
Why must them be destroyed?
When you want something,
you abandon something else.
If you can’t abandon
such prosaic things,
how can you be the Chief God?
Why don’t you be a joke?
If you don’t want to do that, leave.
I never teach anyone unwitting.
I’ll destroy them. I will.
Now that you can abandon them,
come on in.
You can really abandon them?
Bai Jue is right.
I must abandon something
for something else.
When I learn all skills from him,
I’ll first pull down his hall
to avenge all my treasure.
There’s the third thing to do.
How arrogant you are!
I guess you’ll no longer enjoy yourself.
Are you sincere to learn from me?
Yes. I’m completely sincere.
I’m not!
Who wants to always see your cold face?
Don’t put on an act.
When I become the Chief God,
I’ll torture you as I wish.
My salute to you, Master.
Comfortable, isn’t it?
A noble girl like me
respects you so much.
Even your Changyuan Hall is honored.
Honored?
You used Mind Reading on me?
How shameless!
You say you respect me,
but curse me in your heart.
Does it make you not shameless?
When I curse you a little,
does it really hurt you?
It’ll be your real power
if you can do what you want to do.
I’m waiting until you become
the Chief God
and torture me as you wish.
You sealed my spiritual power?
That’s the third thing.
Forget about your tiny power.
Now that you’ll learn from me,
you must obey my rules.
Come at seven tomorrow morning
and don’t be late.
What do you mean?
Master said that when you’re staying
in Changyuan Hall,
you’ll serve as the Attendant God
of the lowest level.
Every day, you can learn from me
the basic attending skills.
You’re simply his Spirit Beast.
Why do you think you can command me?
Master said that
you weren’t the Chief God in this place.
I take care of Changyuan Hall.
I’ll certainly teach you first
and you shall learn from me.
You’re obviously embarrassing me.
Where’s Bai Jue? I want to see him.
Master also said that
if you’re satisfied with anything,
you can leave
and you shall never come back
for cultivation.
I love sweeping.
I don’t like to get close to anyone.
Tianqi, behave yourself.
How did you do that?
What?
She’s sweeping the floor for you?
Work carefully!
Submissive
and hardworking.
Smart and never makes trouble?
Blame the one who said it.
Zhiyang said it.
If she weren’t important for our future,
do you think she could be admitted
to my place
considering her temper?
Bai Jue, Shanggu isn’t that bad.
You simply met her a couple of times.
After you get familiar with her,
you’ll know she’s innocent and lovely.
Innocent and lovely?
Yeah.
Will that enhance her spiritual power?
Or will it make her bear responsibility?
You!
I’m sorry. I’m sorry.
Come on. Have some water.
I didn’t mean that.
I really didn’t mean that.
Bai Jue,
you’re embarrassing me.
After I complete my study,
I’ll expel you from the God Realm!
This is the only existing copy
that Master most appreciates.
How can you...?
What do we do?
It’s from Yuemi. Enjoy it.
What an ugly handwriting!
Come on. Read it and I’ll carve.
Get up.
What? I learned writing from Zhiyang.
You don’t want it?
Are you trying to be indolent
so that I have to do all the work
in the yard?
I’m not!
Then get up and read.
It’s too good for your master.
Look and learn.
Master.
Come with me, Shanggu.
How much do you know
about the Three Realms?
It’s an easy question.
I don’t like cultivation,
but I like plays and story books.
As for the Three Realms...
Seventy thousand years ago,
the Ancestral God divided the world
into three parts.
In the Nether World
of the Extreme North,
God of Devil and Devils are imprisoned.
Where the Nether World is contiguous
to Immortals and Demons
has been sealed
with the Barrier of Chaos
and totally isolated.
Immortals live in the southwest.
There are many blessed caves
where many immortals and immortal clans
have come into being.
Demons live in the southeast.
They’re mostly spiritual beings
who live in groups.
It’s been days since you came.
If you pass the exam today,
I’ll formally teach you spells
and universe rules.
Are you serious?
This is the Red Blood Forest
where Tiger Demons live.
There’s thin spiritual power here
and it’s hard for cultivation.
Tiger Demons suffer from that.
If you manage to make them smile,
you’ll pass the exam.
Isn’t that too hard?
Most Tiger Demons are serious men.
I’m not an acrobat.
Even if I’m a God,
I can’t manipulate others’ emotions.
As the Chief God,
you must keep everyone happy and safe.
If you can’t even do this,
how will you take on
heavy responsibilities?
You’re my teacher.
You should have taught me
how to solve problems.
But you set a difficult problem
to humiliate me.
If you think I can’t make it,
you can resign to Zhiyang.
Why do you pretend you’re teaching me?
I don’t mean to set a difficult problem.
I simply overestimated you.
Forget it.
I’ll give you an easier exam.
Go get something
from the Red Blood Forest.
Wait.
Such an easy job to placate Tiger Demons
will not frustrate me.
In case of difficulty,
you shouldn’t easily give up.
Save your breath. Just wait and see.
Shanggu, what happened?
Tell me.
Did Bai Jue embarrass you again?
He’s always hard to get close to.
All these years, no one gets to him,
except Hongri.
When you learn from him,
you will suffer.
Don’t take it seriously.
Tomorrow is your birthday.
You like the buzz.
Shall I hold a big party for you?
If you feel bored
and don’t want to take classes,
today is the spring day of Demons,
where demon flowers bloom,
let me take you for a walk there.
Demons?
Yeah, you’re a Demon God.
I should have asked you.
Tianqi,
do you know how to make a demon happy?
Make a demon happy?
We demons are straightforward and loyal.
Give him the sincerest care.
The sincerest care?
For example,
hug him.
The sincerest care?
Your Grace.
Greetings, Your Grace.
Don’t bother. You may rise.
Your Grace, tomorrow is your birthday.
We know you don’t like cultivation.
So, we prepared you some novelties.
We wonder if you’ll like them.
I will.
What you offer me every time
always makes me happy.
Have a look, Your Grace.
It took us a long time to prepare them.
A long time?
You’re so serious
for my ten thousandth birthday?
Is it because
you’ve earned too much offering?
Don’t tease us, Your Grace.
We’re not God of Love or Wealth.
We won’t have too much offering.
Your birthday is a great event
in the God Realm.
We should be serious.
Yes, yes.
I’ll accept them, then.
But gifts blind eyes.
What do you want from me? Tell me.
We...
If you want nothing, I’ll go.
Your Grace,
I do want to ask you for a favor.
Go ahead.
We quite admire Master Bai Jue.
Unfortunately, no stranger is allowed
to enter Changyuan hall.
Now, you’re cultivating yourself there.
Your Grace,
for the sake of our admiration
for Master Bai Jue,
- please help us...
- Be a matchmaker for you?
I never expected to do what Puhua does
when I’m in Changyuan Hall.
How unexpected!
Tell me.
What makes you like that cold God?
What makes you?
I don’t understand.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪