=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 2=
I never expected to do what Puhua does
when I’m in Changyuan Hall.
How unexpected!
Tell me.
What makes you like that cold God?
What makes you?
I don’t understand.
Never mind.
For the sake of your gifts,
I have a reason to help you.
Thank you, Your Grace.
Enjoy the tea, please, Master.
Hongri, get out of the way!
I won’t.
Then don’t blame us for being rude!
Master, I used three barriers.
I really don’t know how they got in.
Where’s Shanggu? She isn’t back yet?
Since you asked Her Grace
to solve the problem of Tiger Demons,
Her Grace came back a few times,
but didn’t stay for long.
Maybe she’s trying to solve the problem.
Go get packed and we’ll go
to the lower realm tomorrow.
What about Her Grace’s birthday?
You won’t go to the party?
I don’t like the buzz.
But you should at least
go and greet her.
This morning,
I prepared the washing water for Master.
He looked at me a few times.
What makes you so proud?
I saw his handwriting.
Did you see it?
When he was doing the calligraphy,
he looked so handsome and attractive.
That’s nothing.
The Goddess of Snow even danced for him.
She did?
I heard the music
Master played last night.
They made a perfect couple.
Her Grace helped us
to get close to Master.
Her birthday party is about to begin.
Let’s get in for celebration.
Yeah.
I’ve got a better gift for her.
Maybe,
it’ll be us
who can approach Master tomorrow.
Your Grace, happy birthday.
Bai Jue.
Greetings, Master Bai Jue.
I’ll ask Zhiyang
to issue an instruction feather.
From this day on,
you mustn’t enter Changyuan Hall.
You’re the Chief God of Chaos,
but you sold me out
for such vulgar things.
What a joke!
And you.
Leave with your vulgar gifts.
- Yes.
Those are gifts for me.
Why can you decide?
Right.
I can’t be a teacher
for a vulgarian like you.
After I leave,
go explain to Zhiyang yourself.
Never see you again.
Behave yourself, Your Grace.
This time,
you really disappointed Master.
Forget it.
We’re used to Master’s coldness
over the years.
He’s been so cold
in the past ten thousand years.
Her Grace was scolded most.
Why do you feel so sad?
Master... Master...
He banned me
from entering his hall again.
Look at your tears. What happened?
For your information, Master,
at Her Grace’s birthday party,
Master Bai Jue flew into a rage
and banned us
from entering his hall again.
Well,
he never has compassion for girls.
You know what?
Don’t take it seriously.
But he’s serious this time.
Even Her Grace was scolded.
What? Even Shanggu was scolded?
Why can you still read?
Tell me. What did you do to Shanggu?
Why can’t I feel
her power?
When she was admitted to Changyuan Hall,
I sealed her power.
You!
Do you know she’s missing?
Don’t be anxious.
It’s going to rain soon.
Considering she can’t bear
with any hardship,
she’ll go back after she’s wet in rain.
Bai Jue, what exactly did she do?
What makes you hate her so much?
What did she do?
She’s covetous for treasure.
Shortly after she did cultivation
in my hall,
she accepted lavish gifts
and took Goddesses into my hall.
How ridiculous!
Lavish gifts?
Bai Jue, you get her wrong.
She didn’t do that
to get lavish gifts,
but to solve your problem for her.
There he is.
It’s Master Bai Jue.
It’s really him.
Yeah.
300 miles to the west
of the Demon Region.
Mount Jingyou. Near Qianshui River.
I found it!
Tianqi is right.
Demons are straightforward.
Only the sincerest happiness
will make them happy.
You mean I get her wrong?
I’m warning you.
You must get her back
and apologize to her honestly.
It was her ten thousandth birthday!
Who could bear with such humiliation?
How shall I apologize?
I ate the birthday peach you gave her.
Sweet, isn’t it?
It’s as hard and puckery as you!
Did you lose your taste sense?
Anyway, I thought about it for you.
You like stone carving, don’t you?
Carve a stone bracelet for her.
Girls like jewels.
Don’t pretend you didn’t hear me.
Remember what I’m telling you.
You must get Shanggu back.
Otherwise, I’ll...
I...
Master Tianqi.
Don’t call me.
Come over.
Master Tianqi!
Otherwise, I’ll take him to Taichu Hall
and heat the wine for me every day!
Master Tianqi, you...
What?
Master, we should go find Her Grace.
If it rains heavily,
and she has no power available,
she...
(Changyuan Hall)
Why are you not taking shelter
inside the hall?
Having pity or reflecting on yourself?
You said never see me again, didn’t you?
Why are you coming to me again?
Give my power back to me.
A True God
lives as long as the world
and lasts as long as the universe.
But with sealed power,
he’s merely common.
Put it on. Don’t catch a cold.
Is this an apology?
Will you forgive me?
Forgive you for the robe only? Never!
The Red Blood Forest is on the border
between Gods and Devils.
The battle seventy thousand years ago
led to rare spiritual power in it.
What you did
can only make them happy for a while,
but not forever.
I asked Tianqi.
Even he can’t solve the problem.
Why you want me to do it,
you’re embarrassing me.
Tianqi can’t solve the problem.
Nor can Zhiyang or me.
But you can.
Me?
No one can keep
the God Realm in peace, but you.
No one can make Tiger Demons
happy and safe, but you.
It’s the first exam for you.
It’s also your lifelong mission
as the Chief God of the Three Realms.
I thought you looked down on me.
Zhiyang doesn’t even let me
touch the reports.
My birthday party
is always of high classification.
Gods who come to it
can’t even get in without treasure.
You’re Master Bai Jue,
but what a cheap gift you’re giving me!
Is it enough, then?
I never expect him
to make me happy.
What a rare chance!
I must give vent on my anger.
I’m the Chief God.
No matter how weak I am,
others only dare to gossip behind me.
But what have you done?
You humiliated me in public
over and over again.
What do you want me to do?
I’m not a mean girl.
Well, seal your own power
for half an hour.
All right.
We’re even, then.
Seal your own power
for half an hour.
All right.
How come?
You sealed your power.
Are we even?
You must have cheated.
Without power, you’re common.
I don’t believe this.
Now you do?
The life is long and the world is big.
Once you become the Chief God of Chaos,
you may know new rules and definitions
for everything in the Three Realms.
It’s getting late.
Your Grace, go to sleep early.
Wait.
How did you do that?
If you want to learn it,
come at seven tomorrow morning
and don’t be late.
The chaos appears in the world
and enriches the air.
The world makes up for it in return.
Then the Power of Chaos never stops.
Tun means abundance.
Abundance is where everything starts.
(Endure the Hardship)
Everything is confused at first.
Meng means ignorance.
Ignorance must be cleared out.
So, Xu is right after that.
Bai Jue does have a way to instruct her.
Xu means diet.
There’s a dispute about diet.
It was eight thousand years ago
when Shanggu read a book last time.
Well done.
You know how to control her.
Shanggu is often criticized
for her weak power.
Considering her competitive temper,
it’s the best way to prod her.
Shortly after you’re back,
you know such gossips?
When I want to know something,
I’ll get to know it in a day.
Shanggu hasn’t made any progress.
It’s all because of him, he...
Shanggu said that
you didn’t even allow her
to review the reports?
Because she always made trouble.
When I was travelling
in the lower realm,
I heard of many interesting things.
For example?
The Cold Swamp is in the hinterland
of Snake Demons,
but many Crocodile Demons
stay there, too.
Its ownership was in dispute.
A True God
made a wrong comment on the report
and earmarked Crocodile Demons
into the region of Snake Demons.
So far, they have fought
for a thousand years.
Who was it
that made such a trouble?
I did.
You know that.
At that time,
I just took over the affairs
on behalf of Ancestral God
and I wasn’t experienced.
It could be understandable
when I made a mistake.
Yeah, Zhiyang.
When you first took power,
you made trouble, too.
Why are you overcautious
when it comes to Shanggu?
Tianqi, try the tea.
Isn’t there a burning smell?
Ice Cube,
where did you get such good tea?
I got it from Flaming Woods.
What’s the story about that?
When Zhiyang went to the lower realm
for some business,
a female immortal in Flaming Woods
kidnapped him and forcibly married him.
What?
A serious True God in the God Realm
was forcibly married in the lower realm?
What are you laughing at?
More than that.
I’ve heard some of your love affairs
in Yoyo Valley, the Indifference Cliff
and the Loss Sea.
Come on, Zhiyang!
I’m known as the most flippant
and the most dissolute in the God Realm.
But I think
everyone is deceived
by your serious acting.
What do you know?
Those were accidents.
Don’t bring them up again.
They were old stories.
Ice Cube, have I offended you?
You haven’t.
But you told me something.
Submissive, hardworking
and never makes trouble.
Why must I learn
such childish books?
Bai Jue, come over!
I told you. You can offend anyone,
but the vengeful cold man.
Yeah.
Look. The barrier has another crack.
Why is it coming to the God Realm?
I’d like to meet the Chief God of Chaos
by the Nether World at March
for peace negotiations between us,
from Xuanyi.
Are you kidding me?
Xuanyi asked to see me?
What do you mean?
He’s Overlord Xuanyi
who kills people in cold blood.
Are you really letting me go?
Devils are imprisoned in the Nether World
for seventy thousand years.
But in recent months,
the barrier keeps splitting.
Many devils flooded and made trouble
in the regions of Immortals and Demons.
Zhiyang, now that the barrier
of the Nether World will collapse,
and devils will come to us,
why don’t we accept his invitation
and go there to check?
Are you listening to me? I mean...
But Xuanyi is scheming.
I’m afraid he’s up to something else.
Precisely.
He’s been hiding in the Nether World
for seventy years ago.
He must be up to something evil.
Now, he asked to see Shanggu.
There must be a trap.
Yes. There must be!
Yeah, Zhiyang, how about not...?
Xuanyi used to be
the Leader of True Gods.
If he hadn’t fallen as a devil,
he would have been
the Chief God of Chaos.
Now, Ancestral God fell.
There’s no Chief God in the God Realm.
If Devils start a war again,
people will die and suffer.
If Shanggu can go have a negotiation,
she might get us away from the disaster.
You’re right.
We can’t let the disaster happen again
which happened seventy thousand years ago.
Come on.
I don’t want a war, either.
But look at me.
If I go, I’ll die.
Won’t I?
Bai Jue, I’ll leave it to you.
You must teach Shanggu enough skills
within three months.
Then we’ll go
to the Nether World together.
Come on. I’m the Chief God, right?
Don’t you listen to my opinion?
What Chief God?
I can’t even make my own decision.
Even before I become the real Chief God,
I’m dying already.
He’s Overlord Xuanyi.
He nearly defeated the Ancestral God.
If I go, I’ll die,
won’t I?
What are you going to do, then?
Run away. Or will I wait to die?
Did you just say
you would run away?
No. I won’t ever run away.
God of Kunlun just had a son.
I’ll go congratulate him.
What about the Nether World?
I can’t be in two places at once.
I won’t go with you. Sorry for that.
Seriously?
Sure.
Good. I don’t need to bother, then.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
By the way, find a good weapon
as soon as you can.
In case you meet some devils,
it may help you survive.
There’s no devil on Mount Kunlun.
Xuanyi wants you.
Wherever you go,
Devils will be after you.
It’s easy to find you
within three months.
Are you still leaving?
Tomorrow.
Tomorrow I’ll go to your hall
and learn skills carefully.
You don’t need to wait till tomorrow.
Tell me.
Did you just let him take Shanggu away?
Considering her temper,
how can she bear
with Bai Jue’s instruction?
If you can, go instruct her.
I!
We tried for ten thousand years,
but she made no progress at all.
She’ll face Xuanyi and Devils this time.
In a thousand years, she’ll face
the Tribulation of Chaos.
We can protect her for years,
but not forever.
She’s the future Chief God.
She’ll grow up sooner or later.
This is Mount Lookout
where I cultivated myself
in the lower realm.
Stay here for the cultivation.
I was doing good in Changyuan Hall.
Why must I stay here?
Devils are cunning. Xuanyi is the worst.
Considering your weak power,
how can you go to the Nether World
without hard cultivation?
This is a quiet place
and no one will disturb you.
Go back to the God Realm
in three months.
There’re strict etiquettes
in the God Realm.
I learn cultivation from you,
but I didn’t formally acknowledge you.
So, you can’t make any decision for me.
Master is simply a title. I don’t care.
I decide
when I go back to the God Realm
and when I go to the Nether World.
If you find my plan improper,
do as you wish.
Why is there a barrier?
Mount Lookout is the common border
of Immortal, Demon and Devil Realms.
Without my barrier,
how could this place be in peace?
I don’t want to stay here
for even a minute.
Let me go back to Changyuan Hall now.
You didn’t formally acknowledge me.
You can go wherever you want.
Why do you bother to ask me?
Bai Jue.
I have no compassion for girls.
As you wish, Your Grace.
Forget it.
I must be humble when I need his help.
After I learn some of his skills,
I’ll try to get out of here.
I’m born to be generous.
I won’t argue with you.
I hear that stars over Mount Lookout
are the most beautiful.
I’ll stay as you wish.
For only three months, anyway.
Bai Jue? Leave!
So quickly? I was freaked out.
I was nearly eaten.
In case of danger,
you only know to depend on stronger men
or shrink back.
Your nerve
is really shocking me.
I didn’t mean failing to fight them.
I simply didn’t realize
what was going on.
Let alone you have weak power,
what did you do
in the past ten thousand years?
You can’t even use any basic move.
They’re devils of low grade.
Stop giving me a lesson.
You said there was a barrier,
wasn’t there?
Then how did the devils break in?
How can I train you
without letting you fight
with real devils?
If I have a good weapon,
I can also kill devils like you do.
You can?
You! I...
I can’t hold it.
You want a weapon, don’t you?
You!
Are you giving me a weapon?
You’re trying to crush me.
I simply want to let you know
devils are not immortals
who always flatter you.
Tianqi and Zhiyang
can’t protect you forever, either.
One day, you’ll have real fights
with devils.
If you still don’t
cultivate yourself carefully,
your purest spiritual power
which you can’t use
will make you enjoy your status,
but also get you dead.
You’re powerful. You’re always right.
All right?
Do you know why you can’t
get through your God vessels?
You think I don’t want that?
I want to be stronger, too.
But...
But Tianqi spoils you
or Zhiyang is too busy to teach you?
You!
At seven tomorrow morning,
I’ll help you unblock your God vessels.
That’s great.
When I have unblocked God vessels,
I’ll make you feel sorry.
Your Grace, the day breaks. Get up!
What’s the time now?
Even the cock hasn’t crowed yet.
I’m not getting up.
Ice Cube!
He tricked me again!
There are three levels
for the spiritual power.
The first level is the Power of Chaos
that the Ancestral God used
to create the world.
The second level is the Power of Rules
that True Gods have,
including God power, immortal power
and demon powder.
The third level is the power
of the lower realm.
Devils are coming?
I practiced till midnight last night.
I only slept for four hours
before you got me up for cultivation.
However strong I am,
I can’t hold that.
Sleepy?
Let me help you wake up.
Wait.
I’m quite awake. Let’s continue.
There’re three levels
of the spiritual power.
Wait. Three levels
of the spiritual power...
But why didn’t you mention
the devil power?
Because the devil power
isn’t naturally generated by the world.
Xuanyi had the Power of Chaos,
just like you.
He was the successor
of the Chief God of Chaos.
Now that there wasn’t devil power,
how did Xuanyi turn into Overlord
and how did devils come into being?
Seventy thousand years ago,
Xuanyi was dissatisfied with the way
the Ancestral God ruled the world.
Before he inherited
the instruction feather of Chief God,
he had fought for the throne.
But when he was nearly defeated,
he suddenly went against
the heavenly rule
and forcibly absorbed evil spirit
from dead immortals.
Puffs of evil spirit mixed
with the Power of Chaos in his body,
ending up as the devil power
that could engulf everything.
Evil men in the lower realm
cultivated in the same way,
and became his subordinates.
Then, Devils came into being.
So, that’s how Devils appeared.
After defeating Xuanyi,
the Ancestral God broke the space
and vanished.
His last breath bred you,
who’s the new leader of Four True Gods.
With the Power of Chaos,
you should always warn yourself
not to do what Xuanyi did.
When you inherit
the instruction feather of Chief God,
you’ll bear the responsibility
to defend the world
and open the Human Realm.
I know.
I’m born with the responsibility
to defend the Heavenly Realm,
God Realm and the upcoming Human Realm.
I know that.
With great power
comes great responsibility.
I have very little power.
I think it’s better that
you, Zhiyang and Tianqi
defend the world.
So, you want to learn.
I don’t mean not to learn it.
I told you, didn’t I?
I have blocked God vessels.
I’ll hit your God vessels with force.
It depends on you
if they can be unblocked.
What will you do?
Relax.
Are you trying to hit me again
with an excuse?
Feeling anything?
No.
No?
Be quick. Take back your power.
I don’t know how.
I feel so bad. Too much power.
If it continues, you’ll go insane.
Do something.
I’m still young,
and I don’t want to die.
Close your eyes.
I’ll help you dredge your power.
No offence, Shanggu.
♪Time disturb my feelings♪
Don’t be scared, Shanggu.
Feel it with your heart.
♪Hold tightly with your warm hand♪
♪Look up at the meteor
across the darkness♪
♪Your tall figure♪
♪Is even clear in the haze♪
♪I save some time♪
♪To exchange it for you♪
♪Every second sounds so sweet♪
♪Until I meet you♪
♪I make every attempt♪
♪To have the next life♪
♪When we meet again♪
♪I’ll travel around with you
without hesitation♪
♪Listen♪
♪We feel each other♪
♪And get close♪
♪For a little talk♪
I can’t fall asleep at all.
Why does it feel like this
with unblocked God vessels?
If only I could talk to Yuemi!
♪Hope♪
Ice Cube,
don’t think you can buy me over
with your handsome appearance.
I have unblocked God vessels now,
and I’ll leave here
after I learn some skills.
Your Grace,
Master asked me
to teach you today.
Where’s Bai Jue?
Master...
He’s sick.
Sick?
Is it serious? Let me check on him.
No, no. He just has a cold.
And he coughs.
He doesn’t want you
to risk any contagion.
According to Tianqi,
when I have unblocked God vessels,
if I practice hard day and night,
I’ll greatly improve my power
and get twofold results
with half the effort.
But come on.
Why is he sick now?
I would think he pretended to be sick.
Your Grace,
let’s go for the cultivation.
You don’t want Master to worry about you
even when he’s sick, do you?
Right.
Your Grace, you can’t get in!
Your Grace.
Your Grace, Master is really sick.
The day is breaking. Get up!
You’re my teacher!
I’m doing
what you did to me.
Why do you feel so weak?
You’re really sick?
Are you done?
I’m sorry, I...
I...
I thought...
You thought everybody liked
to get up late like you did.
I’m sorry.
Get out.
You wronged Master!
Your Grace,
you were born by the residual breath
of the Ancestral God
with blocked God vessels.
If it were easy to unblock,
why didn’t Master Tianqi or Zhiyang
help you do that?
If Master Bai Jue
weren’t powerful enough,
it would be you who’s lying in bed now.
Look at me.
I didn’t sleep last night.
But I feel so energetic
as if there were continuous
spiritual power
coming out of my body.
Enjoy the cultivation yourself.
I’m too humble to teach you
and I’m leaving.
Where are you leaving?
Master lost so much power.
He needs some medicinal tea.
I’ll go with you.
Can you be so kind?
I just don’t want to owe him.
What does he like?
Why do you ask?
Just asking.
It’s the medicinal tea I just made.
Would you like some?
I know you’re angry with me.
If you’re so angry,
punish me as you want.
Punish you for such a small thing?
I’m not that bored.
Thank you for unblocking my God vessels.
We even...
I mean
I didn’t know what happened.
I couldn’t stop that day.
I didn’t mean to absorb your power
and even flirt with you.
I don’t care.
What?
Nothing.
You’re so nice to me.
But I was rude to you.
I feel sorry.
Didn’t you say
you would make me feel sorry?
Why would you feel sorry?
I was just joking.
You still remember?
I have a perfect memory.
I...
I never owe anyone.
How do you want me to repay you?
When you cultivate yourself hard
and manage to fight
against the Devil God,
I’ll be relieved.
I swear I’ll impress you.
Go. I’ll teach you swordsmanship.
Swordsmanship?
It’s so great
to have unblocked God vessels.
I can even learn swordsmanship.
You and Yuemi
have known each other for long.
She’s among the best in swordsmanship.
How much of Six Moves of Extreme Yin
have you learnt?
Six Moves what?
How about Star Swordsmanship
or Cloud Swordsmanship?
Never heard of any.
You’ve stayed with Yuemi
for ten thousand years.
What did she teach you?
To drink, play dice, play cards,
watch plays and read story books.
I’ll teach you.
Got it?
Yes.
Try it.
♪Where are you♪
♪Your young face♪
♪Goes with memories♪
♪And is sealed in time♪
I didn’t see it clearly.
Could you show me again?
Just this once.
♪Dreams are imperfect♪
♪I can’t help missing the past♪
♪What’s in my hand is
what I can’t get over♪
♪How are we destined to meet♪
♪Tide rushes and the moon rises♪
♪The trip takes a thousand years♪
♪Wake up the clouds♪
♪But can’t wake up the helpless love♪
♪It’s dreamlike♪
♪And it’s also aimless♪
♪For one single glance at you♪
♪I don’t regret cultivating myself♪
♪Even if I have to love alone♪
♪I’ll never stop loving you♪
How about this time? Remember?
Yes.
It’s not hard to play swordsmanship.
Master, you’re in good mood today.
Nice tea.
Her Grace picked it
behind the mountain yesterday.
No wonder you look so happy.
The water is good.
Her Grace also collected it
from the pistils of flowers
early this morning.
It must be sweet.
What’s your point?
I want to say that
you and Her Grace
often argue.
But you also care about each other.
As far as I see,
you haven’t had the formal ceremony
to be her teacher,
but you care about each other
more than others.
Are you getting yourself
to heat the wine?
Watch this, Ice Cube!
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪