=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 3=
Master, you’re in good mood today.
Nice tea.
Her Grace picked it
behind the mountain yesterday.
No wonder you look so happy.
The water is good.
Her Grace also collected it
from the pistils of flowers
early this morning.
It must be sweet.
What’s your point?
I want to say that
you and Her Grace
often argue.
But you also care about each other.
As far as I see,
you haven’t had the formal ceremony
to be her teacher,
but you care about each other
more than others.
Are you getting yourself
to heat the wine?
Watch this, Ice Cube!
You can’t even dodge that.
Looks like my spiritual power
has increased a lot.
Not to mention one Xuanyi,
even there is a group of Xuanyi,
I won’t be afraid at all.
Don’t get carried away.
What do you want to do?
I’m happy that you made it.
Stop there.
You’ve played such a trick many times.
I know what you mean.
What do I mean?
With that stance and look,
I’m sure you want to take me
to the Nether World to train me.
When I get beaten nearly to death,
you will jump out
and preach at me,
telling me not to be carried away.
You are pretty smart.
Thank you for your compliment.
I appreciate it.
Are you scared now?
You can’t provoke me
into doing anything now.
I haven’t practiced enough yet.
Next time.
Stay here. I’m going to the God Realm.
Yes.
Bai Jue, why are you back alone?
Where is Shanggu?
Bai Jue, Shanggu is naughty in nature.
You mustn’t hit her
if she makes any trouble.
I need four things.
Phoenix Feather, Black Tortoise Shell,
Dragon Horn and Xuanjin Iron.
You want to make a weapon?
Any of our weapons
can be invincible in the world.
And you want to use four items one time.
Are you going to poke a hole in the sky?
Not for me. It’s for Shanggu.
I’m relieved to know
that you are so attentive to Shanggu.
Relieved?
Shanggu’s vessels haven’t been opened.
Even the weapon is made,
she still can’t use it.
I have got through her vessels.
You have?
How did you do that?
Your Grace, you have
practiced for four hours.
Take a rest.
I can’t.
I finally find the feeling today.
I must practice more moves.
You wouldn’t get up at all
a few days ago.
How did you get the hang of it
so quickly?
Cut it out.
That’s nonsense!
Don’t you know how powerful
Shanggu’s chaotic state is?
You two acted so rashly.
You might become dust
if anything goes wrong.
Why didn’t you ask us to protect you?
Yeah.
No offence, Shanggu.
Anyway, I have got through her vessels.
You wanted me to teach her,
and I have my own way to do it.
You...
Never mind.
Xuanyi is what matters now.
It’s good that you are strict with her.
Xuanjin Iron is in the North Sea
of the Heavenly Realm.
You just opened up her vessels.
I guess your power also got diminished.
I’ll get it for you later.
It’s okay. Just a piece of iron.
I will get it myself.
Ice Cube.
Why do you care about Shanggu
so much all of a sudden?
Listen, you can’t fall in love with her.
You can’t be more boring.
Bai Jue.
Shanggu only had
the power of an immortal.
Now her God vessels are open.
I think she will have
her first divine trial soon.
You must stay cautious
when you are with her.
Don’t let your guard down.
Don’t let your guard down!
The demonic miasma?
Your Grace, there is no
barrier here.
Let’s go back to the bamboo house.
Your Grace, what are you doing?
I’ll see what those demons got.
I’ll be right back.
No! Come back!
It’s dangerous! Your Grace!
Come back! Your Grace!
There is no need to be scared.
My God vessels are open now.
A few demons won’t be a problem to me.
That’s it? You are too weak.
No.
If I lose here,
Bai Jue will mock me.
Just a bunch of demons.
Let me show you what I got.
Master.
Where is Shanggu?
Master, you are finally back.
Her Grace went to fight with
demons on her own.
That’s quite a big fight
with the demons.
No.
This is her divine trial.
My goodness.
This thunder trial
is much more scary
than the normal thunder.
Why does the thunder trial
happen so suddenly?
She just had her vessels open
and the trial clouds are so violent.
If she inherits
the instruction feather one day,
I’m afraid the world will be
turned upside down.
How lucky I am.
Even the thunder can’t hit me.
What are you so fierce about?
I dare you to hit me again.
Her foundation is not solid.
If she gets hit by the thunder,
her root might get hurt.
Bai Jue.
What is it?
I’ve almost mastered these moves.
When will you take me
to the Nether World for training?
I’m quite surprised by
your excessive confidence.
What do you mean?
You should know
you might die at the hands of the demons
if anything goes wrong.
What a coincidence.
It went pretty well today.
I not only defeated the demons,
but also survived the divine trial.
You used to be angry at me
because I was afraid of demons and lazy.
Now I am diligent.
I volunteered to challenge the demons.
But you got angry again.
Don’t you think you are
too difficult to get along with?
For me?
You can give it back to me
if you don’t want it.
Why would I not want it?
You gave me a carrot
and then used a stick.
Is it because you think
you reprimanded me
too harshly and you feel
guilty about it?
I just can’t bear to see
someone is too weak
to protect herself.
You became nice to me so suddenly.
Is it because you fall for me?
My taste is not that bad.
All across the Three Realms,
you are not the only one
who falls for me.
There are countless men out there
who are more handsome
and gentler than you.
They are way better than you.
Can’t you even take some bad reviews?
Cut it out.
I have read some plays.
Do you think
I will fall into your trick?
Bai Jue?
Bai Jue, what’s wrong with you?
Hongri!
Your master fainted because of me!
(Xuanyi)
He helped her pass the trial
and make the sword.
That little Chief God
is really special to Bai Jue.
Interesting.
Overlord.
How is it going?
You were right about it.
The Chief God at the Pilgrimage Hall
has had her vessels open.
(Moyu)
The demons I sent are no match for her.
Bai Jue does have something special.
Zhiyang failed to enlighten her even he
taught her for ten thousand years.
But Bai Jue got through her
God vessels within a few days.
I’d like to meet our little Chief God.
Send people to keep an eye on
Mount Lookout.
Report to me if you get any news.
Yes.
As a True God,
how did he just faint like that?
What happened just now?
Just now... nothing happened.
He gave me a sword and then...
What sword?
Master actually made a sword for you.
I’ve been serving him for
tens of thousands of years.
I’ve never seen him
treat anyone so well.
Is it that hard
to make a sword?
Your Grace, your source of power
is different from Master’s.
Considering his status now,
making a weapon for you
would impair his spirit
and shorten his lifespan.
Shorten his lifespan?
How would that happen?
He is a True God. He lives as long as
the heaven and the earth.
Do you really think
the thunder can’t strike you
because you are
the successor of the Chief God?
My master took
those forty-nine thunders for you,
which impaired his spiritual power.
How lucky I am.
Even the thunder can’t strike me.
He even made a weapon for you.
No wonder he lost half of his life.
I usually see him acting arbitrarily.
I didn’t know he did so much for me.
Master’s spiritual power got impaired.
I need to go back to the God Realm
and ask Master Zhiyang for help.
Your Grace, take care of Master for me.
Bai Jue is injured now.
The barrier will be undercut
and the demons in Mount Lookout
will surely notice it.
Go to re-set the barrier
and don’t let the demons in.
But Master...
I owe this to him.
It’s my turn to pay him back.
Well done. Bai Jue.
How can you be so scheming?
You got hurt
so badly for me.
How am I going to
tease you and contradict you again?
Never mind.
I should have
taken these thunders.
I’ll give the power back to you.
I don’t even know
how to transfer my spiritual power.
I’m so useless.
Bai Jue taught me before.
The spiritual power resides in
my original being.
Right.
My original being.
♪Where are you♪
♪Your young face♪
♪Goes with memories♪
♪And is sealed in time♪
♪My thoughts in eyes are now
blocked between my eyebrows♪
♪I can’t see the injuries♪
♪Dreams are imperfect♪
Why are your hands still so cold?
♪I can’t help missing the past♪
Don’t worry.
I will always be here for you.
♪What I can’t get over♪
You must get better soon.
Overlord.
The barrier of Mount Lookout
has been showing signs of instability
since last night.
The barrier is collapsing.
Looks like Bai Jue’s original being
suffered great damage.
Let’s take this chance
to meet them.
His temperature finally goes up.
He should be getting better now.
Don’t get me wrong.
I’m here to see
if you are getting better.
I’m about seventy percent recovered.
Who saved me?
Not me.
Tianqi or Zhiyang?
Tianqi...
He...
Why do you look so pale?
I...
I was worried about
your condition and I barely slept.
But I will make it up
after I get some sleep later.
Hongri told me
that you made a sword
and took the thunders for me.
It’s no big deal.
It’s no big deal for you,
but it’s a big deal for me.
I’ve decided.
Rites and law are strict
in the God Realm.
I haven’t performed the ritual to
formally acknowledge you as my teacher.
I, the Chief God, Shanggu
came to learn from
the True God, Bai Jue.
I will never disobey your order
from now on.
Even if you are arbitrary and assertive,
I won’t be mad at you anymore.
There are countless ways in the world.
We shall never stop learning.
Are you willing to proceed with me?
Since you brought it up,
I’ll take you as my apprentice.
You and I will proceed together
from now on.
Why are you so enlightened today?
I’m not enlightened.
I just feel upset at the thought of
the war between gods and demons.
Those Goddesses,
you, Zhiyang and Tianqi
will get hurt because of it.
Don’t worry.
I will cultivate myself
with great concentration.
I’m glad that you can think in this way.
But I have one more thing to ask you.
Go ahead.
When did I act arbitrarily?
You must be kidding.
I don’t like jokes.
Master, you are awake.
What’s wrong?
The barrier between Mount Lookout
and the Nether World is collapsing.
I’m worried that the demons
will come to invade again.
Those demons won’t spare a moment.
I’m going to change my clothes.
Wait for me outside.
Okay.
You haven’t fully recovered yet.
It’s okay.
Bai Jue, help!
I like to see the way you protect me.
The Nether World
is quite different from
what I thought before.
The Ancestral God created the world
without partiality.
The Nether World was also
one of the blessed places.
But in order to imprison the demons,
the Gods sealed this place.
What kind of flower is that?
It’s pretty.
That’s Deicide Flower.
It’s highly toxic.
Long time no see, Bai Jue.
Shanggu, he is Overlord Xuanyi.
You mustn’t make eye contact with him.
This smart and cute girl
must be the little Chief God.
Sorry that I offended you
at the barrier.
I just want to invite you
here for a drink.
Xuanyi, she can’t drink much
and she knows nothing about wine.
Don’t waste it.
What if I insist?
What are you nervous about?
I just want to have
a good chat with her.
Shanggu!
Where’s Bai Jue?
What did you do to him?
Don’t worry. He is fine.
Only when he is not around
can we have a good talk.
Well, little Chief God.
Are you satisfied with my arrangement?
He is Overlord Xuanyi.
You mustn’t make eye contact with him.
Satisfied. I’m very satisfied.
Your arrangement is
novel and interesting.
Zhiyang doesn’t allow me
to play at all in the God Realm.
That old-fashioned man
hasn’t changed for
seventy thousand years.
If you like,
you can stay here for a few more days.
I know how boring the God Realm is
better than you do.
You are right.
They are all old-fashioned
in the God Realm.
With such a temper,
I guess you were brought up by Yuemi.
You know Yuemi?
She used to steal wine in my hall
when she was a kid.
The time has passed
and things are different now.
The clan of demons has been
imprisoned here for years.
If you are willing to guide
the clan of demons to a good direction,
I think the Gods will let you come back.
What a good way to look at it.
But I almost wiped out
the God Realm back then,
how would they be willing to
welcome me back?
I just saw the way
Bai Jue looked at you.
You two look really good together.
You must be joking.
Well...
I have nothing to do with that Ice Cube.
If Bai Jue hears that,
I’m afraid he will be upset.
Why would he feel upset?
I’ve known Bai Jue
for tens of thousands of years.
We’ve been close once
and we have also fought many times.
But this is the first time
he gets so close to a girl.
You think we are close?
He always bosses me around
or takes a carrot-and-stick
approach to me.
There is something you don’t know.
Bai Jue hates females the most.
He won’t even let a female mosquito
come near to him.
I once thought
that he has no emotions
and he can’t fall in love with anyone.
But the way he cared about you just now
has dispelled my doubts.
Don’t be ridiculous.
Shanggu.
Bai Jue.
Are you all right?
I’m fine.
Did Xuanyi do anything to you?
He seems to have changed himself.
Yuemi once stole wine in his hall.
If he didn’t defect from the God Realm,
I think I would also grow up
in his hall.
Why don’t we have a peace talk?
Let’s stop fighting.
Our little Chief God.
You are a compassionate person indeed.
If you dare to touch her again,
I will burn your Nether World to ashes!
You weren’t this angry when I killed
your heavenly soldiers back then.
Where is that cold-blooded and merciless
God of War, Bai Jue?
Have you become gentle
because you don’t fight a lot recently
and you start to
care about your love life?
Shanggu, to a man like Bai Jue,
you have to use some special tricks
to make him reveal his true feelings.
Shanggu.
I think we are connected in some way.
Why don’t you stay here?
There are no rules in the Nether World.
You can do whatever you want.
You turned into Bai Jue
and it makes me feel sick.
Let’s go.
The injuries you got at Mount Lookout
haven’t healed yet.
Do you really think you can
take her away easily?
Xuanyi blocked here. What should we do?
I wanted to take you here for training.
But I have no spiritual power left now.
I’ll try to break the barrier
and you leave as fast as you can.
You haven’t recovered your power.
I can’t leave you here alone.
We must leave together.
No, I will worry about you
if you stay here.
Xuanyi wants to kill me.
I can’t let you take the risk alone.
You got the nerve to stay here
knowing you will die.
I really admire
your brute courage.
Xuanyi, just come at me.
I’m the Chief Good.
Will do, then.
Go to find Zhiyang!
Xuanyi, the Ancestral God kept you alive
and gave the Nether World
to the clan of demons
because we hope you can
repent your mistakes.
Why do you have to repeat your mistakes?
When I was the Chief God
seventy thousand years ago,
you were nothing but
a sidekick following me around.
When do I need to explain to you
what I’m going to do?
Then have a try.
Seventy thousand years later,
you still can’t win me.
How arrogant.
Today is the day of your destruction!
You came just right.
Hurry and save Bai Jue!
What are you panic about?
That Ice Cube is hard to kill,
He will be fine.
Hold on.
You are not surprised at all.
Do you...
already know it?
Shanggu.
It’s not what you think.
This is all Bai Jue’s idea.
It has nothing to do with me.
Think about how good I am to you.
How would I lie to you, right?
It’s Zhiyang. He made me do it.
Shanggu.
Bai Jue.
I think you are getting naiver
over these years!
It’s just a barrier. Even it’s broken,
I can still kill you.
How dare you set me up!
What’s going on here?
What did you do?
When you rose in revolt back then,
the Ancestral God worried
that such a day would happen.
He cast a spell in the Nether World.
If you don’t rebel,
the Nether world will be the last chance
for you and the clan of demons.
But if you refuse to give up
your sinister plan,
you will be trapped on the
God-holding Platform
for the rest of your life.
You may never leave here again.
Qingtian, you can only trap me here!
But you can never kill me!
I’ll bring the demons
back to the world one day!
What’s wrong?
You imprisoned Overlord Xuanyi
on the God-holding Platform.
You did a good thing
for the people and the Three Realms.
I shouldn’t blame you.
But now I’m very angry.
Tell me.
You took the thunders for me
and got hurt on Mount Lookout.
Among all the things you did,
which of them were planned ahead?
Half and half.
You are frank.
After I was brought to the Nether World,
everything was in your schedule.
Xuanyi thought you were badly hurt
and let his guard down.
You took the chance
and gave him a fatal blow.
You planned them all.
But you could have told me in advance.
I can prepare myself at least.
It didn’t turn out bad, did it?
I thought you got through my vessels,
made a sword for me,
and took the thunders for me
because you cared about me.
I thought you really wanted to
help me advance.
I was worried about your injuries.
Now it turns out
what you did for me
is all part of your plan.
And I’m just one of your pawns.
You have advanced now.
You have improved a lot than before.
Is the process really that important?
Do you even know what I’m angry about?
If the gods and demons have a war,
everyone in the God Realm
will be a pawn.
No one can be spared.
I understand all the things you said.
But you could have told me in advance.
I would do my best
to help you defeat Xuanyi.
Why would you hide it from me?
Xuanyi can pry into people’s minds.
I have no better choice.
We won anyway.
Don’t bother yourself with it.
Old man, have you prepared
the wine for celebration?
Shanggu did a great job
in her first battle.
We must celebrate it.
I don’t need you to tell me that.
The wine is ready.
I told you
not to hide it from Shanggu
and you wouldn’t listen to me.
Come on, let’s go back to the God Realm.
Let’s talk...
Go away!
Do you always think
you are the rational one?
I even performed the ritual to
acknowledge you as my teacher
and said things like
we will proceed together.
Those who are amiable
can’t command an army.
If you need me to do anything
when you rule the Three Realms,
I will shrink from no sacrifice.
I don’t want to hear
your lecture anymore.
Girl! Girl!
Overlord, they fell for our trick.
Qingtian guarded me as I expected.
Finally they showed their last card.
Overlord, Shanggu’s performance
fully meets your expectations.
She is kind and willing to
risk her life to save others.
She is the best candidate
to become the Chief God
and solve the disasters in the future.
Unfortunately,
she is not strong enough.
I wonder if she can inherit
the instruction feather
of Chief God within a thousand years.
Don’t worry.
Now I’m trapped in
the God-holding platform
and Bai Jue will let his guard down.
In order to make Shanggu master
the Power of Chaos as soon as possible,
they will come to me soon.
The Deicide Flower
is about to blossom.
How long has it been
since the fight in the Nether World?
It’s been seven days.
Master.
Her Grace hasn’t come
to practice these days.
Why would Shanggu use her Power of Chaos
to save me on Mount Lookout that day?
I’ve told you many times.
Then tell me one more time.
When you fainted that day,
I told her
what you did for her.
You don’t know how worried she was.
I wanted to go back to
the God Realm and asked for help.
But she worried that demons
would come to hurt you.
So she saved you with her power.
Why didn’t you tell me that day?
You and Her Grace
went to the Nether World
as soon as you woke up.
I didn’t have a chance
to tell you even I wanted to.
It was not easy for her.
It took her so long to
have the spiritual power.
Yeah, and she gave it all
to you at once.
If I knew it would happen,
I wouldn’t let her
go to the Nether World.
Master, it’s no use to tell me that.
The poor little Chief God’s
original being
is still in your body.
There are prohibitions
and barriers everywhere
in the God Realm.
Without the spiritual power,
how should she go on with her life?
Even she wants to take a walk
at the lower realm, I’m afraid...
If you keep talking,
I’ll send you to serve
in the Pilgrimage hall.
We are going to ask for something,
not to fight.
Don’t act rashly.
I wouldn’t have saved him
if I’d known I was being used.
It makes me mad when I
think about his poker face.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪