=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 4=
We are going to get your thing back,
not to fight.
Don’t act rashly.
I wouldn’t have saved him
if I’d known I was being used.
It makes me mad when I
think about his poker face.
All right. You just did a great job.
The Gods are looking at you
differently now.
If you go to pick on him now,
who knows what kind of rumors
will come out.
It’s not me who did a good job.
It’s Bai Jue.
What they want to say
has nothing to do with me.
But you can’t beat him
even you go there.
If he throws you out of
his hall like he did last time,
it will be much more embarrassing.
Do you really not care?
Then there is nothing I can do.
What’s your idea?
All right. I’ll get it for you.
Stay right here and wait for me.
Master has ordered me
that if Her Grace
comes here to ask for it,
I should give it to her immediately.
Goddess Yuemi, take it.
When did Shanggu’s power
become so strong?
Her Grace practiced really hard
and she passed the thunder trial.
Her spiritual power is quite strong now.
It won’t take her long to obtain
the Power of Chaos and be a real Chief God.
We taught her for more than
ten thousand years
and she made no progress at all.
Looks like Bai Jue is quite capable.
My master never complained,
but he has been lonely
for ten thousand years.
Finally he has Her Grace
to stay with him now.
And he is teaching her attentively.
But
Her Grace is not around these days
and there is no smile
on his face anymore.
There is so much dust on my swing.
That Ice Cube.
I’ll break with him
after I get my original being.
He is meditating now.
I can’t be luckier.
I read from books
that when the True God is meditating,
his soul is wandering in the universe.
He won’t wake up for a while.
Let me take the chance
and get back my original being
before he knows it.
Then I don’t need to
waste my time with Ice Cube.
What should I do now?
I don’t even have enough power
to take out my original being.
Could it be...
There is no one here anyway.
No one would know it.
What are you doing?
Aren’t you meditating?
I’m taking a nap.
By rights,
you should have given
my original being back to me
when you got back to the God Realm.
But you didn’t and you made me
come here to ask for it.
Are you trying to embarrass me?
That’s not what I want.
We are finished now.
Shanggu?
Shang...
What are you doing?
It’s really hot today.
Aren’t you afraid to have heat rash
as someone who lost her
spiritual power?
Get up. Come on.
Look what this is.
I’m sure you will be
alive and kicking after you see it.
I asked it from Hongri.
Yuemi.
Don’t come here to see me anymore.
I’m too embarrassed to leave
the Pilgrimage Hall.
Goodbye.
I have something to ask you.
Master, go ahead, please.
I have an old friend who is an immortal.
He is in trouble now.
And it’s because of a girl...
Master, I’ve been
by your side for so long.
What kind of immortal friend
can you have with your temper?
Right. Right.
Your old friend is in trouble
because of a girl.
Master, please continue.
My old friend did something.
But he did it to
fulfill his responsibilities
and to save the world.
But somehow that girl was implicated
and she thought she was used by him.
She got mad at him and blamed him.
What do you think my friend should do?
What’s the relationship
between your friend and that girl?
He is her teacher.
Her teacher...
Did he tell her the truth
and finish the task with her
when he learned
that she misunderstood him?
No.
But my friend
didn’t tell her for her safety.
I see.
He is her teacher.
It’s not like he is a general
and she is a soldier
or he is a god and she is an immortal.
You mean I only care about
the result and the cause
when I act and order
and I’m too heartless?
Exactly.
But we were confronted with an enemy.
What if we lose the fight
because I care about her feelings?
Master, you are too serious about it.
For every girl in the world,
all she wants is to be cared
and trusted.
If your friend
deceived that girl,
then that’s his fault.
Is it really his fault?
What should he do then?
Apologize.
I’ll tell my old friend now.
See?
Look how fast I am.
You both should learn from me.
Your Grace, you’re awesome.
Shanggu.
What are you doing here?
I haven’t forgiven you yet.
You are a Chief God. Excessive attention
to plaything saps the will.
You’d better mind your own business.
I guess
I’m the only Chief God
who was totally being used
and didn’t know it at all.
I explained it to you on that day.
From now on, even it’s not about Xuanyi,
I’ll still be attentive to you.
Just let it go.
You want me to let it go that easily?
For someone who can’t
tell right from wrong like me,
I don’t deserve your teaching.
Ancestral Sword! See him out!
See him out...
See...
All right, since the True God won’t go,
I’ll go then.
Shanggu. Shanggu.
Sit down. Drink with me.
Has your friend from the Immortal Realm
solved his problem?
You are talking about
yourself and Her Grace, right?
Is Her Grace
still angry about what happened
in the Nether World that day?
Do you still want to teach her?
I’ve promised Zhiyang to teach her.
There is no reason to give up halfway.
You are totally right.
Her Grace is impulsive.
In the face of the virtuous cause,
you should be more tolerant.
Master, I have a good idea.
Master.
Where is the person?
We need a fourth in our game.
Didn’t I ask you to invite someone here?
I’ve invited all the Gods here.
They were either cultivating themselves
or appreciating flowers
and tasting wine.
Why do they
not want to play dominoes with me?
Your stakes are too high.
No one wants to come.
Never mind. Leave us.
Yes.
It’s boring for us three
to play dominoes.
How about I ask Bai Jue to come?
Don’t. Don’t,
Bai Jue is pretty lofty.
He can’t stand to see
such vulgar things like dice.
Yeah.
Tianqi, did you just know Bai Jue?
Your suggestion is too unreasonable.
What do you know?
It must feel really good to win
some Sacred Beads from that Ice Cube.
We just need one more person.
Ancestral Sword, come on.
He just looked at you
and you don’t dare to move, do you?
I’ll melt you down one day, you wuss.
Come here.
The divine weapon is
connected with its owner.
Your personality
will determine its personality.
I’m saying...
Use the spell
when you meet Her Grace.
Just read it.
I promise she will be happy to hear it
and she will forgive you.
You are considerate and thoughtful,
gentle and generous,
beautiful and brilliant,
tender and attentive.
You’re the best in the Three Realms.
Did Bai Jue get his tongue hurt
in the Nether World?
His tongue?
I think his brain got hurt.
I feel the same.
I’ll leave then.
You haven’t finished your compliments.
Ice Cube, stop there!
Shanggu!
Look at her.
She just wouldn’t allow us
to mention Bai Jue.
He only said a few words
and she just ran after him.
These two people
are really perfect for each other.
Perfect?
Bai Jue’s stubborn and grumpy.
I’m way better than him.
No way.
They are moving too fast.
I have to do something about it,
or she will slip through my fingers.
What a fool.
Can’t you look back?
There is also someone waiting for you.
I must ask for a good marriage today.
Puhua.
I finally find you.
Master Tianqi.
What brings you here?
Let me ask you.
Did you match Shanggu with someone else?
(Puhua)
You must be joking.
How dare I?
It’s not the right time
for Her Grace to get married.
It won’t work even I do.
What’s more,
the red lines she
messed up last time
haven’t been sorted out yet.
How dare I provoke her again?
That sounds reasonable.
Puhua.
I know
you are in charge of marriage
in the world.
It must be tiring for you.
Not at all.
I’m only in charge of the marriage
of the lower realm.
It’s not tiring at all.
Look.
The Gods in the God Realm
are really old-fashioned.
They cultivate and practice
all the time.
But they don’t know
the harmony between yin and yang,
falling in love and getting married
are the laws of nature.
Master Tianqi,
you are insightful indeed.
I can set people up.
But I can only do it
in the lower realm.
My skills are useless in the God Realm.
How come?
I think those Gods in the God Realm
are quite boring.
I’m thinking about
holding a Dating Event.
Dating Event?
I don’t know if you are
willing to help me.
Of course. Of course.
It’s just there is something tricky.
I need you...
I got it. I got it.
Which goddess
are you interested in again?
What do you mean again?
Among all the goddesses,
Shanggu is the only one I fall for.
The little Chief God?
Hongri!
Bring some tea for me.
That’s how you entertain guests
in Changyuan Hall?
No one will be so rude
in Master Tianqi’s Taichu Hall.
I’m only rude to you.
Little Kylin. you were defeated by me
ten thousand years ago.
You still remember it?
Old Dragon, if it wasn’t for you
to make me drink wines for three days,
how would I lose to you?
Just leave after you pass the message.
All right. I don’t bother to
bicker with you today.
I’m here by the order of my master
to send an invitation to your master.
It’s the beginning of spring
three days later.
My master will hold a Dating Event
for the Little Chief God
in Master Yuemi’s Taoyuan Forest.
All the Gods will be invited
at that time.
Of course.
Your master doesn’t like banquet anyway.
It doesn’t matter if he comes or not.
What does the Dating Event
have anything to do with the Her Grace?
Of course it has.
Can’t you see
that my master and Her Grace
have fallen for each other?
They are perfect for each other.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Her Grace belongs to my master!
Your master?
Don’t be kidding.
Someone like Bai Jue
can even freeze magma into ice.
How would Her Grace like him?
I think he is destined
to be alone forever.
You...!
Zihan.
We haven’t met for more than
ten thousand years.
You are becoming more disciplined.
I was talking nonsense.
Don’t take it seriously.
My master doesn’t mean anything else.
Because Her Grace
is still recovering from the fight
in the Nether World.
The banquet can be a good chance
for her to relax and have some fun.
She hasn’t fully recovered?
Master, you don’t know it?
Yes.
I guess she only
told my master about it.
I got the invitation. You can leave now.
Your jokes are so funny.
Where did you hear them?
As long as you are happy,
I can keep telling you jokes
for three days and nights.
I just want you to be happy every day
and get better soon.
You are right.
As Gods,
the most important thing is to be happy.
Are you happy?
Of course.
Then, do you like me?
Of course I like you.
You’ve been the best to me
since I was young.
You are my favorite god.
Puhua will hold
a Dating Event in Taoyuan Forest
a few days later.
Have you heard about that?
This old man really has a lot of time.
It’s not enough for him
to set people up,
now he wants to set Gods up.
I heard that many Goddesses
and Gods will be there.
Do you wanna come?
It’s such a big event.
Of course I will come.
All right, today’s story is over.
I’ll be back to my Taichu Hall.
See you in Taoyuan Forest
a few days later.
I won’t see you out.
Bye.
Where are we going?
It looks great over there.
Let’s go over the bridge
and take a look.
Okay.
This scenery is so beautiful.
That’s true.
There are so many gods here today.
Isn’t this the God of Disaster?
Master said
that those who attend this banquet
must have a good appearance.
But I think my master will get mad
when he sees your looks.
It’s good to have tea with you...
What a bad day
to meet someone so unsightly.
Goddess of Day, who are you insulting?
The one who answers to me.
I don’t understand.
How could anyone in the God Realm
fall for a crazy woman like you?
I don’t have time to bicker with you.
Let’s see
which of us will find a partner first.
Fine.
I haven’t had such a good time
for so long.
Puhua.
Yeah.
Do you still remember
what I told you?
Of course I remember.
And also, get the music,
petals and rainbows ready for Shanggu.
Okay.
It would be best
if there are one thousand swans
flying over my head,
which will show
who is the focus of the event.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Swans are good.
But, Master,
where can I find
a thousand swans for you
in such a short time?
No swans?
Then hawk can also work.
Hawk?
Only hawk spreading its wings
can show my dignified bearing.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
The Gods are almost there.
Master Puhua.
They are waiting for your magic charm.
Right, I’ll go right away.
Look how busy you make him.
Do you want to win Shanggu’s heart
just like this?
Save it.
Well?
Am I not handsome?
You are handsome enough
to ward off evil spirits.
You don’t know how to appreciate it.
You want to hear compliments?
Fine.
Master Tianqi is impressive in bearing.
I’m sure you will
win the heart of Shanggu.
There you go.
Bai Jue never attended any banquet.
Why did he come here?
It’s Master Bai Jue.
Master.
It’s really him.
He is so beautiful.
Master.
Why did you come to the Dating Event?
Is it because you fall for some goddess?
The beautiful scenery on a spring day.
I just practiced a piece.
May I have the honor to play it for you?
Tianqi.
Don’t bother.
Master, these are newly picked figs.
Do you want to try them?
What’s the situation over there?
Are those Goddesses losing their minds?
Master Bai Jue! Master!
Who knows what happened
to that Ice Cube.
You once sent a Goddess to his hall
and he rejected her.
Now he is here
flirting with those Goddesses.
That’s strange.
Shanggu, what do you
think of my look today?
Are you trying to ward off evil spirits?
What did I tell you?
Shanggu.
Let’s find a quiet place
to enjoy the scenery. Let’s go.
I can see Master again.
You finally showed up.
Why do you care?
I’ve been looking for you.
I think you were
having a good time over there.
I was having a miserable time.
What a joke.
I ran out of the Pilgrimage Hall
to chase you that day.
But you didn’t even look back.
I heard that the injuries you got
in the Nether World haven’t healed yet.
This medicine can heal wounds
and increase your spiritual power.
Take it.
It’s a minor injury. I’m fine now.
By the way,
I was rude that day.
Bear with me.
Hold on.
What?
You blamed me for
making you look bad in public.
Shanggu.
I’m here today to apologize to you.
How could it be the omnipotent
Master Bai Jue’s fault?
About what happened in the Nether World,
I neglected your feelings
and didn’t think
from where you were standing.
It was my fault.
But like I said,
even it’s not about Xuanyi,
I will still treat you attentively.
I really mean it.
Please be generous
and forgive me.
Well...
Ice Cube.
There are a lot of Gods here.
How can a teacher
apologize to his student?
Get up.
There are countless ways in the world.
We shall never stop learning.
Well, tomorrow...
Tomorrow, Yuemi asked me
to play dominoes with here.
Shanggu.
It suddenly occurred to me
that I have something to do tomorrow.
- Let’s cancel it.
- Yuemi, you...!
Since Her Grace and Master
are reconciled now,
let’s have a drink together
and put all these behind us.
Xueying, what are you doing?
Master Tianqi.
I didn’t mean to spill it on Her Grace.
Her Grace’s dress
really matches with
Master Bai Jue’s dress.
Yeah.
Thank you for helping me out.
What a beautiful dress.
I think Your Grace
won’t be mad at me now.
Tomorrow, wait for me in Changyuan Hall.
Okay.
Shanggu, how boring it is
to cultivate and practice.
If you get bored of playing dominoes,
I will take you down there to have fun.
There are countless ways in the world.
We shall never stop learning.
What did Ice Cube do to you
to make you so diligent now?
Well?
Are you unhappy that I’m getting better?
Puhua!
I’ve been looking for you for a while.
Why are you hiding here to drink?
Goddess Yuemi.
Are you also here to ask for
the Rope of Love?
They want your Rope of Love.
But I don’t want it.
Goddess Yuemi.
Are you also
falling for someone?
I think I must be drunk.
Yeah. How is it possible?
I don’t think there is
anyone in the God Realm
who can handle you.
What’s wrong with me?
I’m beautiful
and competent.
Am I not good?
You are good.
You are great.
Goddess, you are
far from gentle and elegant.
But you are bossy and good at fight.
I dare you to say that again!
I just helped you out.
I was wrong. I was wrong.
Goddess Yuemi, let me go.
If I faint,
I can’t give you my treasure...
Goddess Yuemi.
This is my heirloom.
It works every time.
What if it doesn’t work?
I promise you with my life.
Just consider it as a favor
if you get what you want this time.
Don’t make troubles
in my Temple of Love down there anymore.
Take it.
Interesting.
Master.
Where’s Yuemi?
Let’s go to pray
and draw divination sticks.
Okay.
You know Yuemi’s temperament.
I guess
she is hearing gossips somewhere.
Let’s forget about her.
Shanggu, actually, I have something...
Congratulations, Your Grace!
To me?
You just had your God vessels opened
and you sealed the Overlord Xuanyi.
Congratulations.
This is not a celebration party.
What’s the congratulation about?
I’ve always respected and admired you.
You do have an extraordinary bearing
as expected.
It’s a blessing for the Three Realms
to have such a Chief God.
What an ass-kisser.
You’re an ass-kisser.
It’s Bai Jue who directed well.
I just followed the plan.
I didn’t do much.
You are too humble.
Too humble.
It’s widespread in the God Realm
that Bai Jue assisted you
to break into the Nether World.
Bai Jue assisted me?
Who told you that?
Of course it’s Bai Jue who told us that.
You think I don’t know
it’s you two who spoke ill of Shanggu
behind her back?
Well,
are you afraid now?
It’s too late to fawn on her
in the Dating Event now.
I was being mouthy.
Those were just jokes.
Master, Your Grace, please forgive me.
I was blind as a bat.
I thought you are naughty.
But I didn’t know you are so brave.
Remember.
Don’t gossip about Shanggu anymore.
- Yes.
Tianqi, I want to go back
to the Pilgrimage Hall.
Don’t you love banquets the most?
Why are you going back so early?
I have to go to Changyuan Hall
to practice tomorrow morning.
Bye.
Shanggu, I haven’t...
Great, Shanggu.
You created a chance for me.
I will take this chance.
Who dared to attack me?
Little Night.
Why didn’t I notice
that your eyes are so beautiful?
Little Day.
You are the most beautiful
goddess I’ve ever met.
Let’s be together forever.
Who threw the Rope of Love on them?
Why didn’t you throw it earlier?
Yuemi?
Master.
Thirty thousand years ago,
we met in the Plum Garden.
You said...
Who is here?
I’m Xueying in charge of
the four seasons in the Heavenly Realm.
I intruded into the garden
because of the breathtaking scent
of the plum blossom.
Please forgive me
if I disturbed you.
The plum blossoms
are waiting for the snow.
It’s a good name.
The plum blossoms
are waiting for the snow.
That sentence you said
made me wait for three thousand years.
It’s not what I said that made you
wait for three thousand years,
but your own obsession.
I know you are aloof.
I dare not ask for too much.
I just want to stay by your side
and take care of your life.
It’s enough for me to see you often.
You know it’s not gonna happen.
Why do you have to ask me that?
Please go back, Goddess of Snow.
I won’t go back.
If you learn
what love means,
you will know it’s a lifetime.
God lives too long.
I don’t want to spend the rest of
my life in misery and pain.
Even you won’t let me stay by your side,
I still want to tell you my feelings.
Goddess of Snow.
I know
you spilled the wine on purpose.
Needless to explain.
Since Shanggu doesn’t care about it,
I won’t punish you.
I know you still have pity for me.
Master!
Not good.
God of Day and God of Night
went down there together.
Let’s talk about this later.
The two of them are in charge of
day and night respectively.
They can’t go down there together.
I held the Dating Event
when Zhiyang is not around.
If he finds it out,
he will skin me alive.
Let’s go.
Let’s go down now and take them back.
Be careful.
Bai Jue, didn’t you go back?
I’ll take you out of here.
Master Tianqi!
I did you a great favor this time!
Why is there a secret room?
It’s just a spell.
Looks like Puhua did it.
The spell was made
based on Taoyuan Forest.
If I break it, I’m afraid
Taoyuan Forest will be also destroyed.
Don’t.
Yuemi really cherishes her forest.
If it’s destroyed,
she will blame me
for thousands of years.
Never mind. We will be trapped
for a while at most.
If the prankster finds
that we are trapped here,
he will let us out.
Are you meditating now?
There is nothing to do anyway.
But I don’t know how to do it.
What should I do?
You can take a nap.
I will die of boredom
if we are trapped here for hours.
Talk with me.
I don’t like small talk.
If you dare tease me again,
I don’t mind making you angry
one more time.
Then try it.
♪Until I met you♪
♪I tried everything♪
♪Wait for the dawn of the next life♪
I didn’t do it on purpose.
You did.
I didn’t.
I can be easily provoked
and you know it.
♪Listen to it♪
♪We can feel each other♪
Why did you undo it so soon?
What did you say?
♪With a few words♪
I mean, after I practice
for a few more days,
I can break your spell
by myself.
Let me ask you.
Why did you let me take the credit
for sealing Xuanyi?
You are smart. Take a guess.
I won’t.
Childish.
You won’t meditate anymore?
Someone is too noisy.
It’s amazing.
They are so sweet.
It’s much more fun
than the plays in the lower realm.
Bai Jue, come to watch this.
I don’t like these stuff.
Don’t act coldly. Come on.
The so-called falling in love
should be like this.
Why is your face so red?
It’s hot here.
Are you kidding?
You are God of Fire.
Is heat a problem to you?
Let me see.
Where is it?
Even you don’t like it,
I still want to watch it.
Sit down and recite the formula
with me to clear your mind.
Right here, right now?
Recite the mind-clearing formula?
A pure heart is like water.
The pure water is like your heart.
There is no breeze and no waves.
Sit in the bamboo forest alone
and play the zither.
Fall in silence and meditation.
You want me to meditate now?
Fine. Well done.
Since there is nothing to do,
then let me appreciate his beauty.
From now on,
you are not allowed to be mean to me
and pick on me.
Don’t hide everything from me.
Got it?
I’d better
recite the mind-clearing formula.
The exquisite heart with seven orifices.
Flower and moon change with the heart.
The spring breeze is blowing.
Cultivating myself...
Cultivating...
It doesn’t sound like
the mind-clearing formula.
Is this the natal chart?
This place
should be under Puhua’s place.
He is in charge of
the marriage of all gods,
which means he can see
everyone’s natal chart.
And I got it out
by accident.
This is Yuemi’s natal chart.
The God of Flower’s natal chart.
Zhiyang’s...
Doesn’t it mean
I can see everyone’s natal chart?
I didn’t mean to
see your natal chart.
It’s a windfall indeed.
There is no reason to not see it.
This fierce beast harms the God Realm.
Bai Jue, kill it.
Ancestral God, I...
I’m afraid.
Turn your fear into strength.
If it doesn’t die, you will die.
Master Bai Jue wiped out
the nine tribes of the demons.
But that was really a fierce fight.
I guess the True God Bai Jue
also got his spiritual power impaired.
Master Bai Jue is powerful indeed.
He is the greatest fighter
in the God Realm.
Losing a little spiritual power
won’t cause him any harm.
You are right.
He is aloof
and condescending.
No wonder he has no friends.
The natal chart contains the past,
the present and the future of all gods.
Even the Ancestral God will have
a backlash for seeing it.
You only have little power.
How dare you see it?
I’m just curious
what you were like before I was born.
Are you angry?
Of course I am angry.
If you dare to act rashly again,
I will punish you.
I don’t know it’s that dangerous
to watch the natal chart.
I won’t do it again.
I just saw...
The Ancestral God
was really harsh on you
when you were a kid.
I’m used to it.
I used to be a loner.
And I will still be one in the future.
What are you doing?
Don’t push me away.
I have injuries.
Bai Jue.
Not everyone is indifferent
and timid in the world.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪