(All characters, locations, organizations, religions, )
(and incidents in this drama are fictional.)
(Episode 12)
Wait. Oh, no.
Darn it. Who are you?
A smoker.
- What are you doing? - Why do you ask?
Is this a no-smoking zone?
What's your problem? Do you think this is funny?
Is this funny?
I need the lighter to smoke.
I...
Get lost when I ask you nicely.
When did you ask me nicely? You were mean to me.
Darn you! Get lost!
Do you know who I am?
I don't care who you are.
Darn you.
Gosh.
You jerk. Hey.
Hey!
Stop it.
Why... Hey.
No.
- Do you want me... - No.
- to light it up? - No.
Or not.
Gosh. Let go of me.
Who are you?
Why are you doing this to me?
Me?
A victim whose right has been violated.
Are you the owner of this building or something?
No.
If I were, I wouldn't have given you a chance to talk.
What? You jerk.
Hey. What are you doing?
They are just batteries. Darn it!
Darn it.
You killed cats first. Next, you set buildings on fire.
After that, you'll go after kids, elderlies, and women.
That's how it goes down with scumbags like you.
But it has nothing to do with you.
You can just go on your way.
Those are losers, anyway. Killing some of them...
won't make any difference.
I tell her to root out people like you,
but she won't even budge.
No matter how I look at it, this is a better bargain.
Those lowlives started it. They were so loud.
I...
Right. It's too loud.
What are you doing? Stop it.
Why are you doing this?
What a useless dog.
Hey. I just arrived at the hospital.
Okay. See you soon.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello, Ms. Tak. Come on in.
You're here.
You'll get admitted tomorrow,
get a biopsy, and start the treatment right away.
I'll diagnose your illness more accurately...
after the biopsy.
But usually, people start with chemo and radiation therapy.
Listening about my treatment still feels surreal.
There's nothing for you to get nervous about.
If it goes well, you can get treated as an outpatient.
You're very young.
And seeing how you're not experiencing any symptoms yet,
I'm hopeful.
Okay, Mr. Jung.
Wait, no. I should call you Dr. Jung now, right?
Dr. Jung Seung Jun.
Yes. I'll be talking to you as your doctor from now on.
As my patient, you'd better brace yourself.
You're a scary doctor.
Liar.
If I were, you would've been here long ago.
Do you know how worried I have been for you?
I had my reasons.
What reasons?
I definitely had my reasons,
I don't remember them.
Well,
you might have a hard time remembering things.
It's one of your symptoms.
A symptom.
Oh, right. Do you like apples?
I didn't want to come here empty-handed.
You should have them with your bride.
An old lady was selling apples in front of the hospital.
But a guy on a bicycle flipped her baskets.
They weren't on the ground. These are clean apples.
The apples from the ground...
They're in here. These are for me.
You care too much about others.
What?
I'd tell you to be more selfish.
But I guess it's something you can't change.
Just live however you want.
If you want to help someone, help them...
even if that means you'll lose out.
So I won't end up with any regrets just in case?
No.
It's just nice to see that you're always so nice.
In the end,
kindness always wins.
Ms. Tak, you kind soul.
Let's do our best to overcome this.
Okay.
How is it that these humans, whom you love so much,
only get worse with time?
Look at yourself.
Do you really think they're worth all this?
Yes.
They don't know. They know nothing.
You don't know either.
I do know. I know because I've heard it too many times.
I know that the garden isn't yours.
And I'm just a butterfly in that garden.
- Right. - Butterflies aren't like gardeners.
I'm picky with the flowers I sit on.
That means you and I are different.
There's not a single flower that I like.
- Not a single one? - Not a single one.
Don't you feel sorry for them?
Not at all.
And you don't find them endearing?
Not once have I felt that way.
I see.
I'll be off now.
I'm sorry.
It's too late for that.
I'm sorry...
Why is he...
I know I'm handsome. But I'm busy.
Here. I couldn't come empty-handed.
They're clean.
What do you mean they're clean?
They're from you, so I don't care even if they're not clean.
They're apples. How did you know I love apples?
- Thank you. - No problem.
Did you decide to get hospitalized?
Yes.
But the thought of getting checkups...
and treatment at the hospital is starting to scare me a bit.
Look at me.
My surgery went great.
You'll be fine too.
I'm relieved that you're recovering well.
Why do you look so sad? You used to be bright and cheerful.
Who is it? Who made you like this?
"Bright and cheerful"? Me?
You told me you enjoy living life.
I thought you chose to get hospitalized for treatment...
so you could continue to enjoy that life of yours.
But why do you look so down? It's making me feel bad for you.
I guess I told you I enjoyed my life.
To be honest, I don't really remember.
I've become very forgetful.
I heard it's because of my illness.
It scares me to think...
that I've started to forget all my happy memories.
But apparently, I'm pretty healthy and in good condition.
If I'm lucky, I might even become an outpatient.
So I'm going to try and be positive.
Of course. I'm going to wish you good luck.
Thank you for coming, Ms. Tak.
Once I start chemotherapy,
I figured I might not be able to see you for a while.
I'll visit you. I'll visit often.
I'll visit you with delicious food...
and pretty things.
Even if you forget everything,
I'll make sure you keep making happy memories.
Okay.
Do you like tulips?
Tulips?
Someone brought me this earlier,
but I don't have a vase.
I don't want to throw them away since they're so pretty.
You should take them.
Here's one happy memory for today.
Things must've been pretty hectic for me.
What date is it today?
My goodness, this milk is from ages ago!
Is this milk that precious to you?
Is that why you've been keeping it for so long?
My gosh.
You're still in contact with this jerk?
- Who? - Your ex-boyfriend.
- Hey! - Dong Kyung.
You have a boyfriend?
No, it's her ex-boyfriend. You won't believe what...
I don't have a boyfriend. He's just a crazy jerk.
I heard the news.
It really made me think.
I even wondered if you got sick because I gave you a hard time.
After I got divorced and had my hair pulled out because of you,
I had to get treated for hair loss.
But now, I've decided to forgive you.
My gosh.
Has he lost his mind?
I can't believe he texted me.
Joon Woo, I love you.
You know what? Let's be nice. I forgive him.
I forgive everything.
I should forget bad memories too.
"Forgive"?
Forgive, my foot.
Why didn't you block him?
She really had a boyfriend?
He was never my boyfriend. He's just some crazy piece of trash.
My gosh, seriously.
(Block)
Good job.
Let me know if he contacts you again.
I'll deal with him right away.
Shut it.
I might deal with you before you get a chance to do that.
Why are you being so cranky? I'm only looking out for you.
But didn't you also date some other guy?
What are you talking about?
I mean...
Why does it feel like you were also seeing someone else?
Dong Kyung, you must be pretty popular.
Two guys at once?
No, don't be absurd.
Well, I guess I was wrong. You're not capable of doing that.
You're really getting on my nerves. Come here.
You punk. You never learn unless you get a beating.
But I mean, it's true.
Come here. You punk.
What's wrong?
Are you down?
No, it's just...
the thought of leaving the place empty for a while...
I'll have to stop by now and then and check on it.
If you need anything,
I'll bring it to you right away.
What about Uncle?
Uncle?
He's going to Canada to take care of the stuff and move here.
Don't worry.
Because of me...
Hey.
Don't even think that, okay?
(Love Like a Rain Shower)
Leave it. Don't clean up.
Hey... Nice. You look good in the hospital gown.
Is that a cool tone or a warm tone?
Auntie went down to pick up some stuff.
She says she'll be back soon.
You didn't need to come.
Hey.
If I don't come, who will?
I'm a freelancer, remember?
You have a hard time waking up in the morning.
Did you get some sleep? What about your story?
I finished it.
Don't lie to me.
I log in every day,
and there was no update.
Why? Are you stuck?
I'm writing.
I keep writing and deleting.
My heart isn't in it.
Get it together, will you?
You don't write with your heart.
You write with your words.
- What is a writer? - A technician.
Yes. So have a strong cup of coffee,
wake up, and go write.
You can't drink coffee.
You should drink juice. Freshly squeezed.
Okay, fine. I will.
That's why people say...
this hospital was built on suspicious land.
Maybe this used to be a funeral parlor.
I heard they knocked down a building...
and erected the new wing.
That's right. That funeral parlor is brand new.
Gosh.
You're right.
So there must be more than one ghost.
There is more than one?
Yes. Sometimes, he's super tall, then tiny.
Sometimes he's old, sometimes he's young.
That's what I hear.
- The nurse saw a woman. - Oh my gosh.
I just got chills.
So you two should be careful. Don't walk around at night.
I hear he goes around in broad daylight too.
What use is being careful at night?
Still, it's scarier at night since it's dark.
Sure, you have a point.
I heard you came to this hospital often.
Didn't you ever see anything that gave you the creeps?
The creeps?
I did see a super good-looking doctor.
A good-looking doctor?
He must've been the ghost.
What? Why?
I've been here for over a year,
and I've never seen a good-looking doctor.
There's no way we wouldn't remember.
We don't get many chances to see a good-looking man.
Let's see.
How many good-looking men have I seen in my lifetime?
1, 2...
3, 4, 5.
That's it. Only five.
How many of them did I see in this hospital?
Zero.
That's not true. I know I saw one.
He was wearing a lab coat.
I can't listen anymore. It's too scary.
Why?
All of the ghosts here...
act like they're doctors.
Look. There.
- Oh my gosh. - That was scary.
Gosh.
That scared me.
- Is he a ghost? - He's a person.
How do you know?
He's not good-looking.
Go back up. It's cold.
I'll go after I see you leave.
What if you see a ghost?
No. I'll take you to your room...
Seriously. There are no such things as ghosts.
The person I saw was a human being.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
He knew he was good-looking.
So there's no doubt.
A good-looking man who knows he's good-looking.
That's so nice. And dangerous.
Go home and write your story, will you?
Don't come back until you finish.
Hey.
Don't "Hey" me.
Just write.
Good luck, Ji Na.
It's not like I can't. I choose not to.
Fine. I'll write quickly and come back tomorrow.
I like your vigor.
- Get home safely. - Thanks.
Bye.
Did you know my son?
I came to see...
what a dad who beats his kid to death looks like.
So this is what he looks like.
Who are you?
Did his mom send you?
I don't know what you've heard,
but that woman is out of her mind.
This is what I hear from you.
"I'm free."
"I got rid of annoying baggage."
"I can start over as long as I don't get caught."
"It's his fault for whining."
- You killed him. - What garbage...
Hey.
Did that witch say she'll pay you for saying that?
I won't share a dime...
of the insurance payout or compensation,
Just give your monetary gift and go.
Who told you that garbage?
A broken bone in your right leg.
Two broken ribs.
You stepped on and broke...
that tiny body so badly that it was completely broken.
You enjoyed doing as you pleased, didn't you?
Why can't I reach?
Darn it.
I'm sure you didn't know.
It's within my authority to destroy, not yours.
You abused my authority without permission,
so I plan to return the favor.
What do you say?
What a hassle.
(Reloading)
("Love Like a Rain Shower", Episode 1)
(Ad: S Jung Capital)
Darn it.
He should have turned that off before leaving.
("Do you like him that much?")
(After endlessly waiting for someone who would never come, )
(Ji Woo finally realized why after talking to a stranger...)
("Love Like a Rain Shower", Episode 1, Lee Hyun)
Writer Lee Hyun?
What is this?
What is this? Why are you here?
Your story is stuck, right?
Why do you care?
You said we wouldn't meet even for work.
That's what you said.
Right.
I can't seem to stick to what I say.
So why do you keep popping up in my head?
- Are you blaming me for it? - Yes.
I quit my job.
Why? Because of me? Because I made a scene?
Partially, yes.
So you want to hold me responsible?
What does that have to do with my writing?
No. I feel responsible...
because I might be the reason why you're stuck.
Stop speaking nonsense. Just leave.
I'm the male lead.
You knew that I would read it.
- That's... - I...
You can go first.
You're not the male lead.
It's your turn.
I'm going to ask you something important now.
Do you like me?
I want a clear answer.
- Why? - So my stance can be clear.
Either to steal you from him...
- Or get over me? - No.
To be in one-sided love.
I'm sure you need time to think.
Think about it and get back to me.
Where are you going now?
Home.
- Now? - For the next episode,
write about how you met him again after nine years.
He's unbelievable.
I don't drink this kind of stuff.
- You can't drink coffee? - No.
Because it's from the vending machine?
You have a refined palate.
In fact, I don't eat anything.
Is it that you "don't" eat or you "can't" eat?
- I don't. - Then, do you eat food...
from the altar?
- What? - I'm sorry, but can I poke you?
Gosh. I can touch you.
Then, you're not a ghost.
Then, how did you do that earlier?
- "That"? - The cars started to honk...
and the lights were on and off.
Is that your specialty?
- Specialty? - Do you deal with machines?
Or electricity?
I mean, I had the same thought when I saw him the other day.
But how can a ghost look so handsome?
You.
You've seen me before?
What?
You and I bumped into each other at the hospital...
when you were wearing your gown. Don't you remember that?
You remember my face?
Of course, I do.
Your face isn't easy to forget.
That's why the ladies told me they didn't see any handsome guy.
Occupational hazard. I read a lot of web novels.
So I'm used to abnormal situations.
Don't mind me.
Okay. I don't have to.
But how did I suddenly end up seeing ghosts?
Is hallucination a symptom of brain tumors?
Is he a ghost? Or am I seeing things?
- That might be better. - Pardon?
Pretend you're hallucinating.
Okay. What?
Did you just read my mind?
I don't read people's minds. I just hear them.
Why are you eavesdropping on my thoughts?
Is that important now?
You're starting to hallucinate now.
Right.
Why do you think I'm hallucinating?
Do you need to talk to me?
Or do I have to help you let go of your grudge?
I saw you chasing someone earlier.
Should I help you?
I don't need your pity. It looks like you'll end up like him soon.
- Pardon? - You'll die soon.
You'll die.
Whatever you try, you are fated to die.
- I'm going to die? - Yes.
I must get going. I was in the middle of something.
Even if you talk about me with other people,
they'll just think it's one of your symptoms.
So keep your mouth shut.
Wait. Hold on. Hey!
What an annoying jerk.
And why did he talk down to me?
Gosh.
Why am I so sleepy?
Is anyone there?
There's someone in here!
Help!
How does it feel to be locked up for a change?
I'm sorry. I mean, I'm sorry, sir.
Forgive me. Please.
You never listened no matter how much he begged.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
No! No! I'm sorry! No!
Did you hear what happened at the hospital yesterday?
Some guy came to the ER for consuming rat poison.
He was out of his mind...
and kept saying, "I'm sorry. I'm sorry."
He kept repeating that.
Also, some crazy guy...
went inside the morgue last night.
He had gone insane when they found him this morning.
He kept saying he killed his own son.
Apparently, he just kept talking nonsense.
So that's why the police were here.
Yes.
Auntie, should we go to another hospital?
No, I should stick with Mr. Jung as my doctor.
But this place is really weird.
It's the same everywhere.
It won't be much different at a bigger hospital.
Plus, it's better here since you're acquainted with your doctor.
I swear...
there's a ghost here.
Ta-da! Dong Kyung!
Hey, shouldn't you be at work?
What are you doing here at this hour?
I dropped by to see you...
before I went to work.
And my pretty auntie.
- My gosh. - You really know how to flatter me.
They're walnut pastries.
I ran over here so they won't get cold.
They're still pretty warm.
- Hello. - Hi.
I hope you ladies get along with my sister.
- Thank you. - Gosh, thank you.
You guys should try some too.
- Thank you. - Thanks.
You're one handsome fellow.
Gosh, that's nonsense.
You're the most handsome guy I've seen at this hospital.
I agree.
You should come by often.
Okay, I will. Thank you.
I'm off now. I'll come back after work.
- Don't come. - You're all over the place.
- Dong Kyung. - Just go to work already.
My goodness.
- He's second best. - Number two.
Do you know how busy I am?
Yes, I do.
What brings a busy man like you to the hospital?
I'm sure you didn't come to eat walnut pastries.
I had work nearby, so I thought I'd visit.
I was passing by.
But what made you drop by?
How did you find out?
I asked my mom.
I think she asked Mr. Park.
I guess Mr. Park asked Ms. Jo.
Why are you here?
Isn't it obvious?
I came to help you enjoy a more comfortable time here.
How can a writer like you...
I mean, how exactly can you help me enjoy...
a more comfortable time here?
Can't you see that everyone's looking at us?
Even those ladies from earlier...
suddenly looked at us with a smile.
My fans tell me that my good looks are like welfare.
Right.
I guess I'm living in a country with amazing welfare.
Be honest. You're here to check your popularity, aren't you?
Well, that's also part of it.
Gosh.
How did that story go?
What story?
The story where the world gets destroyed if she chooses...
the person she loves,
and if she protects the world, her love ends up dying.
Has the writer decided on the ending?
What? I asked you that?
What? You forgot already?
Gosh, I've been dying to know how it ends.
I thought about it,
and I think it would be a great time-slip story.
You turn back time...
so you can avoid having to make that choice.
You try your best to avoid the situation,
but fate brings you to fall in love all over again.
And then, you'll have no choice but to make a choice.
I see why your time-slip novel...
managed to get into the top 10.
You're really letting your talent go to waste.
Do you really not want to keep writing?
- I do. - You do?
But I'm going to do it in secret.
Gosh, I really need to go to work.
I'll visit again.
What? You're visiting again?
Why? You don't need to.
- I'm going to come. - Why?
I don't have friends.
- You don't have friends? - No.
Really? Why?
- I'm shy. - You're shy?
How exactly? Are you sure you're shy?
Or are you just joking?
You're so funny.
I like you because you're funny.
I didn't mean to be funny. It was a serious question.
Gosh, you're hilarious.
My gosh.
What's so funny?
Do you like me?
Does he think I'm crazy?
("He Always Smells of Soap")
Lee Hyun.
Lee Hyun?
- Kyu! - You startled me.
What?
Did you forget your name?
Why do you keep mumbling your own name?
Kyu.
Lee Hyun Kyu.
Kyu... Hyun Kyu.
Yes, I get it now.
It's Lee Hyun Kyu.
Yes, that's right. Your name is Lee Hyun Kyu.
Let's eat.
Meet me at Stupid Tteokbokki, the place we always used to go.
Hey, I need to go somewhere.
- You'll have to do without me. - Where are you going?
Hello? Sir?
Where are you going?
I can tell he's on his way to meet a woman.
Gosh, everyone's dating but me.
- Thanks for coming. - No problem.
I'll visit again amid my busy schedule.
I'll see you.
Hang in there, Dong Kyung.
Isn't that Park Young?
- You're right. - He's Park Young.
The doors are closing.
Going down.
Should I help you open it?
Here.
Hey, wait.
Have you been to the rooftop?
- The rooftop? - It's nice there.
You should go try it.
Okay.
Do you want my autograph?
Who are you?
- Don't you know who I am? - Am I supposed to know?
- Then why did you look at me? - What do you care?
How immature.
- What? - You're immature.
If you don't know who I am, why did you stop me?
There's enough room to pass by since you're so little.
- Why are you provoking me? - I just want to for some reason.
Get out of my way.
That annoying punk seems familiar. That little rat.
It's just so weird.
Someone recognized me.
- Who? - Isn't that strange?
No one's ever recognized me before.
I was having some fun,
and some weird girl caught me.
But it doesn't matter. She's going to die next month.
By the way, about that plant...
What is that? Why are you tending to it so much?
It's almost dead.
You.
Why is that me?
I thought you hated rice cakes.
I do.
I'm trying to overcome trauma.
Should we get squid tempura?
You loved their squid tempura here.
It was good.
But I can't eat squid anymore.
Why not?
When I was 23,
I got indigestion after eating one. Now, I get hives if I eat squid.
Really?
You can get it if you want.
No, it's okay.
You didn't eat tteokbokki back then when you swam...
because you had to keep in shape, but I guess not anymore.
Well...
I don't swim anymore, so...
Don't you think their food tastes different now?
Really?
I can't tell. It's still good.
Is it?
Wasn't it somewhere here?
Didn't we write on the wall too?
I guess kids still do that even now.
How cute.
This is from five years ago.
- Maybe ours is here too. - It's not.
I looked for it when I came a long time ago.
Too many people wrote over it, so you can't see it.
What are you doing tomorrow?
Tomorrow? I'll probably go to the hospital.
Why? Are you sick?
No, someone I know.
Do I know the person too?
No.
It's so weird...
being in a car with you driving.
Think of our age.
Why didn't you bring your car?
What? Well...
Because I live so close?
You live far away.
Why did you bring yours when you live so close?
So I wouldn't drink.
Because if I drink, I become honest,
and if I'm honest, I make mistakes.
I didn't want to make a mistake.
Do you smoke?
Yes.
I didn't know.
You couldn't have known...
since I started it when I was 20.
Right. If you started to smoke when you were 20...
You hated the smell of smoke.
I know.
I never imagined I'd become a smoker.
Don't you smoke?
No. I smoked a little long time ago, but I quit.
I see. True. Athletes usually don't smoke.
I'm not an athlete anymore.
That's right.
Thanks for the lift.
Go in. I'll call you.
Okay.
Hey.
You said you were a writer, right?
Yes.
What's your pen name?
- Why? - Is it Lee Hyun by any chance?
How did you know that?
- Did Joo Ik... - So it was you.
He didn't tell me.
The main characters in your stories...
Did you read them?
- A few. - Don't read them anymore.
Why not? They were all about me.
Why can't I read them?
That's why.
Since you know the story anyway.
What about your new story?
Your new story...
is about something I don't know.
Well... That's...
Bye.
I shouldn't have asked.
Hyun Kyu.
Let's grab a drink sometime.
I'll be someone you can make a mistake in front of,
someone you can be honest to.
I wasn't prepared today.
Get home safely.
The moon is so bright.
This is really nice.
You again?
You shouldn't smoke in a hospital.
Mind your own business.
It is my own business. Because you'll end up hurting me.
You're the one who will hurt others.
If you want to die, go die somewhere else.
Do you own the entire roof?
Yes, I do.
So die somewhere else.
I said it twice now.
Why do you keep saying I'm dying?
When you're already dead.
I'm not a ghost.
Then you should know even better.
All people die.
I never said I was a person either.
You must really be sick.
Don't start up with me.
I wish...
the entire world will be destroyed right now.
I like that.
What? What do you like?
That you wish the entire world will be destroyed.
You know what? I like you.
You have potential.
What are you doing? You're scaring me.
You're scared? Now, you're scared?
A little late, don't you think?
People say you're dense, don't they?
Seriously. You must really want me off this roof.
Fine, I'll leave.
I'll leave because you disgust me and scare me.
Darn it.
Why are you following me?
I'm not following you.
Either be polite or not. Choose one.
Fine. I choose not to be polite.
What floor?
Who knows?
Fourth floor. Going down.
You'll be in pain soon.
What?
What do you mean...
See? I told you so.
No. Hey. Help me.
Is that your wish?
Help me.
I'm asking you if that's your wish.
If I help you, what can you do for me?
Are you okay?
- Yes. - If you're okay,
ask me to destroy the world.
What?
Ask me to grant you that wish.
- What are you... - You'll die soon.
Don't you think it's not fair?
A kind girl like you will die so young.
But those who are evil will live much, much longer.
On your way out of this world, let's get rid of evil people...
and this world too.
Let's say I make that wish.
Do you even have the power to grant me that wish?
Why do you keep telling me such nonsense?
How will you explain this?
You're not in pain anymore because I held your hand.
It's a coincidence.
I see. A coincidence?
Okay.
Doors are opening.
Then, how will you explain this place?
Is this a coincidence too?
What on earth...
How...
You wanted it.
Who are you?
You're neither a ghost nor a human.
Doom which you've been asking for.
Am I dead now?
Did I die and leave the living realm?
Not now. That will happen soon enough.
So I want to help you a bit.
I'll let you be free of pain until the moment you die.
- How? - I'll hold your hand like earlier.
- What do you want in exchange? - A contract.
You can ask me to destroy the world before you die.
You can do it yourself. Why are you asking me?
If I could, I would've done it long ago.
- You think I can help you do that? - Probably.
- Why? - I don't know.
I don't know. I just...
thought so.
If you're in, hold my hand.
No.
I think I would feel pain...
somewhere else if I hold your hand.
I didn't think you were the doubting type.
I was tempted for a second, though.
I love this place.
You came here when you wanted to cry.
I made a lot of good memories here.
Like what?
I don't see any happy memories.
It must be because of my illness.
I definitely came here with someone.
But I can't remember it.
I think I was really happy here.
As you know, my brain up here isn't working that well now.
- What about the bracelet? - The bracelet?
Oh, this?
I don't know.
I just feel anxious when I don't wear it.
What?
You did something to me, didn't you?
Tell me.
What did you do to me?
I didn't do anything to you. It was her.
I did something...
to Tak Dong Kyung.
I knew it.
Some things are inevitable.
(You have 54 contacts.)
(Search, no recent searches)
(Human)
Tak Dong Kyung.
How do you know my name?
Who are you?
Then, who are you?
(Doom At Your Service)
You did this, didn't you?
Why do you keep following me?
Oh, gosh.
Let me take a look at you.
Why do you always fall?
I have a question.
Did you kiss her?
I don't want to be a coward with you.
Death is nothing.
How...
It feels really lonely...
to watch something disappear.
Don't cry.
I'm sorry.
Don't forget.
We were born with a special gift.
This is Derek.
Tell me everything you know about the culprit.
This may be hard to believe,
but the culprit has a special hearing ability.
If you turn out to be wrong, my sister will be in danger.
Can you guarantee what you just said?
(Voice 4, The 1st episode will air at 10:50pm on Friday, June 18.)