♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
=The Eternal Love S3=
=Episode 20=
So it wasn't
Second Princess that asked me here.
It was you.
I want to talk to you.
Why won't you even give me one chance?
You have a habit of lying.
I won't listen to your lies.
I know you like balsam.
So I asked people to bring some for you.
I'm asking you to give me a chance
to explain the misunderstanding between us.
Talk.
The Empty Fort Strategy and
pretending to surrender
were my doing.
I'll admit my mistakes.
But the ambush
was nothing more than a misunderstanding.
What else could it be?
I was sending something.
Do you think
I'm as deceivable as Her Highness?
I never wanted to lie to you.
It was a border skirmish
and you said the ambush was a delivery.
Isn't that ridiculous?
Not to mention...
You're a married man,
but you're meeting a lady alone
and showing her flowers.
You violated the moral codes for men
and broke the law.
Don't even try to trick me again.
Trying to explain everything to her
is worse than impossible.
Have some patience.
I'll figure something out.
I have an idea.
Who allowed you to come in?
You were forced to have the
peace-making marriage,
but you already have someone you love.
And that's Feng Yang.
You know everything?
Not only do I know,
I can also offer you help.
If you want me to help you,
you must tell me
what happened on your wedding night.
Don't you tell him.
Her plan
won't be as effective as mine.
On the wedding night...
You...
This is how it went.
Are you crazy?
Are all men from Xiyue so impatient?
Xiao Zhen is here?
Don't come any closer.
Don't worry.
I'm not planning to serve you at all.
Official Xiao has gone.
He's gone?
He's been here for ages.
Finally gone.
I'll cut to the chase then.
I could tell
you were in love.
You wanted to save him
so you agreed to this marriage.
I'm in the same predicament.
Are you also in love with someone?
Who is it?
Mo Feng Yang.
Are you a masochist?
Why would you fall in love with her?
Others know she's unyielding and uninhibited,
but I know how gentle and vulnerable she could be.
If you manage to fix me up with her,
I can help you avenge
Mo Lian Cheng's humiliation.
The skirmishes around our borders
will be resolved in no time.
(He seems honest.)
(I don't think he's a spy.)
Who would have thought
you're a man of some tactical shrewdness?
If you're unwilling to help,
then we can go on our separate ways.
May we make a good team.
We came to an agreement.
That's all there was to it.
Blabbermouth.
You ratted me out.
Why should you care what happened
between him and me?
You can just go and meet Her Majesty.
You...
Come with me.
I have nothing to say to you!
We had a deal.
I told you what happened that night
and now you should help me.
Let go of me! Let go!
I'll say this again.
I have nothing to say to you.
Did you agree to marry him just to save me?
I regret it now.
If I had another chance,
I would just give up on you!
Who is blackmailing you?
Her Majesty? Xiao Zhen?
Why are you asking?
What do you want?
One last question.
Did Xiao Zhen tell you
I was in the palace the whole night?
It was Fourteenth.
Would Fourteenth ever lie to me?
He didn't lie.
Her Majesty set us up.
I can see it now.
There was no guard at the forbidden ground.
I lost the dagger after I was wounded.
Her Majesty ordered me to keep watch.
These were all her plans.
Only by letting you know I was injured,
would you agree to the peace-making marriage.
Only when you found out I slept in the palace,
could she alienate us.
You were only there to keep watch at night?
Yes. I was guarding outside the door.
Unlike you,
I never went to her bed.
Then come with me.
It's broad daylight.
Your Highness is so impatient.
You got hurt.
I want to check your injury.
My injury
is only at the shoulder.
As long as you're not upset at me,
the injury is no big deal.
I was so mad at you,
but you still didn't regain your memories.
It seems like
I should take it up a notch.
That proves
my trust in you.
On the other hand,
you don't seem to trust me at all.
Then...
Let me make it up to you with a reward.
Although...
I'm still recovering,
you should check my injury in person.
Don't worry.
I'll definitely...
check every inch of you.
You know...
when I was trapped in the forbidden ground,
what I worry about the most
wasn't my injury.
It was...
what you would think of me.
How could a righteous ruler
employ such a lowly tactic to alienate us?
Don't you think
something is amiss?
You're right.
The entrance to the forbidden ground
was next to the antique shelves
of Her Majesty's bedroom.
The place was creepy and mysterious.
When I went near that place,
the air became stifling.
Perhaps
I was sensing the Soul-guarding Bead.
In that case,
the place you went to
was the Altar of Souls.
The Altar of Souls?
Yes.
In the Kingdom of Dongyue,
the Altar of Souls is where the royal
family pays respect to the ancestors.
It was also used to forge
the Soul-guarding Bead.
If the Soul-guarding Bead is inside the palace,
perhaps...
we will have a way to return to our world.
But if that place is hiding
such unspeakable secrets,
Her Majesty must have her reasons...
to lure me there.
Then...
Can I now...
do as I wish with you?
Come back later.
Leave.
Sorry.
Now that you two reconciled,
he should fulfill his promise.
My problems aren't settled yet.
Do you know why you keep failing?
That's because
Feng Yang thought you were a spy.
That's why
I keep trying to explain to her.
What's the point of just explaining?
You should hear her side of the story.
Who is it?
Who left this flower here?
You, come over here.
General, it was General Yun Xiu.
I don't want to see the flower again!
Here, give it to me.
The more upset you are,
the more innocent he seems.
He is blatantly provoking me
because he's mocking me for
not having evidence.
It's not hard to find evidence.
Plenty of evidence
comes to us effortlessly.
Effortlessly?
Bait him.
If you want the plan to work,
you must first apologize to him.
Your idea
is worse than hers.
It's been hours,
Feng Yang is nowhere to be seen.
It's only been a while and you've
lost patience already.
No wonder Feng Yang says
a man's mind is full
of love.
Stay calm when she's here.
Otherwise, it'll all be for nothing.
Prince Consort.
She is here.
Hide yourselves.
Indeed a good idea.
General, what brought you here?
I saw the flowers.
I misunderstood you.
So Tan Er told you everything.
Those balsams
were the work of yours and
Her Highness's effort.
Since you showed goodwill,
it will be disrespectful of me
to keep turning you down.
As the military customs say,
I'll ask you out for a drink at dusk.
We'll reconcile over the drink.
That's thoughtful of you, General.
I will
meet you there.
Should I bring some snacks and wine?
Don't bother.
I will prepare everything.
But this is the first time.
I should prepare something.
The first time?
It's the first time we set our differences aside.
I hope it won't be the last.
Then, I'll
see you at dusk.
Well?
What do you want to prepare for your first date?
Should I
prepare a valuable present
for Feng Yang?
I don't think so.
After failing so many times,
I have no idea
what is the right thing to do.
There is only...
one right method.
Be true to her.
Come on.
We shall drink heartily tonight.
Bottoms up.
Since we're drinking tonight,
you can feel free to say and ask anything.
When you first saw me on the battlefield,
what feelings did you have?
Are you asking what I think of your troops?
I apologize if I offended you after drinking.
The cavalries of Xiyue are feared by many.
You lived up to the name when I saw you.
But the size of Dongyue's army is now
three times larger than it used to be.
The steeds alone...
Feng Yang, you mustn't talk about
classified information.
You weren't answering my question anyway.
Prince Consort, mind your manner.
I was out of line. I'll drink as my punishment.
What was it that you wanted to know?
What kind of man do you like?
What kind of relationship
are you hoping to have?
Like every other woman,
I like the gentle and subtle men of Dongyue.
As for love...
I'll leave that to the man.
You told me not to prepare anything,
but I insist that you should try
the fine wine of Xiyue.
To remember this meaningful night.
I appreciate the gesture.
Bottoms up.
Come on.
General Mo.
You are the bravest woman I've ever met.
You're back.
Your dark circles...
Are you sleepy?
Not at all.
Get to the point then.
How did it go?
There should
more exciting things than just covering mouths.
Last night,
Yun Xiu went behind General Mo.
And then...
helped her on with her coat.
That's all?
That's all.
That was all he did the whole night?
My hype was pointless.
But for Yun Xiu,
this is a significant breakthrough.
If Feng Yang wasn't so paranoid
of her surroundings,
I would just peek at them.
Go get some sleep.
He's useless.
Although
it's a huge breakthrough for Yun Xiu,
he is barely making any progress.
Lord of Jealousy,
I have two questions for you.
Lord of Jealousy?
You mistrusted the rumors
and used Yun Xiu to upset me.
Keep quiet and listen to my questions.
What kind of girls do you like?
What kind of life do you yearn for?
Because of my amnesia,
I had doubts about many things at the moment.
I found it hard to agree with Eldest
Brother's view on marriage.
So I wasn't interested in girls.
I never yearned for love.
You get an F for that!
You don't know what I want to hear!
After I met Your Highness, everything changed.
It's too late to appease me.
One who has never seen the stars...
will find the night cold and lonely.
One who has never known love...
will use human relations as protection.
You helped me realize
that opening up to others
is the only way to have everything.
The person I love and the love I yearn...
will forever...
be whatever you show me.
Nothing more
and nothing less.
By the way, you mentioned
I was the one wooing you
in the other two timelines.
So...
Was I acting like Yun Xiu?
Back then,
I was the center of all spotlights
and admired by all.
You had it so much worse than Yun Xiu.
Are you ever tired of bluffing?
Believe it or leave it.
Let's get some sleep together.
Feng Yang.
Eighth Brother.
How was last night?
He didn't ask for military information,
ambush me,
or steal my badge.
Then why did I hear that he was acting strange?
What did you hear?
Someone saw you two
hugging each other.
Who is spreading this nonsense?
I'll break their legs!
If you two weren't hugging,
then he purposely
placed his hand over your mouth.
He was covering my mouth
so I wouldn't expose any
confidential information.
So he helped you put on a coat
for some reason?
Who is spreading these rumors?
I'll cut off their ears as a warning!
You're so anxious.
Are the rumors true?
Does it matter?
He said the ambush was a delivery.
No matter what he does, he will
never earn my trust again.
We can do this the nice way or the rough way.
What exactly happened during the ambush?
Would you believe me?
What about you?
Then I should leave.
Come back here.
Even I who know nothing about military tactics
know no one would disguise
an ambush with a delivery.
Not to mention you're a general who knows
how to pull off the Empty Fort Strategy
and pretend to surrender.
The Empty Fort Strategy and pretending
to surrender were tactics indeed.
Until that day...
I was relieving a garrison.
I led them across the border in secrecy.
Why don't we have a bet?
If you can get General Mo's personal trinket,
each of us will give you 100 taels.
Yes.
Get your money ready.
♪Another late autumn, another night♪
♪The swallow has returned, when will you♪
♪Should the yellowing red letters
be taken down or not♪
♪Hope makes it more heartbreaking♪
♪The wind blows, leaves fall on the window sill♪
♪Red brocade in the bronze mirror♪
♪The lonely Jiangnan is still noisy♪
♪And the light sigh from the deep boudoir♪
What are you waiting for? Do it now!
Go on!
♪A dip in ink to draw the birds of spring♪
♪A song of zither to press on the heartstring♪
♪Only the wind brings back your scent♪
♪Blindly believing that you are well♪
♪She longs eagerly day and night♪
♪Each stitch sends love from afar♪
♪Only, how could she let you know of her misery♪
♪All is well in her letters♪
On that day, I was the only one
who saw her weariness and loneliness.
I was also the first...
to admire her for the woman she is.
After that day,
I started to pay more attention to her.
I realized that
we share something in common.
Her determination on the battlefield
cannot conceal her weakness.
She can understand all of my strategies.
She can even stay one step ahead of me.
We are connected.
She has determination and generosity.
In other words,
she is like...
the other me.
The lemons are hanging on the tree,
under the tree, are you and me.
You and I?
Not you and I.
It's he and I.
He and you.
Carry on.
There was high tension at the border.
As part of the defensive forces,
I could do nothing.
When the tension receded,
there was an opportunity for a truce.
I thought
it was the right time to confess my love for her.
But Feng Yang finds you suspicious.
Whatever method you employ,
she will think it comes with a motive.
So I resorted to a desperate plan.
I wanted to give her my truce letter and
the present personally.
But she misunderstood it as an ambush.
So she retaliated.
Xiyue's troops lost.
And after the battle,
I lost my rank...
and was forced to have this peace-making marriage.
Your story sounds very miserable.
But it's not Feng Yang's fault for being paranoid.
Did you manage to give her the present?
I was in a rush,
I couldn't give her the present.
But after everything settled,
I tried my best
and found Feng Yang's personal servant.
I asked him to give her
the truce letter and the present
in the name of an admirer.
What was the present you gave her?
Feng Yang's old sword buckle was torn.
I asked around and found out
her favorite flower is balsam.
So I ordered
to have this pair of sword buckle made.
One for her,
the other is for me.
I've seen this sword buckle before.
Where did you see it?
Feng Yang carries it at her waist.
I've seen her wear it many times.
I have an idea.
You can't stay in the room all the time.
You'll become autistic.
You should come out and have a walk more often.
Admire the flowers and enjoy the fresh air.
Doing so can keep the wrinkles away.
I appreciate Your Highness's generosity.
But...
Sunlight! I'll hold the umbrella for you.
The sunlight isn't that bright.
It might rain later.
Let me do it.
Let me.
How dare you steal from me!
How can you prove this buckle belongs to you?
I carry it with me all the time.
You're clearly...
Where did you get it?
Where did you get yours?
It was a present.
It must be an admirer.
How do you know?
The buckles come in a pair.
They come in a pair?
You mean...
you gave me this buckle?
The container it was kept in
also has a truce letter in it.
Perhaps you never found it.
Where is the container now?
The Mo Residence.
It's simple.
Show everyone the container.
Everything will be clear.
(Truce Letter)
Was this the thing you were delivering?
Why did you hide the truce letter?
The King of Xiyue didn't know my plan.
I hid the letter to avoid further conflicts.
I made the wrong judgment
which led to a misunderstanding.
Please accept my apologies.
This wasn't your fault.
I had wronged you.
I will do my best
to prevent any misunderstanding from you.
But why did you give me a sword buckle?
It was for...
Peace!
It was a token of peace.
I think it's too much for Feng Yang to take in.
We should give her some space.
Yes.
You asked me
to give you an etiquette lesson.
We could start today.
This lesson is long overdue.
Let's go.
Come on.
Feng Yang, we'll leave you
to your contemplating.
This is weird.
The three of them are acting strange.
The misunderstanding has been resolved.
Why wouldn't you let me confess to her?
You're still the Main Prince Consort.
Feng Yang is very law-abiding.
Your reckless confession would
only scare her away.
If you want to win her heart,
you first need her to like you.
Only then will you have a chance.
Indeed.
All she thinks about are
tactics and military affairs.
It won't be easy to get her to like me.
If I remember correctly,
she said she liked gentle and
subtle men of Dongyue.
That's what bothers me the most.
Get rid of the beard,
do some threading,
then get a new hairstyle.
I, Master Tony Tan, will provide
one-stop services for you.
I will surely shape you into
a gentle and subtle man of Dongyue.
Not even your mother would recognize you.
Nonsense.
Men of Xiyue have their charismatic features.
Do not change yourself all for the sake of a woman.
Childish.
When you wooed me the last two times,
you groomed yourself with thick makeups,
like a peacock.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have fallen for you.
A peacock?
I would never do such a thing.
Now that we're married,
you're showing your true nature!
I never hide
my true nature.
You don't understand women!
Stop fighting.
I'm the one wooing Feng Yang, right?
You can decide then.
I'll go with your plan first.
You asked for this.
Don't even think I'll save you later.
You made the right choice.
Don't worry. You can count on me.
Stay still.
Yes, that's it.
Put some strength into it.
Push harder.
I am pushing! It's not working!
Are you up for the job?
Yun Xiu.
Your curly hair is indeed hard to deal with.
Yu Hao, push harder.
I am pushing.
You're useless.
Leave it to me.
Go ahead.
I'll be gentle.
Hold him still.
Look closely. This is the spot.
It's right here.
Now push.
I told you so.
How is this...
Push harder.
It won't work.
Yes.
All right.
It's done.
Okay. Move on to the next.
Next.
There's more?
Yes. Come on.
Turn around.
Bear with it.
Must men of Dongyue go through
this torment just to look presentable?
Just bear with it.
Bear with it.
The mighty eagle
has turned into a peacock in a cage.
You got to be the peacock,
so why can't he be one too?
Is pleasing a woman more important
than being himself?
Maybe I'll find out if it's worth it
after Feng Yang sees me.
Didn't I give you a mission?
Why are still you here to spread
fallacies to deceive people?
Get out.
I...
I have finished the mission.
Yun Xiu, a man dresses to
court with the lady he likes.
I know what girls like best.
After we've groomed you,
you will experience threading
for the first time.
It's so exciting.
Aren't you excited to try it out?
Are you ready?
Let's carry on.
Let's start.
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪A flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter what
hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have to
travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter what
hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have to
travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪