Hey! Hold on. Where did he go?
- Go, team! - Go, team!
- Hey, look! - Where's he going?
- What's going on? - Where are you going? Hey!
- Where's he going? - Where is he going now?
Darn it!
(Residence Hall)
I got you, punk.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Why didn't you pick up your phone?
I asked what you are doing here!
Why would you yell at me?
They told me not to return because of aftereffects.
Therefore, I was appointed as a professor...
at Korean National Police University.
So we're colleagues now.
What?
(Episode 7)
I thought you'd be happy to see me if I surprised you like this.
What's with that look on your face?
I'm just tired, that's all.
Why did you come here today of all days?
The sooner I come, the sooner I can start helping you out.
What?
I know you're investigating the illegal gambling ring here.
Captain told me everything.
Apparently, I told you...
that they're at the Police University.
You idiot, shut your mouth.
How could you blurt it out here?
Leave at once. Get lost.
You're making me even more tired.
Come on. Where are you going?
We should go for a drink and celebrate me joining you here.
The restaurant across the street sells pork rinds.
Chul Jin asked for it, saying he wants to work by your side.
That's why I transferred him there.
Even so...
How could you do this without talking to me first?
Anyway, okay. I have to go.
What happened?
Because of this...
Do you know...
what I had to give up on today because of this?
What?
Someone sneaked into my empty room and went through my laptop.
The frame for my family photo is broken.
(Captain)
Goodness.
Professor.
This jerk...
He's doing some funny things.
Professor.
Professor!
What are you going to do?
Hey, this is a homemade listening device,
and the maximum transmission range is 3km.
The only person within the distance who'd listen in on our talks...
is Mr. Go!
We don't know that for sure yet.
And even if it's him, what will you do right this instant?
I'll figure out what to do, so move out of my way!
Calm down.
That little rat. I will catch him!
- Please, Professor! - Let go, you punk!
(Korean National Police University)
Darn it.
Hey! Why did you try to stop me?
"Why"?
You told me to stop you when you were about to do something rash.
You said that's why every cop needs a partner...
and why 2 are better than 1.
You were the one who told me to do this. And what? "Why"?
Hey, this situation is...
So it's different in every situation?
Then take back what you said.
I don't care what happens. I won't stop you anymore!
So take back what you said.
Hey.
A real man...
never takes back his words because that's just embarrassing.
And since when did you always listen to me?
Okay, fine.
The fact that I had no idea that jerk has been...
sneaking into my office made me blow a fuse.
I'm sorry about that. Are we good now?
Why say that at the end and ruin your apology?
Wait until you get to my age because you'll be doing that too.
What are you going to do now?
What do you think?
We'll get the serial number from the device...
and find out where and when it was purchased...
as well as who bought it.
Then we'll catch the culprit.
What?
No. Hold on.
Hey, stop!
What's with those losers?
Stop!
Hey! You scumbag!
This is actually for the best.
Yes.
Why do you look so upset? What are you thinking about?
What do you think...
he gained from planting a bug?
Hey, think about what we gained.
We've now confirmed that the culprit is close by.
That we haven't been barking up the wrong tree.
He got scared and wiretapped me. Why?
It's because we're so close to catching him.
That's what's important here.
If the culprit is within the range,
that means we're in danger.
He even saw my family photo.
- Gosh. - Come on!
That's exactly what that jerk wants.
Getting scared by this.
And stepping back because we're scared...
so that we won't investigate him!
You punk. Are you going to feed him with what he wants?
But this is my first time!
I've never gone through this before.
Isn't it only natural that I'm scared?
Stop it!
You punk. Why are you whining here?
You should've gotten rid of such thoughts...
before coming here, you brat.
- Hey! - "Hey"?
What now? You want to have a go at me when I'm your professor?
Bring it on.
Gosh, that nutjob.
I can hear you.
What? Why? Are you really going to have a go at me?
Why did Chul Jin suddenly get transferred?
Am I the only one who finds it strange?
That he got transferred to our school now of all times?
Don't bark up the wrong tree.
Chul Jin is here to help with our investigation,
and I knew it all along.
Are you sure?
Are you sure you knew?
Of course, you punk!
Gosh.
Darn it.
Hey, Sun Ho.
Why did you do that?
Back in the field.
Oh, that...
I suddenly got a stomachache.
I must've eaten something bad during lunch.
My stomach was upset.
Is that true?
Five minutes to the evening roll call.
Get ready for the roll call.
I'll get going. Good night.
(Scientific Investigation, Professor Seo Sang Hak)
Do you know the serial murder case that occurred in saunas?
It was raining.
The night was chilly.
The phone rang sharply despite the loud sound of rain.
Ring!
"This is a sauna in Dogok-dong."
"There's a man dying here!"
"What did she say?"
When we arrived at the scene, the victim was already dead.
The suspect set the sauna on fire and fled.
All the evidence was destroyed,
and we were thinking this will cause us a headache.
But right then!
From a distance, someone shouted, "Inspector Seo! Come look at this!"
"What?"
One step, two steps.
I went close to the burned body.
"Wait, that is..."
The suspect's prints were clearly visible on the body.
You're bluffing!
Is this true?
Thanks to the prints left on the victim's body,
the case was solved.
It's the first case of Korea.
No way.
Professor Yu, when did you get here?
I heard you've been teaching as a professor your whole career.
It's just a rumor.
Oh, a rumor?
Right.
What brought you to the clubroom?
Oh, I wanted to...
ask you for a favor.
(Korean National Police University)
Why is the TV off?
My gosh.
The first baseman, Kim Ji Ho, is dashing at full speed.
You've never tasted a beer like this. This is Gossi Beer.
What...
Darn it.
What was that about?
What?
Where did the remote control go?
Well...
Can you check if the print on this remote control...
is on this laptop?
Aren't you going to tell me...
the story behind this when you're asking for a favor?
Don't you think you need to tell me that?
Do you think you can handle it?
It might be disturbing.
I'm weakhearted, so...
Just consider it done.
It's nothing difficult anyway.
Okay. Thank you.
Oh, right.
There's also a difficult favor I must ask.
Do you need anything, Kang Hee?
I...
like you.
Are you that upset?
Do you want to use my holiday?
No, it's not because of that.
You're not even done.
Hey, guys! I got good news!
Did you hear?
They're giving everyone a holiday!
- What? - The faculty members decided it.
Everyone will get a day off!
- Are you sure? - Yes!
It looks like Professor Seo pushed ahead with it.
This is amazing!
Professor Seo is a romanticist in many ways.
Right.
But he used to be really scary when I was in school.
Oh, right.
You went to our school too, right?
- Yes, I did. - You know everything about him.
I guess you've become friends with him already.
I'm in the 25th batch.
I studied at the Yongin campus,
so I'm not very familiar with this one.
How did you become friends with Professor Yu?
He was my first supervisor in Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency.
Since then, I've followed him everywhere.
We were inseparable.
It seems like you remember everything.
Are you sure you're suffering from dissociative amnesia?
That condition can be quite funny.
Some erase the entire memory of their first love.
Some erase the people they met in the army from their memory.
They say an entire part of your life gets erased.
But I'm not sure which part of mine got erased.
I hope only bad memories were erased.
Thank you.
She can be quite nosy.
Where is Professor Yu? Did he go home already?
What?
The surveillance cameras were all very old,
so we've been replacing all of them for a month.
So we don't have any recorded footage.
Then what am I supposed to do?
Sorry? About what?
Sorry about that. Darn it.
(Professor Yu Dong Man)
Gosh, you startled me.
Hey, airhead!
Are you here to see Dong Man? He isn't in.
I'm not sure if you saw the board,
but how could you order fried eggs at a pub?
Is there a law saying that you can't sell fried eggs at a pub?
I'm sure you know about laws better than me.
The one who breaks the law...
knows better than the one who keeps the law.
Well, we all live different lives.
By the way,
did you leave...
after seeing me win in the relay race yesterday?
Relay race?
I didn't see it. Why?
Well, I was just curious if you did.
Since you came to school yesterday.
I see. I just looked around the school.
I went to the residence hall too.
I see.
Why are you so surprised? I was even more surprised.
I'll be off. It's about time for the roll call.
Of course I did.
Gosh, you were so fast.
I see. So you did see me.
Sun Ho ran out first in a flash,
and you ran after him in a flash.
Are you saying that you won with that?
My goodness.
So he was watching all along?
Gosh.
I guess you and Sun Ho are very close.
You guys were totally like a team.
Gosh, that jerk.
What do you think he gained from planting a bug?
Kang Sun Ho.
Eon Ju.
Sun Ho. This is the day.
Weren't you asleep?
(Korean National Police University)
Students in uniform are not allowed...
to stain the dignity of students at the Police University.
Putting your hands in your pocket, clasping them behind your back,
spitting,
smoking, or eating while walking are all forbidden.
Also, you're not allowed to enter places that can damage...
your reputation and dignity.
You're not allowed to enter places that are...
only for entertainment.
Refrain from all acts...
that can harm the dignity of the Police University.
What you do in your uniform...
can become the image of the police.
Please keep that in mind.
We will now check your uniform and hair.
Your decision as a romanticist worked out.
It's against equity though.
I told you to say the right thing at a right time.
People will talk behind your back.
You shouldn't hang out with abnormal people.
Don't fight.
Unfortunately, I'm not the romanticist.
What?
Wear your badge correctly.
Shine your shoes.
I have a date today.
What are you doing today?
I...
have a very important appointment.
"Appointment"?
You're not hiding anything from me, right?
Of course not. I don't have anything.
Sun Ho, what are you doing today?
I...
I don't know yet.
If the culprit is within the range, that means we're in danger.
He even saw my family photo.
Sung Soo, what are you going to do?
- I don't know. - Why not?
Nice.
Let's sit here.
Why? Did you forget something?
I did. I need to drop by the residence hall. You go ahead.
All right.
We're leaving now.
Let's go!
(Korean National Police University)
Professor Yu.
Let's investigate Mr. Park too.
Like we did with Professor Kwon.
It's a relief if there's nothing.
So if we check thoroughly this time again...
I think...
I've told you that Chul Jin is not in the picture.
Your phone.
(Professor Yu Dong Man)
(Will you delete the contact information?)
Stop working on this case.
Is it because I asked you to investigate Mr. Park?
Shouldn't you ask me why I think so first?
Save that foolish assumption for your reports.
Don't you hear me?
Don't come to my office.
From now on, the only place...
that you and I will meet is the classroom.
Is that it?
The partner you've been saying?
You said you'll never give up on the investigation,
but this is it?
You are scared.
Isn't that what you wanted to hear?
Gosh.
Do you think you can break it with that?
(Police University)
Hey, why won't you take the shuttle bus?
Why did you lie to me?
I wanted to kick you but took it out on the poor trash can instead.
Take the next bus!
I'll just go get some tests done at the hospital.
When I'm back, we'll go for pork belly and drinks.
You'd better hurry.
The traffic is bad on weekends.
Dong Man, is everything okay?
Why?
You look like someone...
who just got dumped.
I'll be right back.
You are scared.
Isn't that what you wanted to hear?
(Parking Reserved for Professors Only)
- Are you going somewhere? - Gosh, you startled me.
Yes, I'm going somewhere.
Where? Oh, you bought booze.
I'm not in the mood to joke with you.
You're going to drink soju? With who? Is it a woman?
Are you always this interested in everyone's business?
Or are you just like this with me?
Just with you.
You're a dangerous lady. You really are.
Who is this woman? Is she prettier than me?
That's impossible.
Get in the car if you're curious.
Are you crazy?
How long have you worked at the Police University?
I think this is my 7th or 8th year.
Was Gossi Beer around when you first joined the school?
No, it suddenly opened one day.
That spot has always been like that.
It always had different owners doing different things.
But surprisingly, Mr. Go has been there for a while.
And he befriended all the neighbors very quickly.
Why do you ask?
I should pick up some ramyeon too.
Where are we going?
Do you really want to get kicked in the shin?
Just kick me.
Do it all you want, if it'll make you feel better.
I can put up with it.
But you know, the trial...
Hold on. Gosh.
I've been waiting for this day.
I even put on the uniform without knowing you were...
taking me to my mom's trial,
so I'm...
really upset right now.
You'd better not follow me.
If you do, I'll actually break your leg.
Wait, Kang Hee...
(Court in Session)
All the evidence shows that...
the defendant willingly participated in the opening of the casino.
yet the defendant refuses to accept it?
Well...
She admits to everything and...
Didn't she request an appeal because she can't accept it?
My point exactly!
(Defendant)
Let me do the talking.
Look, Prosecutor.
I admit that I gambled.
Ma'am.
They told me I had to open a crypto account...
or whatever it's called to place bets.
I had no idea what it was, so I asked them to take care of it.
That's why that man opened the account for me.
I played a few games with it but ended up blowing all the money.
Then I quit. That was a long time ago.
And what? I opened the casino?
Come on! I'm not gutsy enough to do something like that.
I'd like to bring in a witness.
(Witness)
I clearly remember her telling me...
that she was running an illegal gambling site...
with some people in the Philippines...
and that it was very lucrative.
You witch.
Don't you dare lie like that.
Why would I run away if I were running something so lucrative?
And why would I let my daughter...
freeload off other people all her life?
Order!
And Witness.
Spit out your gum, please.
Sure.
You two. I bet you talked and decided to dump this all on me.
Ms. Oh Jung Ja.
You said your name was Oh Ga Eul.
Why are you calling me by the name I do not wish to use?
Do I not have any rights?
Hey. From the get-go, you were planning...
to dump it all on me and close the case.
I may look like I've had an easy life,
but I've been through all sorts of things. Don't mess with me!
I bet you were bribed. Who bribed you?
You call this the law?
Hey! Yes, you. As soon as I get out of jail,
I will kill you. Do you hear me?
Let's go.
- You don't need to see this. - Order!
Is this the law?
No. You need to see this, Kang Hee.
You are the only one who can tell whether or not...
your mom is telling the truth.
So you have to stay and watch the trial.
You'd better tell the truth.
Kang Sun Ho, let go.
You let go.
What are you guys doing in a courtroom?
Let go, both of you.
She's lying!
Defendant, please be seated.
Prosecutor, you may give your closing argument.
Let go!
The estimated sum of the bets...
accumulated by this illegal gambling site...
under the defendant's name reaches tens of millions of dollars.
Her accomplice, Kim Soon Ae,
has admitted to everything and withdrew the appeal,
whereas Defendant Oh Jung Ja, who has priors,
is busy listing excuses in this courtroom...
instead of showing remorse.
Ergo, the original sentence of two years in prison...
along with the fine of 500,000 dollars...
for habitual gambling, setting up a site for gambling,
and violating the Electronic Financial Transactions Act was fair.
Hence, I ask the court to dismiss her appeal.
We will hear the defense counsel's closing argument...
before we wrap up.
Counsel.
Your Honor.
(Judge)
You know, I have admitted to everything I did.
Gambling? Yes, I gambled.
And I will gladly accept the punishment for it.
But...
I refuse to be punished for something I didn't do.
Opening the gambling site?
I swear on my daughter's name.
I never did such a thing.
[VIU Ver] KBS E07 'Police University'
"The Disappointment"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
It's simple.
The money that people use to bet on this site...
is saved as cryptocurrency.
It's the same website.
(Court in Session)
(Yu Dong Man, No Result Found)
Right.
Having fun?
- What? - Acting cool, then chickening out.
That's your specialty.
Am I wrong?
Thanks to you guys, I stayed until the end.
Thank you.
But can you guys leave now?
I don't want to be embarrassed anymore.
He's such a puppy.
Sit down. Your legs will hurt.
My mom...
wasn't lying.
She's not at fault.
I know her.
I know how she's like when she lies.
When I was seven,
I asked her why I'm the only one without a dad,
and she said this while avoiding my eyes.
"Your dad is working abroad."
When I was 13,
I asked her if she's going to prison again,
and she avoided my eyes again and said...
that she's not.
But she did.
That's when I realized it.
That...
if Mom avoids my eyes,
that means she's lying.
But in the courtroom, she looked straight into my eyes.
Mom didn't do it.
I'm asking this because I'm dumbfounded.
Why are you here?
My point exactly.
Because I'm lonely.
Why would you come here when you're lonely?
My point exactly.
Because I'm super lonely.
Your close colleague got transferred.
Why didn't you go see him?
Hey, when people are super lonely,
they meet people they're not close to.
The closer you are, you can't be honest.
There are times when you can't share everything.
- What? - Here.
I thought you wouldn't let me use it because it's expensive.
Just hang onto it while I use the restroom.
Gosh, am I getting old?
What's going on, seriously?
Why did you become so weak? What's wrong?
You know...
I said all those things, knowing I'll regret it later,
but I'm regretting it already. Darn it.
Then why did you say it?
I didn't want to regret it more later.
It's strange.
I'm not sure what it's about, but why are you already scared?
I guess it's because I have people to protect now.
I'm scared to make choices.
Who is that woman? Is she prettier than me?
Gosh.
- Eon... - Eon Ju!
What... Noh Bum Tae?
What?
What... Cho Jun Wook?
What are you doing here?
I have a date with Eon Ju.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
How could you not tell me?
You're the one who didn't tell me. I told you I have a date.
Hey, what's the problem?
You both wanted to see me,
so I thought we could all meet up.
Here. Drink up!
- Thank you! Cheers! - Cheers!
Hey, is this the date you mentioned?
What? You're not keeping any secret from me?
What? Are you not going to drink it?
Drin up.
Hurry up!
When it comes to alcohol,
the speed matters more than the amount.
- Drink up! - Bottoms up!
- Cheers! - Cheers!
The last bus to Asan just got all sold out.
We're out of tickets.
What?
(To Asan, sold out, To Daejeon, sold out)
No, it's really fine.
I'll just take the first bus in the morning.
How can you wait until then?
Just come with me, please?
Here's your beer.
- Enjoy. - Thank you.
I'll just have one more.
I'll go home after this.
(Kang Hee)
(Yoon Digital)
You didn't have to get this.
My mom told me to never go empty-handed...
when visiting someone's place.
Kang Hee.
Yes?
Are you and Min Kyu...
- No, never mind. - What about me and Min Kyu?
I was wondering if you two were seeing each other.
Are you crazy? He's just a friend.
Where is your place?
Over here. We're here.
(Yoon Digital)
Dad.
Come in.
Hello.
Is he inside? Wait here.
Dad.
(Yoon Digital, Yoon Taek Il)
Yoon Taek Il?
Dad?
Did he go somewhere?
Dad...
Dad.
- Sun Ho. Hey! - Dad!
(Yoon Digital)
What are you doing?
Sun Ho.
- Hey. Sun Ho! - Dad...
- Dad... - What's wrong?
What happened?
Hey, what's going on?
Dad wasn't home.
Maybe he went out to get something.
Son!
(Yoon Seung Bum)
The guy at the judo gym?
I didn't know they were brothers.
Here, you can wear this.
I'll help you, Dad.
No, it's okay.
Why don't you give your girlfriend a tour of the house?
She's not my girlfriend.
Do you have any photos of Sun Ho when he was a baby?
I only see photos of him grown up.
Oh, that's...
We moved around a lot,
so I don't have photos of my sons when they were little.
I see. Same here.
Where can I get changed?
In that room.
By the way, what happened in your room? It's a mess.
Well, I tried on a bunch of different outfits...
because I wanted to look nice.
Oh, no. I forgot to press the cook button.
I'll go pick up some instant rice.
My goodness.
- Take a seat. - It looks amazing.
Leave it. Just sit down, please.
Gosh, that'd make me uncomfortable. Please let me help.
And please drop the honorifics.
It'll help me enjoy the food even more.
Sun Ho is too nice. He's probably boring.
Sorry? Not at all.
I mean, he is nice.
But he's pretty decisive, and he rarely gets flustered.
Also, he's very outspoken, so our classmates look up to him.
Really?
Yes.
That's why I was surprised earlier.
I've never seen him like that.
He seemed all flustered and lost,
like a five-year-old boy who couldn't find his dad.
I was always afraid he'd disappear one day.
But he's all protective of me now that he's grown up.
He was like the Polkaroo when he was little.
He'd be right behind me when I thought he wasn't there.
And when I thought he was there, he was gone.
He was always like that.
But today, he was right there.
He's no longer like the Polkaroo.
When he walks into the room, you just know.
He sure stands out, wherever he goes.
- I'm back. - Hey.
Go heat up the rice.
Hurry. I'm hungry.
Okay.
I think I ate too much. I'm so full.
Sorry for stealing your room.
Let me sleep here just one night.
Why are you staring at me?
Get out.
Okay. Good night.
(Social Studies, Yoon Seung Bum)
This looks like a monk's desk.
(Ethics and Philosophy, Kang Sun Ho)
(Social Studies, Yoon Seung Bum)
(Yoon Digital, Yoon Taek Il)
Yoon Taek Il?
Do you have any photos of Sun Ho when he was a baby?
I only see photos of him grown up.
Oh, that's...
We moved around a lot,
so I don't have photos of my sons when they were little.
Is that why he seemed like an outsider to me as well?
Do you like her that much?
Why are you so surprised?
Well, we're just friends.
What are you talking about?
Figure out where things stand, no matter what her answer may be.
Right.
Dad.
You said this to me a while back.
About things that happen before I become a cop,
you said I can repay them in the future.
Yes, I did.
But what if...
dangerous things happen when I do that?
And what if I fail to protect someone who is dear to me?
What should I do, then?
That thought terrifies me.
I'm scared. My head is telling me not to do it...
and that I don't need to do it. But the thing is...
But...
you want to do it.
Then you should do it.
You've always held yourself back,
so the fact that you're this torn...
tells me that you should do it.
Just do it.
But make sure you do it properly.
Only then will you become a great police officer...
who can protect everyone who is dear to you.
As your dad,
I will always believe in the decisions that you make.
Why don't we try to analyze this burner phone's call patterns?
There's a program that analyzes call patterns and frequency.
If we look into the base station using that,
we should be able to track down the person using the burner phone.
Done.
(Soju)
Is the investigation still ongoing?
Yes, I haven't caught the culprit yet.
Is Kang Sun Ho working on it with you?
Why are you so surprised?
It's so obvious.
Well, I was just training him.
But he's no longer involved.
That's why you're lonely now.
When you're investigating a case, you have to suspect...
even those closest to you if you spot anything suspicious.
It can be awful and lonely,
but you have to do it.
That's why you were suspicious of me as well?
Just like fishing,
the investigation will eventually come to an end.
What or whom will I see at the end of this investigation,
and what will happen in the end?
I'm scared to find out.
That's when you can...
lean on your friends.
Just come here anytime you're lonely.
What? You caught one.
What?
- Gosh. - Wow!
Gosh, what's this? I caught one!
- Oh, my! Help me. - Wow!
- Help me! - Hold on.
- Wait. - Grab it!
My gosh.
- Look at that. - Wow.
Goodness.
My gosh.
Your dad seems like a nice man.
You've grown up well.
Anyway, don't tell anyone that I slept over at your place.
I don't want people to gossip when we're not even seeing each other.
Kang Hee.
I'll catch the real culprit of your mother's case.
I'll put everything back to normal.
Actually,
I've been investigating a case with Professor Yu.
I see.
- What? - I couldn't finish the race...
because of that investigation.
What are you investigating?
I mean, is that related to my mom's case?
That...
I'll tell you after I discuss it with Professor Yu.
I'm planning to have it out with him today.
Have it out?
Yes, and...
I'm going to have it out with you after him.
It's about time we have it out and decide what we are.
(Professor Yu Dong Man)
Yes, I'll go to your office.
(KCSI)
Did you get his print?
Yes, I did, but...
(Forensic Science Room)
The print on this laptop...
wasn't found on this remote control you brought...
but on this plastic cup.
You look like someone who just got dumped.
I'll be right back. Goodness.
Dong Man.
Professor Yu.
I can't stop working on this case.
No. I won't.
You said the culprit is here.
- How did you... - I must...
catch the culprit at all costs.
So that I can...
protect the people I love.
I've made up my mind,
so you should decide.
I must...
see the end of this case.
Dong Man.
(Police University)
You're not getting Sun Ho...
involved in your private matter, are you?
You did it, didn't you?
We don't know if you were injured...
while carrying out a sting operation...
or if you're just putting on a show.
Is that really what you think?
Do you know what this is?
I got a report.
It says that the sample questions going around the students...
seem to be the exam paper for Criminal Investigation.
He can't deny it.
They even found an envelope of money in his office.
The arrest warrant will be issued soon.
You must hurry.
We'll be able to save Professor Yu, right?
I'm going to save your supervisor.