Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ No longer panicking on the night of the blackout ♫
♫ You're by my side, illuminating a beam of light for me ♫
♫ Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet ♫
♫ Your breath brushes up against my cheek  ♫
♫ With you warming up the stage,
happiness never comes to a close ♫
♫ Boring jokes add some sweetness to the dinner ♫
♫ Daily life is even more like a comic than comics themselves ♫
♫ Happiness and sadness ♫
♫ Make up the moments of life ♫
♫ Rainy days become very special because of you ♫
♫ Picked up a pitiful youngster off the street ♫
♫ No matter when and where, you always appear ♫
♫ Holding me tightly and spinning in circles ♫
♫ Rainy days make me so nostalgic because of you ♫
♫ Becoming some part of the memories ♫
♫ Walking down a street with lights lighting up
one after another ♫
♫ Warming up the whole world ♫
[Please Feel at Ease Mr. Ling]
[Episode 12]
So you guys were together before?
We absolutely did not.
We're just simply classmates.
That's all.
- Also, regarding the photo—
- I know about the photo.
It's obvious that she was using you.
I have such a smart brain. Of course I can think of that.
So is it the same with being afraid of water?
Being afraid of water was all thanks to my elder brother.
As long as you're by my side, I'll be at ease.
After Johnny and them changed jobs last time,
they left with the SA system that we were developing.
Feite Group is about to release the SA system.
If they succeed in releasing it, then ours
will be worthless.
Most of Ling Fang's money was invested in Fang Yu Group.
Developing these kinds of things cannot be done that easily.
Where did he get so much funds?
The people between Feite Group are from the company. I really don't understand.
Why must these shareholders invest in Feite Group?
Looks like they're determined to follow Ling Fang.
Ling Fang definitely promised those people that they'll get more in return
and is also preparing to divide the dividends for New Way.
Let's go to Fangyu Group.
Okay.
Uncles, don't worry. I won't disappoint you guys.
Then we'll all rely on you, President Ling Fang.
You scared me!
W-why did you stand behind me and not make noise?
If you didn't do anything guilty then what is there to be afraid of, elder brother?
I'm happy today. I won't hold a grudge.
You're so merciless this time by using the two-pronged approach.
This gave New Way a heavy blow while taking many huge shareholders from us.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Using Li Group's money to block off New Way's survival.
This is really a good method.
What do you think will happen if dad finds out?
Then tell him.
You were always a tattle teller anyways.
Let me put it this way. It's fine even if he finds out.
Let him see how I, Ling Fang, casually
A small company can easily replace the company, New Way, that you put all your efforts in.
Didn't you always say that only e-commerce
and technology can represent the future of the Ling Group?
I'll let you see what the future will look at.
You always want to defeat me.
- What do you want to prove?
- To prove that I'm the only successor to Ling Group
and you're nothing.
Aren't you afraid that you'll get eaten up by your greediness?
All of this was originally mines!
You just had a share of it!
How dare you say I'm greedy? Ridiculous.
What consequences?
I think you are just being a sour grape.
Then I hope your wish comes true.
How come this brat isn't anxious at all?
Making me not feel good.
Is everything prepared?
Don't let him have a chance.
He's a gecko who pokes into every nooks and corners.
Don't worry, everything has been prepared.
Let's go.
[New Way]
Nana, Jiejie, Beibei, and Xiao Chi, tell the people from your department to have a meeting with me.
- Okay.
The hacker caused the company to lose and leak many important documents.
The company is now making arrangements to get them back.
Less than 35% was found.
In terms of abilities, we have two groups who wanted to resign.
We need to arrange people immediately to get into those position.
Are you trying to murder me?
I w-was practicing.
Practicing?
Why did you come?
Your delivery girl is here to send you shrimps.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Let's go.
Very fresh grilled shrimped
with RIO,
is amazing.
Do you smell it?
What's wrong?
Don't tell me that you never ate grilled shrimps before.
Give it a try. Give it a try and you'll know. It's really tasty.
I'll demonstrate for you.
Remove the head then the tail.
Give it a try. Let me do it.
I don't think this shrimp isn't ready for someone to eat it yet.
How is it? Is it tasty?
Put on the gloves. Here.
Is it tasty?
Your delivery girl has accomplished her mission today.
I won't disturb you from working. I'll get going first.
- Let me send you.
- No need, I can go back myself.
No, wait for me here. Let me go wash my hands.
I'll come back soon. Wait for me.
Don't worry, I'm here.
I won't take up your time from working overtime.
Hurry and finish so you can come look for me.
Gu Xin'er, look time no see.
This is the rich daughter of the Gu family.
She goes on the trending list quite often.
Isn't she the rumored girlfriend with the president of New Way recently?
Is that so, Xin'er?
What's going on with the Second Young Master of the Ling family?
You guys are considered childhood sweethearts.
Why did he personally come out to deny this issue with you?
I heard you're getting married. Congrats.
Is it the Master Chen that we took back our investment from?
No way, I dumped him long ago.
My fiancé is Qin Hui's son.
So, it's the son of President Qin who manages golf for VIP customers.
Since you and Young Master Qin are getting married, then please advise him
to stop sending me flowers each day. It's already been 2 years.
I don't want our company's cleaning staff to do
useless cleaning everyday.
You're spouting nonsense! It must be you who seduced him.
Are you fine?
I'm fine.
Auntie, this fairy sister already said
it's your fiancé with wishful thinking who keeps pestering her.
so please go back and control your man.
Stop splashing others in public.
Make it clear, who's an auntie?
How did you know I was here?
Looks I need to be cautious in my postings in the future.
Your fans won't like it.
Thanks for today.
But at this point, the art exhibition should be closed.
It's fine, there's always next time.
However, there seems to be a performance venue near here
just about to start operation.
Wait for me. I'm going to purchase the tickets.
What is it?
Don't worry. Everything has been prepared.
There's still 3 hours left before Fei Te's ceremony starts.
Is there any movement from New Way?
Nothing much.
Seems like my younger brother is trapped in a warm and cosy place and doesn't want to come out.
President Ling, you are really brilliant in using the element of surprise to your advantage.
Let me ask you. Is Ling Yue,
will he fail to save the hopeless situation?
Yes. He's in a hopeless situation
Am I handsome?
Handsome.
Let's go.
Hello?
Now?
- Boss
- What is it? Speak.
Feite just received a legal notice.
What do you mean?
New Way filed a lawsuit with the Dispute Department to sue for theft of trade secrets.
So sudden.
Do a news blackout. Feite must be listed as per normal.
What's that expression? Say it!
I'm afraid there's no way. It happened too suddenly.
The shareholders of the company have received the news.
They are selling their Feite's stocks at a low price.
These impatient old fogeys.
Can't hold back just because of a lawyer's notice.
It seems that the shareholders received an email last night.
It contained the turnover sales of Feite.
They're saying we're giving everyone empty checks and
that the promised growth rate is very hard to achieve.
Immediately, go buy all those circulating shares back. Do you hear me?
Yes
Come in!
President Ling.
I'm afraid you can't buy your shares back.
What do you mean?
Do you think that Fangyu Construction can't afford it?
Let's not talk about whether you can afford it.
The more important thing is whether I'm willing to sell to you.
What does it have to do with him?
It was you.
Let go! Let go!
Call security!
Are you afraid of a woman?
Look, President Ling, even if the security comes, they wouldn't be able to beat her.
This isn't that simple.
Why do I feel like I got tricked?
Did you plan it a long time ago?
Big bro, do you think I didn't know you coveted New Way for a long time?
My car accident was also a part of your plan.
Stalling me, so that your Fei Te can rise easily.
You even have time to take away my team and stole New Way's core technology.
You already knew?
You did it on purpose!
In order to mess me up, you even dared to give me your own company's core technology. You're really cruel!
But you think you won?
Let's see how long your company can last without the core technology.
I am still Fei Te's biggest shareholder!
Do you think that by taking away my team,
taking away the SA system,
New Way's will collapse?
Actually I need to thank you.
I always thought New Way's personals is redundant. All thanks to you,
you helped me do some staff reduction.
I've always invested within this country in outstanding freshman
to carry out fully automated technology research and development.
So far, it has been very effective and ready to enter the construction phase.
So that SA semi-automatic system,
it was an illusion created by you?
Originally, it wasn't.
It's only that big bro made me advance my plans. That's it.
If it weren't for your greediness,
maybe you wouldn't have lost so much today.
Also, if you keep being so greedy,
sooner or later, you will be swallowed by your ambition.
Either way, you won.
You get to have all the cool talk.
Damn.
Are you okay?
Hello, Director Liu.
No, it is definitely not like what the rumors say.
Our boss...
He isn't here. He left the country a few days ago.
Yes, yes.
Boss, what do we do?
Right now, all the shareholders are looking for you.
What do we do?
Let me think about it.
Everyone that's looking for me, tell them I'm not here.
Okay.
Hello...Director Zhou.
By the way, President Ling, the Dispute Department needs new evidence.
No need.
I understand.
[Resume]
All these resumes didn't get any response.
It's really hard for me to be a corporate slave.
Don't be anxious. I haven't found a job either.
If you really can't do it, just go back and be the CEO's wife.
Or inherit the CEO's family business. It's not bad too.
Look at you again. It's not like you don't know.
Look over there.
Let me tell you.
That person has been taking selfies ever since he sat down.
That's too narcissitic.
With his looks, opening dermabrasion and touch-ups,
-it's also not like this...
- Manager Zhao.
Someone you know?
Stop pretending.
I know you guys have been observing me for a long time.
Waiter, give me a White Water.
Are you looking for a job?
- Yes
- Think about
- coming to my company.
- Your company?
Yes I've resigned and I'm going to start my own company.
I just met an author
but I think his price is rather high.
So I'm still thinking it over.
He just wants to jump bridges (switch jobs), but I can't find any jobs.
Your voice was quite loud earlier.
Great. Manager Zhao has great courage!
Just call me Zhao Lei.
Manager Zhao, why don't you consider Anxin as your business partner?
Our Anxin is a super Webtoon master.
Webtoon master?
No, she's speaking nonsense. I'm not some kind of Webtoon master.
I'm someone that likes to draw mangas only.
What's your ID?
Northwest towards Chang'an.
Excuse me, I couldn't hold it.
I'll do it myself!
Your lipstick doesn't seem to be waterproof.
Apply Armani lipstick and l will smear it for you.
Don't. I don't have any intention of setting foot into the beauty circle lately.
Northwest towards Chang'an, I have always been your fan.
You've seen my work?
Of course!
Not long ago, I pursued this and accidently, picked up a prince.
However, not long after, it stopped uploading. I was even sad for a long time.
Why aren't you uploading anymore?
Y-y-you can come to my company.
You only need to invest in the copyrights.
So this job is
just the two of us?
Our office will expand very quick.
How about including my good friend You You too?
Her sketches are super fast and smooth.
Really?
So how?
Not bad. You have talent.
But who is this?
Mike, an idol.
Most of his drawings are done by You You.
I don't know him. But it's ok.
Then Miss You You, are you willing to join our company?
I'll think about it.
Don't think.
You can't find a job anyway. Let's just do it together.
How do you know I can't find a job?
Would people who can find a job be like you guys?
Just chatting in a cafe in the middle of the day?
How about it?
Fine. I'll join.
Then what's our company called?
Galaxy Cool Man!
All finished.
Isn't still crooked?
It's not crooked. The logo I designed is supposed to be tilted.
That's right, it's fine.
Let's go take a look inside.
Look, how is it?
The new renovation cost quite a big sum of money. It's not bad.
The photos are rather nice.
I was diligent, okay?
Oh right, Anxin that's your spot.
This is the CEO's spot. You You just sit there.
Why am I here?
Because you're close to the door and can easily get the takeout.
Right, we can put a sofa there and put up a poster here.
I think it's rather spacious here.
Look, look who's here.
Why are you here?
Boss, can I work here?
Don't block me.
This person is totally senseless. Come, help me to tidy up.
Don't stop me from looking at how lovey-dovey they are.
Yes, food and housing is included, but no salary.
When do I sign the contract?
Let's go get some food.
Why did you bring an umbrella?
It's going to rain today.
It's going to rain? How can that be when it's so sunny.
Don't you check the weather report?
The weather report is always inaccurate so I never look at it.
Then let's pretend today it's accurate.
I planned ahead. Is there a reward for me?
They're looking.
Now it's okay.
♫ The first time I met you, I have never thought there would come a day ♫
- Let's go.
- Let's go!
♫ You are full of coldness. No way to get close ♫
♫ Prepare for plan two at any time ♫
Anxin, someone delivered warmth again.
Look what it is.
Don't be so nosy. Come help me.
A ball?
The weather is sunny today. Average temperature is 20°C.
The temperate at night is 18°C.
Please wear more clothes to prevent catching a cold.
This is, unexpectedly, a smart globe.
[I will name it Xiao Liu in the future.]
[T/N : Little Six]
[You are Xiao Ba and it's Xiao Liu. Perfect match.]
[T/N : Xiao Ba means Little Eight]
[You are my CP instead]
[T/N : internet slang for Couple Pairing]
[Since you know we are CP, just study behind my back.]
I know much more than you think.
[Bragging? Do you still remember that you short-circuited my microwave?]
[You are not a grounded person.]
Grounded? Just wait.
It's 12 noon now. Time for lunch.
Take your lunch on time so that you will have good health.
Why are you so talkative just like Ling Yue?
What happens if I don't eat lunch? Can you see me?
Not eating on time can cause gastritis, stomach ulcers, and indigestion.
It will reduce cerebral function and affect cerebral development.
- Even this?
- It will also lead to a decline in intelligence...
- I'm going. Stop talking.
Eat!
Is no one going to help me change the water?
President Ling
It's done.
What's going on?
Is the information prepared?
It's ready.
Can we still come back?
If this continues...
I will have nothing and no prospects in the future.
- It's a swift and violent collapse.
- That's right.
If this is the case, there won't be any future prospects.
Alright, no more fighting.
Listen to me.
We are all aware of the situation now.
Dear shareholders, please express your personal views.
Chairman, we and Director Ling Fang
We signed a clear contract.
He said that, in order to develop the the strength of the logistics industry, he fixed that whatever company.
Now, not only the promise was not fulfilled,
we have incurred losses too.
We are family. We don't want to take this to court too.
Chairman, please preside over this difficult situation for us.
Then what do you wish he do?
We just want back our original shares.
Since there's no money,
cash out Fang Yu Construction's stocks
to compensate everyone.
Are you trying to kill me?
Shut up!
Such a big problem happened,
and you want to wash your hands of this?!
Do according to what they said.
Everyone, I have a better plan.
Currently, Fang Yu Construction has been badly hit.
Even if you cash out the stocks, it won't be able to make up for everyone.
At most it will only make everyone feel a bit better.
If everyone is willing, I can sell 5% of my New Way's shares
to you at a lower price.
Take it as my older brother's apology.
I believe everyone knows that New Way is going to be listed in the market.
This 5% profit
will be very promising in the future.
That's right. This is not a bad idea.
with the current situation.
Fine.
It's a solution too.
Yes, it can make up for it.
Look, the report is rather positive. Lao Shen.
Fang Yu Construction is now just an entity without any content.
Instead of being obsessed with it, why not choose choose one with a promising future?
It still requires us to spend money on stocks.
It doesn't look like a great plan.
Since it's like this, you all should just take my brother's shares.
Taking into account our relationship with the Chairman,
I don't want to hesitate any further and go with the decision.
Chairman, we will pass this now. We don't want to delay the handling of your family's matters.
Thank you all for making it out.
Eldest son.
I can't care how you harassed others with unreasonable demands in the past
but your approach has
threatened the interests within the group.
Fortunately, my second son has reaped some profits for you.
Otherwise, I won't be able to protect you.
Dad, I know my mistake.
You know your mistake? Which aspect?
I shouldn't be arrogant and switched from real estate to e-commerce.
My mistake was not predicting the risks and difficulties across the industries.
Let me tell you what your mistake is.
Your biggest mistake was to act recklessly.
Do you think this was due to lack of experience? It's not.
What you lack, is vision and insight.
One day, if you really sit in the Chairman's seat of this group,
how can you convince everyone in the company to
have faith in you that you can lead the company and move forward?!
Dad, have some water.
Cool down. Eldest Brother already know his mistake.
Have a good rest for this period.
Don't bother about the company for the time being.
- Dad...
- Let me tell you.
You should really be thankful to your younger brother for this.
Not only did he help you, he also redeemed huge losses for the Ling family.
Do you know this?
What's wrong? Can't sit still?
Not happy?
Dad, there are still company matters to attend to.
I'm leaving.
Look at how your younger brother handles matters.
You should really learn from him.
Same for you too.
How old are you?
You are twenty two years old and already an adult.
You are pursing a woman every day.
What are you pursuing?
Be more mature and promising, okay?
Hold on.
Why are you raising your guard?
He just helped me. What will I do to him?
Speak. Why did you help me?
You have clearly won.
Once I fall off the stage, everything in the Ling family will be yours.
But you insisted on pulling back at this moment.
I really don't understand your reason for doing this.
Winning or losing is not important to me.
I have never thought of fighting with you.
So, your motive for doing this, is for me to thank you?
I don't care about what you think.
Eldest Brother.
Since this has already happened, just let it pass.
You are overthinking.
I suddenly feel it's not interesting anymore.
What do you mean?
I just experienced a roller coaster.
This is good too. I'm suddenly relaxed.
Eldest Brother, where are you going?
Didn't Dad tell me to go on leave?
I'm obeying him.
[New Way]
Go back to the company first. I'm heading out.
Okay.
Xin'er.
Why are you here?
I know you're working in the area today.
So I wanted to invite you to elope. Are you interested?
Eloping doesn't sound like something adults do.
I'm just joking.
I've come to ask about the date you've promised me.
Where do you want to go?
For a spring outing.
I know there's a huge themed music festival in the suburbs.
I think you'll definitely like it.
But I still have some work I have to do.
It's fine. I knew you would reject me anyway.
Since you have to work overtime, eat more.
Replenish your energy and take good care of yourself.
Thank you.
So, I have awareness now?
But I really have work.
I know you're a big busy person. Go do your work.
Bye bye.
Excuse me, can I give this to you?
I just remembered, my company matters aren't that urgent.
Let's go out first.
Really? Then get in the car.
What's that?
I don't know.
Can I have some?
Here.
What is it? It's so sweet and doesn't taste good.
Let's go.
Great! My comic has already exceeded 100,000 clicks.
Look, the fans in the comments
Thousands of fans are asking for updates for Book of Blood.
Anxin, why do I suddenly feel that this Xiao Yin looks actually like me?
I drew it based on you.
Wouldn't it be wasteful if I don't make use of this beautiful face?
I'm embarrassed.
You should be.
No way. How can you girls keep flattering yourselves?
She has a pancake face. Compared to an oval face, se can't hang anything on it.
Zhao Lei, it's none of your business.
Sometimes, I realize you don't need to have a mouth.
I think it's perfect.
You guys talk.
I wanted to scare you. What's up? Why are you spying on me?
Get in the car.
What's wrong?
Celebrating you guys getting over 100,000 views.
But I still have a lot to do.
You've been working continuously for a couple weeks.
You don't even have the right to a break?
I see other bosses torturing their employees.
But why are you doing it to yourself?
I don't have any employees to torture. The boss is me and the employee is me.
The cleaning lady is me too. Everything is me.
Who else can I torture but myself?
Then where do you want to take me to?
Camping. Didn't you say I'm not grounded?
Camping?
You even know how to correct your mistake?
Okay then. I'm going back to get my drawing board.
My girlfriend is really a workaholic.
Well...
It's a long journey and you lack this super cute girl as companion.
And this beautiful man here can reluctantly accompany you too.
We...
No.
Anxin, we need a break too to prepare for the exceeding of one million clicks.
Right, let's pretend we're going together
to celebrate!
Let's go.
I won't be disturbing you, right?
Get ready.
♫ We encountered in the street tonight ♫
♫ In her heart, her feet decided not to listen and went home with her ♫
♫ She used her faint eyes to quickly tell me ♫
♫ The slender and floating figure silently turned around ♫
♫ and told me, romantic lover, I love you ♫
I already said so. Insisted on drinking two big bottles of water.
Wouldn't we be like this? I'm going to burst soon.
By the way, You You. We are going camping today. Can we really see that galaxy of stars in the sky?
- Yes.
- Really?
I searched it up a few times online.
It said there are many enthusiastic campers at the observatory point here. We will definitely see them.
Then since we can see it, we won't be disappointed.
Can we eat this?
What do you want to eat and drink?
- Are you thirsty?
- I want to eat this but I'll get fat.
- You mean this?
- Xiao Sheng?
What a coincidence.
Second brother, sister-in-law you're also here.
What a coincidence. Where are you guys going?
We're going camping. What about you?
We were also finding a camping spot.
How about we go together?
Anxin, what a coincidence that you're here too.
What a coincidence.
Right, we were planning on camping too.
Since it's such a coincidence, let's go together.
Okay.
Then let's go together.
Im good
Yeah.
I'm so amazing.
It's so successful for the first time setting up a tent.
Help me take a picture.
Okay.
- Okay.
- Done? Let me take a look.
Am I cute?
Zhao Lei, I haven't seen such a narcissist like you.
You saw one today.
- Don't!
- You haven't taken the photo.
Stop messing around.
Are you upset that I called everyone over for camping?
I thought that rather than going to a music festival where we don't know anyone,
we would've been more happy to come camping together with everyone.
Its not because of my second brother?
Anxin is here too.
Look, everyone is here.
I won't be mad at you.
I just thought that it wasn't easy to finally get a chance to date you alone,
but who would've expected that everyone is here.
This isn't considered us dating alone.
Really?
Then what you mean is there's a next time?
Why are you so cute?
Look, your hair is a mess.
What's wrong? Are you mad?
Nothing
Are you mad because my younger brother brought Xin'er along?
You You and Zhao Lei are also here.
Then why do you look upset?
Are you on your period?
Anxin, the nail hasn't been nailed in.
You nail it then.
Moreover, nothing will happen if a nail is missing.
It's so strong. What's wrong?
I'll lay down for you to see.
- I'll try it out for you. Nothing at all.
- Come out.
- It's not strong enough. Come out.
- It's very strong.
- Hurry.
If you want to play, then lets try it together.
I don't want to try it with you.
I already told you that its not strong enough and not safe.
Safer than you.
My goodness.
Brother Yue, are you fine?
He's fine.
As long as you're fine. Be careful in the future.
He's so big and not made of paper. Of course he's fine, right, Ling Yue?
That's right. I'm fine.
He's fine.
Fan over here, You You. The oil is dripping.
Smells good. He already took them away.
Xin'er, I just grilled these. Give them a try.
Xiao Sheng, let's go take a walk.
Are you trying to go look for my second brother?
So, can I reject?
The meat is quite tender.
Smells good. Where's Anxin and President Ling?
Of course they're in their own world.
Give it a try. I cooked them just for you.
Anxin, are you home?
I'll come look for you.
Brother, don't worry. I'm having fun with my friends.
Oh, don't stay up too late. Stay safe.
Are we going down?
Be careful. Slowly.
Why is there a tent here?
Didn't you say you want to star gaze?
I set up a tent here so we can star gaze together.
You even remembered this? So thoughtful.
It seems like we can't see stars tonight.
But it took me so long to find this place.
Then let's look at them next time, okay?
I'm sorry that you couldn't see the stars.
There's nothing to be sorry about, silly.
There's so many.
♫  Watching the street lights going on and off ♫
♫ You can see how far the future is once you turn around ♫
♫ I haven't differentiated it yet I already start to yearn ♫
♫ Embracing you like the whole world ♫
♫ It's too beautiful, but I'm also afraid of the time limit ♫
♫ No matter how much it is, it will never be enough ♫
Do you like it?
♫ Let me love you ♫
♫ Let me use my sincere heart ♫
♫ Learning to be warm to cover ♫
♫ those cold memories from the past ♫
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Memories are soaked in rain ♫
♫ Fate works bizarrely ♫
♫ The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly beats abnormally ♫
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Obviously, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness, for it has always been you ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Yet the longing has never been able to stop ♫
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Using all of my most beautiful adjectives ♫
♫ Is still not enough to describe your name ♫
♫ Our story is exclusively ours ♫
♫ Our palms hold onto the key to the future ♫
♫ Using love to slowly open up a lifetime ♫