[English subtitles are available]
Use me.
I'll be your boyfriend.
This is my girlfriend.
She's pretty, right?
So-bin, is this true?
I hear you're best friends.
My girlfriend having a male BFF
isn't that ideal for me.
I'm afraid
there's too much history between us.
Chan-ki, what's taking you so long?
Her again?
I'm afraid we won't be able to be friends.
Come on. Aren't you coming inside?
I'll be a minute.
Here's my advice to you
as your ex-girlfriend.
Unless you cut her from your life,
you'll never get a girlfriend
or marry someone.
I can do without.
What can I do for you? Just ask.
I'd rather go to my dorm room.
And cry under the covers?
No. But...
But what?
I should've brought
the fried chicken with me.
For you, I mean.
Forget it. I hate fried chicken!
Especially what was meant
for someone else.
Okay, fine. I'll get you
something nicer next time.
I'll go with you then and walk you back.
-No, don't.
-I forbid you to say that.
I did you a favor,
so I'll do whatever I want.
And what would that be?
Speaking casually to you.
When I'm your senior?
Is that a no?
Well,
you're my mentor, so do as you wish.
Your student should oblige
since she only humiliated herself today.
Exactly, So-bin.
Not too casually.
This is how it'll be!
Hey, Yeo Jun. Jun!
Hurry up.
I can't believe you called
right on time though.
Worry swept over me.
And regret.
Regret?
I pushed you
into confessing your feelings.
Stop saying that.
You did nothing wrong.
Rejected or not,
I should've picked another day though.
That I regret.
Why's that?
That ex of his
wasn't too fond of me when they dated.
She told me to stay away from him.
So I promised her.
That I didn't like Chan-ki.
That...
there was nothing between us.
They seem to be back together.
Those candles I lit.
Darn, this is humiliating.
She knows I lied.
Don't cry. I won't let you a second time.
It's Chan-ki.
Don't answer him.
You're forbidding everything.
Didn't I earn that right?
As your boyfriend.
[Chan-ki]
-Declining his call like that--
-He'll be taken aback.
It's why I declined it though.
But we're still friends.
Someone who takes advantage
of your feelings
and stands you up all the time
isn't a friend.
Maybe it's just you who thinks so.
-What?
-Why do you care about a person
who ignores and hurts you?
Why let him own you?
That's...
Of course.
It was probably your only option.
It's not easy
to find someone who can save you
from affection deprivation.
Talk about a punch to the heart.
It hurts.
I'm just as messed up.
How so? Are you in a one-sided love too?
I told you to stay clear from it.
I'll heed your advice, so you heed mine.
As in?
Don't answer his calls
until he apologizes.
Even if you do pick up,
don't agree to meet him.
Not without my permission.
What if I run into him?
Take a page out of Nam Soo-hyun's book.
That's not easy to do.
Repeat after me.
"What business do you have with me?"
"Can you get lost?"
"Why are you laughing?"
You sound just like him.
"Can you get lost?"
"Do I sound like him?"
-"Isn't it this?"
-"Do I sound similar?"
That's how you would say it!
Sound more like Soo-hyun.
Soo-hyun...
[World's Greatest Convenience Store]
That'll be 2,800 won.
Here you go.
[So-bin]
[Good night. And don't cry again.]
[Good night.]
Soo-hyun.
Soo-hyun, it's been a while.
Park Hyung-min?
It's nice to run into you like this.
We used to be close back in freshman year.
Were we? I don't remember.
It's been a while.
Anyway, I have somewhere to be.
Are you perhaps interested
in a part-time job?
A part-time job?
[Mid-term Lecture Evaluation]
[Resume: Nam Soo-hyun]
You've worked
all kinds of part-time jobs before
and have a high TOEIC score.
Is it true
that you provide room and board too?
Of course. Can you start tomorrow?
Yes.
I look forward to the work.
By the way, how do you know the CEO?
The CEO?
[Yield]
There you go.
-Just a second.
-Right there.
[Under Construction, Slow Down]
-That'd be 250.
-Can you pull on that side?
Miss, you can't go in there!
[Under Construction, Slow Down]
Young-ran.
[Safety First]
Tell me. Why did you turn down that job?
It was a good one.
The kind you were looking for.
And how exactly would you know that?
-What?
-A job like that never existed.
I heard that
someone asked the CEO to make an opening.
No wonder.
It had a room and board arrangement,
the job was easy,
and it paid way too much.
Moreover,
someone I barely know offered me the gig.
Come to think of it,
he had a crush on you since freshman year.
So what?
Friends can pull some strings, you know.
Because you are my friend.
Because of me, you're in his debt.
How will you repay him?
Young-ran,
I hate being in people's debts.
I loathe being a problem to others.
I don't know how to repay favors.
Nor do I have the ability or time.
I just...
I just wanted to cut you a break.
[Young-ran]
[Did I say I wanted to die?]
I suppose you say that often
without knowing
what it's really like to want to die.
[Youth Villa]
[Marketing Team Project]
[I forgot I had a tutoring job]
[So-bin]
[and asked us to gather.]
[I'm really sorry.]
[Soo-hyun, can you]
[So-bin]
[gather the materials
and go over them instead?]
[I'm really, really, really sorry.]
Maybe I should skip school today.
[Can't you tell the time?]
I'm only ten minutes late.
[Just ten minutes?]
[I told you to be on time.]
[Being punctual is the first step
to acing tests.]
[-Ten minutes is enough to--]
-I think I'm lost.
I'm at the fountain, so meet me here.
Bye!
Such a nagger.
I took time off practice
to meet him between his classes.
He'll be a while, right?
Let's take a look around.
Him over there.
Seriously? Not again.
Bleaching your hair
damages your roots and scalp.
Is it your roots or scalp though?
-Mind your own business.
-I know from experience.
Soo-kyung,
you think I'm a boomer.
I'm most certainly not.
Then what are you?
All I wish
is to talk about life with students
over a meal.
There's so much I've experienced
that I want to tell them about.
That's what makes you a boomer.
It sure is hot outside.
What is he doing?
Can you believe it?
-Unbelievable.
-He's not that good though.
-Why isn't he getting up?
-He's good.
Soo-hyun!
We're in matching colors today.
Did you copy my look?
Take your pants off too
while you're at it.
Stride in your underwear.
You have a unique talent.
What would that be?
I have so many, you see.
You ignore what others say
and get in their faces with a smile.
Not to everyone, you know.
Just like you said,
I'm more like this
because you're hard to win over.
I just think
you're being pretentious like me.
Pretentious?
I laugh in people’s faces
and it seems like
you’re trying hard not to like me.
Isn’t that being pretentious too?
Hey, you laughed!
I don't know
why I'm trying to patronize you,
but listen up.
In this world,
there are people who don't like you.
That's true.
But I don't think you're not one of them.
I apologize.
I could see right through you
which is why I bothered to converse.
But, just forget about it.
You know how I am
and I treat everyone the same.
You can apologize
by treating me to a meal.
No one has ever
been treated to one by you,
and I'd like to be your first.
You won't agree to a meal that I buy,
-so treat me to one instead.
-Why would I?
You've got to be kidding me.
Look at him.
He can't take his eyes off Mi-ju.
You haven't found a model yet, have you?
-What about him?
-Forget it.
Excuse me.
Are you perhaps interested in modeling?
Sorry? A model?
-Don't.
-She's looking for one.
You'll be seeing her at least once a week.
What? Every week? With her?
-Stop it.
-Do you think you can handle it?
Of course.
I'm confident in the body I carry.
Why don't I show you?
What do you think you're doing?
Soo-hyun, it's...
Let's go.
Just a second!
Did I ask you to strip?
No, that was just me.
He's looking at us
as if we were sexually harassing you.
-Weren't you?
-Of course not!
Then I guess I misunderstood.
It's just that you were all ogling him.
Then apologize.
Apologize for the misunderstanding.
I don't think I can.
Who knows what's actually true?
Come on.
Hi, I'm Yeo Jun,
a younger classmate of Soo-hyun's.
What? A classmate?
This temperamental jerk
has one that talks to him?
Unbelievable.
I'm at least not as immoral as you.
Hold on, will you?
Thank you for being his friend.
I'm Nam Koo-hyun,
Soo-hyun's one and only brother.
It's good to meet you.
This is just fascinating.
Why is someone like you
friends with my brother though?
Does he have some kind of leverage on you?
Quit the nonsense and get going.
That hurts, darn it!
You said we'd see our room,
so I skipped practice and my meal.
I'm telling Mom.
Go ahead. Brag about
stripping in front of the girls too.
Would you like to eat with us?
I'd appreciate the saving.
-His nagging is just--
-Koo-hyun!
-Sure. Let's go.
-Sweet.
What should we have?
[Cash, Credit cards only]
-What's good?
-The pork cutlet.
I'll have the pork cutlet
and ramyeon with cheese.
I'll pay for it.
I thought that was a given.
No, this is a first.
Choose.
Go ahead.
What should I have
that would say I ate well?
Budae jjigae?
This hair isn't appropriate
for someone who wants to be police.
I won't be able to bleach my hair
as an officer,
so I'm enjoying these moments.
You sure are a nutjob.
Have some beef too.
-What about you?
-Eat your fill.
And comb your hair.
Just look at this mess.
Have some beans too.
Go on and stop being a picky eater.
Eat up.
Eat.
Unbelievable.
I'm off to the restroom.
That's a sweet watch you have.
Do you like it?
I'll get going then.
Come back here.
Why? What are you going
to nag about this time?
Don't skip your meals
and open the windows often.
Look after yourself more
and get some sleep.
Get going already.
Don't abandon my brother.
He's a poor guy, you see.
-Aren't you leaving?
-I'm going!
I'll see you around.
Aren't you going too?
I should.
You're quite affectionate
toward your brother.
Affectionate? What's that?
How you treat your brother
is exactly that.
What about you? Any siblings?
No, I'm an only child.
It's easy that way.
You have no one to be mindful of.
You should get going then.
Thanks for the meal.
Sure.
-Soo-hyun.
-What now?
Can I call you again?
No, don't.
You might call me first, you know.
That won't ever happen.
I was treated to a meal by Nam Soo-hyun.
You just don't know me yet.
Just go.
[So-bin]
Hey, it's my girlfriend.
You're adorable.
If only someone like you
were my girlfriend.
Hye-ji.
Why did you call?
Must you be this annoying?
[Oh, I'm sorry. Should I hang up?]
You're so gullible at times.
Are you really not coming?
[Yes, and it's what had me worried.]
[Can you mediate if anything happens?]
[It's your specialty.]
Why do people keep saying
I'm good at things?
[I'll count on you then. Thanks.]
[Bye.]
As if there would be
anything to worry about.
[Myungil University]
There's no need to act so primly.
Hye-ji, let's go for dinner.
-I'm good.
-Come on.
Hye-ji, please.
So-bin, Hye-ji, and I
emailed the materials we researched.
The others should hand them in right now.
Unbelievable.
Soo-hyun, you saw what I sent, right?
Let's discuss that first.
You did a vast research.
I get things done properly
once I put my mind to it.
However,
I can't say it was done properly.
What?
What do you mean?
I researched three marketing strategies.
I got carried away with the brand concept,
but there's a lot to work with.
Mijin Foods is a big company.
You ignored
the distribution network it has
and only focused on marketing
which is why it's not realistic.
There were many typos too
which are a result of you
not knowing proper grammar.
A lot of the materials overlapped too.
Are you sure you didn't
just copy and paste?
If Professor Park saw this,
he'll scold us for playing tricks.
Bad grammar and playing tricks?
Must you be this strict about things?
We're on a tight schedule,
so go easy on it.
Handing in your work
would speed things up.
Yes, of course. I should hand that to you.
But first,
there's something I must collect.
The other day, I only stepped back
because Jun had a fit.
You never apologized
for what you did though.
An apology?
Have you done your research?
How's that the issue right now?
Apologize, you jerk!
So,
you haven't done the work.
-You--
-Is it fun
to belittle people like this?
Being told off
for trying to play tricks
has done it for me.
I can't stay on this team.
I'll get going.
Right. I knew this would happen.
Try getting it done alone, you jerk.
Jun, come on.
Why didn't you go with them?
I don't know.
I'll do the research with So-bin,
so you don't have to contribute.
You're a freshman anyway.
I don't have any expectations.
Why do you assume that I can't contribute?
I could do a good job, you know.
Are you planning to toy around
with me this time
instead of So-bin?
When did I toy around with So-bin?
Some people should never be messed with
and you'll pay for it in spades.
You're one to talk.
If that were the case,
karma would eat you alive.
You said materials on Mijin Group
are hard to come by.
It'll make or break our presentation.
Put me in charge of it.
-You?
-Trust me this once
and see for yourself
if I'm toying with you or not.
I don't like getting disappointed
after trusting someone,
so don't overexert yourself.
It's for the coffee. Bye.
Is it that hard for you to trust me?
"Yes, Father. This is Jun."
"I'm sorry to catch you on a busy day."
"I have something to ask"
"regarding a school project."
No, that's too long.
[Mijin Group Secretary]
[Trust me this once]
and see for yourself
if I'm toying with you or not.
I don't like getting disappointed
after trusting someone,
so don't overexert yourself.
[Mijin Group Secretary]
[This is the secretary's office.]
Yes, of course.
I'll give you the intranet ID.
-Ms. Cha!
-Sir?
Who are you informing of our intranet ID?
[It's your son, sir.]
[He wanted the company files
that were never released.]
-My son?
-Yes.
Well, if my son wants those,
he should have them.
The CEO just approved it.
Gosh, thank you so much.
Goodness.
Does he need them for a thesis?
It's your youngest son, not your eldest.
What?
[You're the winner
of the Dissertation Writing Contest.]
[Congratulations.]
Hello?
Kim So-bin!
Congratulations on winning the contest.
What? No. You don't need to treat me.
Yes.
I'll think about what I want to eat.
Okay.
So-bin should take me out for dinner.
-You? Why?
-I'm the one who gave her the idea.
You did?
You only see the good in others.
She got the idea from the materials
I handed over to her
when doing research for Professor Song.
That's what you think.
-Do you have everything for the lecture?
-Yes.
-Professor Song.
The thing I told you about.
I have to submit all the paperwork
by today.
What?
Choose one out of the students
who are working for you,
and the selected student will receive
more financial aid.
Oh, that.
Right, So-bin won a prize
in a dissertation writing competition.
On a topic that is related
to what you're writing about now.
Really? I'm impressed.
-Then I should choose So-bin...
-Hey, come on.
I told you that I gave So-bin
the idea for it.
It was her first time,
so she was a bit lost.
Professor, I guided her
through your research
and the dissertation too.
To give you all the support
and assistance you need, ma'am.
Kim So-bin...
-Okay, then you can be my main assistant.
-Thank you.
See you later!
[Nam Soo-hyun]
My, who is this? Nam Soo-hyun!
Who knew we'd run into you here?
Are we invisible to him?
-I don't think he can see us.
-Get what you need and leave.
Don't cause trouble in my workplace.
Don't be so rude to your customers.
Buy something,
and I'll treat you like customers.
I'm so sorry! I'll pay for it.
Now, I'm a customer, right?
You'd better not do it.
Why not? Are you going to punch me again
like last time?
Even if you think I'm a complete joke,
you won't hit a customer. Right?
You immature jerk.
You're acting like a revengeful kid.
My foot! Hey, my foot!
My foot! My foot hurts!
Darn it.
Let go!
Hey, do you have a death wish?
-How dare you!
-Enough!
Darn it.
What are you doing to my friend?
Did you pass the exam or something?
You need to learn to enjoy
the small things in life.
You're always so serious.
Just pass the exam, please.
Let go!
-What is it?
-It's nothing.
It's cash.
Where did you get this?
Come on. It's just 100,000 won.
Hey, "just 100,000 won"?
You always work so hard,
so I did some gig work just for the day.
You'd better tell me the truth.
Hey, just let it go. It's really nothing.
Nam Koo-hyun.
Well, I just sold something
I got for free.
From your rich friend.
-Yeo Jun?
-Yes.
I told him I liked his watch,
and he said I could have it.
-And you accepted it?
-Hey.
Of course, I did. It's expensive.
Are you a beggar?
That's a mean thing to say.
What's wrong with accepting something
he doesn't need?
Is this it?
It's what's left
after paying for the gosiwon.
Hey!
[Youth Villa]
-Soo-hyun?
-[I'm in front of your place. Come out.]
Now?
Yes, I'll wait here until you come out.
Okay, give me a minute.
Soo-hyun.
Koo-hyun told me what happened.
Oh, that.
-Why did you do that?
-I gave it to him because he wanted it.
I can just buy another one.
I'm sorry.
For what?
I can't pay you back right away,
but I will.
Will that make you feel at ease?
You said I'd call you.
Were you referring to this?
-Did I say that?
-So, it all went according to your plan.
You made me call you first
and practically beg you.
That wasn't my plan.
You may never have found out.
What do you want from me?
What could it be?
Forget about the money.
I don't need money.
As you know, I can get it easily.
Can you warm up to me?
Nobody warms up to you
because they genuinely like you
without you having you trick them
like this or spend money on them?
That's right.
Nobody.
Don't you pity me?
Don't look at me like that.
You need money,
and I need love. It's the same thing.
You do everything in your power
to earn money.
I'm just doing what I want to do
to get what I want.
All right.
You won. I'll do as you say.
Answer my calls.
I'll head in, then.
Kim So-bin!
So-bin, Kim So-bin.
So-bin, are you mad at me?
I knew you had your tutoring session here,
so I came to pick you up.
Who has such an amazing friend?
You do!
So-bin, don't be mad at me.
Leave me alone, please.
Why did you have to come by that day?
Someone told me
that was the best day to go to your place,
but I ended up humiliating myself.
Who told you that?
Don't tell me... Yeo Jun?
That's right!
My boyfriend said
that promises must be kept
and told me to go that day.
Are you actually seeing him?
You're joking, right?
-That's...
-You're not seeing him, right?
Right, no way! I knew it.
"I knew it"?
-What I meant was...
-What did you mean by that?
Were you saying I shouldn't even dream
of dating a guy like him?
Now, I'm relieved.
Yes, this is the So-bin I know.
The timid, sensitive girl
who can only yell at me.
This is the Kim So-bin I know.
Hey, were you not joking?
Hey! We've stayed friends
even after I got a girlfriend.
Why let that jerk ruin our friendship?
"That jerk"?
Don't call him like that.
Don't trust him.
He knew I'd have a girl over that day.
I told him.
So what?
Are you saying he told me to go over
to your place that day on purpose?
That's absurd.
[Yeo Jun]
[Why don't you tell him tomorrow?]
[If he says no, just come meet me now.]
I can't believe you called
right on time though.
Worry swept over me.
And regret.
He's been kind of creeping me out.
People like him aren't good for you
because you trust others easily
and tell them everything.
But you don't even know him well.
I know a lot more about Jun than you do.
So, you are serious about this.
Yes.
No more crush.
It's over now.
What about us as friends?
Not sure. I don't know.
I want to focus on myself now.
[Don't trust him.]
He knew I'd have a girl over that day.
[Please, I hope I'm wrong.]
[Nam Soo-hyun]
Hey, where are you?
Hi, Jun.
Can we meet now?
You call this a nice place?
To me, it is.
I'll go easy on you
since you asked me to meet up first.
Well... Jun.
Yes?
I had such a long day today.
Soo-hyun and Jung-ho...
You can tell me about that later.
I want to ask you something.
What is it? You can ask me anything.
You know,
that day... The day I went
to Chan-ki's place to tell him how I feel.
Did you know
that his girlfriend would be over
that day?
Do you think I intentionally made you
run into her?
No.
Did you
see him?
Yes.
He came to pick me up
after my tutoring session.
Forget it, if that's not the case.
To tell you the truth,
I did wonder if you did it on purpose.
I'm sorry.
I did.
-What?
-I sent you there because I knew about it.
I wasn't sure whether
the timing would work out,
but I thought it could.
What you were wondering is true.
Why did you do that?
I wanted to end it for you.
I'm sure it's hard for you
to keep getting disappointed.
Was that the only way though?
It'd help you give up quickly.
Are you sure
you didn't want to see me get hurt?
Was it fun for you to watch me cry
like an idiot?
So he rejected you,
just as I had expected.
You should've stopped being so foolish
a long time ago.
Didn't I tell you?
You told me to use you.
What did you mean by that?
I hurt you,
so it's only right
that you gain something from me.
Yeo Jun.
That's the only thing
I've learned in life.
Give and take.
Nothing's free in life.
I was bound to get hurt
even if you didn't get involved.
I'm not trying to put the blame on you.
But I can't figure you out.
You scare me.
I don't think I can be friends with you
anymore.
We'll just be
teammates from now on.
I'm off.
[But you have to keep your promise too.]
You promised we'll be close friends
if I gave you my spot.
You'll do a good job, so don't worry.
[It'll be thrilling
since you'll be working with me.]
[This is my girlfriend.]
She's pretty, right?
[Didn't I earn that right?]
As your boyfriend.
[So he rejected you,
just as I had expected.]
You should've stopped being so foolish
a long time ago.
[Lee Hye-ra]
Okay, let's meet up.
Do you want to come up? I booked a room.
[Road Closed, Detour]
[Yeo Jun]
-[Soo-hyun.]
-Hey.
You picked up.
[Of course. I still owe you.]
[I'm working.]
-At such a late time?
-Yes. At such a late time.
I hurt someone
and I want to know
how to go back to the way things were.
[What are you doing over there?
Get back to work!]
[Yes, sir.]
[Just tell her how you feel
without embellishing.]
-That's it?
-You're bad at that.
Just do what you're bad at.
[Bye.]
I must be out of my mind.
Why am I doing this?
Hey, good actions lead to good fortune.
Do you want me to die of muscle cramps?
Do you have to say it like that?
Why do you get so many cramps?
Because I work my butt off
to make a living.
It's probably because
you're drinking all the time.
[So-bin!]
Hey, did you hear that?
[-So-bin!]
-Who is that?
-Yeo Jun?
-So-bin!
Did he follow me here?
Why do you think it's you?
Maybe he's looking for me.
-It's not you!
Gosh...
-What are you doing here?
-I missed you.
Am I a joke to you?
I came because I didn't want things
to get out of hand. Just go.
I wanted to tell you how I feel.
So everything I heard until now
had nothing to do with your feelings?
Yes.
Please give me a chance.
No.
I don't want to hear this.
I won't be fooled anymore.
Telling you how I feel
is awkward and difficult for me
because I worry that you'll hate me.
Because love is something
you have to earn.
When I saw you have a hard time
with your crush
it felt like I was seeing myself.
I wanted to see that you couldn't
succeed even if you try
when I couldn't give up myself.
I thought I had control over everything
when I had no idea
I couldn't even control my feelings.
What are your feelings?
The moment I saw your tears I realized
what I did was wrong.
I realized if the girl I like is in pain,
it hurts me too.
I never knew that before.
I'm sorry I hurt you. I truly am.
-But...
-Next time.
I'll hear your answer next time.
I'm scared.
If you're going to be informal,
just keep being informal.
Just choose one.
I'll be off now.
-What's going on?
-Hey kid!
-What's the matter?
-What happened?
He just passed out.
-Are you okay?
-Call an ambulance! Hurry!
[Soo-hyun]
-Hey, Soo-hyun.
[-Hello?]
Isn't this Soo-hyun's phone?
[I'm calling from
the ER at Hosu Hospital.]
What?
Sir, can you please go faster?
Dad...
Is Mr. Nam Soo-hyun's guardian here?
Yes.
-Soo-hyun.
-What happened?
-Are you okay?
-Why are you here?
Do you remember collapsing
at the construction site?
They said you have malnutrition.
Didn't you hear me? You have malnutrition.
I don't care.
I'm going to call your brother and mother.
I heard that
you told them not to call your family
when you were rushed to the ER.
What are you doing here?
I called you and a nurse
at the hospital picked up.
Why did you call me again?
What am I, your girlfriend?
I wanted to thank you.
Thanks to your advice,
I got the courage to tell her how I feel.
Good.
Thanks for coming to the hospital
and not calling my family.
I keep owing you. I don't know
when I'll be able to repay you.
Do you have to repay me?
Aren't you that kind of guy?
When you spend money,
you expect something in return.
I was.
But I'm going to change.
Go ahead and change all you want.
Go. It's getting late.
Why are you always so angry with me?
I know.
Every time I see you, I just get angry.
I guess it's because my life sucks.
I don't even have time
to think about things like that,
but when I see you
I feel envious and angry.
Happy?
-I feel the same way.
-Just go
and stay out of my sight.
No.
I'm going to do what I'm good at
so you do the same.
What are you good at?
-Being clingy.
-What?
So you try to push me away.
Let's each do what we're good at.
[At a Distance, Spring is Green]
[No, don't do this, So-bin.
It'll only get you killed.]
[I heard you're going out with Jun.
Is that true?]
I'm going to call you
"honey" and "sweetie".
[You think this will make me
stay away from you?]
It's going to make me miss you for sure!
[You remind me of my brother
and it pains me.]
Unfortunately, you are my brother.
[So you want me
to stop being curious or clingy?]
You called to tell me
to get out of your sight?
Yes. I pited you.
I saw how anxious you were.
[-A fair face]
-That's her.
[-may hide a foul heart.]
-I know right?
[Are you curious about me?]
Yes. I'm curious about you.