[English subtitles are available]
[Moonlight]
[Episode 26]
[Operating at a loss year after year,
management failure adds to the woes]
[So this printing factory]
[has got some history.]
Jiang Yu Cheng, are you free now?
The printing factory
got out of it unscathed?
Sort of.
Where is Chu Li?
She went to her room after lunch
and hasn't been out since.
And you are just going to stay here?
What a good boyfriend you are.
Maybe I should go upstairs
and check on her?
What's there to check?
Given her current state,
just a few words of advice
won't make her feel better.
Is there anything I can do to help then?
How are you and Gu Bai Zhi
doing lately?
Why are you asking this all of a sudden?
I need verifications on several
news articles about the factory.
Since she has a lot of connections,
I need her to put me in
touch with a few people.
Why are you avoiding my eyes?
I am not.
I think
you can ask her yourself.
I ask her?
Then I will be
owing her a favour, won't I?
You can ask for me.
I will just get a free ride from you.
Don't you think you are getting
more and more shameless these days?
That depends on who
you're comparing me to,
if it's to you,
I admit defeat.
I've got other things to do, bye.
What other things?
I can't tell you.
Why is he smiling like a lovesick fool?
Director Gu,
can you explain this to me?
What's wrong with these authors?
Why are they removed from
the Highly Recommended list?
The quality of
their novels isn't good enough
to be on Highly Recommended.
Once the quality of
Highly Recommended declines,
Xin Dun Network will
start losing paid subscribers.
Since this project has
been assigned to me,
you can trust me, Mr Luo.
Fine.
And how did it go with the task
concerning Jiang Yu Cheng
that you were entrusted to?
Once he announces his new book project,
I will seal a deal with him
as soon as possible.
Director Gu,
certain ways and means are needed
to be taken to get things done.
And some things are easier to get done
behind closed doors.
What do you mean by that?
Every one of these young authors
earned their spots here
with their own abilities.
I won't use any dirty tricks
to get what I want.
Gu Bai Zhi,
I noticed that you've been
defying me lately,
from Yun Fei's Imperial Guard's Journal
to Highly Recommended list
and Jiang Yu Cheng.
What's your problem?
Mr Luo, you really have misunderstood me.
I'm just doing my job.
Fine.
I'll just wait for the
results from you then.
Mr Jiang Yu Cheng,
are you here to pick
Director Gu up from work?
Yes.
Just doing her job, huh?
Looks like you can't trust
anything that woman says.
What is that supposed to mean?
I suppose you know
Gu Bai Zhi better than I do, am I right?
Aren't you worried that
she has some other agenda?
Mr Luo,
what are you trying to say?
Such as
to sign your next new book
and be promoted as vice president.
What were you guys talking about?
Nothing.
Nothing important.
By the way,
Zhou Chuan wants to ask you for a favour.
Let's go.
[Amid closures of businesses, former
leading enterprise is struggling to survive]
Did you cut your hand?
Don't you think the broken glass
on the ground
look just like my shattered career?
Don't tell me you broke it on purpose.
I just wanted to drink some water.
Am I really
going to lose my job?
It's been less than 24 hours
since your suspension.
Can you get some sleep now?
Go to sleep.
Why don't
you teach me how to play games?
Or maybe we can just catch a movie?
I think midnight screening
is still available now.
Or should we go out
for a late night snack?
How about we put Er Gou in a costume?
Put you in a costume then, maybe?
Can you find something fun
for me to do?
All right now.
I'll do whatever you want
to do with you tomorrow.
Just get some rest tonight.
Sleep tight.
Mr Zhou, don't go.
I slept too much during
the day, I can't sleep now.
Can you stay with me for a while?
Do you know what you are talking about?
When I close my eyes now,
I can see myself being unemployed
and living on the streets,
Mr Liang and Miao are throwing coins at me
like I'm a beggar and mocking me.
Okay.
I'll stay here with you, all right?
Mr Zhou, you're so sweet.
How could you do this?
Even though I was sad and
frustrated last night,
but that didn't mean you could
take advantage of my vulnerability.
You were the one who
asked me to stay last night.
I...
I did nothing.
You get out.
-I...
-Get out.
But I...
I really didn't do anything.
I've been miserable lately.
I told her that Little Deity
has been widely praised.
Its sales volume is still rising,
it has almost exceeded 150,000 copies now.
She was only happy for ten minutes,
and then she went back
upstairs ten minutes later.
When the night came,
she just started to walk
around in the living room,
asking to catch a movie or play games,
and she had to drag me along.
On the next morning,
she kicked me out.
We kept doing this
round and round for days.
She has been behaving erratically,
like she has been drinking fake liquor.
I kind of get it now what does it mean by
attitude can change
faster than the weather.
Kicked you out? Kicked you out of where?
Is that the only thing you
heard after everything I said?
Our relationship is purely platonic.
I have affection for her,
but I respect her.
I never overstep the line.
I think
you are decent on the outside
and dirty on the inside.
What about you?
What you said is just sour grapes.
There is something wrong with your mood.
You looked like a
lovesick fool two days ago,
what's with the long face today?
Why are you being such a gossip?
You've listened to a lot of
my stories, haven't you?
You think I want to hear it?
It's all because of your strong
desire to express yourself.
You came telling me every time
something trivial happened.
I haven't even charged you
for relationship consultation fee.
Those relationship advice from you?
I had to wash my ears
after hearing your advice.
I haven't even asked you for compensation.
Let me record it down for you,
say it again.
Say you will never seek my advice
on relationship problems again.
Let me remind you kindly
and compassionately that
don't forget the tragic moment you had
when you broke up with her.
Don't come hugging and
crying to me in my house
for three days and three nights again.
Have you been fantasizing about me?
Who are you in a relationship with,
me or Chu Li?
Fine, you'd better not let
me catch you crying again.
Otherwise, I am going to
record it and upload it online
to show all the readers
what a crybaby you are.
All the videos on your phone are about me?
Do you really care about me that much?
Get lost!
This is a public place.
Why should I leave?
Fine, I will go.
Hold on.
The idea that you thought of
before, have you executed it?
Of course.
I have uploaded an 10,000 words
long article before I came here.
You want to denounce the printing factory?
You think I'm some kind
of single-celled creature?
Always use your head
to handle anything.
What?
The printing factory even
issued an apology statement.
The statement also said
they would carry out a
friendly negotiation with us
to cover the loss of
this mistake together.
Of course they should apologize.
This entire thing was their fault.
But I thought they were facing
difficulties in their business?
Why would they be
willing to cover the loss?
You'll have to ask
Mr Zhou Chuan about that.
And what's wrong with Zhou Chuan?
He actually posted a 10,000 words
long article on Weibo,
about the rise and fall
of Zhaoming Printing
over the past fifty years.
He even got a bunch
of writers in the circle
to share it for him.
This old factory that has
an epic and long history,
is poorly managed
and is facing talent loss
due to the external environment.
Such a
devastating story.
But this result is well enough,
isn't it?
It's a happy ending for everyone.
Not only our readers'
anger are dissipated,
but they also believed that Yuan Yue
Publishing House was being generous
for taking the fall for the old factory.
Honestly,
Zhou Chuan has made a really smart move.
But
the question is that after he did this,
who will still hold the managing editor,
Chu Li, for her
responsibility in this?
You see, now everyone believes that
the old factory's slip-up
was because of the external environment.
And the printing factory
is now speaking up for Chu Li,
as a thank you to Zhou Chuan
for creating a good publicity for them.
As a result, Yu Yao and Mr Xia
have gone to see Director Yang
to help Chu Li apply for reinstatement.
We can't have this, Mr Liang.
You have to step up and say something.
Miao, I think you are
getting carried away.
Don't make it personal.
No matter what you do,
you have to put yourself in
Yuan Yue Publishing House's place,
stop focusing on just one person,
am I right?
Now your top priority is to
manage the Animation Column well.
That's your priority, got it?
The result is good.
You've received so much support.
Now Chu Li should be
able to be reinstated soon.
It doesn't matter to me
whether she's reinstated or not.
I just couldn't stand
to see her being sad.
[Luo Wen]
Hello.
All right, I will be right over.
Go home now and coax your girlfriend.
Now is a good chance
for you to claim credit.
Is this Luo Wen
the same Luo Wen from Xin Dun?
Yes.
Gu Bai Zhi's boss?
He said he wanted to
talk to me about something.
Does Gu Bai Zhi know about this?
She
doesn't need to know.
Jiang Yu Cheng.
I don't care if you've
gotten back together again,
or if you have personal ties
with Luo Wen...
Just make sure you know what you're doing.
Chief Editor Yu is helping me
to get reinstated.
If all goes well,
I am going back to work next week.
Mr Zhou, you're so sweet.
Why are you so sweet?
Now you know how sweet I am.
But how have you been treating me
in the last two days?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
See, I've prepared quite a feast for you.
I'm getting just a feast?
Are you happy now?
It's not enough.
You are home.
Why didn't you turn on the lights?
What's wrong?
Since when?
What do you mean?
Since when did you start using me
as a tool to get your promotion
as vice president?
Who told you that?
Answer me.
You've never been a tool to me,
not even once.
You are still lying even at this moment?
Have you been honest for even once?
Have you ever trusted me then?
You suspected that I gave your
manuscript to Yun Fei before,
now you are suspecting me
for using you as a tool for my promotion.
Right, I, Gu Bai Zhi, have been
using myself as bargaining
chip to play with you.
Happy now? Satisfy?
If you want my book,
I'll sign it with you.
If you want to be promoted
as vice president, I'll help you.
Just don't lie to me again.
I don't want to learn about
you from other people again.
If you have any real thoughts,
please tell me.
If you promise me this,
I will pretend nothing has happened.
Go ahead and pretend nothing has happened.
Jiang Yu Cheng,
are you feeling sorry for yourself now?
All these year, I, Gu Bai Zhi
have been approaching
you with an ulterior motive.
I was wrong, you were right.
We shouldn't have started over.
[The Disappearing Amusement Park]
Where is the knife? Where is the knife?
What's the matter with you?
I'm going to kill Liang Chong Lang
that rascal.
Rascal!
-What's the matter with you?
-Let go of me!
-What did he do to you? Tell me!
I'm so mad right now.
Give me the knife.
I say,
Mr Liang, only you are capable of this.
You managed to
talk Director Yang out of
reinstating Chu Li.
And Mr Xia can't
even get mad at you.
Cut it out.
I didn't do that for you.
How did it go with the
popular comic book writer
you contacted?
Time is running short.
Don't worry,
Xiao Niao and I
have accumulated
a lot of resources.
You see,
I just learnt two new massage techniques
during my massage the other day.
Come, sit down, sit down.
Feel it.
Harder.
I don't care.
She's like a different person now.
I kicked the trash can
by accident just now,
and she looked at me like
she was going to kill me.
How can she just turn hostile so quickly?
I don't care.
If you don't come sooner,
I'm dead for sure.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I'm not doing anything.
Are you feeling bored right now?
No.
Go and work on your novel then.
Do the laundry too.
Okay.
Remember to mop the floor.
Sure.
What should
I do first?
Forget it.
You'd better come and help me cook.
[What is this?]
[A gift that should be given
to you three years ago.]
[If you want my book,
I'll sign it with you.]
[If you want to be promoted
as vice president, I'll help you.]
[Just don't lie to me again.]
[I don't want to learn about
you from other people again.]
Okay.
Hello, Director Gu.
No problem.
I'll see you next week then.
Okay.
Okay, bye.
Well played, Mr Luo.
What do you mean by that?
You told Jiang Yu Cheng, didn't you?
Well, you said you
were just doing your job.
So I suppose telling him wouldn't affect
your arrangement, right, Director Gu?
Of course.
These are the works you wanted
to put on Highly Recommended.
I've looked through them,
none of them pass.
You should stop interfering with
Content Planning Department's work,
so that you won't increase our workload.
The incident with the printing factory
has finally come to an end.
Thank you, Chief Editor Yu.
Since Chu Li has been suspended,
so naturally that I should
take care of these matters.
You don't have to thank me.
And about Chu Li's suspension,
is there anything I can do to help?
She has been suspended for a week now.
I've sent Ah Xiang to see her.
Chu Li can take care of it.
When the time comes,
we just have to give her a little help
at the critical moment.
Okay.
Qiu Qiu's birthday
is coming soon.
You'll come to his birthday party, right?
He'll be really happy when he sees you.
When I wasn't pregnant,
I said
you'd be Qiu Qiu's godmother.
Do you remember that?
Qiu Qiu has grown so much now.
Isn't it a bit strange to tell him
that he has a godmother all of a sudden?
No.
In fact, I often brought
you up in front of him.
He knows who you are.
It's okay.
We will see.
This should be the place.
Is this Mr Zhou Chuan and Chu Li's place?
I'm Ah Xiang.
Chief Editor Yu sent me here.
Is there a hope for her
reinstatement again?
Yes, Mr Zhou Chuan.
Have some water.
Thank you, Mr Zhou Chuan.
Have a seat.
So, actually,
Chief Editor Yu and Ms Suo Heng
were supposed to come with me.
But something came up
at the printing factory.
So I came alone.
How's it going?
The gifts have been sent out.
Everything is going well.
Good to hear that.
If it hadn't been Mr Liang's sabotaging,
you would've been reinstated by now.
But Mr Xia still got you
an opportunity from Director Yang.
You know that Yuan Yue Publishing House
is going to reinvent right?
Are you talking about
the new Animation Column?
Mr Liang and Miao have been wanting
to take charge of it for a long time.
It has probably been
assigned to them, hasn't it?
Other than the Animation Column,
Yuan Yue Publishing House
is also adding a New Writer Column
with greatest potential.
You will be in charge of this section.
New Writer Column.
Are you saying that
I am going to scout new writer?
Sort of.
Chief Editor Yu asked you to contact
the outstanding authors
whose follow-ups were picked
in the Interactive
Cultural Festival last year.
As long as you can recruit
a talented new writer,
you'll have no problem getting reinstated.
You got it.
As long as I can keep my job,
I'll do anything.
I will look through the follow-up articles
from the Interactive Cultural
Festival last year now.
I do remember one writer
whose article was good.
I know who you're talking about.
The Ghost Behind You!
Found it.
But I only found his QQ account.
That will do.
Hello.
I am the editor of Moonlight Magazine.
My name is Chu Li.
Looking forward to hearing from you.
I am feeling a little excited suddenly.
What are you excited about?
This is my first time
signing a new writer.
Whether it was you,
or Mr Jiang, or Ms Suo Heng,
you all have some experience
in book publishing.
This is the first time I'm
working with new writer.
He hasn't added you yet.
And you already knew you
are going to work with him?
He'll definitely say yes.
First, he chose your manuscript,
so he is most likely your fan.
Second, even if he isn't your fan,
among all manuscripts,
he and you were like-minded.
So if I can't persuade him,
I can send you to persuade him for me.
That's very cheeky of you.
You were still trying to stab your
husband to death a while ago.
Now you're thinking about
how to take advantage of me.
What a slap in the face.
You'd better not lose
your job again in future,
otherwise, I might as well
just sleep with Er Gou,
it's safer for me.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Who is my husband?
What do you think?
Who else do you think it is?
You haven't answered my question.
You, you, of course it's you.
Now that's more like it.
[Ghost]
Goodness,
This kid is generous
in using exclamation mark.
Let me send him a few topics and ask
him to submit his drafts as try-out.
Director,
I've sent you the information via email.
I'm going take off now.
Okay, get home safe.
We need to talk.
There's nothing to talk about.
Do you really not want to see me?
What? Are you going to
cut me out of your life now?
Gu Bai Zhi.
Bai Zhi.
Drive.
One minute, I just need one minute.
What are you waiting for? Drive.
What are you doing here?
What is this?
This is the manuscript of the revised
edition of Imperial Guard's Journal.
I thought I'd give it to you in person.
[Xin Dun Media "Imperial Guard's Journal"]
Bai Zhi, did anything happen
between you and Jiang Yu Cheng?
Mr Zhou, come and take a look at this.
Ghost's writing is so funny.
It's funny when you laugh like this.
Let me take a look.
Come on.
Look.
What do you think?
[Once Upon a Time in A Mountain]
It's pretty funny.
But what he wrote here
is considered a joke,
not an article.
Besides, sense of humour
vary from person to person.
Not everyone will laugh
so stupidly like you.
Didn't you just laugh like that too?
Ghost's writings
made me feel happy and relax.
All my stress is gone.
And I just talked to him,
I feel that he is a very
energetic young man.
I will text him now
and ask him to meet up.
[Ghost, Male]
And he is a young and handsome man.
I'm getting a little high.
High for what?
It might turn out to be a girl.
I have a lot of fangirls...
You're being narcissistic again.
His QQ account says that he's a male.
Do you really believe in the online world?
You are so easily fooled.
He replied.
He agreed to meet me tomorrow.
Why are you getting so excited?
However, will such an
unusual style of writing
get picked in Yuan Yue Publishing House's
selection process?
Both Ghost's ideas and writings
are trendy and amusing.
I think his appearance will bring more
young readers to Moonlight Magazine.
It will broaden the age
group of our readers.
He is back.
Who's back?
Ma Liang, who makes imagination
come to life with his magic brush.
He's finally back.
[Corner Bookstore]
Are you afraid that
Ghost really is a handsome young man?
Feeling threatened?
Nonsense.
Maybe it's one of my fans.
Can't I come and take a look at my fan?
Can, can.
Your fan, your fan.
Don't worry.
Even though you are not a
young and handsome man,
you can be considered
an old and fascinating men.
Who are you calling old?
Welcome.
Hello.
Monkey design.
You are Chu Li?
[The Chinese Literary Vein, Yu Qiu Yu]
And you are
The Ghost Behind You?
So you are a girl.
Oh my god,
I am looking at a living
editor for my first time.
This is incredible.
Hello, nice to meet you.
You can just call me Ghost.
Hello, hello.
Let's go have a seat.
See that.
You big idiot.
You're younger and cuter
than I thought.
You are still a student, aren't you?
I'm not that young.
I've completed half
of my college years.
You are the first editor who
invites me to write for you.
Let me tell you secretly
I was so thrilled that day
that I couldn't sleep at all.
Have you never published your
article on other magazines before?
No.
I keep getting rejected.
They think my articles
are too nonsensical.
Not at all, I think it's very interesting.
Mr Zhou Chuan thought so too.
Who is Zhou Chuan?
The...
The author whose article
you picked to write follow-up to.
Turned out that you don't know Zhou Chuan.
So you didn't write the
follow-up for his article
because you were his fan?
Of course not.
I just picked what I liked.
Who cares whether it's written
by Zhou Chuan or Ping Chuan?
By the way,
I've submitted your pitches.
I think there should be no problem.
Once the serialization for
your work is confirmed,
it will be published on the
New Writer Column of Moonlight Magazine.
This is Moonlight Magazine's
redesign project.
You can take a look at it first.
Okay.
[Little Monkey]
Did you hear that? You silly peacock.
[Yu Yao]
Ghost's pitches were rejected by Mr Xia.
He'll be excluded from
consideration for now.
I don't understand these,
you can do whatever you want to do.
As long as my works can
get published in the magazine,
even if
I don't get paid, it's fine.
I've been rejected by ten
magazine publishers in a row before.
But I'm not discouraged,
I believe that I will meet someone
who will appreciate my works.
And I met you, didn't I?
You're not done yet, why are we leaving?
What's wrong?
We are going to Yuan Yue Publishing House.
Okay.
Mr Xia, what's the problem?
No, no.
This is the notes I wrote
when I was reading Ghost's works.
He wrote that
side ponytail hairstyle is dangerous.
And also,
the white album.
I mean
how does this
have anything to do with the four seasons?
If I can't understand it,
how will I be able to decide that
whether this can be published?
Also,
Chu Li,
let me ask you,
if a book is incomprehensible to you,
will you introduce it to the readers?
Since this idea didn't work,
we'll find other ways.
Something just doesn't feel right.
Ghost has used too many
anime and manga jokes in her pitches.
People of Mr Xia's age,
just like my dad,
it's normal that they can't
accept it for the moment.
But this isn't
the broad sense of incomprehensibility,
the issue here lies with
the reader's age group.
I can't just give up
Ghost's novel like this.
You want to get Mr Xia to understand
Ghost's Animation, Comics
and Games (ACG) genre novel.
that's okay,
but this isn't something
that can be achieved overnight.
I know,
but Ghost can't wait.
The market is so big,
while we are working
on the New Writer Column,
other publishers are also
transforming themselves.
There will be novels of the same style
on the market soon.
But you have to give Mr Xia time
to understand ACG genre.
It's easy for us to understand ACG,
but it's hard for Mr Xia.
No.
Why must we get Mr Xia understand it?
Besides, what more can we do?
Yes, yes, let me tell you...
Mr Xia!
Mr Xia.
Chu Li, what are you doing here?
Don't you know
you are under suspension?
Miao.
Fine, I'll get on with my work.
Side ponytail is a common hairstyle
for women in anime.
Most characters who
show up with this hairstyle,
they are either dead or going to be dead.
That's why she wrote
"Madam, your hairstyle is dangerous."
The season for white album is winter.
Whenever there is a love triangle
between two women fighting for a man,
people will say,
"This is the season of the white album."
After you explained it,
I get it now.
But you can't explain it
to the reader one by one.
Not everyone
can understand Ghost's novel,
but there must be
a certain group of readers
that will really like and appreciate her.
As long as our New Writer Column
can seize these readers' attention,
we are already half success.
What I'm about to say
may sound a bit overconfident,
but please trust my judgment.
Ghost will definitely become
the most popular author
in the New Writer Column.
Fine.
You want me to trust your judgment.
Tell me then,
what kind of book do you want to publish?
What kind of energy do you
want to convey to reader?
I believe that the energies that a book
can convey to the reader are diverse.
It doesn't have to have
profound ideologies
or educational significance.
As long as it can move the reader
for even just one second,
it's a book that I'm willing to push
through all obstacles to work on.
Did it really make you that happy?
Of course.
Not only did I convince Mr Xia,
but I might get reinstated too.
This would be another highlight
of my year.
What if Mr Xia wasn't convinced?
Not likely to happen.
Entrenchment is
the biggest taboo for a literati.
A literati should be
tolerant to diversity.
Just because Mr Xia was taken aback by
the sudden emergence of
a new generation of literature,
it doesn't mean he rejects it.
Are you that confident?
Yes.
Otherwise, Moonlight Magazine
wouldn't have carried out a reinvention.
I believe that Moonlight Magazine
can definitely
introduce these new generation literature
to those who miss out
on great literary works
because of their traditional stereotype.
Like Mr Xia.
Like your dad.
What are you doing?
We are still in the company.
What? I just want to hold your hand.
Do we really need so many books?
Of course.
When Ghost's novel
is published,
as her editor,
I have to understand
all the references of ACG first
before I can evaluate her content.
You really are...
Really are what...
You really are making me proud.
What are you doing?
This is a public space.
Don't worry, I checked, no one's looking.
Tell me,
if I didn't run
when we first met,
what would have happened?
When we first met?
The first time I found out
you were Monkey was here.
[Mr Zhou Chuan?]
No wonder you ran
away so fast that time.
Weren't you afraid you were
going to fall down hard?
Will you still want me
if I disfigure my face?
Of course not.
What are you doing?
-Grabbing a book.
-Come down.
Come down.
I'll get it for you.
Get me The Garden of Sinners.
Okay.
[Natsume Soseki Collection]
[Sir.]
Have you forgotten that you snatched
Natsume Soseki's Crime from me?
I gave it back to you
after that, didn't I?
But aren't you going to apologize me
after you made a mistake?
Come here.
Why?
I'm going to make it up to you.