["Let's Always Stay in Love" playing]
♪ I've been in Rome ♪
♪ I've been in Paris ♪
♪ I've been in a cell ♪
♪ And I've been infatuated… ♪
I love fashion,
but God, I hate Paris Fashion Week.
- [in French] We haven't ordered yet!
- [in English] I'm not loving it either.
Pierre Cadault is still spiraling.
He won't let us into the atelier.
How do I promote a show
if I can't see the clothes?
Ugh. I'm sorry, Em.
Do you wanna hear some good work news?
Mm. Please.
Remember the drag club I sang at?
- [Emily] Mm-hmm.
- They offered me a job emceeing.
It's just two nights a week,
but they want me to sing.
Mindy, that's fantastic!
Wait, they know
that you're not a drag queen, right?
I mean, I think so.
- I'm kidding.
- [Mindy laughs]
I just need the Duponts
to give me the nights off,
but I can't tell them why.
They're so conservative.
[cell phone chimes]
Oh. Sorry, it's Mathieu Cadault.
Hope this means
it's good news about Pierre.
Uh, I hope this means
you're gonna kiss him again.
- I tell you too much.
- I love it. Wait, are you leaving?
["Mes amis" playing]
[in French] I'm still sitting here!
[indistinct chatter]
You said a drink.
And I meant it.
- [Emily] Oh!
- [cork pops]
[glasses clink]
[camera shutter clicks]
[seagulls crying]
[Emily laughs]
So is a boat ride on the Seine
your go-to move to impress a girl?
[scoffs] I get on the boat
whenever I have a problem.
It gives me a fresh perspective.
What's the problem? Is it Pierre?
He's still reeling from Grey Space.
He won't show me
or anyone the new collection.
You haven't seen it yet either?
But the show's in three days!
- Ugh! Oh, my God, this is all my fault!
- Hey. He's being dramatic. That's his job.
- Come, I wanna show you something.
- What?
My actual go-to move to impress a girl.
["Les Parisiennes" playing]
Wow. [chuckles]
Okay, I can see why this is your move.
Is it working?
I can't believe you live here.
This view is so beautiful.
I couldn't agree more.
[Emily chuckles]
- [ringtone playing]
- Sorry.
- Sorry, sorry, sorry.
- No. [chuckles]
- Ah, mais oui. Mais oui. Sorry.
- [Emily laughs]
- [phone ringing]
- [Mathieu sighs]
What is it? [scoffs]
It's the landline. [sighs]
Nobody has the number except for Pierre.
- Excuse me. Sorry, sorry.
- No, no. Of… Of course.
Allô?
[in French] What? No. I'm on my way.
I'm on my way. Don't move. I'm on my way.
[in English] What happened?
He wants to cancel his show
at the Fashion Week.
- What? Oh, my God!
- I have to go down there.
- Hopefully, I can talk him out of it.
- [sighs]
I'll call you when I know more?
- ["Law of the Jungle" playing]
- [Emily chuckles]
To be continued?
Lock up on your way out, please.
[Sylvie] Well, yes. It's gonna be perfect
at the front row of Pierre Cadault's.
Thank you. Merci.
Oh, Emily. Bonjour.
I'm so glad to see you.
- You are?
- [Sylvie] Yes.
I got your e-mail with the list
of influencers to invite to Pierre's show,
and I agree it's time to shake things up.
- Yes, um, about that. I...
- [Antoine] Ladies.
Bonjour. Sylvie.
Could I see you privately? Please?
- Good. Everyone's here?
- Yes.
Okay.
We can begin.
Hey, your new account manager says
it's time to start the meeting.
Just one minute. [chuckles]
The Zimmer Paris will open
in just two weeks,
and with it, the Maison Lavaux boutique,
featuring the hotel's signature scent.
[snaps]
[in French] Are we ever going to talk?
We're talking now.
Listen to Luc. He's very talented.
[typing]
[Luc, in English] Emily? Could we
pay attention to the presentation?
- S'il vous plaît.
- [gasps]
Oh, my God.
Excuse me. I am speaking.
No, this is an emergency.
Women's Wear Daily just tweeted
that Pierre Cadault is canceling his show!
What? No, that's not possible.
Are you sure? Last night,
Matt said he could talk him out of it.
"Matt"?
What were you doing
with Mathieu Cadault last night?
Why didn't you tell me this
the moment you found out?
- [cell phone vibrates]
- Is that Matt? Give me the phone.
[grunts] Oh, God.
- Allô? Mathieu?
- [Emily] Sylvie! Please wait.
You will never believe this.
- [Mathieu] Pierre forfeited the venue.
- Et pourquoi?
[Mathieu] The new collection's ready.
He won't show it.
We tried a run-through this morning,
and he just screamed,
"Ringarde! Ringarde!"
at every single piece.
[Sylvie] Ringarde?
Okay, well,
please tell me if there's any change,
and take good care of your uncle, Mathieu.
Do you have any idea
of what you have done?
Me?
You convinced Pierre
to donate a dress that got destroyed,
which shook his confidence so badly
that now he won't show
at Paris Fashion Week
for the first time in three decades.
And if that wasn't enough,
you slept with his nephew, Matt.
That last part isn't exactly true.
So now we have a fashion designer
without a fashion show,
which is almost as meaningless
as an American who doesn't speak French
at a Parisian marketing firm.
Sylvie, let me just talk to him.
You are fired.
Get out of my office.
Clear out your desk.
Don't show your face here ever again.
[dramatic piano music plays]
Are you okay?
No.
Sylvie just fired me.
Oh, is that all?
We thought someone died.
Nope. Just my career.
No, it's impossible to fire someone
in France.
- What?
- Oui. The bureaucracy takes months.
Years.
Simply abandon your self-respect,
come in once or twice a week
to move papers around your desk,
and don't make eye contact with Sylvie.
Ouais.
My friend got fired from a law firm.
He was so angry
that he threw his phone into the Seine.
They couldn't reach him
for weeks to complete his termination.
And then, they relaxed.
He's a partner now.
We can throw your phone
in the Seine, if it helps.
Please don't.
Thank you, guys.
I wouldn't have lasted here a week
without you.
Emily, we will never desert you.
Never.
["Paris Rome" playing]
[Camille shouting indistinctly in French]
[Gabriel] All I do is think about you.
I thought it would make you happy!
[Camille] You're so selfish!
No, you're being selfish, Camille!
How can you say such a thing?
- I have to work.
- [Camille] That's all you're good for.
Bonsoir, Emily.
[in English] Hi, Camille.
Is everything okay?
Well, not really.
Well, what happened? Can I help?
- Gabriel found a restaurant he can afford.
- Isn't that good news?
The restaurant isn't in Paris, Emily.
- It's in Normandy, where he's from.
- What? He…
- He's moving to Normandy?
- Yes. Next week.
Next week! Wh...
Uh, why are we just finding out
about this?
- He just told me.
- I don't believe it. I mean, I'm shocked.
Not more shocked than you, obviously.
- You must be très shocked.
- I'm actually really pissed off.
Ah, me too! For you, I mean, it…
[splutters] What is he thinking?
I don't know.
Either he expects me
to move across the country
and leave my whole life behind,
or this is his way of breaking up with me.
[chuckles]
[Emily sighs]
I'm so sorry.
I'm just gonna go
to my parents' house and, um…
I need to think about all this, you know?
I understand.
And I'm here
if you need anything. [chuckles softly]
- I know.
- [Emily] Yeah.
[Camille] I know. Thank you, Emily.
[sniffles] You're such a good friend.
["Paris Rome" continues playing]
[softly] Yeah.
[sighs]
["Quelle surprise" playing]
So were you ever gonna tell me?
Or just leave me a note?
"Hey, going to Normandy.
Have a nice life."
The deal came together quickly.
And you never discussed it with Camille?
She was always going to say no
to Normandy,
or to anywhere
after I declined her mother's loan.
But, you know, I grew up there,
and it's a great opportunity.
I always dreamed
of a restaurant in Paris, but...
Sometimes your dream
is somewhere you didn't expect it to be.
I get it.
I mean,
I thought Chicago was it for me,
and now here I am, saying goodbye
to one of my first friends in Paris.
I just can't imagine this city
without you living downstairs.
And without your omelets.
I'm really gonna miss your omelets.
[sighs] They will miss you too.
I am excited for you. [sighs]
- You have a picture of the new place?
- Of course.
It's next to a restaurant
with two Michelin stars
that is very popular.
Too popular, so I thought,
whenever people can't get in...
- They come to the place next door.
- "The place next door."
- I should call it that.
- [Emily chuckles]
Here, take a look.
It is humble but quite charming.
Hmm. Seems like the perfect fit for you.
Uh, and this is the dining room.
I want to take out the bar.
And, well, the kitchen is a bit small,
but once everything's in place…
- ["Pulse" playing]
- ♪ So long now ♪
♪ Since time stopped turning ♪
♪ Slowing down ♪
♪ With edges gone… ♪
- Bonjour.
What are you doing here?
Do I need to fire you again?
No. Um…
But I have outstanding clients,
and until the paperwork is filed,
I still have a duty to them and to Savoir.
Julien, would you please
bring me a copy of the paperwork
so I can close this matter?
- Mais oui, Sylvie.
- [Sylvie] Thank you.
I'll handle your clients' needs.
But if you insist on coming here,
just get out of the way, hmm?
Sylvie!
I need to talk to you about Maison Lavaux.
I do not think it is the right fit.
Why not?
Me and Antoine?
You know how is it
when you put two alpha males together.
Somebody's going to get killed.
[roars softly]
- Um, I… I'd be happy to help.
- But you no longer work here.
Maybe just until we find
a better solution?
[clicks tongue] Fine.
It'll keep you busy
until the termination is complete.
- You're welcome.
- [Emily chuckles softly]
[sighs]
This just came for you,
and I think you should see it.
Did you open this?
You are very indignant
for someone who does not work here.
Grey Space took over Pierre's old venue.
Oui. What a slap in the face.
[cell phone vibrates]
Matt, I just got an invitation
from Grey Space.
- Pierre got one as well.
- [Emily] Really?
They're dancing on his grave
and inviting him to watch?
- That's so insulting.
- [Mathieu] It's despicable.
He is manic.
Oh, and he wants to see you, now.
Okay. Um…
Tell Pierre I can make it
to the atelier in 20 minutes if I hurry.
Excuse me? You're not going anywhere.
You've done quite enough
to ruin Pierre Cadault's career.
He requested me personally.
[scoffs] Well, I'm coming with you.
[upbeat instrumental music plays]
Ah! Gossip Girl!
- Elle est arrivée!
- Bonjour, Pierre. Comment ça va?
[kisses] Mm. Très bien.
I have something you must see. Come.
Emily, I was about to show a stale,
lifeless collection.
I have been sleepwalking for too long.
And now…
I wake up! [exclaims, laughs]
[gasps] Pierre! Oh, it's amazing!
But you inspired it!
Yeah, it's very original, Pierre.
- The future of Cadault.
- Oh.
And I want the world
to see this immediately!
But the show is canceled,
so that presents a bit of a problem.
I love the idea,
but we can't stage a show with one dress.
I shall make a dozen. Right now!
You forfeited the venue yourself.
Then find me another one!
I've got an idea!
If it's one-tenth
as brilliant as this dress,
you'll be the toast of Fashion Week.
You work on the clothes,
we'll work on the venue.
Mm. Merci, Emily.
And now, everyone out!
[upbeat music plays]
[Pierre shouts, laughs]
So what's your grand idea?
Well, I haven't thought of it yet.
God, you're insane!
And so is he. That explains everything.
Well… [sighs]
- There must be something we can do.
- Yeah, sure.
We can call back everyone we disinvited
and tell them to come
and look at one dress
in a venue we can book in a day!
- See? Easy.
- [Sylvie] Ugh.
No designer will ever want
to work at Savoir after this disaster.
[techno music plays]
[Emily gasps] Look at this!
Grey Space is hijacking Pierre's venue.
More empty stunts.
That's all anyone cares about anymore.
[ship horn blowing]
We need to look at things
from a different perspective.
Yeah, but there's no way
we can find a venue.
I think we might already have one.
- [energetic music plays]
- [Sylvie sighs]
[typing]
[cell phone vibrates]
- Hey, Min, what's up?
- [Mindy] Hey, did you get my texts?
No, I didn't. Sorry.
I've been buried
in work since I got home.
- Oh, good. You're here.
- [knocking on door]
[knocking continues]
[panting] Hey.
You don't have an elevator, do you?
No, what… what's going on?
Could you help me
with the rest of my bags first?
- Sure.
- [guitar music plays]
[grunting] Oh, okay.
- [both grunting]
- [Mindy] Okay. So I did what you said.
I took the job,
told them I would make myself available
on Tuesdays and Friday nights,
and then avoided the question
of gender expression
- with a coquettish laugh.
- [Emily] Okay.
- I was kidding about that.
- And the Duponts fired me!
I thought it was really hard
to fire people in France.
[sighs] It's a lot easier
if you've overstayed your visa illegally.
- I don't know.
- [Emily sighs] Well…
You can stay here as long as you need.
You are the best, Em.
I cannot thank you enough.
[gasps] I'm gonna buy you so much wine.
- [both] Mm!
- Wait, this is gonna be so much fun.
- [knocking on door]
- Oh, you know, um, can I...
- I'm just gonna change in there.
- [Emily] Okay.
Can I just claim a drawer?
There… There's just one drawer. [chuckles]
Cute!
- [knocking on door]
- Uh, okay.
[grunts]
- [sighs]
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Um, I brought you a going-away present.
I think
I'm supposed to get you one of those.
Oh, uh, right.
Well, I thought
you might like to have this.
Really? [chuckles] Thank you.
And also, if you're not doing anything
tomorrow night,
it's my last night at the restaurant.
[chuckles] Tomorrow?
Wh... Why so soon?
You know, why wait to start my new life?
And you and Camille…?
We want different things right now.
And, uh… we need to be free to do them.
What does that mean?
Well, she's not coming to Normandy,
and I'm not staying in Paris,
so we will just go our own ways.
- In America, that's called a breakup.
- [Gabriel] Yeah.
We… We call it that here too.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's just, uh… life.
All right. [sighs]
Um…
Thank you for the pan.
I promise I'll never clean it.
[chuckles] Merci.
Um, I'll see you at the restaurant.
If you can.
Bonsoir.
[Emily sighs]
Hot chef is leaving Paris?
- [Emily sighs]
- And he's single?
You heard all that from the bathroom?
These walls are made of straw
and horsehair.
It'd be harder not to listen.
What happened?
He's buying a restaurant in Normandy,
and Camille doesn't wanna move,
so he's going alone.
That's it?
Em, you've been mooning over each other
since you got here. You have to...
I have a lot of work tonight, okay?
Got it.
[gentle guitar music plays]
- I'll be super quiet.
- [Emily chuckles]
[exhales]
[Mindy exhales]
["My Baggage" playing]
[crowd clamoring]
[Sylvie]
How did Grey Space get such a turnout?
- Nervous?
- Too scared to be nervous.
It's gonna work. It has to.
[tense music plays]
[crowd clamoring]
[reporter] Pierre! Pierre!
[in French] Why did you cancel your show?
[in English] Pierre! Pierre!
Are you here to see Grey Space?
No. You're here to see Pierre Cadault!
[laughs]
[rhythmic dance music
blasting on speakers]
[crowd cheering]
[music grows louder]
[laughing hysterically]
[crowd roaring]
[Emily exclaims]
[Julien] Oh, my God!
["Viva la Resolution" playing]
[Emily cheers]
[group chanting] Pierre Cadault!
Pierre Cadault! Pierre Cadault!
Ooh.
[crowd chanting]
Pierre Cadault! Pierre Cadault!
Pierre Cadault!
["Je ne sais pas pourquoi" playing]
[all] Santé!
- [Sylvie] À la tienne.
- [Mathieu] Bravo.
Paris Match:
"Pierre Cadault takes over Fashion Week."
- Whoo!
- [Julien] Yeah!
Daily Mail: "The old guard is back.
The new guard is ringarde."
Yes!
Daily Mail is appalling.
But I will frame that.
[group laughs]
Thank you for being patient.
We've never been this busy.
Well, I tagged the restaurant
on Pierre's Instagram stories
when we got here.
Sorry for the avalanche.
[sighs]
What?
[gasps] Oh, merde.
[Catherine and Antoine] Bonsoir.
[gasps] Catherine, Antoine!
What brings you here?
Well, I follow Pierre Cadault
on Instagram.
Ah. Merci.
So when I showed Antoine this restaurant,
he said, "Well, I know that place."
So here we are.
Well, you're right on time.
It's the chef's final night in Paris.
He's moving to Normandy.
Are you serious?
Incroyable!
What luck!
Antoine has been promising
to take me here for weeks now.
- Huh, chéri?
- Oh, he's full of promises, isn't he?
Oh, excuse me. [clicks tongue]
So sorry.
Hmm.
So, Emily, I heard that you're in charge
of Maison Lavaux now.
It seems so.
I'm so pleased.
I think you will be a much better fit
for my husband.
- Right. Uh, professionally.
- Whatever you wanna call it.
- [whispers] I approve.
- [Antoine] Uh, chérie.
Our table is ready.
Lovely to see you. Au revoir.
- [Julien] Au revoir. Bonne soirée.
- [Catherine] Bonne soirée.
[Emily] I can't believe
how happy Pierre looked.
Mm-hmm. You are a genius.
Pierre is a genius.
I just pulled off a publicity stunt.
Regardless, I would like to celebrate
with you properly.
[Emily] Hmm.
Have you ever been to…
say, Saint-Tropez?
Never.
What about this weekend?
I'd love to.
[in French] Bye. See you soon.
- Merci. Au revoir.
- Merci. Merci.
Drive carefully.
[in English] The most promising chef
in the city's leaving?
Paris was not what you dreamed?
Not exactly. I… I love Paris.
And I love this restaurant.
Actually, the owner wants to sell, but…
[sighs] …it's too expensive.
That's what investors are for.
[chuckles] I had an offer, actually.
My girlfriend…
- Ex-girlfriend's family.
- [Antoine] Mm-hmm.
- But it was too…
- Compliqué?
[chuckles]
My wife's family invested
in my business when I began, so…
I understand.
You leave your girlfriend,
you lose your restaurant.
[Gabriel sighs]
[speaking indistinctly]
[sighs]
I don't think there's anything left
for me in Paris, anyway.
[Emily] Pierre decided to call it a night?
Of course not.
I just put him in a car,
and he is going to crash
a Grey Space event at Caviar Kaspia.
- I told him we'd meet him there.
- [Emily gasps]
Ah, the chef!
Dinner was excellent.
And congratulations on your new place.
Merci. Um, are you leaving?
One more party
before we put Fashion Week to bed.
[Gabriel] Oh.
Sounds, uh, fun.
Actually, I was thinking
I'm probably just gonna go home.
- [Mathieu] Oh.
- [Emily] Okay?
Of course.
We have all weekend to celebrate.
[Gabriel] Well, uh…
[sighs]
…thank you…
for making my last night
in Paris so… memorable.
I was just returning the favor.
[both chuckle]
Well…
um…
good night, Gabriel. [chuckles]
And good luck.
Au revoir.
["Burst Into Flames" playing]
[Emily chuckles]
♪ I know how to dive into another body ♪
♪ Know how to rest into a car wreck ♪
♪ I know
How to one-two my knuckles bloody ♪
♪ Know how to blow through stacks
Of dead presidents ♪
♪ And I know
It doesn't have to be this way ♪
♪ There's a voice in my head
Saying, "Please, please, please" ♪
♪ And I know
It doesn't have to be this way ♪
♪ But I'm not listening ♪
♪ I burst into flames ♪
♪ So brilliantly ♪
♪ Yes, I do it so well… ♪
Gabriel! Hello?
Gabriel! [sighs]
♪ Wants to see ♪
♪ I burst into flames… ♪
Emily?
[sighing] I… I just, I…
I didn't want that to be the last time
that we saw each other, and I'm...
I'm gonna miss you so much, and I, uh...
- [sighs]
- ♪ To remember me ♪
[door bangs]
[Emily chuckles]
♪ Ashes to ashes ♪
♪ Dust to dust ♪
♪ You'll never have me more than once ♪
♪ Ashes to ashes, dust to dust ♪
♪ You'll never have me ♪
- ♪ More than once ♪
- [both panting]
[both sigh]
- I've thought about this so many times.
- [Emily chuckles]
[sighs] I'd be lying if I said
I hadn't thought about it too.
And… it was incredible.
But you're leaving.
[chuckles] It's just Normandy.
No, I know, I know. It's…
It's not that I can never see you again.
It's just…
I don't think I should…
ever see you again.
Oh. And…
what if I wanna see you again?
Well, then we'd both be hurting someone
that we care about a lot.
[Gabriel sighs]
We never really had a chance.
But at least, now,
we have this one perfect thing.
And I feel like I'm dreaming
and I'm about to wake up.
[bright instrumental music plays]
Well…
let's not wake up just yet.
[upbeat instrumental music plays]
[gasps] Bonjour, Sylvie.
I just talked to Pierre's publicist.
He's doing an interview with French Vogue.
- I was thinking...
- Please, for once, just listen.
About our conversation the other day,
I've decided
not to file your termination paperwork.
Oh. Really?
[scoffs] You have potential,
but you lack polish.
So if you are to remain at Savoir,
I won't be so easy on you going forward.
Understood?
[clicks tongue] Understood.
[Sylvie inhales deeply]
["De profundis
(Ni fleurs, ni couronnes)" playing]
[cell phone chimes]
[Antoine] Emily!
- Hi.
- Hi… Hi! [chuckles]
Wow. You must have really enjoyed
your meal last night.
I'm here for business.
- You?
- Oh, I just live right down there.
- That's convenient.
- Excuse me?
Hey.
Oh! Uh, I…
I thought you were leaving this morning.
Uh, so did I.
So, uh,
what's the champagne for? [chuckles]
- Your last hurrah?
- [Antoine] Quite the opposite.
I could not bear to see Paris
lose its most promising young chef.
Antoine wants to back me
in the restaurant. [chuckles]
In… In Paris?
Of course.
Gabriel belongs here.
He's too talented
to be banished to Normandy.
[Emily chuckles]
[sighs]
[ringtone plays]
My wife. Excuse me.
- So you're staying in Paris?
- Yes.
[both chuckle]
Oh, don't worry.
You can keep the omelet pan.
[Emily chuckles softly]
I'll go get another glass.
["Non je ne regrette rien" playing]
[chuckles]
[cell phone chimes]
[Emily sighs deeply]