["Magnifique" playing]
- [song continues on headphones]
- [Emily panting]
[ringtone plays]
- [exhales] Ah.
- [phone unlocks]
Bonjour, Paris!
Hi, Chicago. What time is it there?
It's 1:00 a.m.
With the nausea, the sore boobs,
and enough gas to launch a parade float,
I can't sleep!
Well, this'll give you something
to dream about.
Aw. Where are you?
- Jogging on the Seine.
- [Madeline sighs]
It's gorgeous. You are living my life.
Except for... the jogging part.
And how's Doug like it?
Uh... Doug isn't actually coming.
We're, um...
We're not together anymore.
What?
So you're single? In Paris?
- So single. [chuckles]
- Okay, now I'm even more jealous.
I mean, your life is croissants and sex.
- So far, croissants.
- [Madeline] Mm.
So, how's the Paris office treating you?
Oh, yeah, they're a fun bunch.
- Uh, I'm fitting right in.
- Wonderful.
I'll send the corporate commandments
from the Chicago office
so you can give them
an idea of our best practices.
Great.
I'm sure they'll love to hear those,
especially from me.
Excusez-moi, mademoiselle.
Oh, yeah, no problem.
- [sighs]
- [urinating]
Emily. Emily, there's a man next to you
who's exposing himself.
- Em... Emily?
- Oh, my God!
Uh, pardon.
Um, no. Sorry, that's my bad, I...
You're peeing, and that's a urinal, um...
- Au revoir to you, monsieur.
- Bonne journée.
["Magnifique" continues playing]
[pigeons coo]
[camera shutter clicks]
[cell phone chimes]
[exhales]
[shower running]
[pipes squeak]
What?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. No!
[panting, sighs]
[groans]
[upbeat music playing]
[Emily sighs]
Ah, madame. Madame.
The shower in my apartment
just stopped working.
Poof! Just like that...
[splutters]...there's no more water.
[in French] Why are you out
dressed like that?
Do you think you're at a carnival?
[in English] The shower.
Can you come see?
[in French] I don't understand.
And I've got no mail for you.
[in English] Is there something
you can do? [grunts]
Oh, hi.
Hi, good morning. Um,
can you please just tell her
that the water cut off in my shower?
[in French]
The water cut out in her shower.
Yeah... and last week, it was a fuse.
Why does she break everything?
Can she tell me why she breaks everything?
[in English]
She wants to know what you did.
Nothing! Nothing.
I was minding my own shower business!
You know, the water is very unreliable
in this building.
The plumbing is 500 years old. Literally.
[in French] She's getting on my nerves.
Nothing but problems since she got here.
- [in English] What did she just say?
- She'll call a plumber.
And in the meantime?
- [in French] And in the meantime?
- Le bidet.
- [in English] Yeah, that one I got.
- ["Big Future" playing]
♪ Big future... ♪
[teacher] Le verbe "aimer."
[in French] I like coffee.
[class repeats phrase]
I like tea.
I like sport.
[class repeats phrase]
I like boots.
I like dancing.
[class repeats phrase]
And I like Paris.
[in English] Bye, everyone. Good job.
- Jacqueline?
- Yeah?
Um, any advice on how to get an office
full of French people to "aimer" me?
You work in an office
full of French people?
- Oui.
- [Jacqueline] Wow.
- That must be... interesting.
- [Emily] Mm.
- I'll tell you all about it.
- [Jacqueline] Yeah.
Maybe we can go out
and have a drink or something?
Oui, bien sûr.
My rate outside class is 50 euros an hour.
Oh... Bon.
Or maybe not.
- As you want.
- [Emily chuckles]
Have a good week.
[upbeat instrumental music playing]
Bonjour, Sylvie.
Ah. Bonjour. [sighs]
- J'aime those bottines.
- Merci.
Why are you smiling like that?
[chuckles] I'm just saying bonjour.
It's a beautiful day in Paris.
There's not so much to be happy about.
We have a big day.
Very important commercial shoot
for De L'Heure.
And if you keep smiling like that,
people will think you're stupid.
[chuckles] Okay. I'll try to stop smiling.
Unless you're really happy.
Are you really happy?
Well, I just split up with my boyfriend,
and the water in my shower
this morning cut off
due to some ancient plumbing issue,
so I had to wash my hair in the bidet.
But...
c'est la vie.
- Oh.
- [Emily sighs]
Well, perhaps you can post that
on your little Instagram?
#BadHairDay.
[upbeat music playing]
[door opens]
[sighs]
Excuse me,
what is this I just received from you?
Oh, it's just something
I sent from the Chicago office,
our corporate commandments.
Oh, and you're commanding us to do what?
"Thou shalt always maintain
a positive attitude.
Thou shalt be on time.
Thou shalt praise in public
and criticize in private."
"Thou shalt avoid workplace romances"?
And "Thou shalt remember
that we are all a team."
And there is no i in team.
Well, the French word for team is équipe.
- And there's an i in équipe.
- Well, let's not get caught up on vowels.
[chuckles] It's about all of us sharing
a global vision.
Ah.
You would like to destroy our French soul!
Well done, Emily.
[tense instrumental music plays]
Look, I wanna be part of the solution,
not create problems.
Well, then, you should listen more
and talk less.
- This is a very important shoot.
- I'm just gonna be getting
some behind-the-scenes
for social in the States.
I wanna make sure
that De L'Heure gets "de more" followers.
[chuckles]
Well, you're stating the obvious.
That's what you're here for.
Antoine!
- ...l'appareil. Bonjour.
- [Sylvie] Mm.
Emily. Nice to see you again.
[chuckles] Bonjour.
I am très excitée to be here.
- [chuckles]
- Excitée? Really?
Um... "excitée" does not mean excited.
It means horny.
Oh, well, not that, then. [chuckles]
Well, you'll have to excuse her.
She washed her hair
in the bidet this morning.
- [upbeat music plays]
- [Sylvie sighs]
[crew members speaking French]
[Antoine] Has Sylvie told you
about the shoot?
[Emily] No, she hasn't.
So, we follow this elegant young woman
walking to work,
and as she crosses the bridge,
she becomes every man's fantasy
and desire.
- Our tagline is "Dream of Beauty."
- Well, I feel like I'm dreaming right now.
This view is magical.
It's so nice
to see Paris through fresh eyes.
[chuckles] Let's just make sure
we don't see any tourists in cargo pants.
Um, I'm just gonna grab some content
for social.
Uh, bonjour.
- Je suis Emily from Savoir.
- I don't speak French.
Me either.
Um, okay, good.
Do you mind
if I ask you a couple questions?
Okay.
Where are you from?
Serbia.
And what is your dream of beauty?
Private jet.
- Okay. Wh...
- Excuse me. We are ready to shoot.
- Okay?
- Okay.
[actress] No pictures.
[upbeat music plays]
Oh, merci... beaucoup.
[director, in French] Cut!
[in English] What do you think?
- J'adore.
- Emily?
Uh, well,
I... didn't, uh, expect her to be naked.
[chuckles] She's not naked.
She's wearing the perfume.
- [Sylvie chuckles]
- It's very sexy, no?
Sexy or... or... or sexist?
I... I don't understand.
How is this sexist?
Well, whose dream is it anyway?
The... The... The men or the woman?
It's her dream, of course.
To be admired and desired by men.
But it's the male gaze.
- Oh mon Dieu.
- Yes.
The male gaze. Exactly.
I... I don't think
American women will respond to this.
What is the problem?
Explain this to me. I'm interested.
[in French] Stop everything, please!
[crew shouting in French]
Merci.
[in English] Tell me.
What is wrong with the male gaze?
The men are objectifying her.
They have the power.
No, she has the power.
Because she's beautiful and she's naked,
which gives her more power.
Maybe in her dream,
she's wearing clothes.
- [scoffs] It's surrealism.
- [lighter clicks]
It's a long tradition in France.
Man Ray, Cocteau...
No, she has no references.
I'm worried it won't translate
in the States.
In today's climate,
it... it could come off
as politically incorrect.
"Politically incorrect"?
Is this the Me Too?
"Balance ton porc."
Excuse me?
That's what they call it here:
"out your pig."
So you know what I mean, right?
Chérie, I'm a woman. I'm not a feminist.
But regardless,
it's her dream to walk naked
across the Pont Alexandre III
and have men want her.
Maybe it's not your dream, Emily,
but that's her dream.
We just need to be sensitive
to the way women are thinking now.
I... I wanna protect your brand.
And we need to protect ourselves
from the morality police.
Desire does not mean lack of respect.
In fact, quite the opposite.
It is a sign of respect.
There is no bigger compliment.
I'm sure you've experienced
this look of a desire from a man?
- On occasion, yes.
- [Antoine] So, you agree.
For her, it is a sexy dream.
It's open to interpretation.
[chuckles] Voilà.
[chuckles]
Is this what you mean when you say
you want to be part of the solution?
[jazz music plays]
[man grunting]
[exhales]
- Non.
- What do you mean, "Non"?
- Impossible.
- But why "impossible"?
Pas possible parce que...
parce que j'ai pas les bonnes pièces.
- Je dois acheter un écrou...
- No, wait! Vous...
Wait! Vous... S'il vous plaît.
Hi. Can you come talk to my plumber?
It's an emergency.
Good morning, Gabriel. How are you today?
- Good morning, Gabriel. How are you today?
- [Gabriel] Asleep. Thank you for asking.
I was having a very nice dream,
and this American girl banged on my door
and woke me up.
- Or maybe I'm still dreaming?
- You're not dreaming. You're wide awake.
Don't let him leave
until he fixes my shower.
Où est-ce que ça bloque?
Je comprends pas.
Pour t'expliquer vite fait,
ce qui bloque c'est que ça, c'est ancien,
ça, c'est nouveau.
La pièce en fait qui fait le lien
entre l'ancien et le nouveau,
c'est un écrou de fixation.
Écrou de fixation ça veut
dire qu'il faut que j'appelle un pote,
ça peut mettre quatre heures à venir.
Je ne sais même pas s'il va trouver
la pièce.
Donc là, ça peut prendre quatre heures.
Donc ça, on a le temps
de prendre un petit-déjeuner,
café, croissant, tout ce que tu veux.
Ensuite, si la pièce arrive,
"si" la pièce arrive,
je peux peut-être réparer le truc.
What did he say?
He would like some coffee.
Uh... and a croissant.
Ce qui s'est passé,
c'est que j'ai commencé dans le sud.
Je suis parti à droite à gauche,
je ne sais même plus
dans quel quartier j'étais.
Je connaissais rien en fait. C'était fou.
- [men chuckle]
- What did he say?
Oh, um, uh, we were just talking
about where we both were
when France won the World Cup.
Honestly, you couldn't walk
down the street that day.
Okay, what about the shower?
He needs a part.
But it's not ordinary,
so it could take a few days.
Or a few weeks.
Depending.
[sighs] Merci.
Merci. Au revoir, mademoiselle.
Uh, okay, what do I do until then?
Use mine.
[acoustic guitar music plays]
[Emily] Hmm.
[sighs]
Merci for the shower.
- La douche.
- What?
[chuckles] The shower is "la douche."
Oh.
Well, I had a wonderful, uh...
douche.
[rhythmic music plays]
[mouthing silently]
So, how to invite somebody to a party.
You start.
[in French] Would you like to go
to Jean-Jacques' party with me?
I would love to.
Would you like to go
to Jean-Jacques' party with me?
I wasn't invited.
[classmate] Do not be sad.
He is only inviting his closest friends.
Voilà!
- ["Moon" playing]
- ♪ And it went like ♪
♪ Mm-mm ♪
- ♪ Mm-mm ♪
- [keys jangle]
♪ Mm-mm, mm-mm-mm-mm ♪
♪ Mm-mm-mm ♪
[in English] You cost us time and money
on the shoot yesterday
- with your questions.
- Bonjour, Sylvie.
Antoine's coming in this afternoon
to show us the film.
- I suggest you stay quiet.
- Did you really not agree with me?
Just a little?
I don't take such a simplistic view
of men and women.
That's very American.
That's literally why I'm here:
to bring an American point of view.
You're more like the prude police.
I'm just trying
to imagine a social campaign
that doesn't seem tone-deaf
to the cultural moment.
- [Sylvie sighs]
- Honestly, I'm only worried about Antoine.
Why don't you leave Antoine to me? Hmm?
[tense instrumental music plays]
[Emily sighs] Hmm.
[gasps, sighs]
Do you have any idea
who put this on my desk?
It wasn't me.
Mine doesn't bend like that.
[indistinct chatter]
[grunts] I am going out to lunch!
A long lunch with wine!
It's 11:00 a.m.
Well, c'est la vie.
[bright instrumental music plays]
[Mindy] "Thou shalt always maintain
a positive attitude.
Thou shalt avoid workplace romances."
You told French people this?
No wonder they hate you.
Oh, not just this.
They disagree with everything I say.
That's the French way.
They're... very disagreeable.
But I'm an agreeable person.
People like me. That's my strength.
- And here, they just wanna slap you.
- Exactly.
I know.
I can't believe I'm drinking before noon.
It's okay. This is Sancerre.
It's a breakfast wine.
Even in French class this morning,
I didn't get invited
to Jean-Jacques' party.
- Uh, what an asshole!
- No, I mean, don't worry.
- He's not real. But, you know.
- [Mindy] You know what?
The Duponts are going
to their country house this weekend.
I'm gonna throw you a dinner party
at their apartment.
Will they mind?
Not if they don't know.
Oh, and you can invite Sylvie.
- I can cook.
- [Mindy] Don't worry.
I'll take care of everything.
- [glasses clink]
- [Emily chuckles]
[French ballad playing]
[ballad continues over TV]
- [whispers] Okay, that doesn't make sense.
- It's a perfume commercial.
It's not supposed to make sense.
[narrator] De L'Heure. A dream of beauty.
So, what do we think? Sexy or sexist?
[chuckles] Definitely sexy.
I'm asking Emily.
Uh, it... it doesn't matter what I think.
It matters what your customer thinks.
So why not let them
make up their own minds?
Put the commercial on Twitter with a poll:
"Sexy or sexist?"
Get a conversation going.
Let the world decide,
and make it part of your campaign.
[clicks tongue] "Sexy or sexist?"
Or maybe both.
[sighs] It's a little controversial.
I like it.
[upbeat acoustic guitar music plays]
Well, finally, Emily,
a reason to smile.
- [Emily exhales]
- Oui? Another suggestion?
No, an invitation.
A friend is having a dinner for me,
- and...
- Sorry, I'm busy.
I didn't tell you when it is.
Oh, whoops. [sighs]
Look, I know
you haven't warmed up to me yet,
but I promise you will
if you get to know me.
I don't want to get to know you.
Okay, fine.
Fine.
Can I just ask why? [scoffs]
Look...
you come to Paris,
you walk into my office,
you don't even bother
to learn the language.
You treat the city
like it's your amusement park,
and after a year of food, sex, wine,
and... maybe some culture,
you'll go back from where you came.
[sighs]
So... perhaps we'll work together.
But no, we won't be friends.
It's tonight at eight.
I'll email you the address.
["Juicy Fruit" playing]
[gate buzzes]
- [indistinct chatter]
- [Mindy exclaims] The guest of honor!
- Mwah, mwah! Oh, you look amazing!
- [chuckles]
Everyone, everyone, everyone,
this is Emily.
I thought you said
it was just a few people.
It snowballed.
[in French] Emily has just moved here
from Chicago to work for a marketing firm.
[guests continue chattering]
[gasps, in English] Louise! Oh.
You know what? Just get a drink.
I'll be right back.
- So...
- Ah.
- Hi. How do you like Paris?
- Hi.
- J'aime beaucoup.
- That's good French.
Margaux? Oh mon Dieu!
Je suis tellement contente de te voir!
- [woman exclaims]
- C'est génial!
- Mais t'es pas avec Lucas?
- Non, c'est bon, je crois plus à l'amour,
- c'est fini.
- Non...
Oui, mais par contre je suis
à fond sur mon boulot.
- C'est génial, ça.
- Oui, c'est génial. Et...
[rock music playing on sound system]
[sighs, in French]
I never get tired of this view.
[chuckles softly]
[chuckles, in English] Oh.
Sorry, I'm the American girl.
- Oh.
- Emily.
Fabien. [kisses]
Very... beautiful,
non?
Oui...
j'aime beaucoup. [sighs]
- And you're coming from?
- Chicago.
Chicago. Visiting Paris?
Working. A job.
Ah.
[in French] Work, work...
[chuckles, in English]
And... And... And you travail?
Yes, um... [clicks tongue]
[in French] I am...
a painter.
[gasps softly] Ah. Artiste.
Uh, no... for the buildings.
[in English] Um...
I'm sorry for my English.
- [chuckles]
- No, I'm sorry for my French. [chuckles]
I like your smile.
J'aime votre...
- [chuckles awkwardly]
- ...tatouage.
[clicks tongue] Tatouage.
[both chuckle]
- [accordion music playing]
- [Emily] J'aime...
the moon.
La lune.
I like...
les pavés.
Cobblestones.
I like I les huîtres. [chuckles]
- Oysters.
- [both laugh]
And I like...
tes lèvres.
My lips.
J'aime... your eyes.
Tes yeux.
[quietly] Tes yeux.
I like...
ton cou.
[kisses]
My neck.
[whispers] And I like...
American pussy.
- [music stops abruptly]
- Excuse me?
I like American pussy.
And I'd really like to go home now.
Alone.
- [indistinct chatter]
- ["Vers les tombes" playing on stereo]
[Gabriel and waiter speaking indistinctly
in French]
Bonsoir.
Are you looking for my douche?
[chuckles]
What I'm really looking for is a drink.
- Ah.
- And a friendly face to talk to.
So, how do you like Paris so far?
Why does everyone
keep asking me that question?
[in French] It's natural.
[Emily, in English] Okay.
Here's my answer.
I like Paris,
but I'm not really sure Paris likes me.
And maybe that's okay.
I've spent my entire life
wanting to be liked.
That's a pretty miserable goal.
Exactly.
So... I'm gonna give up trying.
Well, there's just one problem.
What's that?
I like you.
[cell phone vibrates]
- Hi, Madeline. Don't you ever sleep?
- [Madeline] No, I don't.
I just wanna let you know
that your social impressions
are up 200 percent
since that Twitter poll went live.
BuzzFeed and Jezebel linked to it
in the States.
Fantastic.
But a lot of people don't like it.
Did you send me over here
to increase brand visibility or be liked?
Honey, I think you can do both.
Look, now that you're single,
why don't you go find
some of that French D?
Actually,
I'm on the hunt for one right now.
Donc, là. C'est pas que c'est mauvais,
c'est juste qu'on voit pas,
- si tu veux, donc...
- Ben, je vois pas.
I believe you have an expression:
"Let them eat cake."
[mutters]
[Luc and Julien laughing]
Merci!
Ah. Oh!
- [Julien gasps]
- [Luc] Mm!
["Rouge soleil" playing]
We have a meeting...
for the Renault account.
Exactly five minutes ago.
I'll be right there.
Who's that from?
Nobody. Just a friend.
[Sylvie] Mm-hmm.
[sighs deeply]
[groans]
[theme music playing]