[acoustic guitar music plays]
[door closes]
[Camille and Gabriel speaking French]
[lively instrumental music plays]
[Emily gasps]
["Eighty Jaune" playing]
Oh, no.
She knows, right?
[sighs] Knows what, though?
I mean, what did you really do?
- I kissed him twice.
- [Mindy] First one doesn't count.
Well, the second one
more than made up for it.
- So don't do it again?
- It's not that easy.
Every time we're in the same room,
it's all we can think about.
It's like a fog sets in with him,
and neither of us can see straight.
You can't punish people
for their thoughts.
I'm from China. We've tried.
I think I should just move.
I feel so guilty. I like Camille so much.
If she knows, she probably just wants
to get it out in the open.
Just go to lunch and maybe avoid anywhere
with steak knives.
- What?
- [Mindy] Sushi's safe.
Or anywhere that's Asian.
Although if she's mad,
a chopstick can puncture skin.
- Don't ask how I know that.
- Can we hang this weekend?
- I need to not be home.
- [Mindy] Ugh.
My friend Li
and her five bridesmaids are in town.
- Wedding dress shopping.
- That sounds fun.
Yeah, um…
Wait, why won't a weekend
with your friends be fun?
They're always fun,
but their heads would explode
if they knew I was a nanny.
They're your friends.
I'm sure they'll understand.
Maybe you should just tell them.
Maybe you should just tell Camille
you're obsessed with her boyfriend. Sorry.
We're going clubbing tonight.
- Please come.
- [cell phone chimes]
I need a witness to my fake life.
[sighs] Well, text me details for tonight.
I have to plan lunch with my executioner.
[tense instrumental music plays]
[takes a deep breath] I have
something a bit awkward to ask you.
- I talked to Gabriel about it.
- Oh, well, what did he say?
- He said I shouldn't bring it up.
- Well then, maybe you shouldn't.
Well, I need you to be honest.
Okay. Uh, just say
whatever it is that you need to.
[clears throat]
Would Savoir be interested in taking on
my family's champagne house as a client?
I know we're probably smaller
than your usual clients, but...
Oh, my God!
[splutters] Yes! Of course!
Yes! So, my brother and I finally got
Maman to meet with a firm.
But it's her family's company,
so she's so protective.
- But since we're friends…
- [chuckling] We are. We are.
We… We're… We're totally friends.
So come to the château
with me this weekend.
I'd love her to meet you
and hear any ideas you have.
Otherwise,
I will have to drive down all alone.
Oh. Gabriel's not coming with you?
No, he has to work.
And also, he's still upset
that I asked Maman
for the loan of his restaurant.
I… I thought that he didn't want you to.
He never wants help,
especially when he needs it.
He's stubborn.
I mean, I… I do get it.
He wants to build something of his own.
Just don't let me talk
about him all weekend.
- [Emily chuckles softly]
- To the château. You will come, yes?
Okay, yeah. I… I…
I can pitch it to Savoir this afternoon.
- Fantastic!
- [both chuckle]
- ["Oiseau La Fontaine" playing]
- Santé. [laughs]
[Sylvie] Never heard of them.
Can they afford us?
What was their revenue last year?
I'm not sure.
The market is very saturated.
- What's the brand identity?
- [sighs] I… I don't know.
[scoffs] Do you know anything about them?
My friend's parents own it,
and she asked me
to consider them as a client.
How are you friends
with a champagne heiress?
She's dating my friend, my neighbor.
Oh, the one you went home with
from the Fourtier party.
I didn't go home with him.
The chef from the Zimmer dinner.
- Ah, Emily's boyfriend, no?
- Nah, she just has a crush on him.
- I didn't say that.
- You didn't have to.
So now you're going home
with his girlfriend to meet her family?
I'm just meeting with a potential client.
[in French] Bullshit.
[in English]
I can tell her Savoir isn't interested.
You'll let your sex life
determine business decisions?
We never had sex!
Well, maybe, you should. You're so tense.
[Emily sighs]
[dance music playing]
[Li and bridesmaids chanting]
Plane! Club! Another club! Another club!
Bus! Another club!
No sleep!
- Drink, bitch!
- [glasses clink]
- [group cheers]
- Ooh, your friends are wild!
Maybe too wild.
Here, you should drink some more water.
Water? Oh, we're in Paris, bitch.
[heaves, retches]
Oh, God. Oh, my God.
Oh, Shay. Okay, okay.
Well, I guess you'll get to know Shay
a little bit more later.
But this is Li.
I cannot believe
you came all the way to Paris.
Well, you wouldn't come to Shanghai,
so we've had to bring Shanghai to you.
Em, this is Li, the bride.
The bride and her best friend.
Oh, Li.
- [Emily and Mindy] Li.
- [Emily] Li.
Right. Oh, no,
she's told me so much about you.
Too much, in fact. I feel like I know you.
That's so nice to hear.
You know what she hasn't told me?
- Anything about her life in Paris.
- [Mindy chuckles]
Okay, yeah.
- [Li] Yeah.
- [group cheers]
- Oh! Um, are we getting more champagne?
- We are!
- Excuse me!
- [group cheering and laughing]
I will serve.
- [Emily chuckles]
- [group exclaims]
Wait, we don't get to drink it?
- That's so expensive.
- Relax, they'll buy more.
[Li] Drink, bitch!
[group laughing]
[Emily] I overpacked.
I've only been to one winery in Wisconsin,
and it had a paintball course.
I wasn't sure about the dress code.
I wanted to look professional but casual.
You're not going on a business trip.
You're coming home with a girlfriend.
We can all squeeze in front.
"We all"?
Oh! Uh… [chuckles]
Gabriel's coming. Yay.
- He finally got a weekend off.
- Hi. Haven't seen you in a while.
[sighs] Squeeze in. It will be tight,
but it's only for a few hours.
- Um…
- Uh, you…
- Yeah, okay. Okay.
- [mutters]
[birds singing]
[Emily chuckles]
- [engine revs]
- ["Le Zou" playing]
Everybody okay?
- I'm fine.
- Totally great.
My butt's asleep,
and I can't feel anything.
[Emily] So what else should I know?
Why didn't your mom like the other firms?
- [grunts]
- She hates outsiders.
That's not true.
She's going to love you.
And so is my brother.
What are you doing?
Ignore him.
My brother's finishing business school.
Maman wants us
to take over the vineyard one day.
He might join us this weekend.
I think you will like him.
Oh, yeah, did you get Maman's approval?
- Will she allow it?
- She tried to fund your restaurant.
You wouldn't allow it,
so be nice to her this weekend.
They adore him, Emily. You will see.
Oh, yeah. You will see.
[Camille exclaims]
[in French] Flowers go next door,
please, Isabelle. Oh, my darling!
- [Camille] Ça va?
- [mother] Bien, et toi?
- [Camille] Oui. Ça va.
- [in English] Hello!
- So you must be Emily?
- Bonjour.
- Thank you so much for having me.
- Yes. Ça va, Gabriel?
- Ça va.
- Bon.
[in French] I didn't go to the market.
Too much to do. So you'll go.
Allez, viens chérie.
Of course.
[Camille chuckles]
[mother clicks tongue, mutters]
[in English]
Oh, the château is so beautiful!
I'd love a tour.
[chuckles]
We don't give tours of the château.
We live here.
[in French] It's an American custom
to show off your home to visitors.
Really? Does she want to see our bins too?
[Camille chuckles]
[in English] If you'd like
a vineyard tour, there's one in 30.
Just follow the road signs.
[in French] I want
to show you something in the office.
[in English] Did I just catch "bureau"?
Does your mother wanna talk business now?
Oh, no, we have
all weekend for that. Don't worry.
Um, show her around. Maybe the pool?
Yeah.
Come on. I'll take you.
Oh, I can find it.
[accordion music playing]
- [gasps]
- Bonjour. [chuckles]
[chuckles, in French] You must be Emily.
[in English] Oh, my God. Um… hi.
I forgot you don't speak French. Uh…
My name is Gérard.
[in French] The champagne father.
Le champère. [laughs]
- [chuckles]
- [Gérard, in English] You see?
Because in French, "père" means...
Father! Yep, I got it.
Uh, I remember that one.
- May I offer you a glass?
- No! No, uh, I… I mean, no, merci.
Um, I'm just looking for my room.
Oh, okay! Of course!
- I'm gonna show you.
- I'll just give you a minute. Okay?
- [whimpers]
- [playful instrumental music plays]
- [groans]
- So did you meet Gérard?
Yeah. Thanks for the heads-up.
Gabriel!
- Gérard!
- [Gérard] Bienvenue.
Can I get you a glass?
Maybe when I return.
Louise is sending us to the market.
You are seducing us with another
of your delicious meals, eh?
[exclaims, chuckles]
Emily,
have you tasted this man's coq au vin?
I definitely have not.
I tell you, when it hit my lips,
I was ready to propose to him.
Um, we should get going to the market.
Yeah, yeah. Okay, okay.
Do as my wife says. She's in charge.
Take the bikes!
It's a beautiful day for a ride. [sighs]
- Great.
[Emily chuckles]
[birds singing]
I think I'm gonna go on the tour.
- Sample some product.
- There's plenty of champagne in the house.
We can have a glass before we go.
I want the full experience.
I came here to work.
You're not coming with me?
On a romantic bike ride
to a picturesque country market?
Great idea.
Why don't we just do it in the barn?
They don't have a barn here.
The wine cellar is pretty nice, though.
I'm joking.
I'm not laughing.
You've been avoiding me for a week,
and now this. It's just a farmers market.
You think we cannot keep
our hands off each other for an hour?
I like the odds
when my hands are somewhere else.
I think you're overreacting.
We can be friends.
I feel we've made it pretty clear
we can't just be friends.
- But we live on top of each other.
- You're proving my point.
So what? We just stop speaking?
What do we tell Camille?
We don't tell Camille anything.
We just have to be friendly.
- But not friends?
- Yes.
Can you make me a list of rules?
'Cause it's a little complicated.
Okay, fine. I'll make it easy.
You go to the market, I'll go on the tour,
and everybody
keeps their hands to themselves.
[sighs]
["Yéyé St-Tropez" playing]
[man] …and that brings us
to the subtler step
in the whole process, le remuage.
Each bottle is turned
a tiny bit each day, like this,
to collect,
in the neck, the dead yeast cells.
A professional remueur
can handle tens of thousands of bottles
in a single day.
It is a delicate and precise skill.
Who wants to try?
Mademoiselle, how about you?
What? Me? No. No, no, no, merci.
[in French]
And an American, too. Perfect.
[in English] Come.
Don't worry, I won't embarrass you
in front of the British.
[laughs] Just kidding.
Everybody take a rack, please.
So we'll make a game,
and the first one to turn all the bottles
one-quarter turn wins.
Are you ready?
- Ready, set, go!
- [group clamoring]
[dramatic orchestral music playing]
- Done! [sighs]
- Ah! Congratulations, American.
You just won the first taste.
Everybody will have one, of course.
And…
[in French] …to the Queen of Remueurs!
[Emily] A la reine des remueurs!
[in English]
You're just supposed to taste it, dear.
- Oh, whoops. [laughs]
- [guide] No, it's okay.
We'll continue
to the tasting room, please.
This way.
- [guide laughs]
- Sorry.
No, you paid for the tour.
Actually, I didn't.
My friend's family owns the place.
- Oh, you're my sister's friend?
- Emily.
You're Camille's brother.
- Ouais. I am Timothée.
- [Emily chuckles]
So you're gonna run all this one day?
Maybe someday, yes.
I've been working weekends here
since I finished collège.
Looks like it's gonna be in good hands.
Not fast hands, but...
[chuckles] Okay, I see.
Oh, please, have more.
You know, the bottle costs
just the same whether you drink it or not.
And if you'd like a refill at any time,
just tap me on the shoulder.
Et voilà.
It was a good day at the market.
- [group] Ooh.
- Wow. It looks spectacular, mon amour.
Emily, you must taste his aubergine.
"Aubergine"?
Uh, my eggplant.
Oh, um, I'm allergic,
so probably best not.
Beautiful job, Gabriel.
Oh, thank you. Bon appétit, everyone.
- [Louise] Mm!
- [Emily] Mm!
Wow! This… This chicken is...
I told you. His coq is the best.
It… It really is delicious.
Mm! It's so juicy.
Well,
since you didn't get to try my eggplant,
at least you're enjoying my coq.
Oh, I'm gonna have some more champagne.
[in French] Gérard, serve her.
[in English] I can pour it. It's fine.
Women are not supposed
to touch the bottle at the dinner table.
I know, it's silly…
and it's old-fashioned,
but so is my mother.
Just tap my foot
under the table when you'd like a refill.
- How was the tour, dear?
- [Timothée] Fine.
We went through
more product than usual, though.
The guests were very thirsty today.
Louise, your champagne is so special.
I'm glad I got to really appreciate it.
- Good.
- Yes, she certainly appreciated it.
The point is
that I have some marketing strategies
that I would love to discuss.
[chuckles] The other thing we don't do
at the dinner table is talk business.
Maman has so many rules.
Oh, rules are good.
I like rules.
They force us to behave.
To rules!
Sure. Yeah. To rules.
[all] To rules.
- Gabriel, dinner is amazing.
- [Louise] Agreed.
He really should have
his own restaurant, shouldn't he?
- Maman.
- Well, that's, uh, the goal, someday.
Of course. Just not with our help.
It was a very generous offer,
but one I can't accept.
[Gérard] Gabriel…
when a woman wants
to take care of you, you let her.
Look at me. Have you met a happier man?
- [chuckles]
- I have to, um, take in the soufflé.
Excuse me.
[in French] Just let him be.
[in English] Okay! Okay.
Uh, Timothée,
would you mind getting a picture of us?
[upbeat instrumental music plays]
- Drinking champagne in Champagne.
- [Camille laughs]
[camera shutter clicks]
[chuckles]
[scoffs]
[lounge music playing]
[cheering]
I thought the itinerary said
we were doing The Peninsula tonight?
Well, change of plans.
There's a performer we have to see.
It's kind of the reason we came to Paris.
And now, on our legendary stage,
we have a special guest.
A fallen idol from Shanghai
who has come to Paris
to rise from the ashes.
[splutters] Li, I would love to,
but I… I haven't sung in forever.
I… I've been so busy
with business school...
Oh, my God,
we know you're not in business school.
- And we know that you're a nanny.
- [Shay] Mm-hmm.
And that your parents cut you off.
Uh… why didn't you say anything?
Bitch, why didn't you say anything?
I don't know. I guess
I thought you wouldn't understand.
Mindy, the only thing I don't understand
is why you are in Paris and not singing.
Well, I...
You've been wanting to be a singer
since we were kids.
- Li, I would love to...
- [Li] Good!
Because Shay paid
a ton of money for the stage time.
- What?
- Yeah, you'll thank me later.
Well, um, what song?
You know what song.
No. No. No!
I butchered that on Popstar. I'm not...
Then do it right this time.
- Go!
- Please welcome, Mindy Chen.
[group chanting] Plane! Plane!
Club! Another club! Another club!
Bus! Another club! No sleep! Sing, bitch!
Bonsoir.
- [feedback squeals]
- [Mindy chuckles] Ooh.
- ["Chandelier" playing]
- [gasps]
♪ One, two, three
One, two, three, drink ♪
[mutters] No,
I actually really don't wanna…
- [host speaks indistinctly]
- [Li] You can do it, Mindy!
♪ One, two, three
One, two, three, drink ♪
♪ Throw 'em back till I lose count ♪
- [crowd cheers]
- ♪ I'm gonna swing ♪
♪ From the chandelier ♪
♪ I'm… ♪
Oh, God!
♪ Like, like tomorrow doesn't exist ♪
♪ Like it doesn't exist ♪
♪ I'm, I'm gonna fly ♪
♪ Like a bird through the night ♪
♪ Feel my tears as they dry ♪
♪ I'm, I'm gonna swing ♪
♪ From the chandelier ♪
♪ I'm just holding on for dear life ♪
♪ Won't look down ♪
♪ Won't open my eyes ♪
♪ Keep my glass full until morning light ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm just holding on for tonight ♪
♪ On for tonight ♪
[crowd cheering]
- [applause continues over cell phone]
- [Emily chuckles]
[friends exclaim]
[group] To Mindy!
[cheering]
[Camille shouting indistinctly]
[Camille, in French] …you're ruining
my relationship with Gabriel.
Mom, I'm fed up of you
always trying to control everything!
[Louise] He's crazy to refuse the money.
It's nonsense!
[Mindy's friends cheering on cell phone]
[Mindy, in English] Oh, God!
I wondered where you were hiding.
- [cell phone locks]
- Not hiding, just couldn't sleep.
Ah. Because you heard
everyone fighting in their rooms?
Would you like a coupe?
Okay, maybe I'm hiding.
A little.
I have a motorbike.
Should we run away?
That's always a bad idea.
No? You ran away from home.
Now you live in Paris.
- Not too bad.
- [sighs] I didn't run away.
I moved here for work.
Oh. So they forced you
to come to a country
where you don't speak the language.
That's a bad idea.
[Emily] No, I wanted to come,
but I wasn't running.
I had a nice job, a nice boyfriend,
nice friends.
It was…
- Oh, my God, I ran away.
- [laughs] Yes. It sounds so nice.
It was,
but everything was already laid out.
I mean,
there were no decisions left to make,
even wrong ones.
I always knew what was gonna happen.
And now?
And now I know nothing.
Everything is new
and confusing and,
honestly, kind of scary.
- [both chuckle]
- Yes, but you love it, no?
[chuckles] Oh, slower.
You're supposed to savor it.
[clicks tongue] Okay.
[gentle instrumental music plays]
Let me try again.
I thought that champagne
was supposed to be served in a flute.
Yeah, flutes are a more practical choice.
But coupes are sexier.
They were modeled
after Marie Antoinette's breasts.
They are the ideal size and shape
to deliver pleasure.
["Paris Tropical" playing]
[Emily breathing heavily]
Slower, slower,
you're supposed to savor it.
[both panting]
[rooster crows in distance]
- [yawns]
- [cell phone chimes]
[groans]
[cell phone chimes]
[grunts softly]
[cell phone unlocks]
[cell phone locks]
[groans]
Oh, shit.
[group speaking French]
[Gabriel] Hey!
- Emily!
- [Emily] Ah.
- Bonjour.
- Mwah. Mwah
This is Théo.
Nice to meet you, Emily.
Camille told me
wonderful things about you.
Oh, do you work for the company?
Oh, no, he's, uh,
the brother I talked to you about.
[Emily] Um…
But… But I thought
that I met your brother yesterday at the,
uh, on the tour and at dinner?
Oh, Timothée? He's 17.
[chuckles] But… But…
But he said
that he finished collège, and...
How could a 17-year-old be out of college?
You're thinking of "université."
In France, it's,
how do you say, "junior high."
[scoffs] That is needlessly confusing!
Bonjour, mon américaine.
Mm. Oh.
Sorry for that. I bite too hard.
Oh, my God.
You said you wanted me
to meet your brother. Okay?
And I didn't know he was...
I was drinking a lot of champagne.
[Timothée grunts]
[Camille laughs]
Emily, come with me.
[whispering] Oh, shit.
I didn't know.
[Gérard sighs]
[takes a deep breath]
I need you to be honest with me.
- You and my son...
- I had no idea how young he was.
Camille told me
that she wanted me to meet her brother.
And… And he was such an expert
about champagne.
Stop talking, please.
I don't care about any of that.
I need to know,
is my son a good lover?
I worry for my children's future.
It's a mother's job.
And my little boy...
Oh, my God.
Please tell me this wasn't his first time.
Oh, dear, did it seem that way?
What? No. No, no, no.
He was gentle and… and sweet.
Wait. [chuckles]
I'm sorry, um…
How much detail are you looking for here?
His father
finally passed down something helpful.
[sighs] My husband is a fantastic lover,
but beyond that, he is as useless
as this surplus of grapes.
Thank you, Emily.
I will call you a car
to the train station.
I imagine you wanna run away
from this bomb you exploded.
- [phone dialing]
- Uh, hold on.
I came down here to pitch you Savoir,
and you've dodged me all weekend.
Okay.
- You know about the surplus.
- [Emily] Mm-hmm.
We need to find new buyers
or else pour it all
down the drain. [sighs]
How do we do that?
- [friends cheering on cell phone]
- That's how.
A bottle to sip and a bottle to spray.
You make the same amount
whether or not they drink it, yes?
We could make your brand
the official spray of Paris.
Or anywhere, really.
I can hear my grandmother
rising from her grave to strangle me.
[Emily] Um, you're worried about legacy.
Understood. That's your job.
How about we create
a second label for the spray campaign?
But what to call something so useless?
What about "Champère"?
[chuckles]
I'll consider it.
["Une Evasion" playing]
Maman said
she was really impressed
with your presentation.
Oh, the whole family was impressed.
[Emily groans]
Camille, I'm so embarrassed.
Don't be.
I knew we'd get you
into the family one way or another.
I just didn't know it would be so quick.
I promise,
now that we're working together...
No, Emily, it's really fine.
I can't control who you get into bed with.
- Is this gonna be weird?
- No, we're all adults.
Except for Timothée.
- [laughs]
- Oh, grow up!
But I'm already
far too old for your tastes.
[Emily grunts]
- [engine starts]
- [Camille] Um…
["Viens La" playing]
[theme music playing]