["Afterglow" playing]
♪ We're gonna make it home ♪
- ♪ Before the afterglow ♪
- [young woman panting]
- ♪ We're gonna make it home... ♪
- Run complete.
[automated voice] Well done, Emily.
Five point three miles. Forty-one minutes.
Eighteen seconds faster than yesterday.
- Good effort.
- [exhales]
♪ We're gonna make it home ♪
- [indistinct chatter]
- [gasps] Madeline, you're in Adweek.
What? Where?
Right here, under "Movers and Shakers."
- [Madeline] Ah!
- "Chicago-based Gilbert Group
expands international portfolio
with acquisition of French
luxury marketing company Savoir.
Gilbert Group vet, Madeline Wheeler,
named director of marketing
for Franco firm."
Yes! I am here to prove
that a master's in French
does not go to waste.
- This is going to be amazing for you.
- [Madeline sighs]
I have been dreaming of moving
to Paris forever.
I mean, French men,
they love older women, you know?
Look at their president.
He's young. He's hot.
- He married his schoolteacher.
- [Emily laughs]
Ooh, I just emailed you my thoughts
on the presentation for the new IBS drug.
It's a social initiative
to add meditation to your medication.
If you like it, you can pitch it later.
Uh, you know, for your last hurrah.
- I want you to pitch it.
- Seriously?
Seriously. The client has to start
getting comfortable with you.
I don't want to step on your toes.
You're not. You're stepping into my shoes.
You're ready, okay?
This is an opportunity for both of us.
Come here. Try this.
What is it?
De L'Heure.
It's the latest fragrance
from Maison Lavaux.
[Emily] Mm.
I'll be handling them,
their account in Paris. What do you think?
It's like wearing poetry.
[snaps fingers] I'm gonna use that.
[Emily] Hm.
Oh, that smells really wei...
Does that smell weird to you?
- No, just floral.
- But...
I'm gonna be sick.
Uh... I'm gonna be sick.
- [retching]
- Oh.
[vomit splashes]
- Oh. Uh...
- [Madeline coughing]
[energetic instrumental music plays]
[patrons chatting excitedly]
- Hi, babe!
- [boyfriend] Hey. Oh.
- [Emily] Mwah!
- [patrons cheer]
[Emily squeals]
- Yes!
- What happened?
Bote just smacked a walk-off grand slam,
two outs left in the bottom of the ninth.
- Oh, my God!
- Hell yeah!
Yeah!
Cubs are goin' to the playoffs, baby!
- [Emily squeals]
- [both] Mwah!
- Can we get a couple of beers here?
- [Emily] White wine, actually.
- Anything French, if you have it.
- [server] For sure.
I have some crazy news.
- Madeline's pregnant.
- Madeline?
- [Emily] Mm-hm.
- Like, your boss, Madeline?
- Thought she was too old to get pregnant.
- Well, so did she.
Until she got completely nauseous
sniffing this perfume
she was planning to promote.
She went to the doctor this afternoon.
- Wow. So, who's the dad?
- Oh, well, there are a few candidates.
- She was having a lot of going-away sex.
- Hey. Go, Madeline.
[Emily] Mm-hm. Mm!
But now that she's pregnant, she's decided
she's not gonna take the job in Paris.
So, there goes your promotion?
[Emily] Not exactly.
They still need someone there.
Like, American eyes and ears
to help with the whole transition.
So they asked me
if I would take the job...
for a year.
What? In Paris? [chuckles]
They said that if I did
that they'd guarantee me
senior brand manager when I'm back.
Huh. [sighs]
[mellow instrumental music plays]
So, the apartment there
is already all set up,
and there's a relocation bonus.
And just to explore the idea,
here's a spreadsheet
I made for the next year.
Weeks when you might be able
to come to Paris,
times I can come back to Chicago,
taking into consideration vacation
and sick days.
Wait.
You're serious?
I know it's crazy,
but when will we get a chance like this?
- It'll be an adventure.
- [boyfriend] Unless I missed something,
you don't speak French.
Fake it till you make it. [chuckles]
[sighs]
You look worried.
Oh, I'm not worried.
It's the French who should be worried.
[chuckles]
["Ce soir" playing]
[water splashes]
[brakes squeak]
- [indistinct chatter]
- [birds chirping]
- Uh, Emily Cooper?
- [Emily] Yes.
Hey. I'm Gilles Dufour
from the rental agency.
- Hi. Bonjour.
- Bonjour. [chuckles]
- I've got your keys. Apartment 501.
- ["Summer in Paris" playing]
- Merci.
- Avec plaisir.
♪ I say, "Oui" ♪
♪ You say, "Merci" ♪
- Hi.
- ♪ A s'il vous plaît ♪
- ♪ Goes a long way... ♪
- The building is very old.
- It doesn't have an elevator.
- [panting] Okay.
It's charming. [grunts]
♪ Je ne sais pas ♪
- ♪ Excusez-moi ♪
- [Emily continues panting]
[sighs]
[groans] Is this it?
[panting] It's on the fifth floor.
- This is the fourth floor.
- [Emily] Uh,
I just schlepped up these bags
five flights.
- This is the fifth floor.
- [Gilles sighs]
In France, first the ground floor,
then the first floor,
then the second floor, and so on.
That's weird.
Non, c'est normal.
- [grunts]
- [Emily grunting, sighs]
Et voilà.
Your magnificent chambre de bonne.
Chambre de what now?
Chambre de b... Um, it means,
uh, the room for the housekeeper.
The top two floors were typically reserved
for the servants.
The space is small, but the view...
[bright instrumental music plays]
- [gasps]
- [car honks in distance]
Oh, my God,
I feel like Nicole Kidman in Moulin Rouge!
You've got all of Paris at your feet.
There is a wonderful café just down below.
- A friend of mine is the manager.
- [Emily] Wow.
- So, ça va? It's good?
- [Emily takes a deep breath]
Oui. Oui. Très good.
- Très wonderful. [chuckles]
- Great.
Are you hungry?
Would you like to have a coffee or...?
Oh, actually, I have to get to my office.
Oh. Maybe you want
to have a drink tonight?
I have a boyfriend.
- In Paris?
- [Emily] In Chicago.
- So you don't have a boyfriend in Paris.
- [both chuckle]
- Can I just get my keys, s'il vous plaît?
- [Gilles] Yeah.
Um, my number is on the card
if you need me for anything,
- and in case you change your mind.
- I won't.
[both chuckle]
- Bye-bye, now.
- Yeah.
[birds singing]
[exhales]
- ["Lunatique" playing]
- [camera shutter clicks]
[cell phone chimes]
[door squeaks]
[elevator bell chimes]
Hi. Hello.
Uh, bonjour. I'm Emily Cooper
from the Gilbert Group in Chicago.
You are?
[chuckles] I'm sorry. I don't understand.
Oh.
[purse unzips]
- I'm going to be working in this office.
- [cell phone beeps]
[translator]
Je vais travailler dans ce bureau.
[coworker] Ah.
- [line beeps]
- [in French] The American girl is here.
- [Emily chuckles]
- [coworker sighs]
[footsteps approach]
Bonjour.
I wasn't expecting you until tomorrow.
How was your journey here?
The new apartment and everything?
[in English, chuckling]
You lost me at bonjour.
Oh.
Yeah, I was told the American coming here
spoke French.
Oh, that was Madeline.
Oh, so you're not Madeline.
Uh, I'm Emily. Emily Cooper.
And I am so excited to be here.
Well, that's very unfortunate.
[sighs softly]
- Excuse me?
- That you don't speak French.
It's a problem.
Well, I'm going to take a class, but...
[American accent]
...je parle un peu français already.
Well, perhaps it's better not to try.
- [knocking on door]
- Oh, Paul.
May I introduce Emily,
the American girl
who's come to work with us?
This is Monsieur Brossard,
he's the founder of Savoir.
- Ah. Emily Cooper. Oh.
- [Paul] Hello.
[Emily chuckles]
It is so nice to meet you,
Monsieur Brossard.
It's a pleasure. Welcome to Paris.
So, you've come to teach the French
some American tricks?
I'm sure we have a lot to learn
from each other.
But your experience is not with fashion
- and luxury brands, hm?
- [Emily] True.
Most of my experience
has been in promoting pharmaceuticals
and geriatric care facilities.
In Chicago.
Yes. I mean, oui.
[scoffs]
I was in Chicago once,
- and I ate the deep-dish pizza.
- Ah.
That is our specialty.
We take a lot of pride.
It was, uh, dégueulasse. How you say?
- Disgusting.
- [Paul chuckles]
- Like a quiche made of cement.
- Uh...
Oh, no, you must have gone
to Lou Malnati's.
And the people are so fat.
Why are they all so fat?
Well, perhaps from the disgusting food.
True, we are in the midst
of an obesity epidemic.
In fact,
Merck was one of our biggest clients.
They make a diabetes drug
that we marketed the heck out of.
Sales went up 63 percent.
So you create the disease,
then you treat the disease,
and then you market the treatments
of the disease.
- Well...
- Perhaps stop eating.
- There is no money in that.
- True.
Cigarettes cause diabetes and cancer.
Yes.
[chuckles] Well, smoking is a pleasure.
And without pleasure, who are we?
- German?
- [Paul chuckling]
Exactly right.
[Emily chuckles]
All of the brands we market here,
from perfume to cognac to couture,
- are all to do with beauty and refinement.
- [Emily] Mm-hmm.
Perhaps you have something
to learn from us,
but I'm not sure
if we have much to learn from you.
With all due respect,
I have been sent here for a reason,
so if you wouldn't mind,
I would really like to share
some of my ideas
about your social media strategies.
You mean the Twitter and the Snapchat?
Yes. And the Instagram.
Ah, by all means.
- [upbeat music plays]
- [Paul chuckles softly]
[clicks tongue] First, let me apologize
for speaking English.
I did Rosetta Stone on the plane,
but it hasn't kicked in yet.
- [Paul sighs]
- Oh, Patricia doesn't speak English.
Please continue.
For those of you who haven't met me,
I'm Emily Cooper,
and I'm so excited to be here in Paris.
I'm looking forward to getting to know
each and every one of you
and, likewise, having you get to know me.
Your name, monsieur?
My name is Luc.
Yes, Luc?
Why are you shouting?
[sighs, quietly] Sorry.
[Luc grunts]
Your company works
with some of the biggest brands
in the luxury sector, from Chanel to YSL.
And that makes Savoir, your company,
or, if I may be so bold,
our company, a brand in itself.
But to build a brand,
you must create
meaningful social media engagement.
May I ask who's responsible
for your social media here?
Patricia.
Makes sense.
[inhales sharply] Anyway,
it's not just about
the number of followers.
It's about content, trust,
interest, and engagement.
Excuse me, but the French
are masters of social media.
True.
But Americans invented it,
which is why I hope to become
a valuable member of your team
by adding an American point of view
to your fabulous French clients.
[in French] It's a disaster.
[energetic instrumental music plays]
Paul.
- [Paul] What?
- Who is that girl?
It was one of the terms of the sale.
- They send us one of their people.
- [boss sighs]
- How long do we have to put up with this?
- [sighs] Well, until she decides to leave.
[boss sighs]
[Paul] Quoi?
With me as her boss,
we'll see how long she lasts.
Right, I have to go.
[tense instrumental music plays]
[Emily, in English]
It's amazing, isn't it?
The entire city looks like Ratatouille.
It's beautiful.
So beautiful.
[boyfriend] Ah.
Hey, how was the first day?
Great.
Okay, maybe a few things
got lost in translation.
It took them a minute
to realize I was me and not Madeline,
but I really feel like
I could be a big asset here.
Hey, look what I got.
[Emily gasps] Thank God!
You're gonna love Paris.
I don't want to spend another day
in the most romantic city in the world
- without you.
- I'll be there soon, okay?
Hurry. I miss you already here.
- Mwah.
Bye.
- [cell phone chimes, locks]
- [calming instrumental music plays]
[indistinct chatter in distance]
[water in fountain flowing]
- [keypad beeps]
- [door buzzes]
- [lock clicks]
- [Emily grunts]
- [door slams heavily]
- [Emily] Ugh, seriously?
[sighs]
God.
[exhales]
[softly] Okay.
[sighs]
Come on.
[grunts] This can't be happening. Come on.
[gasps]
Sorry, I...
I thought this was my apartment.
Fifth floor?
This is the fourth floor.
Fifth floor.
Right.
[clicks tongue] Merci.
[chuckles] Uh, I'm Emily.
Emily Cooper, your... your new neighbor.
American?
Oui. From Chicago.
Gabriel, French, from Normandy.
[gasps softly] Oh, I know that beach.
Saving Private Ryan.
- What?
- D-Day?
- Uh, anyway.
- [both chuckle]
Hm. Uh...
Nice to meet you, neighbor.
Enchanté.
Bonsoir. [giggles]
["Real Good Time" playing]
♪ Take your seat here, baby ♪
♪ You know you can have
A really good time... ♪
[in French] Good morning, miss.
Uh... Ah.
[slowly] Une pain au chocolat.
Un! Pas "une". Un pain au chocolat.
Ça sera tout?
Un euro quarante.
[coins clatter]
Eh ben, on n'est pas rendu.
♪ Don't turn away, don't turn away... ♪
Merci. Have un bonne journée.
Une! Pas "un". Une bonne journée!
♪ Take your seat here, baby ♪
♪ You know you can have
A really good time ♪
- ♪ Get back to the beat... ♪
- [in English] Oh, my God.
- ♪ We ain't got no hope ♪
- Oh, my God.
♪ Do you feel on track? ♪
♪ I see you in the darkness, baby ♪
- ♪ Surrounded by the moonlight, baby ♪
- Mm. Oh, my God.
♪ Baby, so obsessed
Lost in your head jest ♪
- ♪ Oh, come on ♪
- ♪ Take your seat here, baby ♪
♪ You know you can have ♪
- ♪ A really good time... ♪
- [keypad beeping, tone plays]
♪ A good time ♪
♪ Good, good, good, a good time ♪
♪ Good time ♪
Sylvie, it's Emily.
Um, are we closed today,
or is there a national holiday
I don't know about?
'Cause I've been hanging around here
for two hours and...
- [brakes squeak]
- What are you doing?
I've been here since 8:30.
Pourquoi? We open at 10:30.
[Emily sighs]
- Bonjour!
- [worker] Bonjour!
- [indistinct chatter]
- [phones ringing]
- [cell phone chimes softly]
- [energetic music playing]
Hi Patricia. I'm wondering
if I can share some ideas I have
about how we might enhance
our social media engagement.
I'm so excited about the potential here.
Je comprends pas.
Oh.
[cell phone chimes]
[translator, in French] Patricia,
I'd like to share some ideas
about how we might enhance
our social media engagement.
Non, non.
[breathing shakily]
- [in English] Do you wanna have lunch?
- No, I'll have a cigarette.
[light instrumental music plays]
Uh, I have a... bad stomach.
[clicks tongue]
I have a previous engagement.
[indistinct chatter]
- [children laughing]
- [Emily] Ow.
- Excusez-moi! [sighs]
- [woman] Laurent! Sybil!
[in Mandarin] Apologize to the lady!
[in French] I'm sorry.
Can I buy you another one?
[in English] Sorry, I don't speak French.
- Ah, American?
- [Emily] Yes.
But did you think that I was French?
Honestly, no. I was being polite.
You... look American.
Are you from Indiana?
- Chicago.
- [woman] Oh. I was close.
I went to junior high in Indianapolis.
- Oh, cool. No way! Why?
- [woman] Mm-hm.
Ah, long story.
Very boring. [chuckles]
The story and... Indianapolis.
But the girls, they look like you. Nice.
- Are those your children?
- [woman] No, I'm their nanny.
[in Mandarin] Laurent!
Stay where I can see you.
[sighs, in English]
I'm teaching them Mandarin.
How long have you been here?
Uh... almost a year. From Shanghai.
But my mother's from Korea.
Another long, boring story.
- Do you love it?
- Uh, yes, of course I love Paris.
- And the food is so delicious.
- [Emily] Mm.
The fashion, so chic.
The lights, so magical.
But the people... so mean.
- I mean, they can't all be mean.
- Oh, yes, they can.
Chinese people are mean behind your back.
- French people, mean to your face.
- [Emily] Mm.
- But you're on vacation here, so...
- Oh, no. Actually, I work here.
I have a job with a French marketing firm.
- [woman] Seriously?
- Yeah.
Well, so you know.
Well, I just started.
Oh.
- Do you have any friends in Paris?
- Uh, no.
Um... but my boyfriend's coming next week
to visit, so...
Are you lonely?
No... uh...
- Sometimes. [chuckles softly]
- [clicks tongue] Give me your phone.
- [Emily] Uh...
- Okay, so here's my number.
[clicks tongue] If you're lonely,
you text me, we have dinner. I'm Mindy.
Emily.
Nice to meet you.
- French people do this.
- Oh.
- Mwah. Mwah.
- [chuckles]
Sybil! Laurent!
- [in French] You're not my mother!
- I want an ice cream!
- [Mindy] Ugh.
- [camera shutter clicks]
- ["Aujourd'hui" playing]
- [phone locks]
[coworkers chatting indistinctly]
Bonjour, la plouc!
- [Paul chuckles]
- Bonjour, la... [mutters]
Bonjour!
[in English] What is "la plouc"?
Oh, um...
It's a little term of endearment,
like, um, mon petit chou, la plouc...
Nice. [chuckles]
Don't worry about it.
[calming lounge music plays]
[Emily] Hm.
[translator on laptop] La plouc.
- [laptop chimes]
- [translator] The hick.
[tense rock music plays]
[Emily sighs]
[indistinct chatter]
[man] Bonjour.
Vous attendez quelqu'un?
Sorry, I don't speak French.
Oh, I'm sorry. Um, is the seat free?
- Uh, yes... yes, please. Yeah.
- [man] Yeah? Okay.
Thank you.
["Ce sera bien" playing]
[cell phone messages chiming]
[sighs]
[camera shutter clicks]
[cell phone chimes]
[scooter motor whirring]
- Ah, Emily. Ah...
- Luc! Hi.
I... I just want to say
I am sorry for this.
I... I do not agree
to calling you "la plouc."
And... I can, uh...?
Y-Yes.
[Luc takes a deep breath, clears throat]
You know...[inhales]
Uh...?
- Mm, I'm good.
- Ah? Okay.
You know,
we are all a little afraid of you.
What?
- Afraid of me?
- Mm-hm.
How?
Y-Your ideas.
They are more new. Maybe they are better.
- [chuckles]
- Now you are here, and,
uh, maybe we feel we have to work harder,
make more money.
It's a balance.
Ex... Exactly. A balance.
And I think
the Americans have the wrong balance.
You live to work.
We work to live.
Yes, it's good to make money,
but what you say is success,
I say is punishment.
But... I enjoy work...
and accomplishment. It...
It makes me happy.
Work makes you happy?
Yes. I mean,
it's... it's... it's why I'm here.
For work.
And look where it's brought me.
To this beautiful city.
Maybe you don't know what it is
to be happy. [chuckles]
Or maybe that's a little arrogant.
Ah. You came to Paris
and you don't speak French.
That is arrogant.
[Emily] Hm.
More ignorant than arrogant. [sighs]
Well, let's call it
the arrogance of ignorance.
I'm sorry if I offended you.
Oh, I'm not offended by anything.
[Emily chuckles softly]
I see you tomorrow, Emily. Mm-hm?
Ah. Don't be early.
Hm? [chuckles softly]
- ["Christine" playing]
- [scooter motor whirs]
[cell phone chimes]
- [cell phone vibrating]
- [Emily grunts]
- [sighs]
- [vibrating continues]
- [Emily grunts]
- [cell phone chimes]
Oh, hey. There you are.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, I just finally got home from work.
It's 3:00 a.m. here.
Oh... whoops.
It's 7:00 p.m. here.
Uh...
What are you doin'?
Sleeping.
I miss you so much.
And I miss you too.
- Hello? Doug?
- [rustling on phone]
Oh!
Get naked with me.
Are we having cybersex?
Well... if you insist.
- Hold on. [yawns]
- [rustling on phone]
[sighs] You better not be recording this.
No. Never.
Oh, wow. You are so beautiful.
Mm, thanks.
Uh, so, um... [exhales]
...you do you, and...
I'll do me.
[sighs] M'kay.
[slow-paced music playing]
[breathing heavily] That feel good?
- [exhales] Yeah.
- How good?
- [pants, moans]
- Oh, you're so sexy.
I feel...
Oh, my God.
- [Emily panting]
- [moans]
I feel overwhelmed. I...
[breathing heavily]
I feel like myself but not myself, and...
it's all so crazy.
It's crazy, but it's... it's nice, and...
it's kinda sexy, but...
And I...
Doug?
[distorted] Oh, wow.
- Doug? Babe?
- [distorted moaning]
[static crackles]
Doug?
Oh.
[sighs]
["La paix" playing]
[Emily groans softly]
Ah.
There you are.
[softly] Okay.
[exhales] Okay.
- [electricity crackles]
- [screams]
- [electricity thrums, pops]
- [Emily sighs]
[dogs barking in distance]
Oh...
my God.
["La paix" continues playing]
[theme music playing]