[English subtitles are available]
[Moonlight]
[Episode 23]
[Yuan Yue Publishing House]
Xiao Niao.
You're taking all the drafts home?
You're still here?
It is Valentine's Day.
I'm going out with my boyfriend.
Today is Valentine's Day?
Yeah.
It's okay, Chu Li.
You can celebrate too
when you have a boyfriend.
Yes, dear?
You need to work overtime?
Carry on with your work then.
You're still here?
Mr Zhou Chuan.
You just got off work too?
Where are you going?
Can you give me a ride?
We're heading to different directions.
You sure are hilarious.
I haven't said where I'm going.
I know I'm hilarious.
Get in already.
I knew you were joking.
I never said you can get in.
Are you coming or not?
Sure.
Thanks, Mr Zhou Chuan.
The back seat? Really?
Do you think I'm your driver?
We happen to head to the
same direction when going home.
That's why
he will
give me a ride.
Are you done?
Time is flying.
Okay.
Bye, Xiao Niao.
Well,
it's fine to have Chu Li sit beside me.
My girlfriend likes her as an editor.
Bye.
[Yun Fei]
Bai Zhi.
Regarding the fans
the other day,
I'm really sorry.
It's my bad for being careless
when it comes to publication.
It's not your problem.
We finally get to
work with Director Lu Fang.
Cherish it.
But don't rush it too.
Today is Valentine's Day.
What's your plan?
Finishing my work.
You should go home too.
Do what you need to do.
Okay.
Why are you smiling?
Don't you find it romantic?
Rain on the Valentine's Day.
Didn't you listen to the weather forecast?
It's supposed to rain at this hour.
It will stop later.
Besides,
I don't care
about a festival
that only favours the capitalists.
But this is
our first Valentine's Day.
Yes, the first Valentine's Day.
And Jiang Yu Cheng
asked you out for dinner.
He must have an evil intention.
What did you say?
He asked you out too, didn't he?
What is it?
Are you in a bad mood?
And why did you bring up
the girlfriend topic
all of a sudden just now?
Forget it. Never mind.
By the way, I talked to Yu Yao today.
I'm almost done with my research.
Starting tomorrow,
I won't be working at Yuan Yue anymore.
Mr Zhou.
Are you really not going to
do anything on Valentine's Day?
Tell me what you want. I'll buy it.
Forget it.
Cheers.
Don't drink too much wine.
I haven't even started.
Chu Li.
I have to thank you this time.
I heard that you fell sick
and hurt your back
because of me.
My apologies.
Please don't mind
about the contract termination.
It's okay. It's my honour to help you
get your book published.
All my efforts are worth it.
Hi. Today is Valentine's Day.
We are holding an event.
If a man confesses to the lady he likes,
they will be given a bouquet of flower.
Do you need it?
Ask him.
Me?
Never mind.
I don't celebrate Valentine's Day.
Sorry for disturbing.
Enjoy your meal.
I'll answer the call outside.
Don't tell me
you prepared nothing for Valentine's Day.
Do I need to tell you?
No.
But you need to let Chu Li know.
This is your
first Valentine's Day, after all.
You're acting like you don't care at all.
I want to let her feel disappointed
before showing my surprising gift.
You know nothing
for someone who had a girlfriend.
Fine.
You're getting tricky.
Hello, Chief Editor Yu.
The Disappearing Amusement Park
is of high importance to the higher-ups.
They increased the marketing fee
and have promised to publish it
in one month.
Is that true? Awesome.
I'm having dinner with Mr Jiang.
I'll tell him now.
You're having dinner with him?
Isn't it Valentine's Day?
You two...
Nothing like that.
Mr Jiang wanted to buy me a meal
to thank me. That's all.
Mr Zhou Chuan is here too.
Calm down.
Many writers and editors
fell in love too in the past.
[If you're together,]
I will give you my sincere blessing.
But doesn't Mr Zhou Chuan
have a girlfriend? If I'm not mistaken.
I think so.
He's eating with you guys
[instead of being with his girlfriend?]
[What a funny guy.]
So, enjoy your dinner.
I'm just calling to let you know.
Okay. Bye.
Mr Jiang.
I have a good news for you.
Chief Editor Yu said
the higher-ups think really highly
of The Disappearing Amusement Park
that they added
a huge sum of marketing fee,
and promised to
publish the book in a month.
That means it won't clash
with Huang Quan Inn's publication.
Too bad.
I thought of competing with you.
Chief Editor Yu also asked
if you want
a signing event on the launching day.
Signing event?
Okay.
When the speech on the film was cancelled,
it was a pity for many
fans who were at the event.
Thank you, Mr Jiang.
I will see to it that
your book is published.
Can we not talk about work
and just enjoy our meal?
By the way, Chu Li,
I heard you went to see Director Lu Fang
on the aeroplane.
You even talked through the entire flight.
It was so close.
When I got to Linzhou,
he already passed the custom.
Fortunately, I booked a ticket
of the same flight in advance.
That's how we stopped him on the plane.
"We"?
Me. Alone.
Luckily, it was a domestic flight.
I couldn't have done anything
if he was going abroad.
Chu Li.
Does Gu Bai Zhi have anything to do
with my cooperation with Director Lu?
Why did you ask that?
Just tell me.
Yes or no.
Yes.
Like what you thought.
The only person who can solve this
or would think of this idea,
and realise it
is Director Gu.
I heard from Mr Zhou Chuan
that tried to have Mr Jiang
collaborate with Director Li Yu,
but it failed.
The only director
who is as famous as him
in the country is Director Lu Fang.
So, is it possible
to help me contact him?
If The Disappearing Amusement Park
can be made into film,
the book can definitely be published.
Why should I help you?
We can persuade Director Lu Fang
to make a series of the film.
By then, you can also sell
the copyright of Yun Fei's work.
These two writers have similar style.
Yun Fei's can somehow
get some popularity back.
I thought you'd play the emotion card
and say Jiang Yu Cheng missed the speech
because of me.
That's the truth, isn't it?
But I'm sure
that even if I don't bring it up,
you'd still try to help him.
You could've just left it to me.
No way.
I'm in charge of him.
I will spare no effort to help him.
And I don't know about you.
So I must
get things under my control.
Let's work together.
Really?
But on one condition.
What's that?
Don't tell Jiang Yu Cheng.
Not only did Director Gu help me,
she even found out
about Director Lu Fang's schedule,
and quickly drove me to Linzhou.
When the tire blew out,
she fixed it on the road.
Her only condition
is not to let you know about it.
It suddenly occurred to me
that I have something on.
You guys enjoy.
Look at you. You must've caught a cold.
Drink warm water
the first thing you get home.
[Drink warm water?
An insensitive man, indeed.]
Put my interest first next time.
Stop working so hard for Jiang Yu Cheng.
I'm in charge of him.
Who else would fight for him if not me?
By the way,
did Gu Bai Zhi say something
I can't listen to the other day?
As she refused to let me enter.
She only gave me a reminder.
I'll get going.
The relationship
between an editor and a writer
isn't really romantic.
It will be harder for you
when the guy is Zhou Chuan.
"It will be harder when the guy
is Zhou Chuan?"
What did she mean?
Is it because she and Jiang Yu Cheng
didn't end well
that she tried to poison your mind?
She's just jealous.
Don't discuss her
experience in the future.
Mr Zhou, I think you should
reflect on yourself instead.
Look.
You don't even bother
to prepare anything on Valentine's Day.
I think Director Gu is right.
Even an outsider
can easily get between us,
is it?
Do you like me or not?
It's a secret.
Say again?
[What do you think?]
[Of course I do.]
[Jiang Yu Cheng]
Hello.
Now?
I'll be right there.
How is your wound? Better?
It has recovered long ago.
I heard from Chu Li that you
even know how to change tyre.
When did you learn that?
So you've learned that.
Thank you.
Well, you didn't even hesitate
to come and help me
once Yun Fei called you.
Jiang Yu Cheng.
Whatever happened,
we once matter a great deal
in each other's lives.
Let's not say thank you.
♫ I've been giddy from drifting
in a sea of people ♫
♫ Unwilling to admit my anticipation
of getting submitted to gentleness ♫
Sir.
Would you like to buy her a rose?
Never mind, girl.
It's okay. How much is it?
-Twenty yuan.
-Okay.
♫ I want to be led by you,
albeit a meager freedom ♫
Here you go.
Thank you.
♫ The Hand of the Creator
has finally heard the call for help ♫
I remember
our first Valentine's Day.
We were silly back then.
♫ I'm drifting in a sea of people.
And will frequently look back ♫
All I care about was working
with books in the bookstore,
and prepared nothing.
I promised
♫ Scared to reach out my hand
that no one will save me ♫
to buy you a rose.
And here it is.
♫ How rich can concrete skyscrapers be ♫
Actually, I didn't really care
about receiving roses
or celebrating Valentine's Day back then.
But, thanks.
♫ You are a rare shining oasis ♫
Didn't you just say
not to say thank you to each other.
♫ Exactly what I want ♫
Go back to your room now.
Don't infect me with it.
I need to burn the midnight oil
to do word coding.
If the instalment is affected,
you may lose your position as an editor.
Got it.
I'll isolate myself upstairs right away.
[The Disappearing Mr Fox]
[It's Valentine's Day.]
[Instead of giving me a present,]
[my boyfriend is running away
from me as I've caught a cold.]
[What should I do?]
[The Disappearing Mr Fox]
[Maybe he's secretly
preparing a surprise.]
More like a shock.
[The Navy Hired by the Monkey]
[More like a shock.]
I don't get it.
Why are girls obsessed
about such boring festivals?
[Selected Stories of Natsume Soseki]
Guess I'll give her
this original edition
as a Valentine's gift.
[Stinky Monkey, after years of fighting,
you can have my favourite book. Mr Fox]
What's going on?
A blackout?
Management.
What's with the power cut?
The circuit breaker tripped? Where is it?
How would I know?
Could you send someone here?
Twenty minutes?
Fine. Hurry up.
The circuit breaker tripped. Stay still.
Don't blame me if something happens.
I'll be right back.
Where are you going?
Don't mind me. Stay where you are.
He actually left
his sick girlfriend alone
in the dark house.
Hi, I need cold medicine.
The medicine we eat if we catch a cold.
Okay.
This one will do.
Drink with warm water.
You'll be fine with some warm water.
I'll have this one.
Okay.
The power panel is right behind the porch.
It can be fixed easily.
Er Gou, why aren't you sleeping yet?
Er Gou.
Isn't this pyjamas my present to...
[Stinky Monkey, after years of fighting,
you can have my favourite book. Mr Fox]
The power is back on already?
The circuit breaker tripped.
But I fixed it.
You're sick. Just stay in your room.
Why come downstairs?
Here.
Take the medicine.
Mr Zhou.
I found something interesting.
This pyjamas.
It was Mr Fox's birthday gift from me.
And the Natsume Soseki's book.
Why is Mr Fox's signature here?
Can you explain?
What's going on?
Why did you enter my study room again?
Is that the only thing
you have to say to me?
[The Navy Hired by the Monkey]
[Where are you? I want the truth.]
[The Disappearing Mr Fox]
[In front of you.]
When did you find out that I'm Monkey?
A few days before
the Book of Luo He God's signing event.
It was half a year ago.
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't see the need,
-so...
-You didn't see the need?
[Added to Blocked list]
You blocked me?
Aren't you childish?
You might as well block my real account.
I don't want to talk to you.
Where are you going?
I have no idea.
But I'm not talking to a liar now.
Does it matter if I'm Mr Fox?
Does it not?
Don't you know
I've always regarded Mr Fox
as my best friend?
You've been using this identity
to spy on my life,
thoughts and even feelings.
What did you say when I asked
if you're Mr Fox?
Yes, I denied it.
That's because I...
Because you never wanted to tell me.
It must be fun
fooling me with two accounts.
So you never planned to stop.
Or maybe in your mind,
an insignificant editor like me
doesn't deserve to have
a popular writer like you
to be my internet friend?
Why must you
make it so complicated? This...
That should be my line.
All this while,
you can't stop making fun of me.
Let me tell you.
I won't continue
such a childish game.
Let's stop it here. Let's break up.
Break up, you say?
Who would put himself
on the line for just a game?
Put on the line?
I'm the one who was kept in the dark.
Yet you said you suffered the losses?
Ridiculous.
I do
feel like I am a monkey
being fooled now.
He lied to me all this time.
Am I a fool to him?
Hello, Jiang Yu Cheng.
You got it right again, jinx.
This is bad.
Er Gou.
After I'm out of here,
don't forget to eat.
Don't be like someone.
She went to work already?
She's trying to avoid me again.
Chu Li.
Why are you spacing out?
Ah Xiang.
Can I
stay at your place for a day or two?
What happened?
Did your new landlord kick you out?
That's not the case.
The Disappearing Amusement Park
is going to launch earlier, isn't it?
My workload suddenly becomes heavier.
Your house is near the printing factory.
So, it's more convenient.
Sure.
Just move in.
Really?
I'm ready.
No problem.
Thank you.
You called me in the middle of the night
just because
she found out you're Mr Fox
and you don't know what to do about it?
Don't gloat over that.
You still
don't stand a chance.
I'm already over her.
I regard her as my sister now.
If I were her,
given how my boyfriend
neglected our first Valentine's Day,
and lied to me,
I would certainly
break up with you.
Shut up.
Now that makes me furious.
How could she say "break up" so easily?
Who am I to her?
Are you sure you want me to shut up?
Fine. I thought you asked me out
to give you advice.
Say it already.
Firstly, you must apologise.
Then,
be it she's angry about
you denying to be Mr Fox,
or not preparing for Valentine's Day,
when she said she wants a break up,
that means she feels insecure.
Simply put,
she is unconfident
about your relationship.
Unconfident?
I never said no to her.
I even did things I wouldn't do
in the past.
Men and women
are totally different.
Sometimes, we think
that we've done everything,
and that living harmoniously together
is the promise we gave.
But diamond rings, flowers,
and being romantically ceremonious
mean more to girls.
It
might be a white lie to you.
But to her,
if you would lie on a small matter,
then you might also
lie about important things.
She may think that you've never wanted
to spend the rest of your life with her.
That's not right.
She's my chosen one.
Had you told Chu Li earlier,
things would have been fine.
What should I do now?
It's easy
to ask for her forgiveness.
When you see her next time,
apologise first.
Then, hold her in your arms.
And kiss her.
Then say it out loud
that you like her,
you love her,
and that she's fated to be yours.
Is such pretension and
exaggeration necessary?
Prepare to get dumped then.
Not really.
Maybe to Chu Li,
she's not dumping you.
It could be
simply wonderful moments
that didn't end well.
Look at you.
Despising me for falling in love.
Annoying.
Same to you,
you highly
ignorant guy.
What have Chu Li done wrong?
Ah Xiang.
If... I mean, if.
If you found out that the person you like
is actually your
long time internet friend,
who has been keeping the truth from you
even after learning it
a long time ago,
and he created two accounts to fool you,
not planning
to tell you the truth.
What would you do then?
Is it about your friend?
Chu Li.
I think that guy has gone too far.
Right?
This is irritating,
isn't it?
That was my first ever Valentine's Day.
Not only did I receive any present,
I even found out that he is a liar.
This is too much for me to take.
You finally admit
that you are the friend.
Did you realise that long ago?
Well, not exposing someone is a virtue.
You won't be mad at me, will you?
Of course not.
You kept quiet
so that I won't feel awkward.
It's different from that heartless guy.
Don't be mad, Chu Li.
Ignore him.
Let's go home.
Exactly what I thought.
Where is she?
Why isn't she home yet?
How come her luggage isn't here?
[Where are you?]
[Zhou Chuan]
[Little Monkey]
[Ah Xiang's place.]
[I'm staying here for now.]
[You won't even feed Er Gou?]
[What does your
conscience say about that?]
[Running away from home just like that.]
[Aren't you incredible?]
[So you're rich now?]
Okay.
[Zhou Chuan]
[Not Drama King, it's Saviour: Okay]
What... What's wrong?
Did that guy say something?
Nothing. Don't bring him up.
I plan
to buy a cheap spring bed
and stay longer here.
Is that okay?
Sure.
Stay as long as you like.
This is really tasty.
I want to buy ten more.
Which flavour would you like?
I love the braised meat one.
Someone
irresponsibly broke
my 28-year-long
unrestrained lifestyle,
and made me getting used to
eating on proper time.
But now?
All of a sudden,
I no longer have meals ready on time.
Wouldn't you
feel upset?
You at least have your canned food.
But me?
I have nothing to eat.
[Zhou Chuan: Where are you? Little Monkey:
Ah Xiang's place for now. Zhou Chuan: Okay.]
It's been a week.
She doesn't even bother to
urge me to deliver my work.
Is she really not coming back?
Who's that?
Hi.
I'm here to clean the house.
Did you make a mistake?
Excuse me.
Hello, Jiang Yu Cheng.
Hello.
Chu Li isn't home.
Isn't it time to clean your house?
I ordered a cleaner for you.
She should have arrived.
Mind your own business.
Thanks.
Hi.
I'm a cleaner.
Did you order a three-hour
cleaning service?
Where should I work on?
Come on in.
Okay.
So,
do as you see fit.
Okay.
No, Jiang Yu Cheng.
How do you know Chu Li isn't at my house?
I even know
she's staying at Ah Xiang's place.
How could you only reply an "okay"?
I'm speechless.
I spent hours
explaining to you the mindset of a woman.
Did you keep it in mind?
Hold on.
You haven't told me
how did you know Chu Li isn't at my house?
Are you two together?
We're checking on the
book cover at the printing factory.
[I'll try to get you]
[Ah Xiang's address.]
[Don't let the chance slip.]
Remember, no matter what,
apologise first.
Oka...
Stop nagging. I'm hanging up. Bye.
I can drive you home.
Never mind.
Ah Xiang's place is just
two train stations away.
It's convenient.
No problem.
Since it's near,
I can get you home very quickly.
Then, thanks, Mr Jiang.
I should be thanking you.
It's been a while
since I saw my own new book cover
that I thought I won't
get to publish books anymore.
Don't say that.
Being able to
publish your book
still seems unrealistic to me even today.
When I saw the book cover,
I got so emotional that
I couldn't sleep for nights.
I guess when I see the real book,
I will cry out of excitement.
But I think there's another reason
why you couldn't sleep.
No, there isn't.
Let's go.
Give me Ah Xiang's address.
Come on, Er Gou.
Go, Er Gou.
Why are you here, Er Gou?
What a coincidence.
You talk. I'll get going.
Thank you, Mr Jiang.
Why are you here?
I'm walking my dog.
You sure have been walking far.
Carry on. I'm leaving.
Do you really hate to see me that much?
Why do you pull a long
face when you see me,
and keep smiling when
you see Jiang Yu Cheng?
He doesn't lie to me.
Nor did he fool me
with different accounts.
And he didn't live in a house with you,
or cook and walk the dog with you.
Fine. I don't want to talk to you.
What do you mean by "fine"?
Like, let's break up?
What am I to you?
A writer.
An internet friend.
A boyfriend.
Or neighbour?
I don't even know.
Let me ask you.
If I hadn't found it out,
when would you tell me the truth?
Must you
know everything
about your internet friend?
So you don't think you did anything wrong.
What's the point of coming to see me?
I'm just taking Er Gou here to ask
when will you come home?
You've stayed too long here.
It's time to come home.
Er Gou and I have lost weight.
It's not my business.
I'm not your maid.
Chu Li.
You're back from the printing factory?
Hi, Mr Zhou Chuan.
Er Gou is here too?
I...
Did I disturb you?
No, we're done.
Mr Zhou Chuan was going to leave.
Yes.
I can't deliver my new
outline on time anyway.
I'm just telling you. Bye.
-Let's go.
-Bye, Mr Zhou Chuan.
You saw that, didn't you?
She wanted to draw the line with me.
It's only been one week.
Where has her manners gone?
I should've recorded that
and show it to her.
That is too much.
Also...
Look at me.
What's the use of a leash?
Why didn't you hold me back?
I've actually decided to...
I've already decided to apologise first.
Is that your sister?
It's you?
Where's Chu Li?
You screwed up?
Didn't I say
to apologise first?
Swallow your pride.
Why won't you learn?
You're one to talk.
Why does she always smile
so happily when she sees you,
and pull a long face when she sees me?
When I think about it,
I can't help but get mad.
Hey.
What a jealous guy.
Seriously.
Can't you stop being jealous?
Listen.
I
am the writer Chu Li is working with.
Of course she will be polite to me.
Why would she treat you the same way?
If she does,
then you should really be mad.
Think about that.
What should I do now?
I actually planned to have a meal here
if Chu Li is in.
Seems like I'd better leave.
I'll place a delivery order.
Pick what you want.
Such kindness.
What do you want?
Update me on what Chu Li is doing anytime.
Since she's always nice to you.
I want the most pricey
Buddha's Temptation.
1,988 yuan per portion.
That expensive?
What is added to it?
Just order it.
Two portions?
One, for yourself.
I'm not hungry.