(Gwangju Station)
The police are investigating
an unidentified skeleton...
found at a construction site
in Gwangju this morning.
The police have sent the skeleton...
to the National Forensic Service...
for DNA analysis
in order to identify the victim.
Those in the political circles
are saying...
the skeleton may belong...
to one of the victims
of the Gwangju Uprising...
and that the blood sample may need
to be compared with the families...
of those who disappeared
during the Gwangju Uprising.
Who's he? Another relative
of a missing person?
No. He's an informant.
- An informant?
- Yes.
(Video Survey Room A)
Father.
Why are you out here
instead of coming inside?
I didn't even know you were coming.
I'm fine.
You're not hurt, are you?
No. Shall I go and get my bag?
No, no.
You wait here a little longer.
I'll go get your sister.
Can't I come with you?
It's dangerous outside.
Stay here and don't go anywhere.
I won't be too long, okay?
Aren't you Jung Tae's mother?
Why aren't you coming inside?
Would you mind
getting Jung Tae for me?
Okay.
- See you soon, Father.
- Sure.
Go on.
(Episode 11, Mudeung Stadium)
If he can't even introduce you
to them,
how can you trust him?
You're going to regret this.
Come with me to Naju.
Don't say that.
You don't understand.
Ms. Kim!
Dr. Yoo and Mr. Hwang...
They were in a hit-and-run.
(Emergency Room)
(Gwangju)
Where's the other one?
Is he on his way?
There was only one patient.
What are you talking about?
The two left together.
There's another person.
But there was only one person there!
Hurry.
Dr. Yoo.
Dr. Yoo. Are you all right?
Are you awake?
Myeong Hee.
Dr. Yoo. Hee Tae.
What happened to him?
He wasn't at the site.
The punks who hit us took him.
They took him?
They drove right into our car,
then took Hee Tae who had fainted.
They loaded him
into their car and left.
(How to Use)
Myeong Hee.
Here you are.
I thought you'd left with Hee Tae...
Soo Ryeon.
Hee Tae...
What about him?
Myeong Hee, what happened? Tell me.
Myeong Hee.
Are you awake?
I know I'm not one to talk,
but you, Father...
You're quite something yourself.
(The Lord will keep your going out
and your coming in, )
(from this time forth,
and forevermore.)
Leave for Seoul in 10 minutes.
There are no buses or trains.
You'll go by car.
Treatment...
can wait until you're in Seoul.
Where's Lee Soo Ryeon?
I don't know.
Then we'll say
she disappeared in Seoul...
and her whereabouts are unknown.
What are you trying to do?
You were never in Gwangju.
You can brainwash me all you like,
but that won't change the fact
that I was in Gwangju.
Then I can destroy all evidence
that you were here.
For example...
That brat who's at the hospital.
The doctors, nurses,
and patients there...
So many people saw me.
Will you blow up the hospital
or something?
That's not a bad idea.
I can wipe out the building...
and blame it on the spies.
Why? Do you not like that?
Then how about we say...
we killed the spies
that infiltrated the hospital?
I must have become
your Achilles' heel.
This is when
you should be your busiest,
and you're trying so hard
to erase my existence.
My being in Gwangju...
seems to be a huge threat to you.
Am I wrong?
Let me go.
If you let me go,
not only will I leave Gwangju,
but I'll disappear from your life
for good.
Just as I expected.
You're very smart,
but you're bad at reading
someone's mind.
Once you think you know
your opponent's moves and get cocky,
it's practically the same
as exposing your next move.
You've lost.
Just stay here
until the situation comes to an end.
Myeong Hee.
I requested the search team...
to look for him extra carefully.
Doesn't the search team...
only look for dead people?
What are you talking about? No way.
They're even finding fugitives
that are on the run.
I'm sure he was dragged away
after being hit by the car.
His father is probably behind it.
If Hwang Ki Nam is really behind it,
he probably wasn't taken
to Defense Security Command.
So you should calm down...
There's nothing I can do.
He probably bled a lot.
He might be dying somewhere
right this moment.
But there's nothing I can do.
Myeong Hee.
Pull yourself together.
Why isn't there anything you can do?
You need to wait for Hwang Hee Tae.
You just...
want me to wait like this?
I'm certain Hwang Hee Tae
will come back.
So until then,
you must stay strong. Okay?
Hee Tae.
You don't have to leave us
on purpose.
I'll just drop by
the hospital nearby.
I have nothing to say to my father.
Can you not go and just stay here?
I'll be right back, so wait for me.
Myeong Hee.
Kim Myeong Hee.
Come with me now.
We must go before it's too late.
Myeong Soo and your mother
are waiting for you too...
I'm headed to the hospital.
What are you talking about?
Why the hospital?
Why would you go back there?
He said he'd come back
to the hospital.
I'll wait for him there.
You just take Myeong Soo and leave.
What are you talking about?
What kind of father in this world...
would leave his daughter
in this kind of dangerous place?
I can't leave him behind either.
Oh, goodness.
Oh, dear. My gosh, what happened?
My poor baby.
My poor baby, what happened to you?
My goodness.
Oh, dear.
My poor baby. I can't believe it.
Soo Chan has arrived safely
thanks to you.
We're indebted to you yet again.
Thank you so much, Mr. Hwang.
No need to thank me.
Let's each take care
of our own children from now on.
Yes. I promise something like this
will never happen again.
We were unfortunate this time...
I'm not talking about your son,
but your daughter.
Sorry?
Soo Ryeon is in Seoul...
She's in Gwangju right now.
I've found my son
and he's with me now.
So you should look carefully
for your daughter as well.
- Let's go!
- Yes, sir!
As of this moment,
Operation Choongjung...
will change its focus from
suppression to total lockdown.
Barricade all roads
leading out of Gwangju,
in order to stop the rebels
from escaping.
Any rebel that disobeys orders
is to be shot immediately.
They really had...
the eyes of a hunting dog
that even kills humans.
- What?
- You know...
those soldiers from the other unit
that passed by.
I don't know
if it's because of my insecurity,
but they really seemed like
they actually killed people.
Will we be able to go back there?
Will we be able to...
return to Gwangju?
Hello, ma'am.
You must be working really hard.
Soo Chan.
Are you hurt? What happened?
Well, it's...
Don't worry about it.
The thing is...
I came here to ask you something.
What is it?
Soo Ryeon and Hee Tae...
are back in Gwangju.
So you knew.
Then...
do you know where Soo Ryeon is?
- Well...
- Please tell me if you know.
I must find Soo Ryeon
before Mr. Hwang hurts her.
I heard that he found Hee Tae
and has him now.
So it's only a matter of time
before he finds Soo Ryeon.
Did he really say that?
He said he has Hee Tae with him?
(Gwangju Pyeonghwa Hospital)
You're really going to stay here...
until Hee Tae returns?
Mr. Hwang took Hee Tae.
You know what that means, right?
It means if you keep staying here,
you don't know
when you'll fall in danger too.
I'm worried about you...
as much as Soo Ryeon, Myeong Hee.
When I was young,
whenever my dad took me
to the market,
there's something he always said.
He told me to stay put
and not go anywhere...
if I let go of his hand
and got lost.
He told me I'd go missing
if we both wandered around...
looking for each other.
He told me to stay put...
until he found me.
I'll stay right here
even if lightning strikes...
so that Hee Tae can find me.
Myeong Hee.
This is what I liked so much
about you.
You were always brave and strong.
Be careful.
And call me anytime
if you need my help.
Okay.
Jung Tae. Are you up?
Come downstairs to eat.
Your father will be home soon.
Didn't I tell you not to stomp
on the stairs?
Haven't you even washed up yet?
I'm not hungry.
Even if you're not hungry,
your father is coming home
for the first time in days.
You should eat with him.
Go wash up.
Never open this door again.
Have you lost your mind?
What's going on in our house?
Like I said,
I'm doing this for my family.
For your family?
But the person locked up in there
is your own child.
No. What's in there is
a ticking time bomb.
Just like your father.
Thanks to your mighty father,
we've been stuck in this countryside
for ten years now.
It's my first chance in ten years.
Do you understand?
I can't be hugging a bomb
just because we're family.
I won't make
that stupid mistake again.
(Male, 29)
(Navy trousers, purple shirt,
brown jacket, brown shoes)
(Deceased)
Lee Soo Ryeon.
Soo Chan.
I did suspect that.
Now that Hwang Hee Tae
has been taken away,
it should be my turn next.
But Hwang Ki Nam is a threat...
to every single person here.
I can't go back home...
just to save myself.
What about Father?
I'm not asking you
to come back home for good.
But shouldn't you at least
go and see Father once?
If I see him right now,
I won't be able to leave home again.
Soo Ryeon. Now I understand...
why you must do this.
But must you really
turn your back on your family?
- In a situation like this...
- All these posters...
were put up by people
with missing family members.
Without even knowing
whether they're dead or alive,
they cut out pictures of them
and made these posters.
(Kim Sung Wook, 18)
At least everyone in our family
is alive...
and we know that.
We should be grateful...
Soo Chan.
I heard everything from Soo Ryeon.
Judging from how you look,
you must not be sleeping or eating.
Do you think this will make people
praise you for your loyalty?
I can't sleep even if I lay in bed.
And I don't feel hungry.
Don't worry too much.
I doubt even the evil Hwang Ki Nam
could harm his own child.
He would do anything.
Still, they're father and son.
What kind of parent would kill
his own child?
What are you talking about?
You... Do you have any idea
what his father,
Hwang Ki Nam, is like?
I do.
You do?
And you still dated his son?
Hee Tae didn't do anything.
His only fault is
that he's his father's son.
That's precisely the problem.
Do you think
he'll be any different...
from his savage father?
The apple doesn't fall
far from the tree.
After being stigmatized
all your life yourself,
how could you say
the same thing as Hwang Ki Nam?
Follow me.
Come with me to Naju right now.
Let go of me. Let go!
You should stop here.
He's going to ruin your life
in the end.
He's not the one who ruined my life.
It's you.
- How could you...
- Stop it, both of you!
Stop fighting.
Please stop.
(Emergency Room)
Don't waste your energy.
No one outside can hear you anyway.
The people in this house
will hear me, at least.
Isn't that why you came?
Don't you want to know
what's happening outside?
The martial law army has retreated,
so everyone's celebrating.
They have no idea
it means isolation, not liberation.
Gwangju is now
a rat trapped in a cage.
They'll slowly bleed to death
unless they surrender.
Just like you.
I finally understand.
My mother said
she'd rather let her lungs rot...
than receive treatment
with your money.
I think I understand her now.
I don't understand why both you
and the morons outside...
are so stupid.
As long as you keep quiet
and behave,
you'll be let go sooner or later.
What's the point of being let go?
You'll just lock me up again
when you feel anxious.
That's not the same as being let go.
I'm just on a longer leash.
I am not your pet dog.
So...
stop interfering with my life.
I cannot do that.
I have already paid the price.
Oh, that's too bad.
I don't think I can go on
playing the good son.
I think I should start
with protesting.
I was already arrested before.
The repentant Head of Anti-communist
Investigation's son?
That would paint a pretty picture.
Or should I go for
disguised employment?
Teach students at night...
You should know
when to stop fighting back.
You're not the only person
who can ruin my life.
So stop interfering with my life.
You were an orphan
and I took you in.
Yet, you forget your place
and act up?
Why am I an orphan...
when my father is
alive and well right here?
Don't get the wrong idea.
I chose you to be my son.
If not for my selection,
you are an orphan.
The orphan
who begged for funeral expenses.
The corpses in the street
at least have families to get them.
No one will look for you...
as you bleed to death in here.
And then...
nothing will happen,
as if you never existed
in the first place.
The orphan...
is not me but you.
No one will choose you
to be their family.
Sir, there's an emergency call.
You must head back.
(Gwangju Pyeonghwa Hospital)
Father, when are we going back
to Naju?
Should we kidnap Myeong Hee?
You grab her arms,
and I'll grab her legs.
Then we could take her back to Naju.
It's no use taking
just her outer shell with us.
Her spirit will remain here.
What's with her anyway?
I understand she loves Hee Tae,
but shouldn't her family matter more
to her than anything?
Do you know who gave me this watch?
Isn't it something
Grandpa passed down to you?
No. Actually, it was passed down...
to my brother.
Then as he was leaving home,
he passed it down to me...
when I was just about your age.
Why did he leave home?
My brother...
also had something
that mattered more than his family,
just like your sister.
You never know what'll happen
when you grow up.
You might also find something
that matters more.
I don't think so.
To me, my family will always
matter more than anything.
Goodness. Come here, my boy.
What did you think
of Mudeung Stadium?
It was a lot bigger
than the schoolyard, right?
Of course, the schoolyard
can't compare with Mudeung Stadium.
It's the same thing.
Your family, of course,
matters to you.
But sometimes,
you find things in life that are...
much larger and more important,
like Mudeung Stadium.
It's not that your sister
doesn't care about her family.
But she can't come home yet
because of something more important.
Here.
Hello?
Jung Tae, is that you?
It's me, Myeong Soo.
Kim Myeong Soo.
Are you back in Naju?
No. I'm still in Gwangju,
because of my sister.
Your sister? What about her?
She's waiting for Hee Tae.
She won't step outside the hospital.
So I want to ask you.
Has Hee Tae come home?
Haven't you heard anything?
Hee Tae...
might die.
What? What are you talking about?
My father...
What he did to Hee Tae...
Are you really not going to tell me
who that was?
Hwang Jung Tae.
Aren't you concerned?
- What?
- There's no sound...
coming from the study anymore.
What if Hee Tae is already dead?
If Father can do this
to his favorite son,
who knows if he'll lock me up too
in the future?
That's never going to happen,
Jung Tae.
Your father and Hee Tae just had
a small disagreement, that's all.
Mom.
Can't you let him go?
Father isn't home right now.
I can't.
Father will let him go
as soon as he calms down.
Don't worry, okay?
I...
I'm going back to the camp.
What? Don't you know how dangerous
it is out there now?
Any place...
would be less scary than home.
Wait.
Can I...
ask you for a favor?
Please...
call the hospital.
If Myeong Hee is still there,
please tell her that I'm safe...
and that she should go back to Naju.
I'm sorry...
but I can't do that for you.
That look won't do you any good.
You already know...
that there's nothing I can do
in this house.
The only thing I can give you...
is just a cup of water.
You must hate
and resent me for that...
Mother.
I do not resent you.
I never hated you.
I understand how you feel.
I'll ask for something else then.
Take Jung Tae...
and leave this house.
Jung Tae is still young.
Hey, wake up.
Wake up, okay?
Pull yourself together.
You moron.
I'll kill...
everyone in your family.
Why?
10-33 Wolhyang-ri, Wolhyang-myeon,
Hampyeong-gun.
Your grandmother's place.
It's a desolate area,
and just perfect
for your ailing mother.
Unless she's there like your father
to look after your grandmother,
no one will know who lives there.
Naturally,
no one will know who dies there.
Jung Hye Gun.
Let's end this quickly.
Isn't it tough on you?
Let's go and see your parents.
Hey. Say I'm taken by
Defense Security Command.
If I drop your name,
will your father get me out?
Will he?
Give it a go.
The moment you even say
one syllable of my name,
my father will kill you.
Father.
Hee Tae's father.
It's me.
Hee Tae's friend Hye Gun.
What is this fool saying?
Sir. Why are you pretending
not to know me?
You said you'd let me off
if I mentioned Hee Tae.
It's me, sir.
I'm Hye Gun, Hee Tae's best friend.
Let go.
Darn you.
Let go of me. Let go, punk.
Darn you. What did you say?
You deserve to die.
How dare you threaten me?
Who said you could say that to me?
Just die.
Die already. Just die.
Dr. Yoo was discharged.
His family came and took him home.
- Goodness, he went home?
- Yes.
That's great.
I was worried he was badly hurt.
Hey.
Does Mr. Hwang have no family?
Pardon?
I mean, he went missing...
but no one is asking
or looking for him.
Does he have no one else?
The militia got us medical supplies.
If you need anything for the ER,
come and get it.
- That is just great.
- It is.
I'll go and get it.
I look forward to May every year.
Why are you working on your own
and tiring yourself out?
You see, sir,
I left my spot
only to go to the toilet, but...
It was you.
You did it.
Jung Tae, go to your room.
Hwang Jung Tae, go, now.
No, don't get up.
Oh, dear.
(Regular savings account)
That's the money I saved
to send Myeong Hee to college.
And I also saved the money
she sent me all this time.
I know it's not much,
but it'll be enough
to get you two settled.
You should give this
to Myeong Hee yourself...
No need. You can hold onto it.
Myeong Hee will just throw a fit
and refuse to take it.
Now, this money...
belongs to you both anyway.
Father.
Also...
Can you give this to her too?
Although Myeong Hee...
met a lousy father like me
and suffered all her life,
she is truly...
a precious child.
I hope you both forget
about the tragic past...
and cherish each other
and live happily.
We will.
Kim Myeong Soo.
Are you upset
because of your sister?
Whatever.
Have some of these.
- Oh, gosh. Thank you.
- No problem.
You should thank her.
Okay. Go on and eat it.
Here. You can have the big one.
Go on. I already ate.
(Blood Donation)
Father.
I think I understand now.
Something as large and important
as Mudeung Stadium.
What did you say?
I like these rice balls.
What?
I'm glad you're here.
They already searched this place
last time,
so it'll be safe for the time being.
We'll just stay
until the lockdown is over.
- Oh, this is...
- Right.
Hello, I'm Hwang Hee Tae.
So is this...
Yes, the one in the banner.
Is he the reason
you mentioned last time?
"Reason?"
Father, let's go inside.
Can you really walk?
It's quite far, you know.
We always used to walk
before there were buses.
I've marked the inspection points
guarded by the soldiers.
So please be careful.
Thank you.
It was a safe trip thanks to you.
Myeong Soo.
Here.
Thank you.
Take care then. Let's go.
Be careful, sir!
Are you really not going to look?
Don't you want to know
what's inside the envelope?
I don't want to know.
Stop talking and face forward.
Gosh, you're truly blessed.
You're blessed with love.
If only I had a father like that,
I'd be the happiest guy on earth.
You're so spoiled, you know that?
Children who were raised
in happy families...
always turn out to be spoiled.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Even you aren't reacting
to my jokes now.
I don't have anyone left
in this world anymore.
Don't...
Don't ever say that again.
What?
Don't say you don't have
anyone left.
Don't say it anymore.
I mean...
It's just that
you weren't saying anything,
so I was just joking...
Are you mad?
Yes, I'm mad because you said that.
The entire time I was waiting
for you,
I kept thinking of the things
you said to me.
You said I have Myeong Soo
and my parents...
but you...
don't have anyone beside you
except for me.
- That was...
- The more I thought about it,
the angrier it made me.
You made it sound like
I'll be okay...
even if I don't have you.
- Myeong Hee.
- I'm not okay.
If I lose you,
I don't have anything left either.
Myeong Hee.
After my mother passed away,
do you know what I feared the most?
Blood. Being in pain.
Since I had no one left
to take care of me,
I was worried I might die
alone and in pain.
And I was worried no one
would notice even if I died.
That's why I went to live
with my father's family.
Even if they weren't my real family,
I thought it'd be better
than being alone.
But now, I don't need a family.
I have you.
I'll...
I'll be your family.
Let's get married.
Where is it?
Are we on the right path?
Father, are you sure
we're on the right path?
I don't think this is the one
on the map.
You think so?
That can't be right.
This has to be the right path.
Let me see.
Can you even read maps?
Come on.
I'm at least better at it than you.
From here...
This is...
- That way!
- Hurry!
You go that way!
Go that way!
Turn off the flashlight.
Gosh.
Let's hide over there.
Hurry!
- Yes, sir!
- Father.
- Quiet.
There's no one here, sir.
It's clear here too.
- Search thoroughly!
- Yes, sir.
It's clear here.
- Search everywhere!
- Yes, sir.
Myeong Soo.
I'll go and talk to them.
Stay here...
and keep your eyes closed.
- No, Father.
- Keep it down.
Where did the punk go?
Son, listen.
Until I come back,
no matter what you hear,
never come out.
Do you understand?
(Youth of May)