♪You crossed the sea of ​​stars
and came with light♪
♪My heart is like the dust, and I
couldn't bear to stain the hemline♪
♪To love in a different way,
the fireworks are in the stars' good graces♪
♪I turn around and realize that
my heart is empty♪
♪I miss the overflowing galaxy
surging into the sea♪
♪Even the fireworks desire
to give the stars a future♪
♪As long as you are around♪
♪Even the fireworks fear to bloom♪
♪Looking at you,
the light in your eyes dimmed♪
♪I laughed at myself
and that I deserve it ♪
♪My heart skips a beat, but I'm afraid
I'm not worthy of the future that you desire♪
=You Are My Glory=
=Episode 29=
We've changed the curtains too.
That is a nice color.
I know, right?
This color is very hard to get.
I waited for a month for these
before they arrived.
The ones before
looked too stuffy.
Yu Tu said
that those didn't easily look dirty.
That's how he is.
Aside from wearing
dark blue,
he wears black.
I didn't touch the book shelves.
I didn't tidy them up either.
He knows where he places his books.
He'll be annoyed if he can't find them
because I move them.
That's how he's been
since he was little.
He'd get mad
if you cleaned them up for him.
Right.
That was why I didn't bother,
and just let him do it himself.
The one on the sofa
is a prize from his unit.
Mrs. Yu.
I bought new tableware.
I'll show it to you.
Let's ignore him today.
He said that he had to write
a thesis today
and told me to go and have fun
by myself.
Yu Tu.
It's Sunday.
I don't comment when you usually
work overtime.
But today,
you must spend time with Jingjing.
She was the one who said that she was
going to read her script this afternoon
and told me to find something to do.
Mom.
Why do you still believe her?
Have you fogotten?
When you first met,
she lied to you already.
Go away.
Write your thesis.
Mrs. Yu, let's check the tableware.
I'm so sleepy.
I can't do it anymore.
Even the power of love
can't sustain me.
I'll read the script with you later.
I'll answer the phone. Let me go.
During your last film-shooting, they said
that your boyfriend had gone to visit you,
and Zhou Xiaoqi had been so furious.
Is that true?
It's been over a month
since filming was wrapped up.
Where did you hear that?
I just heard about it.
It's true.
I laughed so hard.
That feels so good.
When will you
let me meet your boyfriend?
He's talented.
You've been together for so long,
and you won't let me meet him.
That's not appropriate.
You speak
as if we met very often.
Let's have dinner when we have time.
How about tonight?
I don't have work today.
I'll tell someone
to bring hairy crabs over.
The type that weighs 300g each.
That should be fine.
Let me ask him.
It should be fine?
You still need to ask him?
Qiao Jingjing, do you know who I am?
I'm Chen Xue.
I'm very famous.
I'm very hard to meet.
I'm inviting him, and he's not coming?
His girlfriend is also
very famous, okay?
You think you're all that?
He he he.
The Dynamic Solution Method
of Low Thrust Orbit Design.
Chen Xue wants
to invite us for dinner
at her house tonight.
Do you still remember her?
Can I forget her?
She said that I sounded
like a scumbag.
Why do you like holding grudges so much?
That was two years ago.
Is tonight fine?
Yes.
Dinner is fine.
Thank you.
Hey.
I'll invite Duan Wu
and Mr. Zhou later too.
That's fine, right?
Sure.
We all know each other well.
They're in Shanghai too?
Yes.
My next film is with them.
I asked,
and they're still around.
This way, after we have dinner,
we can play mahjong.
No, I won't play that.
I don't know how to play that.
You just want to win my money.
Listen.
I just earned some money in the desert.
Was that easy for me?
Come on.
No.
My boyfriend needs to write a thesis
when he comes back.
Isn't he working already?
Why is he writing a thesis?
Don't you know
how scientific research works?
Yes.
He's doing scientific research.
Right.
We can't
play mahjong.
That makes us seem like
we don't do decent work.
Don't worry.
Let me handle it.
I'll surely make you look good.
Ms. Qiao.
Missus.
You're here.
Chen Xue is waiting for you.
I'll get you some slippers.
No.
I must save them.
With what?
Those dilapidated starships
in the Star Port?
(Don't worry.)
(We'll surely look)
(very professional)
(and academic.)
(Is this what she was referring to?)
(Can they stop it?)
You're finally here.
Jingjing.
Ms. Qiao.
I haven't seen you in a while.
It's been a while.
I brought my boyfriend over
for dinner.
I know.
Introduce him to us.
This is my boyfriend, Yu Tu.
This is Mr. Zhou, the best actor.
Hello.
I've worked with him before.
This is Duan Wu.
Nice to meet you.
This is my bestie, Chen Xue.
I've heard a lot about you.
What are you doing?
Next month,
we'll be filming a movie together.
While we're all here,
we're going through the script
to get some ideas.
This is a group scene.
We happen to need
one more person.
Can you
help us out, Ms. Qiao?
Help you out?
Do you mind
lending us Ms. Qiao
for a while?
Of course not.
Come on.
(What does your movie)
(have to do with me?)
(Aren't we here for dinner?)
(You tricked me into coming here
for work.)
(Come on, stop dilly-dallying.)
(Your boyfriend is watching.)
(Look academic.)
Okay.
Let's do it.
This is
an interstellar theme movie.
This scene is mainly
about the argument between the faction
seeking peace and the one seeking war.
Ms. Qiao.
You're the leader
of the peace-seeking faction.
The leader?
He's an old man?
You can do it.
Right.
I can do it.
A professional old man voice.
Give me five minutes.
Let me memorize the lines.
Please have some water.
Thank you.
Okay, let's start.
You memorized it so quickly?
Come on.
No.
I must save them.
With what?
Those dilapidated starships
in the Star Port?
Major, have you forgotten?
The one you're calling a hero
took away all the elites
in the Federation.
Should we
just be at the mercy of others
and be swallowed up little by little?
That's enough, Major.
Calm down.
The nation
can't experience another war.
Besides, this is
a war we're bound to lose.
I understand
how a warrior thirsts for battle.
But please also consider
those ordinary citizens.
Sir.
It's not like
we have no chances of winning.
The science institute's latest weapon
can be installed in the starship.
We need to discuss
how we'll do this part
of the scene more.
For example,
these.
What do you think?
Don't we seem professional
and literary?
We were playing Dou Dizhu earlier.
When you arrived,
we immediately put the cards away
and started going through the scenes.
Right.
We quickly got into character
so professionally.
Let me ask you.
Doesn't this
have
an academic vibe?
Isn't this artsy?
We're completely on par
with scientists, aren't we?
Please.
When we're eating later,
stop how you're acting now.
Continue
that academic vibe earlier.
Please. Thank you.
Of course.
We can maintain
this image
during the meal.
How about another scene?
There's no need.
If we continue,
the academic vibe
will be too forced.
Just have enough of it.
Just enough of it.
What do you think?
Was I good at portraying an old man?
Yes.
However,
your lines earlier
involved
the performance parameters
of a new weapon.
In
an interstellar era,
it's a bit too conservative.
Thank you.
I'm confident now.
I'll revise it immediately.
Afterwards,
can you help me take a look?
No problem.
Let's exchange WeChat Contacts.
Sure.
I'll ask Jingjing to send it.
Okay.
Another question.
When I was writing it,
I already had doubts.
There's a plot
regarding wormhole.
I also want to discuss it with you.
This scriptwriter is a big shot.
When have you seen him
being so humble?
Your boyfriend is incredible.
And he's so handsome.
If I say that he's handsome,
he really is.
And he's so knowledgeable.
No wonder he suppressed
that heir boyfriend
of Zhou Xiaoqi.
I finally know
why you chose him.
I would want him too.
Say that again.
I'm just
expressing my admiration
for my bestie's boyfriend.
How can I want him?
That's more like it.
You're so petty.
Okay.
Actually, some people in the circle
are bitter about your relationship.
They said that you chose
a government worker
among all of them.
I didn't quite understand before.
Why didn't you
choose Mr. Su?
Actually, Su Ye
is a good catch.
He just has minor shortcomings.
But men who are handsome
and rich
are all arrogant.
However, come to think of it now,
aside from satisfying our vanity,
there's nothing good about him.
We have money ourselves.
Let's choose someone we like.
It doesn't matter
how much he earns.
I didn't choose that at all.
I know.
However, Jingjing,
if you're
not an actress,
and you don't earn that much money,
will you still choose
your boyfriend now?
I'm so beautiful,
and I work so hard.
How can I not earn any money?
Even if I'm a live streamer,
I'll become rich too, okay?
What if you were unlucky,
and you couldn't earn money?
Are you stupid?
If that really happens,
I must hold onto him tightly
all the more.
It's a bit bitter.
Why are you so happy?
Because a famous scriptwriter
consulted you?
No.
I'm happy
because my girlfriend is super smart.
She's so logical.
Now, you know.
How exactly
did you figure that out?
For example,
you brought
all their uncooked crabs
home.
Dr. Yu.
Yu Tu.
Tonight
is the basketball semi-final
in the institute.
Someone's leg has got injured,
and he can't play.
Can you play?
I said
that I'd have dinner at home.
Don't we have new graduates
in the unit?
They're quite tall.
Being tall
doesn't mean that they can
play basketball.
Hu is an example.
Besides, they just joined us.
We haven't played with them yet.
You do it.
Okay.
I'll inform the one waiting for me.
The one waiting for you?
I'm curious.
A while ago,
Meng mysteriously said
that you had a girlfriend,
and she was very, very beautiful.
Is she
who you were referring to?
That was what he said?
Yes.
His facial expression made me
want to beat him up.
I don't know why he's being
so mysterious.
It's my girlfriend.
Meng is right too.
She's very beautiful indeed.
My heart
can't take this.
Love is in the air.
Fine, I'll go ahead.
See you at the basketball court.
Hey.
Jingjing.
I won't be home for dinner.
There's a basketball game
in the institute.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
I marinaded the steak already.
I was originally not part
of the semi-final.
Someone has suddenly gotten injured,
and he can't play.
Do you play basketball so badly?
You're just a substitute?
In senior high, I remember you being
the main force in the varsity team.
Ms. Qiao.
I'm old.
Right.
Mr. Yu, you're already
32 years old.
In high-intensity sports
like basketball,
your stamina surely can't compare
to those young, fresh graduates.
What about you?
I think we're the same age.
No.
No, I'm not.
Listen.
A while ago, a marketing account
even said
that I looked like a young girl.
Before,
I was the one who voluntarily
left the team.
Look at them.
They get me as the substitute
once they need someone.
Doesn't that prove
that my stamina and standard
are stronger
than other youngsters in the unit?
Fine.
If you don't believe me,
you can come and confirm it yourself,
and cheer for me as well.
(CATC)
Did you bring your ID?
Of course.
There's no time to eat at the canteen.
I bought corn juice.
Okay.
Let's go.
Hello.
I'm an employee of Base 158.
This is my girlfriend.
She's here to watch the basketball game.
Here.
Register your information.
You need to fill out the information
of the visitor and the person visited.
(Qiao Jingjing)
I'm sorry.
I'm used to wearing this.
You're from Base 158?
Yes.
Your girlfriend
is here to watch the basketball game?
Yes.
When you come out,
exchange this for your national ID.
Thank you.
Aren't you hungry?
How can you drink the corn juice
while wearing a mask?
Meng kept telling people
that my girlfriend
is very beautiful.
I want to officially show you off.
Okay.
I'll grant your wish then.
You should have told me that you want
to show off.
I just applied make-up base today.
And I didn't wash my hair.
It seems like I just
look half as beautiful
as I can be.
Is that so?
Let me see.
How can it just be half?
It's at least two-thirds.
That's enough.
Yu Tu!
I'll hit you!
Yu Tu, where have you gone?
The game is going to start.
I'll be right there.
I've picked up Jingjing by the gate.
Who?
Jingjing.
My goodness.
This is going to be exciting.
(Inspire dreams, fight hard to shine)
Xiao Yin.
I just called Yu Tu.
And he told me
that he had gone to the gate
to pick up that person.
Who?
Speak clearly.
His girlfriend.
Really?
No way.
Is she
the beautiful girlfriend
Meng kept telling us about?
That's great.
I'm so curious
because of what Meng said.
I really want to see how beautiful
his girlfriend is.
- Hi, Yu Tu.
- Hey, Yu Tu. You're here.
Here they come.
Yu Tu.
Over here.
Why does Yu Tu's girlfriend
look so familiar?
Qiao Jingjing.
That's Qiao Jingjing, isn't it?
What's going on?
We invited a female celebrity
to cheer
for our basketball game?
No.
Yu Tu is holding her hand.
Xiao Yin.
His girlfriend is Qiao Jingjing.
- Why didn't you tell us?
- Oh my god.
You're so tight-lipped.
Xiao Yin.
Yes.
Mr. Yu, what can I do for you?
I'll let you take care of Jingjing.
I promise to take good care of her.
Hello.
I came to watch Yu Tu's basketball game.
Go ahead.
Go get changed.
Come on.
I'll go get changed.
Come on, move over there a bit.
- Jingjing, sit here.
- Okay.
Let me introduce you.
Jingjing, they are
our colleagues.
And this is
Yu Tu's girlfriend.
I don't need to tell you her name,
do I?
There's no need.
Who doesn't know her?
Right.
This is unbelievable.
Who could have thought
that Qiao Jingjing is the girlfriend
of our colleague?
Actually, it's not that unbelievable.
Yu Tu and I were classmates
in senior high.
So you've been dating since senior high?
I'm sorry. I'm not being nosy.
You don't need to answer.
No.
We studied hard
during senior high.
We weren't dating.
After many years,
we found out
that we were both still single,
so we just made do with each other.
Love is in the air.
We don't believe that.
The game is about to begin.
Why are you here?
I feel quite pressured.
I feel like
it would be bad if we didn't win today.
I believe in you.
All the best.
Believe in yourself.
You're old but vigorous.
Old but vigorous.
Oh my god.
Jingjing.
You can do it!
Go!
Hurry!
You can do it!
- Go!
Go for it!
- Go for it!
- You can do it!
- Go!
- Go for it!
- You can do it!
(Base 158, Base 159)
That last three-point shot
was way too cool!
Am I comparable to youngsters?
It's not comparable to yourself
when you were younger.
In senior high,
when you played basketball,
you obviously made more direct attacks.
Now, you just
make three-point shots.
That's obviously because your stamina...
You obviously won
through technique.
Can't you say something nice?
You're so cool.
I like it so much.
Let's go home.
What do you think?
Is my ID photo
very beautiful?
Let me see if
yours is really
as handsome as you say it is.
Let me compare which one is nicer.
(Qiao Jingjing, Yu Tu)
How can you compare them?
If we want to compare them,
shouldn't we take one
under the same exact conditions,
the same lighting,
the same photographer,
and the same venue
before we can reach a conclusion?
Should we be so strict about this?
Yes.
So,
when will we take
our certificate photo together?
That was a marriage proposal?
Of course.
It's so obvious already.
Let me ask you.
How is that obvious?
So you just agreed
so easily?
Don't tell me you have already
registered your marriage.
How is that possible?
That's good.
I knew it.
Mr. Yu
isn't an unreliable person.
We're planning
to meet our families next weekend.
That's considered our engagement.
Should I start planning
your wedding?
I guess so.
This matter
must be planned carefully.
The venue, guests,
wedding dress, gifts.
Oh my god.
I'm so overwhelmed
just thinking about it.
Do you have
any thoughts about it?
What kind of wedding do you want?
When do you want to hold it?
Actually, we haven't thought about
all those things.
In terms of the date,
after my next film is done?
Your next drama is only 12 episodes.
You'll finish filming in over a month.
You want to plan a wedding
in just over one month?
Have you gotten married before?
Take a look.
Hainan is so nice.
I think
it's also good to hold
the wedding in Hainan.
The confidentiality factor will be high.
Right?
But so many people will be going
to Hainan.
It would be very fussy
about mobilizing everyone.
That's very troublesome.
Mrs. Qiao, don't worry.
Ms. Ling will make arrangements.
We'll organize it.
We guarantee that
we'll make proper arrangements
for your relatives and friends.
We can also hold the wedding
in Shanghai.
However,
the confidentiality factor will be low.
Am I right?
What about our hometown?
What are your thoughts?
We... We don't have any thoughts.
We'll just do what Yu Tu
and Jingjing want.
Yes, we'll listen to them.
Let's do what Jingjing wants.
Then we won't get the matter settled.
She's so fickle.
Xiao Zhu.
When other celebrities get married,
once there is a mistake,
they will become trending at once.
"It's too formal." "It's too simple."
Some would comment that way.
They'll also comment
about the gifts given.
We must be careful.
You must manage
the guests and stuff.
Mrs. Qiao.
Don't worry.
Xiao Zhu.
You always call Yu Tu
Mr. Yu.
Why is that?
Because a few years ago,
when Mr. Yu taught Jingjing
how to play games,
that was how we called him.
We're used to it.
That was how Mr. Yu
tricked Jingjing
into being his girlfriend.
Didn't she tell you?
Son.
You were that good?
Mr. Yu.
Your daughter
can't be tricked that easily
in the future.
Mrs. Qiao.
That won't happen.
He must go through me first.
At that time,
you'll be a 50 or 60-year-old man.
How can you fight a youngster?
At 80 years old,
I can still make a Penta kill,
don't you think?
Continue bluffing.
Mr. Yu.
I have to drive Jingjing
back to the film set.
I'll get something in Shanghai first.
Then I'll meet up with you in Hengdian.
Okay.
Look.
It's almost New Year,
and you even accepted
a film-shooting project.
After getting married,
you must take care of your household.
It's fine, Jingjing.
You can do your work.
At home,
Yu Tu can take good care of himself.
Accept film-shooting works if you want.
If not,
just rest at home.
You don't need to mind him.
It's true. You don't need to mind him.
Mom.
That wasn't
what you told me before.
What did I tell you before?
No.
Your mom told me about it.
Look.
Let's just see
what Jingjing wants to do.
Right.
Jingjing.
You call the shots.
So your mom's requirement
was for her daughter-in-law
to take good care of you?
But when she saw you,
she forgot what she originally wanted.
She's not firm at all.
But what kind of son-in-law
do your parents require?
Just being handsome is enough.
I fulfilled that once I was born then.
I'm ignoring you.
There's another successful rocket launch
("Science 20" successfully launched)
at the Taiyuan Launch Center.
(at the Taiyuan Satellite Launch Center today)
A few days ago, it seemed a rocket
also successfully launched in Jiuquan.
Right.
I think Science 20 was the one
that launched today.
How do you know it so well?
Because I'm following a lot
of your industry's official accounts.
Like CATC,
Shanghai Aerospace,
and also your unit's official account.
Aren't I
the very qualified family member
of a aerospace worker?
You follow a lot more accounts than me.
Of course you are.
Do you follow
any official accounts
in the entertainment circle?
I'm sorry.
I didn't do my job well.
Here.
I'll follow them now.
I don't want you to follow them
when you're told.
And lately, I have
a romance drama coming up.
Forget it.
If some official accounts
have some photos
with sweet interactions
with the male lead,
someone might be unhappy
if he sees them.
Is that considered
a romance drama?
You break up at the beginning.
Isn't the story afterwards
about the female lead's career?
Right.
I forgot you read the script.
You were hasty.
But Jingjing,
when accepting film-shooting works,
you don't need to consider me.
It's true.
I'm fine.
All right.
I won't
intentionally avoid
sweet scenes and stuff.
It will depend on the script.
One may say that he doesn't mind,
but I wonder who takes the script
and studies it carefully
every single time.
Yu Tu.
I just discovered this
from the official account
of your unit.
I want my wedding
to be done this way too.
♪I dreamed of starlight
pulling the sleeves♪
♪A white top
covering the thin shoulders♪
♪I have seen the wounds healed
with each passing year♪
♪There will always be people
running towards eternity♪
♪The bustling intersection♪
♪Looking back all of a sudden
under the dim light♪
♪I loved your eyes
looking at the starry sky♪
♪And I loved the universe in your heart♪
♪Time does not stop, remember the time
that we failed to treasure♪
♪The wind passes by the tall buildings
with no one awaiting it♪
♪I've dreamed of traveling
around the planet♪
♪Seeing the galaxy
pass through the clouds♪
♪I looked at the hills with sorrow♪
♪Will the exit of the dream lead
to the end of the starry sky?♪
♪Looking back all of a sudden♪
♪Which galaxy am I drifting on?♪
♪Looking into the distance,
which of the stars are your eyes?♪
♪It's out of reach,
so dazzling and hard to get♪
♪Time does not hold back, the spring
and autumn in the passing time♪
♪The wind sings the song of freedom
as I listen to the tenderness of time♪