♪You crossed the sea of ​​stars
and came with light♪
♪My heart is like the dust, and I
couldn't bear to stain the hemline♪
♪To love in a different way,
the fireworks are in the stars' good graces♪
♪I turn around and realize that
my heart is empty♪
♪I miss the overflowing galaxy
surging into the sea♪
♪Even the fireworks desire
to give the stars a future♪
♪As long as you are around♪
♪Even the fireworks fear to bloom♪
♪Looking at you,
the light in your eyes dimmed♪
♪I laughed at myself
and that I deserve it ♪
♪My heart skips a beat, but I'm afraid
I'm not worthy of the future that you desire♪
=You Are My Glory=
=Episode 30=
Why haven't you signed up?
There are only 12 spots left.
You're about to miss out.
Stop kidding around.
I'm not kidding.
I'm being serious.
If we participate
in this group wedding,
then we'll be able
to put all our troubles
behind us.
First of all,
we don't have to worry
about what everyone thinks of us.
We don't even have
to book the banquet ourselves.
Besides,
we'll only need to invite
those closest to us as guests.
If this isn't a dream wedding,
then
What will be?
I'm so considerate
that even Ling
would be driven to tears.
Jingjing, roll call!
Coming!
That's it for now.
Now hurry and sign up.
I have a filming session.
Okay.
I'll go check it out.
Good luck with your movie.
What was that about?
Our wedding.
What's it going to be?
I've never been
to a celebrity wedding.
Is it going to be grandiose?
Do I need to wear a suit?
She told me to reserve
a spot at a group wedding
organized by our unit.
What?
Your girlfriend is a celebrity,
and that's what
she could come up with?
But then again,
it really suits you.
Didn't you say to keep it simple
when you took part
in our colleague's wedding?
When was that?
Years ago.
Well?
Are you going to sign up?
No way.
She'll
change her mind in a few days.
After all, Ms Qiao's plan takes us
from the beach to the grass,
to the hotel,
and to the beach again.
(Are you off-duty?)
(Have you signed up?)
Are you serious?
Of course.
You haven't signed up yet, have you?
There are only twelve spots left.
Hurry up and book us a spot.
You can't change your mind
after you sign up.
Otherwise, you'll waste
spots for others.
Are you sure
that you won't change your mind?
Of course not.
I was a little impulsive that day.
But now the more I think about it,
the more appropriate it is.
Before we talk about appropriateness,
have you even taken
your parents
and also Ling into consideration?
Will they agree?
Never mind about Ling.
As for Mom and Dad,
I'll take care of it.
If they agree,
then you'll sign up?
Yes.
I'll go ask them now.
(CATC)
The tender
will be in half a year's time.
And I'm already nervous about it.
Somehow I didn't even notice that.
Come on.
(Missed Calls: Ling, Mom,
Mrs Qiao, Shen Jing)
(Mrs. Qiao)
Yu Tu.
Mrs. Qiao.
I was in the lab.
Jingjing called us.
She said, she wanted to join
the group wedding organized by your unit.
Are you aware of this?
Yes, she told me.
But I don't think it's appropriate.
I see.
Jingjing
made several calls
to tell me this.
At first,
I firmly disapproved of it.
But somehow,
she won me over.
Haven't you
agreed with her about this?
I thought you wouldn't agree.
You see,
We and Jingjing's parents
sat down for a meal
just to talk about this.
And then,
she won over her parents too.
They were kind of pleased.
My boy.
If you have any
reservations about this,
you can talk it over with her.
Yes, Mom.
Yu Tu.
Aren't you joining us for dinner?
We've got overtime.
You guys go ahead.
I'm going home.
That workaholic
is ditching his overtime today.
The big star is filming right now,
isn't she?
Why is he going home so early?
(Mr. Yu.)
(You've been through)
(a really rough day.)
(Life needs a sense of ritual.)
(I'm a pragmatist.)
(Well then.)
(Your pragmatism has to go.)
(See,)
(isn't it much better?)
(Qiao Jingjing
Jewelry Endorser Interview)
Jingjing,
if you're getting married,
what kind of wedding do you want?
My dream wedding
should be
a very, very romantic one.
I'll have the ground
littered with flowers,
invite lots and lots of friends,
and we'll all sing and dance together.
I'll wear a white wedding dress,
and gradually walk towards the groom,
Then he'll hold my hand
(and put a ring on me,
and we'll recite our vows.
To me,
that's love at its best.
(If there are stars in the sky,)
(then it should be quite romantic.)
(This is my very ideal)
(romantic wedding.)
(Hengdian, Zhejiang)
Who's there?
It's me.
What brought you here?
Tomorrow's the weekend?
Come in quick.
Come on.
Why do we have to attend
a group wedding?
You drove over 200 kilometers
just
to ask me this question?
You said it.
You've dreamt
of a very romantic wedding
littered with flowers.
And lots and lots of friends will be invited.
Wait.
When did I say that?
Two years ago.
When you were interviewed
as a jewelry spokeswoman.
You fell for that?
When they asked me
during the interview,
I had to make up an answer on the spot.
Then what kind of wedding do you want?
Yu Tu.
Do you think that
I'm concerned about your finances,
so I came up
with the group wedding?
Jingjing.
I also want to do the best I can.
Thank you.
I'm about to marry you.
Of course you have to do your best.
But for now,
all I really need
is just a simple wedding.
You know that
I'm at the center of attention.
You must consider many things
if you want to get married.
If you want to keep it secret,
then it's hard
to get it done.
I want to invite
only a few close friends.
But someone will resent it eventually.
So in the end,
our wedding may be a social gathering.
We have to keep socializing,
toasting,
taking photos.
There may be a tiny hitch
that might end up trending.
But if we participate
in your unit's wedding,
such problems will no longer exist.
By then,
we'll be but a pair of newlyweds,
albeit with many more newlyweds.
So what?
There're so many
people getting married every day.
We are just
an ordinary couple
amongst them all.
A young couple.
But I think that
belongs to both of us.
Just you and I.
No disturbance.
No social media.
A wedding is between two people.
From you to me,
and from me to you.
I hope you don't mind
having such a wedding.
Jingjing.
I suddenly felt
that my previous proposal
wasn't very formal.
It was a bit rash.
I want to do it again.
To propose to you formally.
I didn't think so, but...
All right.
Qiao Jingjing.
We have known each other
for almost 16 years.
Because of my prejudices,
we have missed 13 years.
You may not regret it,
but I do.
Fortunately,
we still have decades ahead of us.
Please leave the rest of your time
to me.
With diligence...
and best effort,
I will be a good husband.
Good.
I will be good too.
Thank you.
Come in.
Ms. Wang?
Dr. Yu.
What brought you here?
Ms. Wang,
I'm here to sign up
for the group wedding.
Dr. Yu.
Well...
Do you
have a new girlfriend?
No.
Here's the form.
And the pen?
Thanks.
Yu Tu,
come to my office.
Mr. Zhang.
Yu Tu.
Come on in.
Take a seat.
Well...
Have you not...
No.
What?
I don't have a new girlfriend.
I wasn't about to ask you about that!
If you had a new one,
would the folks at that department
have called me about it?
I was about to ask you.
Do you have
any trouble
turning around
your finances?
If that troubles you,
my wife and I can help.
Thank you.
But I'm doing fine.
Jingjing and I,
we just want to make the wedding
a little simpler.
Did she agree to that?
She suggested it.
She suggested it?
She's been...
rather mischievous.
However,
she wants to keep things simple.
She thinks she'd get away from the media
if we hold it in the institute.
I know, that can't be possible.
So last night,
we discussed
that if it couldn't be kept secret,
then
it'd probably affect
my colleagues.
So we would back out.
That was what
I told
the secretary just now.
Keeping your nuptials a secret?
That's not a problem.
We are the best
at keeping secrets.
By then,
you'll show up
after the wedding ceremony
begins.
But what if
the secret was leaked midway?
What would you do?
Surely the wedding
won't be held in the institute.
It should be in a nearby hotel,
just like it's always been.
So it may not be kept secret.
So it's not in your unit, then?
If someone finds out,
we'll just run away?
See,
that's the benefit
of joining a group wedding.
If we hold our own wedding,
we can't run anywhere.
Then,
I'll have to get myself
a pair of sneakers.
And so will you.
I'll just get us one pair.
You'll carry me on your back?
Then I'll have to order
a 50-kg wedding dress.
Can you cut it down to half?
Make it 25 kg.
12.5 kg?
Plus me, that makes 100 kg!
I need to eat more.
It depends on when it gets leaked.
If it's early,
we'll switch plans.
If
the leak happens
only during the wedding....
We'll flee right away.
Once you're done hosting,
find another place
so we'll hold a second ball.
What are you kidding?
This is a wedding,
not a guerrilla gig!
This is simply nonsensical.
Mr. Zhang.
Have some water.
You're so sly.
You're setting me up?
Yu Tu.
At last,
you've completed
the most important event of your life.
I'm so happy for you.
Ms. Qiao is a fine young lady.
From now on,
you must treat her well.
I will.
(One month later)
(Love is in the Air)
(Shanghai Aerospace 10th Youth Group Wedding)
Families to the air show, get on the bus here.
We're about to set off soon.
They're coming now?
The bride is still wearing a veil.
No one seems to notice them.
Let's leave them alone.
Why are there some brides
who haven't put on their makeup?
Fix this for me.
There you go.
Okay.
There are so many people.
Are you nervous?
A little bit.
Give me your hand.
Are you still nervous?
I'm feeling much better.
Thank you.
Mr. Yu,
Ms. Qiao.
If you
need anything,
call me.
We've been
having our pictures taken outdoors.
Come in and take a rest,
and enjoy the atmosphere.
You don't have to mind us.
Okay.
We only found out today
that you're here for the wedding.
I'm really surprised.
But don't worry.
All our staff
will keep your secret.
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
As it should.
Are we going to gather up
at 10:28 later
to head for the banquet hall?
Yes.
(A Match Made in Heaven)
You haven't taken part in the rehearsal?
Then do you need me to explain
the whole wedding process
all over again
once you're in the hall?
Don't worry, I got that covered.
I have a lot of experience in this.
I will take good care of Mr. Yu.
I have BDS.
So it's okay.
Then you may excuse me.
We're expecting
a team of makeup artists
who seem to be late.
They'll be here as soon as they can.
What's going on?
I called them.
The makeup artists' ride
crashed into another vehicle.
Are they all right?
Yes.
But they're slightly injured.
So they won't make it.
So we're four makeup artists down.
Are we able to cope with it?
It's too late to find substitutes.
Well...
Go ask the hotel
and see what they can do.
All right.
We have a problem.
You see,
the makeup artists
we originally appointed
suddenly could not make it.
So now,
we're four makeup artists down.
So I'd like to ask
if anyone can volunteer
to be our makeup artist.
Can any brides apply makeup
on their own?
I don't usually wear makeup.
I'm not even good at makeup.
I'm no match for a makeup artist.
Besides,
Our marriage is such a big deal.
How can you suggest that?
It's okay...
Will we make it
if we get our other makeup artists
to speed up?
It's definitely too late.
Sorry.
I'll think of a way.
Do you guys
need a makeup artist?
I brought over a team.
Hello.
We are Ms Qiao's
makeup team.
May I ask who are the brides
that need us to make up?
These four.
Some grooms also need
to be tidied up a bit.
Will we make it?
The wedding will begin
in one hour.
The brides are very beautiful.
Of course we'll make it.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Yu Tu?
Mr. Wang.
You're part of the group wedding?
No way.
Your girlfriend's a celebrity, right?
I don't suppose you're a best man?
Today
I'm a groom too.
Congratulations.
It's Qiao Jingjing.
Qiao Jingjing? Where is she?
Let's get out of here.
Are Mom and Dad here?
Not yet.
Then where are we going?
You said it yourself
that we'd run if we were spotted.
Three...
two...
one.
Do we really have to run?
My parents will kill us for this!
We're not running.
Suddenly, I've gotten a little nervous.
What if I made a mistake in the process?
Let's go to practice again.
Come on.
Is this it?
(A Match Made in Heaven)
Yes.
We'll tie the knot inside.
Let's start rehearsing.
Before the wedding,
a staff member
will bring us here.
And then, one couple after another
will be admitted in order.
We are the last newlyweds
to enter.
Are we too far behind?
No.
I've always been the last on stage.
I thought so.
All right.
Let's go in.
So romantic!
This runway is in the shape of a spoon.
It's the Big Dipper.
You are now stepping on
its Alkaid star.
If I walk right down,
will the other six stars shine?
They'll light up wherever you walk.
Your aerospace people
are so romantic!
Who came up with this?
Those in charge created a group
from our unit.
I added it under my alternate account.
We all selected the cosmic theme.
But this runway,
I designed it.
It was you?
I don't believe it.
When I said
that I'd plan my own wedding,
did you not
think of anything?
Okay, stop running around.
Let's hit the stage.
Next,
we'll walk on the stage together.
We will stand here.
Looks like you've memorized it all.
You don't need me to navigate.
Today, I am your
BDS.
And then?
Then...
the emcee will announce...
that the wedding officially begins.
My mentor...
will witness our marriage.
Today,
(Shanghai Aerospace 10th Youth Group Wedding)
it is a great honor for me
to witness the marriages
of twelve new couples
from Shanghai Aerospace.
We have a huge crowd...
Our parents,
relatives and friends,
will watch us from the audience.
That is,
to meet
our beloved
life partners
who support each other.
We desire
a stargazer's romance.
We also desire
a well-grounded
happiness.
Next,
we'd like to invite
our newlyweds on stage
to face each other.
(A Match Made in Heaven)
We'll exchange rings...
and recite our vows.
Together we will shoulder
the responsibilities and obligations
that come with our marriage.
To honor our parents.
To teach our children.
To respect and love each other.
To trust and encourage each other.
(A Match Made in Heaven)
And to fulfil our marriage.
Finally
I may hug you...
and tell you...
that I love you.
Grooms,
you may kiss your brides.
♪You crossed the sea of ​​stars
and came with light♪
♪My heart is like the dust, and I couldn't
bear to stain the hemline♪
♪To love in a different way,
the fireworks are in the stars' good graces♪
♪I turn around and realize that
my heart is empty ♪
♪I miss the overflowing galaxy
surging into the sea♪
♪Even the fireworks desire
to give the stars a future♪
♪As long as you are around♪
♪Even the fireworks fear to bloom♪
♪Looking at you,
the light in your eyes dimmed♪
♪I look forward to every second♪
♪I can run toward the future with you♪
♪Regardless of everything♪
(Jingjing, you're great!)
(Blessings! Together forever!)
(Jingjing is so gorgeous!)
(I'm so envious!)
Qiao Jingjing has got married!
And it's in a group wedding.
No way.
This news is so fake.
The photos are out.
It is a group wedding.
I'm going to be a fan of hers.
A celebrity actually joined
a group wedding?
That's not something you get every day!
She surely loves her husband a lot.
Isn't her husband
that guy from
National Aerospace Research Institute?
No kidding!
But it's so low-key.
It must be true love.
Oh my God!
I want
her husband's picture in one minute!
Her husband is so handsome!.
Qiao Jingjing is so lucky.
He's a national scientific researcher.
I think we've got
the best brother-in-law!
I'm so envious of her.
(A group wedding?
OMG, that's amazing!)
(Oh, my goddess is married!
Congratulations!)
(Blessings!)
(Together forever!)
It's so quiet.
I'm going to post on Weibo
to tell my fans I'm married.
The phone, please?
No,
you post it for me.
Post what?
Post
I love you too.
♪I dreamed of starlight
pulling the sleeves♪
♪A white top
covering the thin shoulders♪
♪I have seen the wounds healed
with each passing year♪
♪There will always be people
running towards eternity♪
♪The bustling intersection♪
♪Looking back all of a sudden
under the dim light♪
♪I loved your eyes
looking at the starry sky♪
♪And I loved the universe in your heart♪
♪Time does not stop, remember the time
that we failed to treasure♪
♪The wind passes by the tall buildings
with no one awaiting it♪
♪I've dreamed of traveling
around the planet♪
♪Seeing the galaxy
pass through the clouds♪
♪I looked at the hills with sorrow♪
♪Will the exit of the dream lead
to the end of the starry sky?♪
♪Looking back all of a sudden♪
♪Which galaxy am I drifting on?♪
♪Looking into the distance,
which of the stars are your eyes?♪
♪It's out of reach,
so dazzling and hard to get♪
♪Time does not hold back, the spring
and autumn in the passing time♪
♪The wind sings the song of freedom
as I listen to the tenderness of time♪