[antifan_act, hashtag anti-fan, follow]
[Choi Tae-joon]
[Choi Soo-young]
[Hwang Chan-sung]
[Han Ji-an]
[Kim Min-gue]
[So I Married the Anti-Fan]
[Episode 15]
[The Undelivered Heart and Soul]
And I know many people are interested
in my relationship with Ms. Oh In-hyung.
Yes, we had a special relationship.
But she became a victim
to many misunderstandings and rumors
that she used me for her success.
I hope Ms. Oh will not suffer
from any speculations or rumors.
It'll only end if I do this.
In-hyung.
I came a long way with the wings I got
thanks to those lies.
[I realized I had nowhere to return to
with the wings made of lies.]
I admit to everything as reported,
and I will gladly accept any decisions
you make at your disposal.
Once again,
I'm truly sorry.
-Who-joon is here.
-He's here.
Are you like the Boy Who Cried Wolf?
-Anything else to say?
-Please move aside.
-There's breaking news!
-What?
-JJ got into an accident.
Did you hear of JJ
and Oh In-hyung's accident?
Reports say
Oh In-hyung tried to kill herself.
-Leave us a word!
-Is this related?
-Do you have anything to say?
-What's the truth?
Ji-hyang, can you find out what happened?
-Su-hwan.
[-Geun-young, did you watch the news?]
Yes, the press conference.
[No, not that.
Oh In-hyung tried to kill herself.]
-Who-joon!
-Wait, Who-joon!
-Say something!
-Who-joon!
-Please tell us something!
-Anything to say?
[Woojin Hospital]
-Please say something!
-What happened?
-Are you involved in this incident?
-Who-joon!
[If I went with Jae-joon back then,]
[if I didn't give up on In-hyung,]
[if I told these truths earlier,]
[what would've happened
to the three of us?]
[Operating Room]
["Who-joon: My Life Had Been Fake"]
["I'm Deeply Sorry"]
["Who-joon's First Love, Oh In-hyung
and JJ Hospitalized After a Car Accident"]
["Did Oh In-hyung
Try to Take Her Own Life?"]
["What's the Truth Behind the Accident?]
["Did Oh In-hyung
Try to Take Her Own Life?"]
[Everyone has fallen.]
[It's all my fault.]
[Operating Room]
Thankfully, the surgery went well.
But they're still unconscious.
Mr. Choi's condition is
far worse than Ms. Oh's condition.
They've been sent to the ICU.
Let's keep an eye on them.
Thank you.
Please...
["Did Oh In-hyung
Try to Take Her Own Life?"]
[Are Jae-joon and In-hyung all right?]
[Jae-joon]
Jae-joon, you aren't
such a bad person to me.
Why didn't you tell me that
a little sooner?
What you just said right now
felt like something you'd say
to humor a jerk and a rebel.
[Intensive Care Unit]
[Woojin Hospital]
Are you all right?
How are In-hyung and Jae-joon?
They're in the ICU.
I'm so sorry. It's all my fault.
Geun-young.
I have too much on my mind right now.
I'm so sorry,
but please give me some time.
[ICU Precautions]
Joon, how long will you stay here?
We need to wait and see
how they do, so let's go home...
They'll wake up.
Yes, I know.
I'm sorry to bring this up now,
but there are some problems
with your advertisements and movies.
I'll go meet the advertisers first.
I'll go myself.
Are you sure?
I won't avoid anything anymore.
Let's go.
Okay.
[Two-faced Who-joon, Know thyself,
How do you call yourself a human?]
[Who-joon the liar, retire!]
-Who-joon, you!
-You liar!
[Who-joon the liar, retire! Liar Who-joon]
-Move back!
-How can you lie to us?
[Who-joon the liar, retire!]
-Take a step back.
-You're the worst!
[Who-joon the liar, retire!]
Please step back.
-Stop right there!
-Step back!
I can't believe those people.
-Let's just go, Ji-hyang.
-They're awful.
-Stop!
-You liar, retire!
-Please say something!
-You need to retire!
-Did anything else happen?
-No, sir.
I'm sorry.
Our legal team is
urging us to file a lawsuit against you.
Please give it some time.
People will quiet down soon.
It's not about what people think.
It's about your image.
We can't cover for you anymore.
You should get ready
to pay for the damage.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
I doubt they'll file a lawsuit.
I'm sorry, Ji-hyang.
I made you pay compensation
as soon as you became a CEO.
Don't say that, big star.
I set up a meeting with the film company.
Let's face everything one by one.
Okay.
Joon, In-hyung woke up.
Who-joon.
I'm so relieved.
What happened?
What happened to Jae-joon?
He'll wake up soon too.
You woke up, after all.
It's my fault.
It wasn't your fault, okay?
We just
all forgot what's really important.
["How Will the Boy Who Cried Wolf End?"]
What about Joon? The public will
turn their back on him at once.
He'll have to deal with that,
and can you deal with him
when he's in that spot?
[Mr. Joon]
[Can he really deal with this?]
[He's having such a tough time,]
[but what am I doing here?]
[Happy birthday, Geun-young.]
This is when.
I knew something was up back then.
Goodness, of course.
You have a good hunch.
Come on, stop that.
What's wrong, my fairy?
Gosh, what fairy? Stop it.
My goodness.
[Chief Director: Cancel the show!]
What is it?
The aftermath of his press conference.
We're to cancel the show.
He's telling us to cancel it altogether?
I guess the higher-ups
already made a decision.
He told us to air
the last episode this week.
I can't believe the amount of trouble
I went through while doing this show.
The top celebrity Who-joon falls,
then I'm told to cancel the show.
I can't believe
how these things keep happening.
Stop editing the show.
We can't put it out anyway.
["So I Married the Anti-Fan"]
[He made it through,
but I'm not sure when he'll wake up.]
In-hyung woke up in good health.
So
I hope you wake up soon too.
I had to clean out Mr. Choi's office.
Most things were just office supplies,
so I took care of that.
But these seemed important,
so I brought them here.
Thank you.
[I'll remember the day we first met.
The streets, the moment.]
[Please come back to me.]
[He missed those days too.]
I was going to leave this world.
Why are you lying here like this?
Why didn't you just let me be?
Why did you do that?
["Oh In-hyung Wakes Up,
but Who Saved Her? Who-joon or JJ?]
What a relief.
[Mr. Joon]
[I miss you.
I'll see you at the park at 7 p.m.]
Once again, I'm sorry.
Could we postpone the release date?
That's not easy to do.
We're about to premiere soon.
But if we released it now,
we'll all go under together.
I'm so sorry.
I'll figure out
what I can do to pay for the damage.
Money isn't going to cut it.
The director is coming over right now.
Let's wait.
All right.
[Film]
[Mr. Joon]
[The person you have reached
is not available. Please...]
[Just Lee Geun-young]
[I'm sorry.
Something came up, so I can't make it.]
[I'll call you later.]
Why isn't he coming?
I must be out of my mind.
It's snowing.
Who-joon, I'm sorry. I'm a little late.
[Film]
Please.
All right, then.
Let's have a discussion
about this trouble we're facing.
I have no excuses to make.
[Mr. Joon]
[I'm sorry.
Something came up, so I can't make it.]
[I'll call you later.]
[It's all right.]
[Don't worry about me and go on.]
[Just Lee Geun-young]
[I'll take care of everything soon
and run to you.]
Joon.
I don't think we can avoid the lawsuit.
We can't help it, then.
I need to find a lawyer.
Get some rest.
Everything will be fine.
[Cho-Yoon Law Firm: Cho Hae-yoon]
It's him.
He's your father.
[Cho-Yoon Law Firm: Cho Hae-yoon]
[Cho-Yoon Law Firm]
[CEO's Office]
[CEO Cho Hae-yoon]
How may I help you today?
I wanted to discuss something with you.
I'm sure you've seen the news.
Yes, I read articles
that things have been hectic.
What's the problem?
I'm about to enter a lawsuit.
I have to pay some compensations.
I see.
What's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
You've been staring at this ring.
Oh, it looked similar to a ring I had.
Then take a closer look.
Where did you get this?
I'm not sure
if it's the ring you're looking for.
Why do you need that ring?
It's not a big deal.
I just lost it a while ago.
Why did you lose it?
Sorry?
This ring.
No, your son.
It's not a big deal?
Once you abandon us,
me and my mom, then is that just it?
Then you're...
I shouldn't have come here.
I never abandoned you.
The ring is mine,
but the one who gave that ring
to your mother was him.
-That means...
-Yes.
He's your father.
He was my best friend.
Your mother, him, and I had been
good friends.
They were deeply in love,
but the problem was your father's family.
They were rather affluent.
He walked out of his family
and moved in with me.
Then engraved those letters on my ring
and proposed to her.
-Then these letters mean...
-You are my all.
Only the first letters.
Then why did they
fall apart?
His family didn't give up easily.
Your mother had much self-respect,
so it was tough on her.
In the end, they broke up.
Then his family
rushed to have him married.
And just before he was about to marry,
she found out she was pregnant with you.
Nobody knew about you back then.
Someone with your mother's character
wouldn't have wanted to hold him down
by using a child as an excuse.
And yes, that's how she disappeared.
Mom must have had a tough time.
So my father.
Where is he?
Goodness, Geun-young.
-Goodness.
-Hey.
You wouldn't pick up your phone.
My goodness, seriously.
Why are you two here?
You wouldn't pick up your phone, you brat.
My gosh, look at this girl.
I told you
she'd be looking awful like this.
Are you badly ill?
I heard he's on the news and stuff.
Is it because of him?
No, I just caught a cold. I'm fine.
Are you sure? It's the first time
you stayed in bed all day
after your dog died in elementary school,
yet you say you're fine?
Did the TV station
bother you again because of him?
Those scumbags. I'll get...
No, please. It's not like that.
Enough is enough.
She'll collapse any minute now.
Hey, you need to go lie down.
-Yes, get a good rest.
-Goodness.
We brought everything you like,
so eat, sleep, eat again, sleep,
then sleep, eat, then eat and sleep again.
[He was never that strong.]
[I figured he'd live a good life
in his arranged marriage,]
[but he must've been tortured inside.]
[It has been ten years]
[since he left us.]
[Rest in peace, Choi Seong-wook]
[The last time I saw your mother was
at his funeral.]
[That's the first time I found out
she had you.]
[I heard she cut off all ties,]
[then left the country with you.]
[Have you been well?]
[Your son came to visit.]
[I thought it was about time
he found out.]
[Joon.]
It's me, Mom.
I'm glad I'm a tall guy.
Geun-young, get up. Have some porridge.
You didn't know this was out?
Right, I guess so.
You need a new tube.
I also need to fix the weak water pressure
in your bathroom too.
I'll fix everything, so don't worry.
Goodness, where are you going this late?
I need to get a new fluorescent tube.
Goodness, I need to fix this door too.
You can tell me everything.
So what's going on?
Is it really because of him?
No.
Then what's he doing right now?
I don't know what's going on,
but people say everything was a lie.
Is that true?
He's not like that, Mom.
I'm not really sure.
Well, I figured
since you two
came to visit us at home together,
so I thought you two were close.
Jae-joon.
I found...
my dad today.
He went a little far away, though.
Jae-joon, get up.
Jae-joon.
You have to wake up, okay?
You're only starting to feel better.
Where are you going?
I feel suffocated to be locked up at home.
I'll go out for just a short while.
Goodness.
Come here.
It's cold.
Don't be late.
Okay. I'll be back soon.
All right.
Why did you get me these?
I heard giving shoes is like
asking them to leave.
You're practically begging me to run away.
No, if you run away
with the shoes I gave you last time,
you can come back in these.
["Top of Space"]
-Hey, Ji-hyang.
[-Joon.]
[Jae-joon woke up.]
[More Beautiful Than Flowers]
Geun-young.
Have you been well?
I've been all right.
What about you?
I'm the same.
How's Joon? Is he doing okay?
Well, I doubt he would be all right.
I think he's holding out pretty well.
So? Do you get along with him?
Remember those shoes?
The limited-edition shoes
that you threw out
in front of my restaurant.
How could I forget those shoes?
Those shoes are what got me here today.
Joon got mad at me saying
why I got you such huge shoes.
He knew about us?
He gave you a pair of shoes
as a present, right?
He asked me for your size
when he bought those.
Do they fit well?
He's up?
His frontal lobe was damaged
due to the shock from the accident.
His loss of speech
may be temporary.
Loss of speech?
Yes, let's keep an eye on him.
Loss of speech...
Why?
Why? Why did you get into my life?
If it hadn't been for you...
[I spent every moment of my life for you.
And now,]
[there's nothing more I can do for you.]
It'll only end if I do this.
In-hyung.
Let's see.
Are you playing hwatu all alone?
No, I'm just playing with it.
Let's see. Yes. And then...
Right.
Joon told me this.
He said you're like December in hwatu.
Mom.
What are the cards for December?
December?
Let's see.
Yes, there they are. These cards.
What do they mean?
Tears.
December Rain is
a sad Bright card with no presence.
The youngest,
Double Junk is way more popular.
So? What about December?
Well, someone said
I'm like December cards of hwatu.
-A surprise, then.
-What?
-A surprise?
-Yes.
December Rain hides quietly,
then gets together with other Bright cards
and gives you scores, so it's a surprise.
If you let it slide,
you will end up paying the price.
You only miss it when it's gone,
so it's a rather sad Bright card.
So once this card comes out,
you don't feel comfortable leaving it,
so you'll only feel rest assured
once you take it.
What is this? This person
doesn't want others to have you.
But feels too much pressure
to take you. Wait.
Who is this?
-That scumbag.
-Who is it?
-Who is this guy?
Whatever.
Go back inside. It's cold.
You should stay one more day.
No, we can't stay away from home
for too long.
You're impossible.
So if your shooting is over,
when will you visit home again?
After I figure some things out.
I have to look for a job,
and I'm signing up for English classes.
I'm always here for you,
so you live doing whatever you want.
Yes, if all fails,
you can quit and come home.
Start writing again.
Should I?
Gosh, I'm so glad
I have my mom and dad here for me.
Go home.
Oh, and about that guy.
When people criticize someone,
the parents feel heartbroken.
I was going to cut off all the TV station
wiring when people did that to you.
So you be nice to him.
I'll do that.
Let's go already. She's tired.
-Bye.
Your decision is
always the right decision.
Have a safe trip.
You can't give me to other people?
He has such an awful way of talking.
[Ms. No]
[Geun-young, today's episode
will be the last one.]
[Things ended up like that.]
[Everyone regrets.]
[Nobody is perfect.]
[That's why
I'm not going to do that anymore.]
[Someone told me]
[not to be afraid,
that this too shall pass.]
[So please don't be afraid.]
[Geun-young is touched and speechless.]
[You helped me return to who I really am.]
[Today is...]
[It's almost their last moment.]
[the last day we spend together.]
[-It feels weird. Doesn't it?
-It does.]
[Don't forget
all the time we spent together.]
[How could I? I had such a tough time.]
[You're right.]
I miss her to death.
[I want to run over to you,]
[but please give me a little more time.]
[They say goodbye serenely.]
[I'll be here living my own life.]
[Business English Academy]
There's a great tteokbokki place
in Dangjin, actually.
Goodness, Just Geun-young?
When I heard
all those bad things about you,
it didn't feel too great.
And I felt a little guilty.
It's comforting to know you felt that way.
I felt bad thinking
you might have wanted your revenge
because of me.
To be honest, you weren't fired
because of Who-joon.
-What?
-Our magazine company was
getting ready for layoffs.
We wanted to stop the company
from going bankrupt,
so we began to downsize.
Then why me?
I took many of your article proposals.
It felt uncomfortable to have you around.
That's why you were
the first to be dismissed.
I'm sorry.
Then why didn't you just say so?
How can I be frank
about something like that?
At the very least,
you got your severance pay.
We're all about to be dismissed
even without that.
Isn't that a bit comforting?
I need to catch my class.
Goodbye, then.
I hope we could meet again next time
comfortably, Geun-young.
See you around.
[Staff Only]
My debut?
You said it's Jae-joon's turn.
Joon, this song suits you better.
And we need to turn someone into a star
for another to debut.
But still, I can't do that.
You know how hard
Jae-joon worked for this.
I can't do that, Mr. Bae. I'm sorry.
I'm already set on this, so it's final.
Jae-joon.
[Staff Only]
You don't have to make such a long face.
You can get your big break first.
It's all right.
I hope it goes well.
[Girin Hall]
You said you'll let me debut.
Let's go by the order, please.
I became a trainee first.
So what? Do you want to ruin his future?
It's a done deal.
This isn't your last chance.
Don't be like this.
Yes, not yet.
I guess he has nothing to say.
Transfer him to a quiet and scenic place
once he gets discharged.
All right.
Did you say you had a younger brother?
Yes, sir.
What kind of an older brother are you?
Me? I'm just a normal guy.
Just an older brother
who's not any special.
An older brother.
Do you think
he doesn't want to say anything?
He might have all kinds of things to say,
but he just can't.
The doctor said it might be temporary,
so let's give him some time.
I hope time passes by quickly.
In-hyung.
Don't feel so guilty anymore,
and go back to your place.
I'm sure that's what he'd want.
I should.
Back to my place.
I didn't get to show people
everything from the shooting,
but I'm satisfied with it.
You know,
you become satisfied way too quickly.
That's your problem.
I'm way too quick.
Goodness.
What's wrong?
-I'll be back.
-Yes, ma'am.
Are you not satisfied either?
But still.
Doesn't Who-joon seem different now
than when you two began?
Did you know things will become like this
from the beginning?
I told you to try reading
"Pride and Prejudice".
We all cover ourselves
with prideful wrapping paper.
The moment I saw that photo of him
getting hit with your shoe,
I kind of saw something similar
in both of you.
[Two-faced Who-joon]
[Trash Bin]
[Mr. Han told me
to read "Pride and Prejudice."]
[The Pride and Prejudice...]
[Perhaps to him,
our beginning seemed to be]
[about Who-joon's Two Faces]
[revolving around]
[Who-joon's pride
and my prejudice on who he is.]
[Where do pride and prejudice begin?
I was confident of...]
[I'll remember the day we first met.
The streets, the moment.]
[And finally, I realized
deeming everyone as bad...]
[for having two sides is
our pride and prejudice.]
[The Pride and Prejudice
about Who-joon's Two Faces]
Wow, Geun-young. When did you write this?
You're such a loyal person.
Please publish it on "Wonder Woman."
That's about the only thing I can do
at the moment.
Anyway, so Who-joon didn't get you fired?
I ran into Mean Moon-hee
at the English academy.
She told me
I was going to be fired anyway.
Wait, Mean Moon-hee is
taking English lessons?
Your company will lay people off
by your proficiency in English.
Man, I can't believe Mean Moon-hee is
only trying to save herself again.
Su-hwan.
Please do this for me.
Don't worry. I'll have it published,
then I'll give it out to reporters.
I'll call you.
[This is the end to our story
of your pride and my prejudice.]
[I hope the world
tunes into my story just this once.]
Here.
What's this?
A present for you, Geun-young.
[One of our crew members
didn't know how to turn off the camera.]
[I retrieved it.]
[I'm the only one who saw it,
so don't worry.]
How did this...
I miss you.
There are so many stars.
There are.
So? Do you want me to get you one?
I am
doing very well.
As always.
[Mr. Joon]
Why have I been crying so much
since that moment? Gosh.
[Mr. Joon]
If you were going to cry like that,
why did you say you can wait well?
How did you...
I was worried that you were gone.