(People are always used to judging new things)
(by experience.)
And at first my parents didn't agree either.
The same with my parents.
My parents also didn't quite agree.
It's normal.
Among us,
except for K
who has never mentioned his parents,
the parents of the others
are all quite assertive that
they are against it.
What's so interesting about that?
Your parents aren't
supportive of you playing e-sports?
My dad is all right.
My mom...
(Subconsciously accuse it.)
What e-sports?
It's just playing games.
You kids
are not only addicted to games
and lag behind in your studies,
but also find high-sounding excuses.
(Refuse it.)
Get your ass over here.
Bastard.
(Few people believe in their passion,)
(nor do they understand)
(what this love means)
(to them.)
How dare you not answer my call?
Come back!
- No, no.
- You come back to me.
=Falling into Your Smile=
=Episode 24=
Come on, Auntie, Uncle. Please have some tea.
You're here for…?
That brat.
Pig brain.
He ran away when he saw me.
You go get that brat over here.
Don't be angry.
What exactly do you want from K?
Boss.
No, no, no.
- We.
- Rui.
Just call me Rui.
Boss Rui.
It's like this.
Nowadays, the national policy is better for us.
Our township
has given us an extra piece of land.
This boy's brother just got married.
We are considering building a new house
for his brother.
He can't live with us
all the time.
Don't you think so?
Yes, yes.
Young people do need their own space.
A few years ago,
his father injured his right hand
at work.
Now he can't do any heavy work.
Can't find a job either.
All kinds of things in the family,
big or trivial,
all require money.
Think about it.
Where can we get the money?
Yes.
We also know
it's not easy for him
to work far away from hometown.
What's not easy for him?
His brother lives in the countryside.
How can he compare with him?
Now,
his brother is desperate for money.
He wants to build the house.
We just wanted to borrow some money from him.
Why wouldn't he want to help him?
He didn't even answer our phone calls.
Now he's not happy about it.
We can't even see him, think about it.
Who does he think he is?
We are his parents.
How could he not answer the phone?
As soon as he saw me, he ran away.
It hurts us!
But then again,
if we had choice,
I wouldn't have come here to find him.
You are the leader of my child, right?
Kind of.
It's good that you were there just now.
I just want to ask you,
how much money can he earn from
the games he plays?
Well.
We have signed a contract with the players.
The salary is confidential to the public.
In theory,
it should be him to tell you that.
I'm not supposed to say it.
What's confidential?
I am his father.
Everything he owns is given
by me and his mother.
That's right.
I just want to know,
how much money can he earn from
the games he plays?
Well.
I'm really not supposed to say it.
Stop it.
This is all the savings I've had
since I started playing professionally.
In addition to the money
I give you every month
and my daily expenses,
the rest is all here.
You can take it all.
Do whatever you want to do.
Build a house for him.
Pay a bride price.
Go gambling.
Waste it all.
There is no need to make up so many reasons.
Now all this is yours.
Dad.
Mom.
I really thank you for raising me.
But I ask you not to come to the base anymore.
Don't bother me
and my teammates here again.
You brat.
What are you doing?
K.
Rui.
Please
book tickets for their return trip.
Deduct the money from my next month's salary.
This brat is becoming
more and more disobedient.
How can he do this?
(Once you throw it away,)
(you may never get it back.)
There are things that
you don't want to get back.
Ever since I was a kid,
everything I do has always been wrong
while my brother has always been right.
When I wanted to study,
he told me I wasn't cut out for it.
I was told to learn a trade
and work with my father.
I didn't want to.
I wanted to go to school.
That's when I developed
my game-playing skills,
making money by playing for others.
Tong Yao.
You know what?
In fact, at that time,
I didn't like playing games at all.
I thought it was just a tool to make money.
If I hadn't met Ming later,
I might never have known
what e-sports was.
Then I got into it.
I understood it.
But to my parents,
it was still just a tool to make money.
Actually, it's understandable, right?
We just need to communicate more
with the older generation.
My parents are the same.
Haven't you seen them?
Tong Yao.
We're not the same.
How?
Your parents are good.
They love you very much,
while my parents…
So now I really have nothing
except for e-sports.
You still have us.
Tong Yao.
I'm sorry.
I was against you before.
And what I said
when your parents came to the base.
It's been so long.
Why do you still remember?
I've long forgotten it.
Let's go, K.
Let's go back to the base.
Why did you call me here so early?
Yao, I'm impulsive.
What's wrong?
Come, I'll show you.
Look at this.
(YQCB e-Sports Club Equity Transfer Agreement)
What's this?
The Equity Transfer Agreement of YQCB.
(Assignee: Chen Jinyang)
Transferee, Chen Jinyang?
You really bought YQCB?
Of course it's true.
Could I forge that?
Boss, I bought the RIO you wanted.
What flavor do you want?
Peach flavor.
She... She really bought your team?
Of course she did.
She's now the owner and manager of our team.
This...
Does this make sense?
Yes, it does.
I've thought about it carefully.
Although
I have no talent for games.
And I don't know anything about this industry.
But no one can deny that I'm smart.
Everything can be learned.
And I also think
the e-sports industry is promising.
My dad also thinks
it's a very promising investment.
My honey is smart.
Of course.
I'll go back and digest the news first.
Don' go.
I still have something to discuss with you.
What is it?
Didn't you tell me last time
K's parents came to the base?
I found out later
many parents are just like his parents.
They think e-sports is just playing games
through which they can make
a lot of easy money.
Ai Jia thought the same way before.
Don't mention me.
Although I used to love to play games,
ever since I've started
playing professionally,
I find it's too hard.
It is.
There is no such thing as
playing and making easy money
at the same time.
Many people can't see
the pain and pressure
behind professional players.
That's why there are so many parents
who don't understand
their children playing e-sports.
Bestie, you've grown up.
Of course.
Do you think I'm just
a boss who would have
a relationship with the players?
And
ever since I bought the team,
I've always had an idea.
I must do something for the team.
So
I now have a great idea.
You,
you don't want to buy ZGDX too, do you?
And then unify the gaming world?
I'm not as rich as Cheng.
I'm planning to
hold a carnival for you and Ai Jia.
A carnival?
Why are we going?
We're going to the event
held by the next-door team?
Because that's me and Ai Jia's alma mater.
So I have to go.
Well.
That's not appropriate, is it?
We have such a tight schedule these days.
Carnival.
I told Cheng about the last event
and he didn't even agree.
I'm sure he…
Okay.
Carnival?
Tong Yao,
is the cafeteria of your alma mater good?
Foodie.
University carnival?
Is that a show?
Douchebag.
This is a stage to show the charm
and ecology of e-sports.
Look at all of you,
staying up late every night for training.
Either you have dark circles under your eyes
or dry and rough skin.
Where's the charm?
Tong Yao.
Your recent skin condition
is also not so good.
I've recently been using a hydrating mask.
It's excellent for moisturizing.
Why don't you try it too?
Come on.
Try it yourself tonight.
Okay, I'll try it after I go back.
I'm sure you'll be able to
face everyone
in your best state.
(E-Sports Carnival)
(Shen Gang University)
Today, we are honored to invite
two current members of
(E-sports Carnival)
famous gaming teams, ZGDX and YQCB
to our event today.
And now
let's give a warm applause
to YQCB's manager
Chen Jinyang.
Ai Jia.
Tong Yao.
All right, please take your seats.
Okay, now it's time for audience interaction.
Are there any students who want to
ask questions to your senior schoolmates?
You can raise your hand.
Okay, this girl.
Hello, Tong Yao.
I'd like to ask you a question.
Did you go into playing games
because of the games themselves
or because of your boyfriend at the time?
It was indeed him
who brought me into the gaming world.
But it was me
who took up e-sports
as a profession and a dream.
So in a relationship,
if one person likes to play games
while the other hates it,
does that mean
they are destined not to be together?
I'll answer this question.
I believe that in this world
there are no two people
who are exactly the same,
especially between lovers.
Just like
me and Ai Jia.
One of us
is a professional player
who is expected to reach the Finals,
while the other is just a girl
spending money on game skins
who doesn't even know
what equipment to buy in a game.
I really don't like to play games.
Like many girls,
I don't understand the fun of sitting
in front of the computer for hours,
just tapping a few keys back and forth.
Of course.
Ai Jia doesn't understand
what I do either.
He doesn't understand
why I only have two feet,
but have two hundred pairs of shoes.
I only have one mouth,
but have 500 lipsticks.
And they look all almost the same.
But he still praises.
Even if he's in front of the computer
for ten hours a day,
he can still tell
I've changed my hairstyle and colored it.
My clothes look better today
than they did yesterday.
His attention to me
never gets taken away by the game.
So do I.
I don't know the game.
But I know
e-sports is a kind of sportsmanship.
It's not just about
hiding in the game, flaunting one's ability.
He has just changed a way
to prove his strength to the world.
Just like now,
Ai Jia's taste has improved dramatically.
And I
have also found the direction
of my future career.
Okay.
Okay, any more questions from the students?
This female student.
I'd like to ask you a question, Miss Tong Yao.
How did you manage to
become the Lord of Kyoto in the game
and at the same time,
still be able to balance your studies
and be an outstanding graduate?
I think it's a matter of
scheduling your time wisely.
Choose your priorities in accordance with
your status.
If you're a student,
you have to
finish all your classes
before planning your time wisely.
Nothing can be an excuse.
So when I was a student,
I studied twice as hard.
Because I didn't want those who
knew little about e-sports to say
playing games was just sapping my spirit.
Of course.
Now we have more or less
improved our understanding,
and reduced our misunderstandings of it.
According to the data,
in the last year,
the World Championships have
reached tens of millions of views.
And this figure
is actually bigger than
that of many traditional athletic projects.
We also know that nowadays
more and more universities,
for example,
Communication University of China,
have now created a major in e-sports
to provide professional talents
for the future e-sports industry.
Yes.
So I'm very grateful to my bestie Jinyang
for proposing to hold this carnival.
We hope that
you can understand more about
what e-sports really is,
through getting in touch
with professional players.
We will also try to
change your views on players,
make Chinese e-sports proud
and let the world see
the power of our Chinese players.
Okay, this male student.
Hello, Mr. Ai Jia.
I'm a fan of yours.
I heard a lot about you
when I was enrolled.
I want to know
how did you persevere until now
when the people around you
didn't understand e-sports,
or even rejected it?
When you were alone against everyone,
did you ever think about giving up?
I…
never thought about giving up.
But I did
once hurt
my family
because of my love for gaming.
My experience, I guess
is like that of a little bastard.
Disobedient,
wanton, reckless.
Gave up on school.
Ran away from home.
Aren't you going to leave?
Go.
You've grown up anyway.
You're independent now.
You won't listen to anything I say.
All you do is play games all the time.
Playing games.
How many times have I told you?
Have you ever listened?
Tell me,
what future can you have by playing games?
What can you contribute to society?
This is what I like to do.
I won't give it up.
Mom.
Can't you understand me?
I understand you?
What can I understand about you?
I'm a teacher.
I can teach so many children well.
Why can't I teach you well?
Let me ask you one last time.
Do you still play games?
Yes.
Okay.
Get out of here.
After you leave,
don't ever come back.
So,
from the day I made this my career,
I told myself
I would never go home
without accomplishing something.
I want everyone to know
not everything that
goes against the norm is wrong.
I can be responsible for my own choice.
I'm aware that
many people in real life
don't understand our profession.
They think that the e-sports industry
is just a way to mess around
and play games.
It's no different from
being in an internet café.
People may just see the rewards
given in live stream,
the craze of fans,
and those millions of annual bonuses.
But I want to ask you,
is this all true?
Like all sports,
e-sports
is a competition between all the top players.
And the training and pressure resistance
that these top players go through
are definitely not any easier
than athletic sports,
no worse than any of them.
A senior player once said
our world
is as cruel as the other sports,
because there are so many cases of failure.
Those who have talent
are not necessarily able to play well,
those who play well can not
necessarily be remembered.
Those remembered by people
don't necessarily have good results.
So
those professional players
who have achieved success
have put in more effort than others.
Their efforts determine
the ceiling of their success.
Just like all of you,
doing exercises, memorizing words
and preparing for IELTS.
If you fail,
will you regret
playing games in the first place?
Although e-sports is a game,
the process to its success is not a game.
I tried my best.
Even if I failed, I wouldn't regret it.
Youth is not an excuse to cover up mistakes.
But we do have youth only once.
Once you decide to do it,
you must have the courage to never look back.
Okay, classmates.
This year's championship competition
has already started.
The Final will be held in Shanghai.
This is a great honor.
Please be sure to cheer for your schoolmates
and for Chinese e-sports.
Go! Go! Go!
Where's Jinyang?
She's still busy.
Then let's go first.
What's the hurry?
Auntie, you're too kind.
Hello, Ms. Lin.
When you graduated,
you said you didn't know
what was right for you,
and now you've become so good
within less than a year.
You were even invited back to give a speech.
No.
It's all because of Jinyang and Ai Jia.
Ai Jia.
Mom.
I didn't expect you to come.
I was asked to come by Jinyang.
She and I had a long talk
about you,
about e-sports,
about this business of yours.
I didn't think I would come either.
It was Jinyang who convinced me.
In fact, even up until now,
I still don't understand
e-sports,
or clubs you're talking about.
But there is one thing I do understand.
My son has grown up.
He can also
make the right choice
for his own life.
I believe
he's growing up.
He will succeed.
I have a class to teach. I'll leave now.
Auntie.
Mom.
I haven't been back to school
for a long time either.
Why don't I
walk around with you?
Sure, sure.
Come on.
Let's go.
You go ahead.
I'll wait for you here.
If you're free tomorrow,
can you come back to visit your father?
Bring Jinyang with you.
Let's have a family dinner
together.
Let's talk about that later.
You're that busy?
I have to make money, right?
(Wu Zihan Cultural Communication
Ambassador of Shandong Province)
(Sent to Lu Sicheng)
(It'd be wonderful)
(if I have my picture up there too one day.)
(Don't be in a hurry.)
(You will have everything you want.)
(Yuan Shiren
Secretary of the Chinese Medical Association)
Explosive news!
There's big news!
- What's wrong?
- Hurry up.
- Have ZGDX's Double Carry players started a relationship?
- What's wrong?
I felt something wrong before.
As a girl,
I think eyes can't deceive.
Let me see.
This.
Mentioning Tong Yao the first time
in the MVP interview,
Lu Sicheng praised her
as a very capable player.
Eyes down with tender expression
and a faint smile on his lips.
The classic motion picture is from
when Tong Yao's shoe was stepped on by Chubby
and she was then lifted up by Lu Sicheng.
It is essential.
Look at this and this.
Look at this.
They were caught by the fans
when they went to the movies
for the first time.
Tong Yao tilted her head
and looked at Lu Sicheng.
Fans quickly found out that they were in love.
It's amazing!
What are you looking at?
The carnival thing is on the hot search?
No, no, no.
I'll show you the photos.
Isn't it exciting?
Oh, my God!
This…
How come such a good thing
as the carnival hasn't gotten on the trending topic,
and this has?
When did the Double Carry players
in our team get together?
As our team manager,
I should say no one informed me of that before.
Tong Yao, what's going on?
Why do the people of our team
get to know it later
than the netizens in E-sports Industry Farm?
When did you guys start
sneaking around in love?
Traces can be hidden.
But the way they look at
each other can't fool anyone.
Can't fool anyone.
What look?
The netizens are like Sherlock Holmes.
(Sent to Lu Sicheng)
(Downstairs.)
Either they're
definitely together,
or Cheng is unrequitedly in love with Tong Yao.
Tong Yao.
We dare not ask Cheng.
You tell us now.
There are already netizens betting on
getting upside down to eat shit.
Look at this.
What is this?
This eye was almost completely filled with water.
Oh my God!
It's a PS photo, right?
I'm gonna throw up.
I have to send it to my mom
for her to appreciate.
Summer is here.
It's that time of year again
when your oldest son
has his annual crush on girls.
In past years he hid it well.
This year he probably didn't manage to hide it.
What's all the noise in the middle of the night?
You won't let me sleep.
Someone at the e-sports industry farm
says you had a crush on Tong Yao.
It's obvious they say we're having an affair.
No.
The post initiator says
she can see from your eyes
that you had a crush on Tong Yao.
Tong Yao was watching the game
while you were watching her.
Yes, I have a crush on her.
Boring.
It was just a joke.
It's not like anyone's
really saying you're together.
My Cat is hopeless.
(Lu Sicheng)
(Don't worry.)
(I'm here.)
Go get your brain changed.
(Onmyoji Arena)
♪Across a thousand distances♪
Okay.
The audience on site and off the screen,
hello!
This is the scene of the National League 2020
of the Onmyoji Arena.
I'm Dudou.
I'm today's commentator Qiu.
(Today we have CK versus Red Arrow.)
(A strong match.)
(Another exciting game.)
(We can look forward to
the fancy moves of Yang again.)
♪In the middle of the vortex,
can you use your antidote♪
♪To save my heartbeat♪
♪The sea of time♪
(Look, it's Cheng and Tong Yao.)
(Is there a sequel to the "E-sports White Snake"?)
♪A rekindling confession for you♪
This... this...
♪I'm afraid of the sudden silence in the air♪
I forgot what I was going to say
with you singing.
But these people
are really good at making trouble.
It's embarrassing.
What are you embarrassed about?
Didn't you say that you don't read posts
on the e-sports industry farm?
I... well...
Well...
I definitely don't read them
after the game commentary,
just like many players
who will also uninstall
the App on their cell phone
after losing the game.
They're afraid of being scolded.
Yes.
But
if there's some big news,
I will still pay attention to it.
After all, as a commentator,
I should catch up with the latest news, right?
I really underestimated you.
(While following the event…)
It's too embarrassing to sit here.
How can I play games in the future?
Bear with it for a little longer.
It's about to start.
No one will say anything after it starts.
(It seems that you are experienced in)
(reading posts
on the e-sports industry farm in secret.)
Isn't that Lu Sicheng?
ZGDX also came to observe the game today?
Yang,
that scene during the Spring Playoffs
is still fresh in my mind.
Yang.
I have to remind you today.
You have to hold on today.
(The director is messing around again.)
Recently the relationship
between Smiling and Chessman
has really drawn a lot of attention.
That's right.
They look like a perfect match in appearance.
Wait a minute.
As I predict,
something big is going to happen today.
Beware of being beaten by fans after the game.
(Photographer.)
(You have a bone to pick with me, do you?)
(It seems I should not have come today.)
What? The photographer must be messing around.
What's he up to?
(But today is special.)
(It's two contestants.)
(I wonder what they will do.)
What are you looking forward to?
Kissing?
Are you stupid?
So stupid.
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
What's going on here?
You didn't report it to the club either.
Mom, look!
(This love means)
Am I being cheated on?
(I don't care about anything.)
Yang.
- You don't have to, Yang.
- Jian Yang.
- All right.
- Don't be angry.
Don't be upset, don't be upset.
(Live Stream)
(Before the start of today's game,)
(we found that the camera has caught)
(ZGDX team's ADC Lu Sicheng)
(and midsolo Tong Yong)
(kissing openly)
(in front of everyone's eyes.)
(They are already in a public relationship.)
(Yao, are you going to play e-sports)
(This scene made everyone present surprised.)
(or act in an idol drama?)
(And CK's jungler Jian Yang
sitting on the game stage)
(was so pissed off
that he dropped his mouse.)
Good for you, my bestie.
If it were me today,
I'm sure I'd brag about it
to my grandchildren.
Back in the day,
your grandfather and I
kissed
in front of everyone's eyes.
Are you being bombarded?
I guess my parents
will be coming to the base soon.
What did they say?
What can they say?
My mom is baffled,
asking me if I'm here to play professionally
or to star in an idol drama.
And my roommate of four years in college
said she wanted to end the friendship with me.
You're the one
who fell in love with the gaming idol,
while playing professionally after all.
And you didn't inform anyone of it.
Of course, friendships will be at risk.
You're still laughing?
What should I do?
What should you do?
Wait to marry into the rich family,
or
wait for Mrs. Lu to make
an offer of five million yuan,
to get you to leave her son.
I didn't want to announce it either.
I knew I would be judged so harshly.
What if
something goes wrong during the future games?
What if I get beaten up again?
What if Lu Sicheng's fans jump off a building?
Mind your own business.
Why do you worry about others?
It would be fine as long as Cheng loves you.
I love you too.
See, you've got so much love.
I feel like I've been possessed by their words.
I'm starting to wonder
whether e-sports players in a relationship
is a bad influence.
You didn't
just fall in love today.
When you first started to fall in love,
there was no bad influence.
It was fine, right?
What? Are you going to let go
such a good man?
Get out.
Hit it.
You shut up!
Concentrate!
You're making a lot of noise.
You've been unginged lately, haven't you?
Wake up!
(Mrs. Lu)
I'm so annoyed.
Hello?
I was just playing a game.
I didn't see it.
I said I didn't.
You're just guessing.
And you blame me for your incorrect guess?
The little girl?
That's right.
That girl is Tong Yao.
Yes, yes, yes.
She looks quite young.
But she is 18 years old and an adult.
It's not illegal.
What was that noise?
I kissed her.
What?
You want to come to Shenzhen?
What are you going to do in Shenzhen?
Don't scare her.
What does her family do?
Can you not act like a
noisy relative?
If you keep being so unreasonable,
I will hang up the phone.
Cheng.
It's mom, right?
Dad saw it too.
He said he couldn't
get through to you on the phone.
Go away!
My brother has been on the phone for so long.
He must be thirsty. So am I.
Hurry up and fill us both a glass of honey water.
You wish.
I'm your future brother-in-law.
If you don't please me now,
it won't be easy for you
when you marry into our family.
(Real Estate)
Rui.
What are you doing?
Selecting houses for Tong Yao
so that she can move out quickly.
Then you probably won't see
my brother anymore.
Then I'll give her a new security door.
It's useless even to install a hundred doors.
The little girl will open the door for my brother.
Will she?
I see.
What's wrong?
My mother insisted on coming to Shenzhen.
Mrs. Lu?
(Check: five million yuan)
(Payee: Tong Yao Purpose: to leave my son)
Five million yuan.
Leave my son.
(That bitch.)
(Who's she alluding to?)
(Shame on you.)
(Are you playing professionally
or finding a boyfriend?)
(The former poster is so jealous.)
(If ZGDX doesn't win the championship,)
(wait to be judged as a sinner.)
(Is Tong Yao bad?)
(How would she become a sinner?)
(Don't you see who pulled Chessman down?)
(Some damn girls making up
the CP of Chessman and Hierophant.)
(Why don't you accuse them
of distracting Chessman?)
(The "rotten girls" are harmless.
Who have they provoked?)
(Such dirty words.)
(Who first called whom shameless?)
(I am a man.)
(I also think that Cheng has disappointed us.)
(I expected him to win
the national championship trophy.)
(I don't know what he is doing.)
(It's killing me.)
(Is Smiling Su Daji?)
[*Su Daji: Concubine of the last ruler of the Shang.]
(Though she's in a relationship with Lu Sicheng,)
(they've only played one half of the league)
(and didn't lose a single game.)
(Has it already been decided
that they won't win this year's championship?)
(She is like Su Daji,)
(a selfish bitch who thinks of
seducing someone regardless of the team.)
(Disgusting, I want to vomit.)
(And you still want to
play professionally like this?)
(Make a little girl suffer internet violence.)
(Good for you, Tong Daji.)
(Apologize to her now.)
(It's funny.)
(The victim hasn't yet said anything.)
(You guys jumped out
and blamed the victim first.)
(Are you still humans?)
Take it easy.
I will first take the initiative
and admit my mistake
as the team manager later.
Then we'll play well with each other.
We'll be fine.
They're coming.
Mr. Li.
Director Wang.
You guys continue the meeting.
It was me who took the initiative to go after her.
I also asked to make it public.
I will bear all the consequences.
Well.
I just finished a meeting with the PR department.
We have an emergency PR plan
for this incident.
There's a game coming up.
We promise
the personal issue
will in no way affect the game later.
Please don't worry, boss.
Director Wang, Mr. Li.
You guys should come out and explain it.
(I have never seen such an irresponsible club)
Netizens are scolding me on the official blog.
Look!
There are all sorts of curses.
I really can't stand it anymore.
Then get cracking on
issuing an official announcement.
What are you waiting for?
Director Wang.
In your opinion,
is it okay to deal with it this way?
Okay.
Let's do it this way.
You guys go out for a while.
- Okay.
- Okay, okay.
Come on, Mr. Li.
You two wait a minute.
♪You say the world
is always not gentle enough♪
♪Fortunately, you're free,
the most special player♪
♪Invite me to be your number one teammate♪
♪So I had my first encounter with my dreams♪
♪You said you'd always be behind me♪
♪Rumors ran to me and hurt you♪
♪How long will it take
from now to the future♪
♪You're love that never needs a reason♪
♪I want to be close to you,
a little closer to you♪
♪You can be expressionless
and pretend to be calm♪
♪The rhythm of your heart is the best proof♪
♪You never say anything,
your eyes send a message♪
♪You and I are the only ones
in the world who understand each other♪
♪The moment you think of me♪
♪I happen to be thinking of you too♪
♪I want to be closer to you,
a little closer to you♪
♪You can be expressionless,
pretending to be calm♪
♪The rhythm of your heart is the best proof♪
♪You never say anything,
your eyes send a message♪
♪You and I are the only ones in the world
who understand each other♪
♪The moment you think of me♪
♪I happen to be thinking of you too♪
♪You never say anything,
your eyes send a message♪
♪You and I are the only ones in the world
who understand each other♪
♪I like in every season♪
♪I'm at the top of your list♪