Unforgettable Love
EP09
Shenghuai is sick,
not me.
It's your mistake.
Be careful.
Qin Yiyue
Don't touch me.
My legs...
I have checked.
It's a ligament strain.
There is no fracture.
If you want to recover,
it's better to rest a bit more
after the bandage is applied.
Xiaoyue, how do you get hurt like this?
Change the doctor.
If you think I'm not good enough,
can you?
If you want to help,
please go out.
Zhou Ziyang is an orthopedic doctor.
You should trust
our expertise as doctors,
okay?
Is there a fracture?
No.
It's a ligament strain
and sprained ankle.
Stick with the medication for two to three weeks
and you'll recover.
Take your time.
All right, Dr. Zhou.
I'm sorry.
It seems that I owe you an explanation.
It's all over.
Is he good to you?
Zhou Ziyang
It's over
between the two of us.
You don't have to pretend
to care about me.
I don't need it.
Yes.
You're right.
Well.
I can do it myself.
Please
bring the crutches over.
I'm coming.
No need.
Let's go home.
I can do it myself.
If you really could,
you wouldn't have gotten hurt.
Wait for me.
You'd better put me down.
If you don't want to fall again,
just hold me tight.
What has happened to
Mr. and Mrs. He?
But it doesn't seem
to be a good thing this time.
Really? Let's hear it.
A netizen named Sheng Huai Ma Ma
posted a Weibo accusing Dr. Qin of misdiagnosis.
She said she spent her days
indulging in being Mrs. He.
And she said she was addicted to being on the hot search.
She said that she
had no ethics as a doctor.
Said she neglected her duties.
There were also
personal attacks on the patient's family.
Leaving patients
without
reasonable access to care.
shirking her responsibility
and saying the patient's family was mentally unhealthy.
I knew about it.
Qin Yiyue did well.
It was the family that overreacted.
If it is an ordinary doctor-patient conflict,
so be it.
But sister-in-law's status
is too special now.
So the matter
is instantly brought into the spotlight.
Is it serious?
I will inform the PR and legal team.
It's bad.
Someone live-streams
that the hospital is now surrounded
by people at the entrance.
Where is my sister-in-law now?
She's at home with a leg injury.
Can you tell me
what happened at that time?
She scribbled medical records.
What medical records?
You see, I'm normal, right?
Right?
I, Qin Yiyue,
am so strong.
I can!
When did it happen?
Just a few days ago.
Anyway, this doctor is particularly bad.
The hospital is still protecting her.
We can only rely on postings and videos.
That's Shenghuai's mother.
Why is she here?
Qin Yiyue.
Here she is.
Go go go.
C'mon. It's me.
Ning Fang, what's wrong?
You
end up as a cat's paw for others again.
Get in the car quickly.
Come on.
I'm not quite sure of
the details.
It's hard to say.
This case
had previously been
the responsibility of Dr. Qin.
The patient is a child
with a severe psychological disorder.
Dr. Qin previously treated the patient for six months,
but the patient did not recover.
Of course this cannot exactly be said to be
a problem of Dr. Qin's ability.
As you know,
she has a lot of personal life.
That distracts her a lot.
It will inevitably affect the quality of work.
As her colleague and schoolmate,
I've known her for so many years.
I believe in her.
Oh, my God.
Can she shut up?
It's just adding fuel to the fire.
Don't look.
Forget it. Don't be angry.
Let her go.
Anyway, I have a clear conscience.
I hear from Xiaoan.
Did she call a group of We Media
to the hospital to block you?
Fortunately,
Ning Fang appeared.
Or
I'd be getting gangbanged right now.
Is that so?
Don't go out alone
these days.
Wherever you go,
I'll be with you, okay?
You'll be with me?
Are you the pendant on my bag?
Yes.
You can use me
as your amulet,
pepper spray and the bear pendant.
Anyway, everything is fine.
As long as you're safe.
You're right.
I think it should be...
Are you angry that others slander me?
I'll make you a pot of tea.
Take your time.
I'd like jasmine tea.
OK.
Many products
are quite expensive
due to R&D costs.
In addition, the promotion of infrastructure cannot be mass-produced.
The result is that the willingness to use is not strong.
The company still has to be able to
prove to consumers
that these devices
are worth their money.
So do you have any questions?
I'm sorry.
Let's end it for today.
Sorry.
Inform the PR team
to think of
a response immediately.
Stop all the other work.
Well.
They are already in a meeting.
I don't want a meeting.
I want results.
Well.
In addition, notify the legal department
to have all of them prepare
materials to sue.
Yang Shenghuai's mother
for malicious defamation
and all the We Media accounts
that spread false statements.
In addition,
in my name,
draw up a statement.
Well.
Mr. He.
The Emmonds Group Jackson team
came over from the United States.
Will our meeting continue?
Delay.
But this meeting
was already scheduled last month.
It is crucial.
It is related to
the third quarter of our group...
I've already said it.
I don't want to say it a third time.
I've been with you for so many years.
You never postpone
a meeting that has already been planned.
Ten minutes have passed.
Where is my wife?
She was photographed
being driven away by a man in front of the hospital.
By now she should
have been safely returned to her home.
Mr. He
You must have misunderstood me.
Why sue me?
It's all interpreted out of context by the media.
I.
I didn't know that would happen.
I don't come here
to hear you say that.
I'm just relaying
the hospital's decision to you.
Your remarks
are the source of the slander
of Yang Shenghuai's mother.
We have filed a lawsuit.
The next thing she will face
will also be the punishment of the law.
He Qiaoyan
You've got the wrong person.
What does this matter
have to do with Ye Qing?
You make her quit.
You even fire her.
You're going to sue her now.
You are too overbearing, aren't you?
There is no you talk of.
You...
First,
all of the hospital's decisions about Ye Qing
are not caused by me.
Second,
Dr. Ye's inappropriate comments
have caused
great negative impact and damage to the hospital.
The hospital could have punished her.
It has nothing to do with me.
Third,
Yang Shenghuai is Dr. Qin's patient.
Dr. Ye did not follow up.
What qualification does she have to judge
Dr. Qin's practice?
Do you think punishing Ye Qing
can save Qin Yiyue?
It's already happened.
No matter what the result is.
It is
a fatal blow
to the career of any doctor.
No matter
what it is,
I will solve it for her.
In addition,
my wife cannot
get even with you.
But I can't
let you guys bully her.
I'm coming.
Mr. He, are you here again?
I've been miserable enough these days.
Go out and let me have a rest.
This wouldn't have happened
if you had just stayed home
and let the driver pick you up.
I don't go back.
What about Xiaobao?
It's okay if you don't go back.
I'll bring Xiaobao.
But why haven't you
changed your water purification system
here?
No fire protection.
The electrical appliances are right next to the sink.
There is a risk of electric shock.
Why are vegetables not sealed?
Why aren't these bottles and jars
covered?
What's this?
Homemade substandard product.
Substandard product?
This is the pickle made by my mom.
Do you understand pickles?
What's that?
Do you just put cockroach medicine
on the windowsill like that?
How do you make sure
that when you open the window for ventilation,
the powder will not be blown down into the food
because it is dispersed?
So don't breathe when you go to the bathroom.
If you breathe,
those volatile molecules of excrement
floating in the air
are all sucked in by you.
You're right.
Just to remind you.
So install a fresh air system
in the bathroom, right?
In summary,
this place
is a serious safety hazard.
As the guardian of Xiaobao,
I can't let him stay here.
If you have to let him
stay here by force,
I can sue you.
You threaten me?
Not really.
I just don't want you
to double your debt.
Don't you love to reason?
Contract
is the most powerful reasoning.
OK.
In that case, Mr. He, goodbye.
You need to go back with me, too.
Xiaobao needs
your care as a psychiatrist.
Also
if any accident happens to him
because of your negligence,
you need to
bear all the consequences caused.
Please
look at my legs.
I'm hurt.
I need to rest.
I advise you to be kind.
You're right. You need to rest.
It just so happens
that your job doesn't require you to go out.
The Mrs Liu and I
can take care of you 24/7.
Five times the salary for sick work.
By the way,
shorten the contract period.
Deal.
You're pushing my foot.
I'm sorry.
Really five times, Mr. He?
Mr. He
Please
You have only one leg injured.
It's such a short walk,
you can just jump over
with your other leg.
Come here.
What can I do for you?
Use one leg, right?
OK.
Then you carry me.
Impossible.
Didn't you say
to use one leg?
Carry me up.
Have you
been eating a lot lately?
Care your head.
And shoes.
I've done so much,
should that be enough?
I have prepared a supplementary agreement
specifically for special cases.
It is mainly for
this situation today.
No more unauthorized runaways
will be allowed.
Otherwise, it will be regarded as a breach of contract.
You will be required
to pay thirty percent of your salary
as liquidated damages.
In addition,
You are also required to pay liquidated damages
if you terminate your contract
without permission before it expires.
I won't sign this contract.
This homecoming is temporary.
I didn't really intend to stay.
I'm also considering
other job opportunities.
And
I already have a new intention.
Which company
would pay and treat you
so well?
I have already made an agreement with Ning Fang.
When my foot recovers,
I'll go to him for part-time work.
As for you.
Whether I can stay or not
depends on your performance.
Depend on my performance?
I'm going back to my room to sleep.
Sure.
What's the matter?
My hands are shaky
after pushing the wheelchair all day.
I can't pick up a storybook
to tell Xiaobao a story.
Do you think
Xiaobao will worry about me?
Do you think someone
will want to take care of me?
I think so.
Well.
I'll buy you
an electric wheelchair tomorrow.
That's no safe.
If I have
another accident,
what will Xiaobao do?
Let's go.
Well.
You did it?
Your love skills
have finally made epic progress.
But she
still wants to quit.
She said the final decision
depends on my performance.
Remember, no matter what she says,
you must obey absolutely.
How can cooperation
be absolute obedience?
But you two
are so unusual.
You can't do things by common sense.
All in all, remember.
A woman who says no means yes.
A woman said nothing is something big happened.
Women speak one way
and think another.
Come on
for a new day.
Come on.
This is a small difficulty.
It would be nice
to have Ruowei around at this time.
It's all He Qiaoyan's fault
for having to let me come back.
I just can't believe I can't do it.
I'm changing.
What are you doing?
Don't you need help?
I don't need it.
Well.
All in all, remember.
A woman who says no means yes.
I'm not trying to help.
I'm just heartbroken
about this custom crystal glass.
Luckily it's not broken.
Here you are.
Get out.
Well.
Are you sure you don't want me
to help you change your clothes?
Wait.
After I finish changing my clothes later,
please
help me into the wheelchair.
Well.
I haven't changed it yet.
Take your time.
A woman who says no means yes.
A woman said nothing is something big happened.
Women speak one way
and think another.
It turns out
that women's logic is really like this.
Why should we be blamed?
What's going on?
Mr. Wen
Wen is inexplicable.
What's going on?
Aren't they Mr. Wen's four attractive ladies?
Secretary Yang
these ladies
were fired.
Again?
You'll never guess
who fired them off this time.
Director Wen?
It's Mr. Wen.
Mr. Wen?
Why?
Who knows?
Maybe he got tired of them.
Maybe
there will be four more tomorrow.
No, eight attractive ladies.
It's none of our business anyway.
Work hard.
Mr. He
The car is ready.
Today's dinner
is at Director Lin's clubhouse.
Okay, just a minute.
We meet
at the supermarket near our home after work.
Let's buy some food
and cook for dinner at home.
Later you go to the supermarket
to buy some food.
My wife is going to cook at home.
Well.
It's a family activity.
Don't throw it to others.
Be sure to be there in person.
Let's change the plan.
Cancel the dinner with Director Lin.
Take me home, I will stay with my wife.
Well.
Xiaobao
Stop.
Wait.
That's it.
Tonight I'm going to buy some food
and make something delicious.
I want to prove to Xiaobao
that I can not only make
stinky snails rice noodles,
but also aromatic
and exquisite meals.
This is what Xiaobao likes to eat.
Xiaobao, here you are.
Stop.
This one.
Snacks contain
a lot of additives.
I said before
that you can't eat.
Snacks are okay
to eat once in a while.
We'll pick up
some
children's food later.
Snacks are junk food.
You gain nothing...
Look at this.
This is
a very tasty
cookie.
Right?
And this can also be used to fill toys
after eating.
Right?
Crayfish.
Look.
This is delicious, too.
Do you want to eat this?
I'll pay.
Mr. He
I know what you think.
Snack is not eaten every day
and every meal.
It's okay to have a little snack
once in a while to have fun.
Think about Ultraman.
You can't deprive children
of the joy they deserve.
Right?
Xiaobao
Let me know what else you want to eat.
Here you are.
This is my favorite.
Today only.
Xiaobao, do you hear that?
Your dad says
every Friday
will be a snack party.
Let's
thank him.
Let's go, Mr. He.
Let's go over there and have a look.
Hot Pot?
Didn't you say you were going to cook yourself today
in proving your ability?
Mr. He
Just eat what you can.
I'm just
too tired today.
I'm tired of washing.
This is family hotpot.
It's self-help.
Did you
wash it clean?
Is it absolutely safe to put raw ones in the pot
together with cooked ones?
And
after eating,
how to remove the smell of this room?
Xiaobao, let's eat.
Is it hot?
You can't eat spicy today.
Eat this.
Put it down.
You can only drink hot water today.
Thank you.
Have a good meal.
My God.
How come
there are so many girls' backs?
They are not the same person.
He Qiaoyan is not a pervert,
right?
Mommy
I found it. I'm coming.
Shall we draw a planet here?
Great.
Draw.
Color it.
You need to color it.
This one.
And this one.
What are you drawing?
You are back.
Work. Look.
The ones behind this
are all the works
we finished today.
And this one.
Look what it looks like?
Colorful ham.
You're a ham.
This is the space world.
All these colorful ones
are large and small planets.
Xiaobao said he would take me
on a trip to the solar system
and to Mars.
Look if the Martians
look exactly
like us.
Mars is good.
But do you know that
with the current technology
it needs cost $10 billion
to build a Mars vehicle?
If it is too expensive to go to Mars,
we can also
go to the moon.
See what Wu Gang and Chang'e's home
actually looks like.
A trip to the moon is also good.
But
do you know
that a ticket for a spaceship
needs cost
$75 million?
Also the sun we see on Earth
is yellow.
But it should be white.
The colors we see
are just
the colors filtered by the sunlight
passing through the atmosphere.
Xiaobao
We don't have to listen to your dad.
Some one
is just talk anyway.
If he were to do it himself,
he wouldn't be able to do anything.
There should be no one else in this family.
Someone is definitely not talking about me.
Mr. He, do you know
there is a saying.
What you hear about may be false; what you see is true.
Done.
Xiaobao, does this look good?
Let's give dad applause,
shall we?
Xiaobao
You're interested in the solar system.
In the future,
if you have any questions
about the solar system,
you can ask your dad.
Your dad is excellent.
Tell me which one you would like to know about?
This one?
This is called Jupiter.
It is the largest
of the eight planets in the solar system
and has the fastest rotation speed.
It ranks fifth
in distance from the sun.
Although it is the largest in size
in the solar system,
the masses of the other seven planets
are added together
and multiplied by two and a half
to make the mass of Jupiter.
Do you get it?
This
You have to let your mother tell you this.
Why is the hair so dirty?
Is it running out?
Why can't I press it out?
Dr. Qin, wait a minute.
That should be prickly heat powder.
Do you have rash in your hair?
I didn't wash my hair.
The wash free spray is also running out.
I can only use prickly heat powder.
It can barely work.
I haven't washed my hair for three days.
No one can help me.
Do you need help?
Who can I ask for help, Xiaobao?
Whatever.
I can tolerate it.
Well.
Women speak one way and think another.
Come with me.
Go.
I don't expect him to do well.
Don't leave.
Come on.
Let's say goodbye to dad together.
I'm going to work.
You should kiss mommy before going out.
Who said that?
This is a sweet habit
of my older brother and sister-in-law.
Well.
Don't be serious.
You can relax.
I'm not interested in
the fried leek dumplings you've eaten.
You don't understand its deliciousness.
By the way
today Ma Fada will bring the lawyer
to the home.
He will ask you some questions.
I tell you first.
Then I'll go to work.
I'm leaving.
Take care of yourself.
Say goodbye to dad.
What's the meaning of this?
Mrs. He
This is the evidence
we have gathered so far.
We also need your complements.
We can file the lawsuit
against Yang Shenghuai's mother this week.
Lawsuit?
Yes.
Why do you sue Shenghuai's mom?
This is also what Mr. He wants.
Her
slander
and attacks on you
have done you harm.
Also the injury to your leg
is caused
by her intentional injury.
Is this what He Qiaoyan thinks?
Yes, Mr. He wants to protect you.
He called the company's legal department
to respond to the matter
on the very day it happened.
Mr. Ma, Mr. lawyer
Please go back.
I personally don't plan to
sue Shenghuai's mother.
Mrs. He
This is what Mr. He means.
We also...
I'll talk to him.
I am the person concerned.
I have the decision.
Please go back.
All right, Mrs. He.
We go first.
Goodbye.
Why did you sue Shenghuai's mother?
Her false accusations of disinformation against you
have caused damage to your reputation.
Shouldn't she be sued?
What's more, you are my employee.
Her malicious injury
caused your leg to be injured,
thus affecting the progress of work.
This has indirectly resulted in
my interests as an employer
being affected.
Shouldn't I
ask her to compensate?
Things about her
have passed.
I don't blame her.
It's not an easy life for her.
And
are you aware of
the impact your prosecution
will have on her life?
Sit down.
Why should I listen to you?
That's the price she should pay.
Everyone should
be responsible for what he/she says or does.