Unforgettable Love
EP10
Sheng Huai's parents are divorced.
His mother is raising the child by herself.
It's very stressful.
She was defensive and prejudiced against me.
As a psychologist,
I can understand.
And these things
are within my range.
And,
every patient and their relatives
are my friends and family.
The child's psychology is fragile,
but parents' are more fragile than they are.
It's my duty to protect them.
So please drop the case.
Feelings and principles
are separate.
If you frame someone up, you should apologize,
and if you hurt someone, you should pay for it.
This is a natural truth.
How can you
be so inflexible
and unreasonable?
Dr. Qin,
I think you're
being sentimental.
I have started to
implement it.
If nothing happens,
please come back.
You should know that
it is your duty to
take care of Xiaobao
and not to leave without permission.
I don't want to stay any longer
in your cold office.
Take care.
Good-bye.
Hold on to your crutch.
Leave me alone.
Didn't you just say
you didn't want to stay here any longer?
It's been a minute
and you still haven't left.
You shut up!
Stop talking.
I'm at my wit's end.
Sit down in this chair.
I told you to
leave me alone.
It's not up to you.
You, I, I...
Hello, Mr. Wen.
Yang Ruowei,
Compensation for my emotional loss.
I don't know what you mean.
It's because of you that
I'm getting misogyny.
Does this matter concern me?
I've completed
all the tasks you gave me perfectly.
Don't forget
that I still have
someone's secret in my mind.
You're endless, aren't you?
Do you think I'm really afraid of you?
You can talk about it to others.
Let's go.
Say it, or you are coward.
You're a girl.
Why don't you care about
your reputation?
Say it or not?
Don't say it, do you?
All right, I say.
I...
No, no, no, no.
Go, go, go.
Xiaobao,
it's time to read.
Last week, we have read
Einstein Papers.
This week we'll read
Galileo's
dialogue on the two world systems
of Ptolemy and Copernicus.
What's that?
Whose dialogue?
Ptolemy and Copernicus.
They are the father of physics.
Galileo's classic works
popularized the
heliocentric theory in the form of dialogue.
This is a basic physics reading.
After my selection,
I selected the most suitable one for Xiaobao's
advanced reading.
Xiaobao, can you understand it?
Xiaobao, look at my books.
I've got some good books.
I bought a whole series at once.
There are not only picture books,
but also picture guessing.
And,
there is also a game to develop intelligence.
These readings are too young for him.
His reading lists
were carefully chosen by me.
That's why he has
more knowledge than peers.
That you imposed on him.
Children should read books
appropriate to their age.
These books,
both on illustration design
and the plot sense,
are the work of
countless child psychologists
and education experts.
I've done
research before.
Don't use your IQ
to measure
the child of mine.
Xiaobao,
let's play a game together.
Let's see who finds it first.
Book.
Boring.
Book...
Where is it in this book?
Have you found it?
Not this one. This one is a calendar.
Here it is.
How does it hide here?
Xiaobao,
let's look for the snail.
Where is the snail?
It's here.
Then you can find where the love is.
Where is love?
Here.
Did you see it before?
We should look for the hardest things.
Can you find
where the hat is?
Wrist watch.
These books are not interesting.
Xiaobao, let's take a look at this one.
Drawing.
You guys have fun.
Xiaobao, draw it by yourself.
Why is he so intelligent?
I get angry when I see him.
I'll go out
after he gets into the bathroom.
She has trouble with her legs.
I should let her go to the bathroom first.
So as not to make her angry again.
Why is he still in bed?
It's been a long time.
You'd better go.
Don't care,
I'll pretend I didn't see him.
I've gave you
a night to think it over.
Can you drop the case?
No.
I've thought it through.
I'm going to stick to the end.
Drop the case.
Put me down!
I told you that
if you don't put me down,
I'll be angry.
If you
don't put me down,
I'll
get you in trouble.
He Qiaoyan, give my stick back!
He Qiaoyan!
Xiaobao, take care of your mommy.
Don't let her get away.
What are you doing?
Mr. He's sexy picture.
The desire of thousands of girls.
I'm here to do good today
to help the girls realize their dreams.
Give the cell phone back to me.
Give me back.
He Qiaoyan!
My sexy pictures have been deleted.
Please do more meaningful things.
Take it.
I'll keep shooting.
Miss Qin,
do you know how heavy you are?
You have to lose weight.
Get up.
I dropped my crutch so I couldn't get up.
I won't get up.
Get up.
You are going to
lie here till dark, aren't you?
Anyway, if you
don't drop the case today,
I won't get up.
I tell you
if you touch me again,
I'll yell.
Mr. He. Mr...
Mr. He
Sheng Huai's mother is anxious to find you.
I... I can hardly stop her.
Got it.
Sorry!
Wait for me!
If you want to sue me.
I'm not wrong.
I can also sue
the Dr. Qin's misdiagnosis.
Whether Dr. Qin's diagnosis of you
is a misdiagnosis
will be
determined by
a professional organization.
I think you
know better than anyone else
whether Dr. Qin is misdiagnosed or not.
Do you know why
I haven't sued you yet?
It's because of Dr. Qin
always insisted that
you were
just acting on impulse.
She refused to
hold you responsible.
Though because of you,
she was injured
and on crutches,
she asked me not to sue you.
Heshi's charity foundation
will pay for Sheng Huai's
treatment and education
for the next 10 years.
In addition,
I'll arrange
a psychologist for you.
Sheng Huai's mother,
you should face up to
your own psychological problems.
At the same time, admit your mistakes.
Please set an example to your child.
Good boy.
You are reading.
Do you have any question?
Reward you with a box of yogurt.
Try not to eat
after eight p.m.
It's not just any yogurt,
but He Qiaoyan's
reward for helping others.
I'm just afraid that
you might run after me
and mess around all day.
It will affect your feet.
In addition,
If the injury gets more serious,
who will take care of Xiaobao?
Never say uncle.
Is it that hard
to admit you are kind?
I do this
not because I'm kind,
but think what you're saying is right.
I should trust you.
I have tried
to do it
according to your principles.
Not bad, it turns out.
I said it's okay to trust me.
I think
you are
getting cute now.
Please take a close look at
this month's performance appraisal.
Performance appraisal.
He Qiaoyan,
Did you put a
surveillance device on me?
Sleeping late and staying up late
are counted in my performance.
Do I have to
report all the meals
I eat at your house?
Fortunately, he didn't see it.
Or else I'll be charged again.
Ex-girlfriend?
The gossip is on me.
Why is my head so dizzy?
Are you finished?
I just saw that you didn't look very well.
Do you feel uncomfortable?
I'm done.
What's the matter with you?
Haven't you finished?
Why are you still sitting here?
Get up, I need to use the bathroom.
Qin Yiyue.
You are a liar.
I...
Why is my mask missing one piece?
Did you use it secretly?
You're such...
Are you okay?
Is your cold still?
five, four, three, two, One.
Time is up.
It's only 38 degrees Celsius.
Your reaction just now
made me think you have a fever of 40 degrees Celsius.
What is only 38 degrees Celsius?
Do you know
that a person's normal body temperature
should be
between 36.3
to 37.2 degrees Celsius.
It's relatively constant
and fluctuates
within a normal range.
I'm obviously not normal.
You are sick and still here to lecture me.
Set by set.
It doesn't matter. You'll be better after a sleep.
Where are you going?
Go to the hospital for a drip.
You only have a fever of 38 degrees Celsius.
Calm down, not so serious.
People who are sick have to see a doctor
and get a drip.
And some serious diseases
begin with
a persistent low fever.
I have a very important
meeting tomorrow.
I can't afford it.
I am here to
teach you the science for free.
Fever is
one of the body's
defenses against disease.
Use your own defense system
to keep the germs out.
If the body temperature does not exceed
38.5 degrees Celsius,
just use physical cooling.
Don't be in a hurry to
take antibiotics and antipyretics.
If the body temperature
persists above 38.5 degrees Celsius
and other complications
develop,
you can consider antibiotics
and hormone therapy, get it?
Methods of physical cooling...
Let me see...
Wait for me.
Do you know how cold it is!
Not cold.
when I was a kid, I had a fever
and my mom put ice on my forehead.
Come on.
Take it away.
You are so effeminate; let me change another way.
Sweating. Sweating!
Really good.
Did you come to my house
to murder me?
Take it away!
I forgot to wring it out.
Have a bowl of ginger soup.
Is ginger soup made with cubes of ginger?
Shouldn't it be made of shredded ginger?
It doesn't matter whether it is cubes
or shredded ginger.
The soup is no difference.
Come and have a drink.
I will drink it by myself.
You can't drink it by yourself.
I'll help you.
You are so stupid.
The soup is finished.
All right, I'll go.
Wait a minute.
Take the bowl to the kitchen.
Items should be returned in time.
If you need service, please tap the head of the bed.
But I can't guarantee that
I can hear when I'm asleep.
Without you,
I would have lived a few more years.
Sleep!
Who have I offended?
Come on, look at this. Is this one?
It's just similar.
But not her.
All right.
It's up to you.
I'll keep an eye on it for you.
I told you,
in recent years
whenever I have encountered
a similar girl
in the street,
I hurriedly took out my cell phone
and took secretly shots.
Thanks to my good looks,
Otherwise, I would have
beaten up
as a hooligan.
The car you saw last time
is for you.
I'm willing to take pictures for another five years.
No, ten years.
But who would have thought
Mr. He's first love
is turned out to be a
a girl he had never met.
First love? What first love?
Yes,
you've been looking for her for five years,
and you can't forget her.
It's not only your first love,
but also, a strange love.
I just think
I should have found her.
But...
Are you really sure
this person exists?
You just
saw her in your dream.
What's more, it's just her back.
Are you finished?
You can leave.
I have to work.
When will the car you just mentioned
belong to me?
It's depends on my mood.
How are you feeling today?
Not so good. Please go.
Bye.
Good morning, Dr. Qin.
Good morning.
The fever should be gone.
I'll make breakfast.
Come back.
Don't go.
Don't leave me.
Don't go. Don't go.
Don't go.
Don't leave me.
He Qiaoyan said it
refers to the girl in silhouette
or the girl in the picture.
How's it going? Dr. Qin
Are you ready?
Good morning, Mr. Ning
Everything is ready.
First of all, welcome
to join our clinic.
To have a
Child psychologist like you
volunteer to help us
is our pleasure.
Who says I'm voluntary?
I need you
to treat me hot pot to make it up.
OK, I'll
take all your hot pot in the future.
I'll take you to meet new colleagues.
Let's go.
Don't forget to meet
the staff of UNIFON
at ten a.m.
I've arranged assistant Yang Ruowei
pick you up at 9:30 a.m.
Yang Ruowei
was in partnership with my father
to spy on me.
Mr. Wen
I'm your new assistant.
It's only half an hour left
before the 10 o'clock meeting
with UNIFON.
I Know.
Chairman Wen specially ordered that
this cooperation is imperative.
As the VIP special product
of Wenshi Hotel suite.
The brand book has been given to you in advance.
UNIFON.
The brand of UNIFON
combined with the modern science and technology
to reproduce the culture and skills of the prosperous Tang Dynasty.
and create the skin care art
suitable for Oriental women.
I know that.
The mask in your hand
is the flagship product of their brand.
It focuses on the whitening effect of plants
and extracts the essence of Glycyrrhiza glabra,
which is as valuable as gold.
It's milder and gentler, right?
Not bad.
Of course.
The project of cross-border cooperation
is my idea.
Find ordinary people or internet celebrity
to take V-logs.
On the one hand,
it can record the feelings of using the mask.
On the other side,
we can give them Jinli awards to publicize the hotel.
Isn't that great?
By the way,
what are you doing here?
I'm your new assistant.
I beg your pardon?
You mean that
let me be Mr. Wen's assistant.
You can make a request.
Why me?
Because I noticed that
Wen Gu listens to you.
Eh...Chairman Wen
I think you may have misunderstood.
Mr. Wen and I
are not familiar.
Take it easy.
I don't need your explanation.
I don't care of the process, but the result.
Chairman Wen
what kind of results do you want?
Assist Wen Gu
and do this project well.
You can ask for
position and bonus.
Are you being
pushed to get married?
I'm telling you to be sober.
I'm not interested in you.
What are you running for?
Are you afraid that you will fall in love with me?
I'm afraid you'll fall in love with me.
I'm afraid I can't get rid of you.
Now that we have reached a consensus.
It will be easy.
Clearing in the past.
From now on,
we will only have working relationship.
Let's go.
I'll attend the meeting of UNIFON by myself.
You don't have to follow me.
Isn't he just a playboy
with a weak hand?
I'm sure I can handle him.
Cheers
Mr. Wen
Take us
to your yacht in a while.
Have you played games recently?
Let me tell you that
I've just reached the top of the national service list.
Yeah, I'm great, right?
Miss, this way, please.
Come on, let's celebrate.
Cheers, cheers!
Leave her alone.
Keep drinking.
See you tomorrow, Mr. Wen
Are you finished?
Can you continue to eat with me?
This girl
is really good at picking the time.
Come on, celebrate me
to settle the big trouble.
I have successfully joined the new hospital.
By the way, and my broken leg
is finally healed. Cheers!
Cheers!
Sir, five more roast lamb legs please.
OK.
Five...
Can we finish it?
My leg has just healed.
And I firmly believe what my mother said.
Eat what you lack,
and you are what you eat.
Fine.
Sir, here
five more baked brains.
Here's a woman
who needs a brain tonic here.
You're the one who needs a brain tonic.
I'm brilliant.
By the way, let me show you something.
You see, this is his brother.
This is his sister-in-law.
Who do you think this woman is?
You see where she stands
and how close they are.
It should be his girlfriend
at the time.
Sure enough, this is a woman's intuition.
I think so, too.
But I haven't heard of
him having any intimate
heterosexual friends.
And,
he's never been in a relationship.
Do you think this person will be his
sister who has been anonymous for many years.
Are you jealous?
No.
Are you sure you don't want to know
anything about his past relationships?
Not interested.
That's ok.
Do you think
this woman
could be his classmate in primary school?
Impossible, impossible.
Absolutely impossible.
Primary school classmate?
High school classmate!
Oh, no way, no way.
It could only be his ex-girlfriend.
It's definitely
not his high school classmate.
Maybe he just got dumped
and had no face to talk the past.
He's unforgettable in his mind.
Sister,
You've guessed they were separated brother and sister
to their hidden marriage.
Aren't you curious?
Don't you want to know?
No,
I don't want to know.
I just want to take a taxi and go home now.
Boring.
It must be his ex-girlfriend.
Watch your head, ok.
You go back to wash and sleep.
Driver, be careful on the road.
Why does she feign indifference?
Obviously, she cares about him.
Silly girl.
Do you think she could be
the hidden boss of Heshi Group?
Living in overseas for many years
and unwilling to participate in family disputes.
Did you read too many novels?
Can we
change another topic?
I don't want to
discuss this.
You know nothing.
I am
seeking the truth for the masses,
and giving full play to
my network detective skills.
Let's suppose that
she is his ex-girlfriend.
Oh my God, Ruowei.
The imagination of netizens is so rich.
They replenish his lover from celebrity to top.
I'll forward it to you.
Just read it
as a bedtime story.
I think I am
a real gossip genius.
Oh, my God.
Wrong. Wrong.
Oh, my God, Ruowei.
The imagination of netizens is too rich.
They replenish his lover from celebrity to top.
I'll forward it to you.
Just read it
as a bedtime story.
I think I am a real
Gossip genius.
Oh, my God, Ruowei.
The imagination of netizens is too rich.
They replenish his lover from celebrity to top.
I'll forward it to you.
Just read it
as a bedtime story.
Couldn't the choice of bedtime stories
be a little more advanced?
Dr. Qin.
Ranking results of search engine
have many kinds,
What you see is not necessarily true.
Does Dr. Qin really want to
know about my affair?
I didn't mean that.
I just...
I just want to know more about
your past.
It can also help Xiaobao
cure his illness.
Now that Dr. Qin
has seen the photos.
Explain it from your
professional point of view.
Photos?
I am not unintentional.
It fell out by itself.
And
didn't you say that
I can borrow the books
in your study room.
Please answer my question directly.
I don't want to know about your personal affairs.
I just think
you, in the photo,
are very happy.
You are happy
when you are with your family.
So, I want to help you
find your warmth.
It's for Xiaobao, and also for you.
Smile.
You look pretty with a smile.
Remember who you are.
Just take care of Xiaobao,
and don't be distracted by other things.
And
it's none of your business.
It doesn't pay to be the good guy.
Don't worry,
I'll only care about
Xiaobao.
It won't waste a little bit
to someone else.
Ruowei, Ruowei!
Did you see it?
I've already said that
don't eat on the sofa.
Forget it.
Aren't you going to think twice
about the Sunshine Primary School?
I know you're worried about
Xiaobao's academic performance.
But what he needs to do now
is not to be a high-achieving student.
Graduation rates
and subject education
are not the first considerations.
It's important to communicate with people
and make friends with others.
You have no idea
how much fun he had
when I took him out
this afternoon.
Ning Fang is trying his best
to help him.
There will be a group activity
in Sunshine Primary School tomorrow.
Ning Fang invited him
to join it.
Tomorrow?
Whether you say yes or not,
I'm going to take him to the activity.
I'm not like some people
who break their word.
I've hooked up with Xiaobao
and said that cheating is a puppy.
You go.
Did he agree?
Professor Wu, this is He Qiaoyan.
I sent you an email last night.
Here's the thing.
I want to fund
a school for special children.
Compared with the lack of funds,
I need more
professional teachers
with relevant background experience.
I wonder if you have any
suitable candidates to recommend.
I can hire them at a high salary.
Well, please.