(The characters, locations, incidents, organizations,)
(and background of this drama are fictional.)
Let me go! Where am I? Let go of me!
Oh Yoon Hee? Shim Su Ryeon?
Get off me!
Where am I? What's going on?
Shim Su Ryeon. Oh Yoon Hee. What's going on?
What are you doing here?
How did you manage to get out?
I guess you did a pretty good job of acting like a psycho.
Or did Joo Dan Tae help you?
Did you help him kill Logan?
You killed Logan, didn't you?
What are you talking about? It wasn't me!
You killed him.
Do you think I don't know that?
Why are you doing this?
Why are you doing this to me?
Thank you.
Wake up. I know you're not dead.
What's going on?
Why are you doing this to me?
Finally, here we all are.
Good job, everyone.
Shall we start cornering the rat then?
What are you talking about?
Our beginnings may have been different,
but we all want the same ending.
We want Joo Dan Tae gone.
There's nothing I wouldn't do for that happy ending.
I'm ready to join hands with anyone.
So? Are you telling me to cooperate with you?
Joo Dan Tae is in action.
He is now the owner of the 85th floor of Hera Palace.
At today's Cheong A Group shareholders' meeting,
he'll be appointed the only president.
Is it okay if you lose the entire Cheong A Group to him?
Bring evidence that he killed Logan.
Whatever it takes,
I need you to approach him and find some evidence.
What should I do that?
That's the only reason we saved you.
Do you want to help us or...
die here?
What?
The choice is yours.
I'm ready to get rid of you anytime.
Just like you tried to kill me two years ago.
Do you think I'm still the weak Shim Su Ryeon you used to know?
Can you do it or not?
Betray us, and I'll kill you with my hands.
Shut it.
Do you know what got me through in that cold prison cell?
Gnashing my teeth every day,
dreaming of paying Joo Dan Tae back.
Joo Dan Tae.
I'll never let you two kill him.
Ms. Cheon!
I'll be the one killing him first.
Is it really okay to let her go like this?
What if she was involved in Logan's death?
How can you trust her?
I don't.
We'll see if we watch what she does from now.
Anyway, why did you get me out?
You even changed your witness statement.
The moment Joo Dan Tae was released,
the entire legal system collapsed.
Ro Na may be in danger again.
You need to be there to protect her.
Never trust the law again.
- I'll take you to the hospital. - There's no need.
What time is the shareholders' meeting today?
It starts at 2pm.
It seems like Mr. Joo is planning to dismiss...
every executive on your side.
Now that I'm out of prison, he can't have his way.
How much money do I have left?
Your buildings in Gangnam have been sold,
but after paying Ms. Shim 50 million dollars in compensation...
and paying a forfeit,
there's not much left.
That's impossible.
Do you know how many buildings I own in Myeongdong?
They should be worth at least hundreds of million dollars.
All your real estate has been transferred...
to the lady in Seongbuk-dong and Mr. Joo.
Do you mean they took everything away from me?
Was there anything strange on the day Logan died?
I told you to put a tail on Logan.
Here are the photos from where the explosion happened.
The old man right next to the car,
who sells popcorn, seems fishy.
An old man?
What about Eun Byeol?
Where's she now?
Here.
It's tasty.
"TOEFL Preparation Institute"?
You should take the TOEFL test once you enter university,
so I went to ask some questions,
and they keep calling me.
Eat up.
I love the shave ice here too.
This is the first time we've been here together, right?
When you eat this,
you're supposed to pour this over it.
It's so good.
When did you get released?
Are you released for good?
You look a mess.
I have nothing to say to you.
Eun Byeol, how have you been?
Are you well?
How did you get released?
I thought you got a seven-year sentence.
It's for you.
I was worried about you and missed you so much.
Look at me.
Eun Byeol.
Why did you show up in front of me?
I'd forgotten all about you and I'm doing well.
What are you talking about? I'm here to pick you up.
Who says I'm going back to you?
I'm living happily with Ms. Jin.
I get to eat and do whatever I want.
Your mom is here. Why would you live with her?
Do you want her to ruin your life?
You're the one who ruined my life.
- My criminal parents did. - What?
What can you possibly do for me?
Do you have any money?
Do you have the power to get me into Seoul National University?
You even lost our place at Hera Palace to Seok Kyung's dad.
You've been kicked out of...
both the classical singing world and your company.
And you even went to prison.
You're nothing but humiliation and an obstacle in my life.
You have nothing left. Where can you take me?
I'll get everything back!
I've never been poor in my life.
Money? I can always make more.
I can do anything for you.
No. Don't do anything.
Without Ms. Jin,
I'd be in juvie now.
With even Grandma refusing to be my guardian,
who else could I rely on?
What did this woman do to you?
Let go of her!
Lay a finger on her,
and I'll kill myself.
Eun Byeol.
I've never been this happy.
Please don't take Ms. Jin away from me.
It's my last request.
Ms. Jin, let's move to another table.
Eun Byeol wants me to be her guardian.
She's the one who asked me to help her escape from Hera Palace.
That's not true. My daughter wouldn't do that.
She has her performance test for Seoul University next week.
She's sensitive right now, so don't try to see her again.
What's your relationship with Yoon Hee?
Was she the one who sent you to us?
Did she hire you to ruin Eun Byeol's life?
What if she were? Will you take revenge on her?
Were you really communicating with Yoon Hee?
Logan introduced us.
He's the one who brought me from the US.
Logan?
Then...
Does that mean Su Ryeon was in on it too?
I felt bad for never visiting you in prison.
Would you like a shaved ice?
Fine. You should leave me.
If I have you,
I'll have to let Dan Tae attack me again.
The more I have to protect, the more vulnerable I am.
I won't come to you...
until I put everything back to the way it was.
Open up!
Open up, Dan Tae!
Dan Tae! Open up!
This is my home. Dan Tae!
You changed the code?
You changed the code? You changed the code?
How could you break someone else's door down?
Get out of here!
We're in trouble if Chairman Joo comes.
I'll get fired!
Darn it. Get over here.
Don't you dare touch me!
This is my home.
I'll show you whom you'll bow to. Just wait and see.
(Cheong A Group)
We will begin the Cheong A Group shareholders' meeting.
What kind of risk management...
have you been doing?
There are no bank investments...
and our stock prices have tanked.
Cheong A is about to go bust.
Did you decide to give up and watch it sink?
I mean... The owner was linked to a murder.
How could the company survive?
You're paid a high salary...
to take care of things like that.
That's why you're sitting there, Director Cho.
Companies have a system.
If Director Cheon Seo Jin were here,
it wouldn't have gotten this bad.
I won't tolerate your abuse of power any longer.
Listen to that wild hog talk.
If you miss Seo Jin so much,
go visit her in prison.
You're fired.
Chairman Joo!
Even the chairman can't abuse executives like this.
You're fired too.
Anyone who's unhappy with me, submit your resignation.
I won't stop you, and there's no way I'll listen to your criticism.
Cheong A will be run as Joo Dan Tae dictates.
If you want to end up on the street, keep yapping away!
We must work together...
to save the company.
Let's hear your ideas...
for how to save Cheong A.
Seo Jin?
Honey. I've missed you so much.
What are you doing?
Thank you...
for doing everything you could to get me out of prison.
It's all thanks to you.
What are you babbling about?
Chairman Joo.
Thank you for agreeing to give us the first interview.
Me?
You returned quickly amidst much criticism.
Stock prices have been hitting all-time lows.
Don't you think your return was a bit rash?
You're the one who's rash.
How long has it been since he made his return?
However, Cheong A Group will change very soon.
Upon opening Cheong A Art Center,
we will make a great leap forward.
Ms. Cheon. Is it true that you gave Shim Su Ryeon...
50 million dollars in compensation?
Whereas I was wronged in many ways,
I've cleared up my misunderstandings with her.
Please explain the rumours of your problems with Chairman Joo.
My husband and I do not have any problems.
Those rumours are all lies.
My husband and I will make it up to the people.
We will cherish family...
and give our all in saving Cheong A Group.
We'll make more and use the money for good.
Please trust us...
and watch how we do.
[VIU Ver] SBS E04 'The Penthouse 3'
"Mr. Baek is Missing"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
Smile a little.
Like you're in total bliss.
Thank you.
("Joo Dan Tae Reunited with Cheon Seo Jin, Stock Prices Soar.")
('Cheon promised that she will make it up to the people...")
See?
Seo Jin hasn't changed at all.
No, she became more evil.
She went back to Dan Tae.
She had no choice but to join forces with him...
in order to increase the value of Cheong A stock.
This is what I was after.
You were after this?
I cut off all of her sources of funds.
That way, she'd run to Dan Tae.
I plan...
to fight fire with fire.
Since it's true that he messed with her profits.
Do you think she'll help you though?
Would she bring you evidence that he killed Logan?
Why are you pretending to be strong?
You're not fine at all.
You're dying inside because of Logan.
You watched...
the man you love die.
You can be honest when you're with me.
I'm more worried because you're acting so tough.
I don't have the luxury of crying.
I have to prove Dan Tae killed him. That's priority.
You planned this little charade as soon as you got out.
Let's remain married until Cheong A is stabilized.
Consider it a contract marriage.
Says who?
I can de-list this company...
or build it up.
In other words, if I can't have it, I can kill it.
You can't return to Cheong A Group.
Your followers have been fired already.
I know you're here...
to stab me in the back.
I can't trust you either.
It's simple. We'll use each other.
Until we have money in our hands.
If stock prices shoot up every time we smile at each other,
what's so hard about it?
Weren't you planning...
to build up the company and sell it anyway?
But sorry.
I...
don't want to team up with you...
in the slightest.
You'll regret it.
What is this?
Your disguise was incredible.
It's so you.
Who is this old man?
You know exactly who it is.
Did you forget?
Secretary Do is great at his job.
But then,
he learned from the great Joo Dan Tae.
I was actually quite surprised.
That you'd kill Logan to get a not-guilty sentence?
I never even imagined that.
Turn my Hera Palace to what it was.
And make me a joint partner of Cheong A Group.
Are you crazy? Why would I do that?
You don't want to?
Would you not mind if I send those photos to Shim Su Ryeon now?
Actually, no.
Wouldn't it be best if I send them to Logan Lee's...
grieving family in the US?
I heard they're frantically trying to find their son's killer.
What shall I do?
I quite like the new interior and furniture.
Good job.
Oh, right.
Who's the guy who came in with Logan?
Did you kill him too?
He was with someone?
My goodness. You didn't know that either?
It's not fun if there are too many witnesses.
Darn it!
What is it, Su Ryeon?
It's nothing.
Mom.
Who are you people?
How did you get in here?
Oh. So you're the infamous Su Ryeon Shim, huh?
Who are you?
I want you to answer my god damn question first.
What did you do to my brother Logan?
He is Logan's older brother.
Do you actually think I killed Logan?
Yeah. Because all the motivations are there.
You see, you must have a grudge against my family...
for what my parents did to your daughter.
But shoot. Did you really have to go that far?
Yo, my parents, they're already on trial.
My parents, they're already paying for their mistakes.
So why the...
Logan has to go and die like that?
You call this revenge?
I wish I were the one who had killed him.
What was that?
If I hated him,
and I killed him because I couldn't forgive him,
then at least I'd feel better.
He called me every day and showed his concern for me,
and suddenly he's gone from my side.
Do you know how dreadful that feeling is?
So many times a day I think I should've stopped him from coming.
Was there something I could've done for him?
The regret and anger are driving me crazy.
If only I could turn back time,
I'd be okay with not seeing him ever again.
I would do anything if only I could bring him back.
Then you should've never called him back in the first place!
You should've just let him go!
Don't you know him better than that?
He wanted to be responsible for what his parents did.
I trusted his sincerity.
We...
Jesus.
Shoot.
Now, on the day of Logan's death,
there was 10 billion dollars...
withdrawn from his personal bank account.
You know where this money is, right?
I don't know about that.
Liar!
If you don't know where this money is, then who does?
He told me that money was for Seol A.
Move.
No, sir.
You cannot leave the house. Direct orders from the master.
I have to go.
Can't you tell I'm with a company?
- Get out of the way. - Hey!
Just where the heck do you think you're going?
- You are going nowhere. - Alex.
Why are you stopping me too?
Joo Dan Tae's a very dangerous person.
If I don't go back and prove him guilty...
for all his wrongdoings in the past,
and have him rot in jail,
Su Ryeon can end up in danger again.
Well, that's exactly why I'm telling you...
you are going nowhere.
Do you not know what you mean to this family?
Do you not know what our parents did...
to save your darn life?
You.
You're the one who's supposed to take over Pop's business.
I have to go and protect her, no matter what.
I promised her that I'd make her happy.
Do you really think...
this woman, she's going to forgive our family?
That's more the reason why I'm sorry.
Instead of hating me like she's supposed to,
she chooses to care for me.
Alex. I need her by my side to be happy. So please.
Let me go.
Jesus Christ.
What about the 10 billion dollars you cashed out from real estate?
Is all that money for her too?
That money was for Seol A anyway.
I never thought it was mine.
For goodness sake, Logan.
Who, I mean... What is this woman to you?
I like her. I like Su Ryeon.
What did you say?
I like her.
Very much.
Listen, Alex. I only got a second chance at life...
because of Seol A.
The new life she gave me, I want to spend for Su Ryeon.
My heart...
and all my belongings.
Now, whoever was after Logan for that 10 billion dollars,
I swear to almighty, I'll find him...
and I'll kill him.
Even if that means you, lady.
So you best be prepared.
Hey, yo! Let's go.
Was there really something between Mom and Logan?
No, right?
The weird rumour isn't true, is it?
I told you to trust Mom.
Once we believe, we trust forever.
Mom.
My little girl.
Have you been strong?
You're not sick, are you?
You look like you lost weight.
I went on a diet.
I missed you, Ro Na. I missed you so much.
You stupid jerk!
You had no idea Secretary Do was following you?
Why didn't you tell me he had company?
What if he saw something?
You haven't found him yet, have you?
I'm checking all the CCTVs...
and dashboard cameras from nearby...
and he didn't show up.
What do you know so far?
Nothing other than that he flew in with Logan.
His name is Baek Jun Ki.
Baek Jun Ki?
Have the police not yet called about Baek Jun Ki?
I don't think they found him yet.
Where is he hiding?
Any departure records?
None.
I downloaded a tracking app on the phone...
Logan gave him to use in Korea,
and he hasn't turned on his phone yet.
That means he's still in Korea.
We must find him first.
Before Joo Dan Tae does something.
Bang.
Yes, honey. Did you get there okay?
What's the weather like in New York?
The jet lag must be killing you.
Okay.
What? Of course, I'm home.
I just lay down to go to bed.
Got it. I love you.
No!
Get out. Get out.
Get out.
What are you doing here?
Shouldn't you lead with "long time no see?"
Is this why you never visited?
I'm disappointed.
There she is. Your mom.
What happened?
Seo Young, what is all this?
There you are.
You said my adultery...
brought shame to the family.
But I don't think your daughter leads a much better life.
What? "Your daughter?"
I believe Seo Young's in-laws are very sensitive about these issues.
Is it okay if...
I tell them?
Their classy, quiet daughter-in-law...
cheated on her husband with their driver.
- What are you doing? How crude... - Crude?
How classy did you think I was going to be after serving time?
Is that why you never visited...
when your "classy" daughter went to jail...
and even pushed Eun Byeol away?
How dare you call yourself family?
What is it...
that you want?
Return everything you stole from me.
Cheong A Foundation,
and the Myeongdong building.
(Building transfer agreement)
What are you waiting for? Sign it.
Unless you want to destroy...
the life of your precious daughter.
Mom. Tell her we'll give anything.
You want to see me get divorced?
(Building transfer agreement, Share transfer agreement)
I'll give you back the Myeongdong building.
But not Cheong A Foundation.
I sold it to Shim Su Ryeon.
How can you sell that?
Bring it back!
Even if it means a high penalty!
It's already done.
Please, Seo Jin. Let's just end it here.
I beg of you.
Please. I'm sorry.
- Seo Jin... - She's your sister, after all.
- Seo Jin, please... - Seo Jin, we're family.
Shim Su Ryeon. Of all people, why?
You really want to be my nemesis?
What's this?
What? Do you think it's poisoned?
If we're going to pretend to be a happy couple,
you should get used to this much.
Don't do anything unless I ask you to.
Do you think I wanted to do this?
Since we made a deal,
I think we should sign a contract.
I find it offensive when you invade my personal space.
Gladly.
This time, I get to decide.
Strictly abide by the rules written here.
Every time you break a rule, you lose one percent of your stock.
Sign it.
(Contract Marriage Rules)
"We do not intrude on each other's privacy."
"We do not eat at the same table at the same time."
"We must attend each other's official events."
"We smile kindly to each other when others are around."
"We keep a distance from each other at home."
"Joo Dan Tae answers all Cheon Seo Jin's calls."
"Cheon Seo Jin decides when and how..."
"to split the property."
What is this, a slave contract?
The show will go on...
until Cheon A Group's stock price doubles.
Once my goal is achieved, we'll get divorced...
and part ways. Keep your promise.
You should do the same. I'm not some thug.
You're not a thug. You're a scumbag.
What did you say, you wench?
Remember this.
Your life depends on me.
Get on my nerves again,
and the whole world will find out about your explosion show.
Unbelievable.
(Enter password)
(Would you like to install the spy app?)
(Installing)
(Installation completed)
Did you know about this?
Did you know Dad moved back to Hera Palace?
Seok Hoon, I can explain.
I'm the one who asked the restraining order to be lifted.
What?
Why? Can't I do that?
He's been cleared of murder charges.
Why can't he live here?
Why should we object to the court's decision?
I thought we were finally out of Dad's grip. Why in the world...
are you doing this?
Seok Kyung, if you want, I'm not going to stop you...
from seeing your dad.
But think about Ro Na.
If your dad lives at Hera Palace...
Why should I think about Ro Na?
She's a victim.
She can't live in the same building as the perpetrator.
You still see Ro Na's mom.
You keep the woman who killed your daughter with you.
Why not Dad?
- Seok Kyung! - Don't yell at me!
I know you're going to the US with Ro Na.
Did you think I wouldn't find out?
You only care and think about Ro Na.
You don't care at all about me,
so why are you stopping me from being close to Dad?
Did you forget what he did to us?
He even tried to kill our mom.
How are you still like this after all that he did to us?
I need him more.
Mom doesn't want me to go to Seoul University.
What do you mean,
I don't want you to go there? You're mistaken.
Why did Logan's family come to see you?
Is that a misunderstanding too?
What did he mean to you?
Did you like the jerk who harassed us or something?
Was he the one who tried to send Seok Hoon to the US?
To claim the penthouse by yourself as Dad said?
That's enough, Joo Seok Kyung!
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
You have no right to hit me!
Are you happy now?
You turned us against each other. Does that make you happy?
I will never leave the penthouse...
because this is my dad's home.
Hey.
I keep running into you.
I heard your mom got out.
Will you keep living here?
You're the one who should leave, not me.
You are just as shameless as your mom.
I live here too. On the 85th floor.
We'll run into each other morning and night.
Do you not care?
What? Are you looking for your bodyguard?
Stay away. I warned you.
Get away from Seok Hoon.
I don't know what you're up to and why you approached my son...
What do you think you're doing?
I remember everything you did to me.
So don't underestimate me.
- I'll make sure you pay! - You witch.
You witch!
I should've killed her for sure back then.
You did well.
You did well, Ro Na.
(Seoul University of Music Classical Singing Performance Test)
Finally, the performance test is seven days away.
Jenny's father...
prepared all organic foods so that you can eat and be strong.
Applause.
(Seoul University of Music - You! Jenny!)
Thank you. Enjoy.
And get along with Jenny.
Okay.
- Thank you. - Thanks.
What does my daughter want?
Caviar? Lobster?
- All of it. - Okay. Give me a minute.
The pizza's good.
Seok Hoon. I'm going to apply to Seoul University.
You are? You'll really take the test?
I have no reason to run away.
I'll prepare hard.
Good. I'll help you.
Thanks.
Ma Doo Ki speaking.
Why are you telling me that now?
Come on. Drink faster.
Hey. Drink like Jenny.
Okay. That's it.
Want to die?
Sorry?
How much are you going to eat?
Here, my princess. Eat more.
You need to eat well and be strong to perform well.
I don't want to eat anymore. I'll gain weight.
I have to watch my weight now.
I want to do everything for you that I couldn't while I was away.
Why are you refusing?
You're just excited that Mom's coming out, aren't you?
Gosh. That too.
Now that our family's reunited, we are invincible.
Stand tall. Stand proud.
Don't be discouraged, okay?
I must be studying too hard. I'm hallucinating.
What's your problem?
What do you want?
You haven't changed.
You're a spoiled brat and a rude punk.
Are you done?
It's a compliment.
No matter what happens,
you're strong and confident. That's your strength.
I really want you to get along...
with my daughter Jenny.
You're friends.
(Joo Seok Kyung)
Otherwise, that would be a really big problem.
Is the boys' room this way?
See you later.
Mr. Yoo. You've messed with the wrong girl.
I'll make you regret that.
(Director Cheon Seo Jin)
Seok Hoon's mother... I mean, Director Shim.
I just heard the news.
That you'll be our interim director.
I got the call too late.
I didn't get to clean up. I'm sorry.
- Mr. Ma Doo Ki? - Yes?
As the interim director,
I'd like to see all the student records.
Will you get them for me right now?
Why do you want to see...
I see. You must be worried about Seok Hoon's...
and Seok Kyung's college applications.
You don't have to worry about a thing.
You know me.
I've made sure they're perfect as per Chairman Joo's orders.
I made sure they won every award that was given out...
within the school.
They received 50 awards.
I heard you've even lost your house in a speculative investment.
I guess you still haven't learned your lesson.
- Pardon? - From this day forth,
you've been removed from all of your duties.
The grounds will be what you just admitted.
Manipulating student records.
But I did that for your babies...
I mean, your children.
I devoted myself to them.
It is my rule...
that no one gets special treatment. Not even my own children.
Given the disgraceful incident...
during the festival this year,
the principal will no longer give recommendations.
That is all. You may leave.
This is unfair.
All I did was devote myself...
to the school and the parents.
And I've played a big part...
in sending so many students to the top colleges.
You can't do this to me.
I'll submit a complaint to the Ministry of Education.
I won't go down alone.
So please, give me one more chance.
As an educator,
you should not have submitted to the parents.
I'm done listening to you.
Ma'am. Director Shim. Director Shim!
He must be waiting.
Mother, do you really plan not to go?
Why should I go there?
Did Kyu Jin save the country or something?
When I think about my money that he blew,
I stay up at night crying.
I'm only stopping by because of my grandson.
Well, now that you're out, I don't need to come anymore.
Mother. He'll be very hurt.
Father...
cut all ties with us as soon as he went to jail.
He's just waiting...
for us to post his bail.
Give me a break.
My son is in prison.
My daughter-in-law is out on probation.
My grandson is a school bully.
What idiocy is this...
in a family of lawyers?
Don't come over for the time being.
Stay quiet until you hear from me.
Mother. Mother.
You can't just leave, Mother.
Mother!
[VIU Ver] SBS E05 'The Penthouse 3'
"Reunion of Hera Club"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
I am free of my in-laws.
I am free of my husband!
It's been so long since I was free.
Kyu Jin, I'm sorry.
You never served in the army,
so you've never lived with a group before.
Since you're in there,
I hope you come back out as a decent human being.
Good luck.
I wish you the best.
Sang A!
Why am I hearing things?
Come back home
Kyu Jin got out on bail.
Sang A!
(Seoul Bank)
Hey! Mr. Yoo.
Attorney Lee, you got out.
I should've visited you sooner.
Your wife got out too, right?
You bet. I did my time,
and then Kyu Jin got out to see you.
Why is there black stuff on the surface? That's a bad omen.
I think there's an issue with the plumbing.
It smells bad, doesn't it?
I'll call Maintenance...
and fix it up perfectly myself.
I'm sure they'll manage.
Let's get going. Chairman Joo wants us there by 9pm.
But darn it, this rotten smell is really bad.
Do you think it's a dead body?
Let's go.
Oh, my.
Cheers.
Are you sure Cheong A Group can make a comeback?
Your shares reached a new low. It's killing me.
I trusted my stupid aide and bought at the last minute...
and now I'm totally ruined.
But then, both husband and wife ended up in handcuffs.
Who would invest?
Have you forgotten already who got you out on bail?
Do you know how much I spent to get your wife out too?
Try not to get too upset.
I said that out of pure concern.
Stock prices will rise again with one good piece of news.
What good news? A friend?
Do you have a friend called Good News?
Good news isn't a person's name here.
Dong Pil is way older than me,
but you're an idiot.
What gives you the guts to keep sidling up to me?
If there's no good news, make some.
Right, Chairman?
Don't you have a plan?
- Cheonsoo District. - Cheon... Cheon...
Not again. Not that darn Cheonsoo District again!
I sunk millions of dollars into that...
and my mom disowned me and I had to quit politics.
My whole life was ruined!
Get back up after you fall. Isn't that how life is?
Do you have what I asked for?
Here's the report on Opyeong District.
After the redevelopment was announced,
everything's been going well without a hitch.
Opyeong District's redevelopment. We have to flip it.
Does that make sense? The land there...
was flattened out...
and they started work already.
Isn't that why we gathered to put our heads together?
How did you pass the bar with a brain like that?
The planner of our group...
was always Dr. Ha.
Yes.
He was a hypocrite, but he was a smart one.
I lost my appetite for alcohol!
Why must you mention a fool...
who needs to rot in jail for much longer?
So I invited another person...
with the smart brain that you want.
Come in!
How've you been?
Stay seated.
You don't have to stand to welcome me.
It's too much of an honour.
Ha Yoon Chul, how come you're here?
When did you get out?
Just today.
I had the shortest sentence of us all.
Wasn't my release a long time coming?
This is fantastic.
Let's talk about work first.
Mr. Yoo briefed me on why you're meeting today.
I'm here because I'd like to join this project.
Why did you invite him without my permission?
How much did you tell him?
Two years ago, near Opyeong District,
a Joseon kiln site was found.
You know that, right?
The trick to put a stop to the Opyeong District development.
I have one.
I did some thinking when I was left alone in jail.
What do I get from pretending to be...
just and straight?
I won't do that anymore, and now I know my place.
I decided to be the worst of the worst trash.
Wrong.
I disapprove.
He's an expert at stabbing people in the back.
Don't you remember how he betrayed us in court?
Chairman Joo, you won't trust Traitor Ha, will you?
Right now, right here, no one's as desperate as I am.
I lost everything.
My wife, kid, home, money, honour, everything!
Even my doctor's license was suspended.
I can't even practice now.
Isn't that why...
you're back here, to get revenge on us?
Hey. Do you think we are stupid and...
Revenge is only possible when you have money and power.
I need to survive.
What must I do to make you believe me?
He's insane.
Shall I dig out my heart too?
Do it.
Stop.
You won't regret this.
I'm even prepared to lick the soles of your feet.
(Opyeong District Redevelopment Plan)
(Wiretapped)
You idiot. How many times must I tell you?
Look. If an artifact is unearthed in Opyeong District...
Construction will be stopped...
and an investigation will begin.
Then Cheonsoo District that was going to be redeveloped...
but then not will resurface as the next place to redevelop.
It's next to a kiln site,
so the artifact should be pottery.
I will look into that.
We'll get something if we ask a fencer.
We'll need an excavator.
I will drive it myself.
I can invite reporters and civic groups...
to make a huge fuss.
Hey, Ha Yoon Chul.
I can no longer stand watching you be so haughty.
Tonight, let's get things straight.
We need to sort out our rank.
I was born in October of 1978.
I was born in early 1978.
But you can be my senior.
I am your minion!
It has been a while since the four of us got together.
We must make it big.
Let's score so that we stink of money.
You're way too eager.
The group feels perfect now that Dr. Ha is back.
Let's make a toast.
Here's to the grand return of Hera Club in its entirety.
- Cheers! - Cheers!
- Hey. Yoon Chul. - Yes?
Why don't you sing for us?
Freeze.
Do you know what time it is?
Your wife was released from prison today.
How could you come home at this hour reeking of alcohol?
Honey.
Sweetheart.
My lady, tonight is going to be an unforgettable night.
- Dad! - Jenny.
Jenny, were you still up?
Of course, I waited up.
Our family is finally reunited. How about some chicken and soda?
Dad, I found an amazing chicken place.
You did? Then shall we?
This is not okay. I had a plan, Jenny.
- Go in. - Okay.
Come on.
Let me just change first.
Order everything you want.
Anyway, why did you come home so late?
Did you already start working?
I should get moving soon.
I had a business meeting.
The fountain on the first floor seems to be out of order.
Has it ever happened before?
The fountain is out of order?
It was built with the best materials from Europe.
That's strange.
As the person who built it, I feel bad.
I should probably take it apart myself.
You're going to quit this, right?
Quit right now.
I'll make sure we move to the top floor of Hera Palace.
Well...
I'm still too young to retire.
As long as there are ladies who insist on receiving my service,
how can I quit?
Here. Cheers.
I hope you're not getting involved with Joo Dan Tae.
I'm not. That's absurd.
You'd better not.
I won't sit back if you get involved with that jerk in any way.
He deserves to be torn to pieces. That piece of trash.
You're on probation now.
You shouldn't tear a person to pieces.
So? Are you going to continue to hang out with him?
You were in prison for six years because of that jerk.
- It makes my blood boil. - Is someone talking about me?
Are you listening to me or not?
Jenny, has the food arrived yet?
Wait.
He's not only good-looking but also so kind-hearted.
I can never relax.
I'm so worried.
SNU's performance test is right around the corner.
I wonder if I can lose weight until then.
It's your kid taking the test.
Why should you lose weight?
As her mom, I should do something.
It's the least I can do to get her into SNU.
At our age, we don't have the energy to work out.
And it's not easy to lose weight simply by fasting.
You're right.
- Excuse me. What's taking so long? - Gosh.
Hello.
Oh, my.
How have you been?
Yoon Hee, what are you doing here?
Don't tell me you work here.
I did hear that you got released,
but I didn't expect you to find a job so soon.
Anyway, how did you get released so early?
We really need stricter laws in this country.
Joo Dan Tae and Cheon Seo Jin walked free...
after committing crimes too.
Are you okay with that?
I got released legally.
Stop being nosy.
How dare you speak to me like that?
You're a murderer!
My gosh.
You scared me.
From now on, please be more careful.
The first time is always the hardest.
Let me know if you need any help.
Gosh.
Did she just threaten to kill us?
Unit 4502 belongs to JohnBIO,
so I thought she'd move out immediately.
But apparently, I was wrong.
Hera Palace is no rehab center for criminals.
To rent a shop this size in Hera Palace,
she must've paid a huge deposit.
I wonder where Ms. Oh got that much money.
I know. Maybe Su Ryeon lent her some money.
No way.
Why would she lend money to a woman who killed her daughter?
Did she hit the jackpot or something?
Did she make money in prison?
She sure has a way with money.
That's not it. Be quiet for a moment.
There must be something huge behind her.
Su Ryeon, it's been a while.
Thanks to you, I experienced so many things...
that I never imagined I would.
I see.
You know,
if we're going to keep seeing each other as neighbours,
I think we should let bygones be bygones.
We went through so much in there.
You have no idea.
It must've been so hard.
Is that what you want to hear?
Let's face it, you're not entirely innocent either.
Oh Yoon Hee is already out of prison...
and has even opened her own shop.
It isn't exactly a pretty sight, I must say.
She opened her own shop?
You didn't know that?
We thought you financed it.
Then who financed it?
Did Logan leave some money to her...
when he died?
Why would he?
What's their relationship?
Could it be that Oh Yoon Hee...
Killed him?
You people haven't changed a bit, have you?
Do you still fear nothing in the world?
Watch your mouth.
Is she going to report us or something?
What's the big deal about Logan?
Is he someone sacred we can't even talk about?
- I know. - Fine, go ahead and report us!
Using accurate data,
we first find out why you gained weight to begin with.
We provide customized solutions.
I hope you can trust us and give it a try.
What do you think?
I heard you called, sir.
Come sit down.
(Cheong A Group)
I was too harsh on you yesterday.
I thought about it,
and I think it was a great move...
to invite Yoon Chul to join the Cheonsoo District project.
Thank you for thinking of it that way.
Is Jenny doing okay with getting ready for college?
Do you need anything?
No, it's okay.
You've already given us a great house,
and you helped my wife with her work.
I have no idea how I'm going to pay you back.
These days, I spend most of my time doing things for Jenny...
to make up for the time while I was gone.
Jenny doesn't know...
that you went to jail...
for murder, right?
Of course not. I'll keep my lips sealed forever.
Good. I'll do the same.
You and I go way back.
Our kids will all get accepted to Seoul University of Music.
So let's throw a big party once they finish their exams.
I'd be honoured.
You really are a generous man.
I admire you, sir.
Okay, you may go now.
I'm impressed.
How was that?
Do you believe me now?
I have Jenny's father...
in the palm of my hand.
You're right.
I hated how he kept going around acting like a big shot.
Now tell me why you're here.
What is it that you want?
Mom doesn't want me to go to SNU.
As soon as she became the director of Cheong A Foundation,
she forbade the principal from recommending anyone.
Well, obviously.
You and that woman...
aren't related at all. She's pretty much a stranger.
Why would she want you to go to SNU...
when you were one of the kids who bullied her daughter?
You're my daughter,
so she'll never let you become happy.
What would you do if you were in her shoes?
Wouldn't you want to destroy whomever hurt your daughter?
Don't speak ill of her.
Just get rid of a disgusting loach for me.
A loach? Whom?
- Bae Ro Na. - "Ro Na"?
But she's not even going to take the CSATs.
She changed her mind.
I bet Mom convinced her.
Do everything you can to make her fail the test.
You'll do that for me, right?
When have I ever let you down?
Don't worry. I'll deal with it for you.
I really want to go to SNU.
With Seok Hoon.
Yes, of course. It's only right that you go there.
(Seoul University of Music, Day of the Exam)
(Examination Hall College of Music, Seoul University)
- Good luck! - I wish you the best.
You can do this!
- Show them what you got! - Good luck!
Your dad is the best.
Let's go.
Who brings their dad to the performance test?
Kids who are bound to fail always make a big deal of things.
As soon as I retired,
it felt as if my life had come to an end.
But my husband continued...
to stay by my side.
I'm the one who's grateful.
If I didn't have my wife by my side...
when I was falsely accused, I never would've made it.
I love you, honey.
- I love you more. - Honey.
Thank you. Thank you.
Is it okay if we take a photo?
- Sure. - Of course.
- Take one more from here. - Okay.
Hey, shouldn't you be at SNU for your daughter's exam?
What's gotten into you? I thought that'd be your priority.
- Shut your mouth. - Got it.
I'll go ahead and take the photo.
Min Hyuk.
Ha Eun Byeol is here.
Eun Byeol.
Are you waiting for someone?
No, I'm not waiting for anyone.
All I need is you.
Why are you shaking so much?
I don't feel so good. I feel like throwing up.
You know what? Why don't you take your medicine?
No, I'll try to overcome it.
Ms. Jin.
What brings you here?
Hey, long time no see.
Why don't we talk over there?
I'll be right back after I talk to her.
Are you also here for the exam?
Why? Am I not allowed to be here?
You're also here, but I don't ever remember you apologizing.
I got punished too, okay?
I even got sent to a youth detention center.
Cut it out. I'm sick of your excuses.
- Seok Hoon. Hello. - Hi, Ro Na.
Did you do well?
Isn't that Ha Eun Byeol?
The loser who can't do anything without her mother?
How hilarious. Look at her face.
What happened?
I thought you went back to the States.
I'm actually taking care of Eun Byeol at the moment.
She has no parents.
What do you mean? They both got released.
Why are you still taking care of her?
I don't see why I need to explain my private life to you.
We should stay away from each other. I'm sure it's uneasy for both of us.
You know Logan's dead, right?
Yes, it's such a pity.
When was the last time you contacted Logan?
Probably the day you turned yourself in.
I never got to see him again after that.
It's almost time, right?
Can I have my medicine? I think I need to take it.
Sure. Good thinking.
It'll help you calm down.
(TOEFL Preparation Institute, Get the job done properly!)
(Test ID, Joo Seok Hoon)
Are you Joo Seok Hoon?
Yes.
You look very much like your father.
I'll see you later.
Don't be nervous. Take it easy.
Seok Hoon, I bet you'll get in just by playing a few notes.
Why don't you just play the melodica?
Get lost.
Hey, the piano performance test is held over there.
(Examination Hall College of Music, Seoul University)
(Test ID, Joo Seok Hoon)
What's wrong? Does your throat hurt?
- Water. - No, no.
You need to drink hot water.
Gosh, the water in the Thermos has gone cold. Just a minute.
I'll go to the car and get your scarf.
You just wait, sweetheart.
But I need to go...
My gosh, they're unbelievable.
Your dad seems to care for you a lot.
I really envy you.
I've always wanted a caring dad like yours.
Don't talk to me.
But your dad never went to Dubai, did he?
What is it that you want to say?
I don't know if this is the right occasion to tell you this,
but I heard your dad went to jail for murder.
Cut the nonsense!
I know you can't believe me, but it's true.
(Share with Yoo Jenny)
(You've received a voice recording file.)
Go ahead and check for yourself.
There comes your father.
Jenny doesn't know...
that you went to jail for murder, right?
Of course not. I'll keep my lips sealed forever.
I'm not late, am I? They didn't call your name, right?
Here's your scarf...
Why are you so nervous?
Your face is pale.
Don't worry. Just be at ease.
If my daughter doesn't get into SNU, the school will be losing out.
Wait. I need to go to the bathroom.
The bathroom? I'll go with you.
- Jenny. - You're unbelievable.
- You can't go with her. - Oh, right.
Why does she keep going to the bathroom?
Do you think it's because she's nervous?
I know, right?
Everyone, attention.
The performance test for classical singing will begin now.
Please get ready according to the number you picked out.
You are not allowed to bring in cell phones or voice recorders.
Please take off your headbands...
or any other accessories that could make you stand out.
Jenny, are you ready?
(Yoo Jenny's father is a murderer!)
Jenny.
(Judge)
(Yoo Jenny's father is a murderer!)
Jenny, I need you to get lost.
I can't go to the same school with someone I bullied.
I don't want to be labelled as someone who bullied you.
(Judge)
(Examination Hall College of Music, Seoul University)
[VIU Ver] SBS E06 'The Penthouse 3'
"Performance Test For Seoul University Of Music"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
Mom.
Hey, Ro Na. Did you do a good job?
Yes, I got to sing the song I practiced the most.
I'm so glad to hear that. You did great.
You have no idea how nervous I was.
Let's go.
Ha Eun Byeol, get ready.
Don't get nervous. You can do this.
You even took your medicine.
- Okay. - Okay. Good luck.
(Judge)
(Examination Hall for the entrance of 2023 Seoul University of Music)
What is that?
Did you bring your cell phone?
No, I didn't.
Are you still going to deny it?
No, I swear I put my cell phone in my bag earlier.
You're disqualified. You may leave now.
It really isn't mine.
You have to believe me.
Ro Na?
It was here.
Where did it go?
Bae Ro Na!
What do you think you're doing?
Did you really have to do this?
So this is what you do to ruin my life?
Why can't you just hit me and push me like I did?
I worked so hard the past 12 years just for this day.
Did you really have to go this far?
Have you lost your mind? What's the matter with you?
Eun Byeol, what are you trying to do to Ro Na again?
Have you not learned your lesson?
I became disqualified for the test because of your daughter.
I don't care what anyone thinks now.
I can't believe this is how you chose to take revenge.
Fine. I'll do the exact same thing to you.
I'm not going to be the only one who fails to get in.
I'm going to raise an issue with this.
You're the one who cheated,
so you deserve to get disqualified too!
Stop taking it out on her...
just because you failed your test.
Stop crying and tell me what really happened.
While I was taking my test,
your cell phone suddenly rang inside my pocket.
You put it in there on purpose, didn't you?
You witch.
You darn witch!
That's enough, Eun Byeol.
Don't get nervous. You can do this.
You even took your medicine.
(Examination Hall College of Music, Seoul University)
(Examination Hall for the entrance of 2023 Seoul University of Music)
Ha Eun Byeol, disqualified!
Where did Seok Hoon go?
Did he even take the test?
- The receiver cannot be reached. - I don't know.
- You will be directed to voicemail. - Why won't he answer his phone?
Please leave a message after...
What are you doing here?
My precious kids took an important test today.
So it's only natural that I'm here.
Seok Kyung, did you make any mistakes?
I think I did a pretty good job.
I'll be spending time with Dad.
He promised to buy me something to eat after the test.
I'm sorry you have to leave alone.
Your mom's down to earth, so I bet she won't care.
Let's go.
Seok Kyung.
Seok Kyung will be home late.
She might not even go home tonight.
Hey, Mr. Hong. What's up?
Baek Jun Ki just turned on his cell phone.
We got his location from the application.
Where is he?
Ro Na will get disqualified...
along with Eun Byeol.
I knew it was you.
Eun Byeol is so dumb. She's nothing without her mom.
By the way, whom did you ask to do this for you?
That's a secret.
Jenny seems to have failed the test too.
That means I might be the only one who gets in.
Not everyone gets into SNU.
But you'll get accepted because you're my daughter.
Do you know why your mother's so nice to you guys?
Why?
She wants to become your sole guardian...
so she can take the inheritance of your biological mother.
She's not that kind of person.
I'm sorry.
But it's true.
She's related to...
the death of your biological mother.
Really?
Did Logan really kill our biological mom?
Because of Mom?
- Excuse the mess, everyone. - Sorry for the mess.
We're sorry.
You're Baek Jun Ki, aren't you?
Let me go. I'm going to kill him.
Baek Jun Ki, who are you really?
My daughter's there.
I can't let her watch her own father die right before her eyes.
(The Penthouse 3)
- There you are. - You said you'll kill Joo Dan Tae.
My heart still beats like crazy every time I see you.
Did you really kill someone?
A million times more! I'm a father.
Joo Dan Tae's dog. It really suits you.
You don't need to worry about my family or house.
A billion dollars?
Logan's money suddenly disappeared.
How would I know about that money?
Oh Yoon Hee took a billion dollars?
- Mr. Baek. - Logan?
It seemed like he cared for you a lot.
Do you like it?