fTiming and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ No longer panicking on the night of the blackout ♫
♫ You're by my side, illuminating a beam of light for me ♫
♫ Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet ♫
♫ Your breath ♫
♫ brushes up against my cheek ♫
♫ With you warming up the stage,
happiness never comes to a close ♫
♫ Boring jokes add some sweetness to the dinner ♫
♫ Daily life is even more like a comic than comics themselves ♫
♫ Happiness and sadness ♫
♫ Make up the moments of life ♫
♫ Rainy days become very special because of you ♫
♫ Picked up a pitiful youngster off the street ♫
♫ No matter when and where, you always appear ♫
♫ Holding me tightly and spinning in circles ♫
♫ Rainy days make me so nostalgic because of you ♫
♫ Becoming some part of the memories ♫
♫ Walking down a street with lights lighting up
one after another ♫
♫ Warming up the whole world ♫
[Please Feel at Ease Mr. Ling]
[Episode 20]
Why did you do that?
What makes you think I wouldn't do that?
Because I know that you're someone that would use such tactics.
Then you have to hurry up
or else you may not be able to
handle everything later on.
President Gu, the other company provided evidence and pointed out
that the plan for An Xing exists.
Stop filming. Move aside.
I hope you'll stop letting your emotions affect your decisions
and eventually become someone that you don't even know yourself.
What's wrong? It's so late and you're still not asleep.
I can't fall asleep.
Would you like to drink a glass together?
Okay.
Someone gave me 10 bottles of wine.
Every year
and each flavor
are different.
Are you talking about Ling Sheng?
Brother,
what kind of person do think Ling Sheng is?
Ling Sheng seems to have always been well protected by his family.
He's an outgoing person.
Even though I don't like the people from the Ling family,
but Ling Sheng is indeed different from the others in the Ling family.
What's more important is that he's been serious about you all these years.
I know,
but I'm very confused right now.
I have no way
to completely let go of Ling Yue.
Xin'er,
ever relationship has its overdraft.
If the overdraft is empty,
then there's no need to continue.
If its weren't for other people appearing,
my relationship with him wouldn't be like what it is now.
I want to test it one more time
and for the last time.
It's Ling Yue.
Hello.
Okay, let's meet after the celebration then.
Ling Yue wants to meet you?
For what?
I don't know. Who knows what he's up to.
Brother, can you help me go to the wine rack to get me another bottle?
Okay, I'll drink with you until you're satisfied tonight.
Wait for me.
Let's arrive before 11 o' clock tomorrow.
Let's meet at the small auditorium near the east corner of the school.
I didn't expect this place to be abandoned.
Is it just like our memories?
They're being all thrown away by you.
Why is it you? Where's Gu Ansheng?
My brother didn't come.
You kept avoiding me and not seeing me.
I can only use this method to invite you over.
I came to find Gu Ansheng regarding the collaboration. If there's nothing else, then I'll get going.
Why do you always avoid me each time you see me?
Do I look that scary?
Our time is very precious.
- Stop doing things that are meaningless.
- I know,
but this is the last time.
Let me finish what I want to say, what I couldn't say, and what I didn't have time to say.
Can I?
I locked all the doors.
I also blocked all the signals.
- What on earth do you want to do?
- I want to make you stay.
I want you to reconsider and think it through.
Who on earth is your right decision?
You're wasting time.
Compared to the future,
this time that is wasted is considered nothing.
When revisiting here,
is there a different feeling?
I know your relationship is sweet now,
but I'm really not willing to believe it and give up
that the person you chose at the end is her.
What decision I made
is my business.
Brother Yue, we grew up together.
We didn't need to waste 20 years to understand and know each other.
How can you confirm that within such short period of time,
your decision won't be wrong?
As long as its Anxin, then it won't be wrong.
If you want to keep talking about this to me,
then it's unnecessary to continue.
Since I was young,
even once or even a moment,
were you not moved?
We knew each other for so long.
You were always someone worth respecting
and a friend that I was close with.
That's it.
It's been 10 years.
I liked you for 10 years.
Our relationship for so many years
cannot be compared to a few months with her.
Since I chose Anxin,
then I won't like anyone else.
Stop being entangled with something that won't have a result.
President Ling is not back yet?
President Ling did not come to work yet. Theres already few important phone calls for him
but we could not contact him
Hello?
Miss Anxin, do you know where President Ling is?
How would I know where he is?
We can't find President Ling at the company
everyone is extremely worried
when I woke up this morning he had already left
So he didn't tell you where he was going?
No
He told us he needed to clear something about you
About me?
let me see if I can reach him
Wait a moment.
[Ling Yue]
"i'm sorry the number you have reached is ..."
Please try again later.
The opening event Invitation...
I know where he is!
'man stalking'
Lingyue
Anxinou
You're okay! You scared me
You're not angry at me anymore?
You did this on purpose
I'm sorry I made you worry
It was you using my brothers name to meet Lingyue
your brother?
He's my brother!
Gu Anxin.
You really like what's mine
I have no interest at all in what's yours.
what do you want?
What I want?
what Ling Yue has done to me in the past?
I don't want to know.
We...
have a past
that no one can replace.
do you want to know?
I don't want to hear it
Fine
Then you can see it
What can it prove?
Your relationship is great but...
Gu Anxin did you ever think about
what right do you have to love him? you already ruined Yuguo's life
Now you want to ruin mine? 10 years.
I waited for him for 10 years! What did you do for him?
All you are just average standing
Couldn't even finish college
I finally realized my patience and holding back
only makes you more eager.
Gu Xiner, let me just say. I did nothing wrong
from now on...
I am no longer going to get bullied
and hold my patience
I will live properly
to love Lingyue properly
So please live your own life properly
Let's go
10 years!
My 10 years is nothing compared to her few months?
Somethings are not how you see them.
It isn't just a sudden love?
No, we are not.
As with you...
it is only like that picture
a misunderstanding
Lingyue and Anxin has left
I knew you would find me
Then that picture...
that was just a prank by Lingfang
then if I see another picture like that
you're dead to me
I promise there won't be a next time
how can you smile?  you were almost kidnapped
I was just smiling at you claiming me
That's right. I've already made a vow of sovereingty.
then this life you are mine
then you can't be shared with anyone else
and in your heart you can only hold me
that so?
Ok! Got it
Xiner...
you don't look so well, are you alright
Why are you here?
Didn't you say you don't care anymore?
I wasn't''t honest
When I heard about you I started to worry again
So I came without a second thought
That night...
That night nothing happened. I asked a female worker at the hotel to change your clothes.
That night you were drunk
How could I?
I know you don't love me.
Then why did you leave?
I was just frustrated at the way you hurt yourself
just like now
you already know he doesn't have feelings for you
yet you won't give up and continue to struggle
you already waited 10 years, will you continue to wait?
how many 10 years would you have?
is it worth it?
actually, before you came
I was still hateful
and blaming
and did not want to quit
but when you showed up
I suddenly don't feel that way anymore
I said it inside my heart.
Thank you, Ling Sheng.
No matter what state I'm in, you're willing to keep me company.
I promise you. This time
I will definitely let go.
Let's go.
Okay.
Come on. I'll carry you.
That is what happened.
Regarding Yu Guo's issue, Yang Hong is the most suspicious.
Oh right. Why did you look for my brother?
For a collaboration.
It was always my uneasiness that got me.
I always feel like he was our barrier
so I wanted to kick him away,
but it won't bring me anything even if I do.
It happens to be the opposite.
When he was destroying the people and things I loved,
no matter if it was you or Ling Group
I always thought I should use another method to protect the people and things I love.
Regarding your uneasiness,
I can understand.
You're still the Ling Yue that I love.
So you mean
you don't love me when we argue?
But I don't like you less when we argue.
I don't know who it was
that didn't say anything and kept it inside.
What's wrong?
I finally contacted you. Are you fine?
I'm fine. I'm with Anxin.
Your dad suddenly had a stroke and was rushed to the hospital. Hurry and come over.
- Great Auntie.
- Auntie.
- What's that situation now?
- The surgery is in progress and the doctor didn't say anything.
Dad was fine. How come he suddenly fainted?
How is he fine?
Your dad is so busy with work.
He haven't taken a break for half a year.
Who was by his side when his illness acted up?
I was by dad's side.
Dad was in the studyroom. He was fine,
but then he suddenly said he was dizzy. I thought something was wrong
so I immediately called emergency.
When the ambulance arrived, he already fainted.
How long was the time period from when he fainted until he reached the hospital?
Doctor! Doctor!
He patient's condition stable right now, but he still needs to be observed.
When we ask, everyone says stable. He's not awake. What do you mean by stable?
It indicates that he's stable. It requires time for him to gain consciousness.
Doctor, there's so many documents waiting for President Ling to sign.
Can you use better medicine
so that President Ling can gain consciousness earlier?
Is the patient's health more important or signing the documents?
All the brothers are here.
Is there no one else in the Ling family?
Find us if there's anything.
I'll get going.
You've worked hard.
Regarding work,
let's talk after your dad wakes up.
I think before President Ling wakes up,
letting Ling Fang handle it
is more suitable since he's the oldest one.
This isn't suitable.
How is it not?
The company has to have someone in charge.
No, after hearing President Ling was unconscious,
the shareholders discussed and decided to call a lawyer over.
Why did you guys notify a lawyer for?
Everyone this is Mr. Ling's signature
for his emergency letter and his will.
President Ling is unconscious right now so its considered an emergency.
According to this document,
Mr. Ling Yue will be temporarily in charge of Ling Group.
President Ling, since this is Old President Ling's meaning,
then I'll have to trouble you to go back to the company with us.
There are a lot of things that you need to go back and handle.
President Ling Yue, if its not taken care in time and the information gets leaked,
it will affect the company and the stocks.
President Ling Yue.
Go ahead, I'm here. Don't worry.
Okay, I'll leave him to you guys.
Tell me immediately when dad wakes up and I'll come over.
Take care.
Why are you looking for me?
I want to remind my old friend.
I already know what you want to say
so you don't have to look for me in the future.
What about what happened in the past?
Don't worry.
This is already buried deeply.
Ling Yue.
What's wrong?
Why are you sweating so much?
Did you have a nightmare?
I'll bring you out for a walk, okay?
Here.
How is it? Are they cute?
There are more downstairs. Let's go take a look.
Let's go.
There are sharks downstairs.
What are you guys doing? Can't you guys see that this area is on maintenance?
We already brought tickets.
You still can't go in even if you guys brought tickets. Come next month.
You guys can't go in.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Hug. Hug me.
Come in.
Welcome to the world of bad kids. Let's go!
Who is it?
That's odd.
Do you know why I brought you here today?
Your feud with my brother reminded me
that we are kids that were once hurt.
Even though wounds will heal,
but scars won't come off.
But
as long as we don't let our fears get at us,
then memories cannot swallow us.
Just like today. We neglected the risks
so you can appreciate what's happening now, right?
I always wanted to get rid of the dangers that the environment brings me,
but I neglected the biggest uneasiness in my heart.
Anxin, thank you
for letting me experience
how each situation comes from one's decision.
What I need isn't a fence,
but to walk out of the safe area.
Don't worry, you can do it.
I will always keep you company.
I'll have trouble you then.
Stingrays! Hurry, its string rays!
Wishes will come true if you make a wish in front of stringrays.
- Is there really such a thing?
- Yes, I just came up with it.
President Gu, President Ling is here.
What's up? Are you hear to declare war
or to take account of past affairs?
None.
I'm here to talk about a collaboration.
President Ling,
why are you suddenly collaborating with your enemy?
If its because of Anxin,
then I don't think its necessary.
I don't want her to get involved with our issues.
I won't make her be in a hard position.
It's Anxin who let me understand the meaning acceptance.
Fighting alone for temporarily benefits
won't last long.
I hope you can understand this.
Are you still the
Ling Yue who is decisive and stops at nothing?
Because I have yearning
so I became more frank.
Then why are you so confident that I'll definitely collaborate with you?
This is your best choice now.
Also, I trust Anxin and to be relatives with you to work together.
Shaking hands in the past
tells the other party that they don't have any weapons in their hands.
Expanding your hand out now
means
we don't want to harm anyone.
I valued the prospects when I wanted to add in 5G.
I didn't want to compete with you on purpose.
It's just that after doing it..
deviated.
What you mean is you didn't know beforehand?
President Liu didn't tell us that he was collaborating with you guys.
Can you still contact President Liu now?
I can't. After something happened to the Gu Group, we couldn't contact him.
Ling Sheng,
didn't we say that you'll arrive in front of me at 10 o' clock sharp?
It's almost time. Where are you?
I already arrived.
Where are you then?
Walk towards the balcony and take a look.
Walk towards the balcony?
What are you up to? So mysterious.
Where are you?
Open it and take a look.
Behind you.
This is...
Xin'er,
do you still remember this?
This is the first gift that you gave me.
Even though I know this was originally for my second brother,
but was reluctant to even wear it once.
I'm sorry. Regarding this, I actually...
There's no need to explain. I understand,
but there's something that you probably never knew.
When you went abroad to look for my second brother,
I would secretly go look for you quite often.
Even though you never noticed me each time
and we would brush pass each other,
but as long as I can see you each time,
I always feel really satisfied.
I went to all the cities that you went to.
I started to slowly collect these tickets and postcards.
I already collected so many without realizing.
How come you never told me this before?
You never told my second brother everything you did for him.
Xin'er, we're the same people.
We were too silly when we loved others.
I'm telling you this now just to let you know
when you secretly look at my second brother, there's also another person
secretly protecting you.
You don't have to love others so tiredly.
You deserve to be loved and cherished too.
Ling Sheng.
Xin'er,
when second brother would look for you in the past
and when you step in
without hesitation,
you'll run the rest of the path for him.
But do you know?
As long as you nod,
without hesitation, I can also
run crazily for you
so are you willing to accept
the me, who is willing to run crazily for you?
Thank you.
I love you.
The patient has a nose contusion. Routine blood test for blood clotting,
STD screening, kidney function, electroylytes, etc.
Gu Anxin?
I seem to have no impression of her.
I can guarantee that no one will know.
Don't let there be a next time.
Teacher Shen.
Teacher Shen?
I already looked at the report. It's quite well written.
Near the end, regarding the patient being discharged and their basic medication needs,
there needs to be some specific and reasonable
physiological
and daily life recommendations for the patient.
I know now, Teacher Shen.
Thank you for instructing me during this time.
Let me ask you a question.
Why are you being a doctor?
I never had any ambitions since I was young,
but I feel like being able to relieve pain and save lives
is great thing to do.
If this can become my career,
then I think
my life would be more meaningful.
President Ling, Jack and them should be at the airport now.
They will reach the meeting location in about 30 minutes.
Bro, I feel so bad.
What's wrong?
I don't want to continue staying here. I want to resign!
Can you be more rational? Where are you now?
I'm not good. I cannot be rational!
Shen Yishan?
Hello?
Turn around and go to Shen Yishan's house.
Bro, you're here.
Drink with me.
Ai Li? I was must dreaming.
Dreams are wonderful. Even Ai Li is here.
Then, why did you come in my dreams?
You value your lover more than your friends. Looks like you're not drunk.
You don't know how bad I feel.
I won't ever go to the hospital again.
Starting tomorrow, I will accompany Ai Li
to wonderland.
I rarely see him like this. Just let him open up for once.
Hello?
President Ling, Jack already arrived.
We must depart now.
I'll go over there. Keep him company.
- But—
- He needs you right now.
Moreover, you've worked hard recently. Treat it like a break for yourself.
Old Jiang, oh Old Jiang. Teacher Jiang.
Why did you do such a thing?
Why?
Is it because of Jiang Tao? Is it necessary?
You don't know how important he is to me.
He's my mentor.
Since you feel so bad and he's so close to you,
why aren't you reminded him to take responsibility?
Do you know how many people he saved?
Do you know he's the hope of many people?
If it was me who sent him to jail,
then how should I face him?
But you'll only hurt Anxin and them by avoiding the problem.
Moreover, you and your mentor will suffer just as much.
Aren't closest people all like this?
It's hard to say it and face it.
Just like you. You always avoiding my pursuing.
Look! Why?
Why?
Stop being like this. You can't solve the problem by acting like this.
But at least I can relieve the pain.
Ai Li,
you're a robot.
Only I, Xiao Yi Shan,
understand why you're single.
♪ The gust of wind blows pass my heart ♪
Stop singing and go to sleep.
♪ It won't ever cry for me ♪
L-let go, Xiao Yi Shan.
I'm not letting go.
I want to keep hugging you until forever.
- Let go first.
- I'm not letting go.
You'll fly away once I let go.
I know you probably don't like me that much,
but can you give me a chance to like you?
L-let go first.
I'm not letting go unless you promise me.
Promise you what?
Promise...
to let us be together.
Say it.
Okay, I promise you.
President Ling said you had no food at home so he told me to bring breakfast for you.
It's all my favorites. Thank you.
Thank you, Ling Yue too.
Hurry and eat, then go to work.
Go to work? I'm not going.
I'm going to turn in my resign letter today.
I'm not working anymore. I'm resigning.
President Ling said he's not allowing you to resign.
Based on what?
He's not my superior. I can do whatever I want.
Then, what if I don't want you to resign?
What?
Y-you're also not my superior.
What am I to you then?
Good friend.
That's right, good friend.
You don't know that I have people that I don't want to see at the hospital.
I feel bad if I see him.
I know.
You know? How did you know?
You said it yesterday.
Yesterday?
Yesterday, you were the one who took care of me?
Who else then?
I didn't say anything I wasn't supposed to, right?
I didn't do anything I wasn't supposed to do, right?
I also dreamed that I hugged you.
Yes, in your dreams.
It's good that its my dreams.
Xiao Ai is getting her vaccine today. Let's go together.
How come women change their faces so quickly? Why is she angry?
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Memories are soaked in rain ♫
♫ Fate works bizarrely ♫
♫ The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly beats abnormally ♫
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Obviously, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness, for it has always been you ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Yet the longing has never been able to stop ♫
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Using all of my most beautiful adjectives ♫
♫ Is still not enough to describe your name ♫
♫ Our story is exclusively ours ♫
♫ Our palms hold onto the key to the future ♫
♫ Using love to slowly open up  ♫
♫ a lifetime ♫