Your mind keeps going back
to May of that year.
That's not strange at all.
If you lose your favorite umbrella,
you think of it whenever it rains.
It feels even worse...
if the season
you lost your loved one...
comes back every year.
It's only natural...
that our minds return to that day...
as if it were yesterday.
Sir, I'm sorry to disturb you
during a session.
Hello.
Did you get the text message?
They found her.
(Episode 12, The First May)
Don't kill me.
Let me live.
Over here! There's a kid here!
My goodness. Don't.
Don't look at what I'm writing.
The writing's so small
that I can't even see it.
We're going to read it
out to each other anyway.
What's the point
in writing so small?
Can't we skip the prayer?
Marriage vows are enough.
We have no officiator or guests.
And we didn't prepare
outfits, wedding gifts, or anything.
We should exchange something
to commemorate our marriage.
I'm useless at writing essays.
I didn't tell you to write an essay.
Just write what you want.
I bet it'll all come true.
The Lord will take pity on us
because we're penniless.
Why aren't you
writing out your prayer?
I memorized mine already.
There's a prayer I say every day.
What is it about?
If I die,
I want you to be buried with me.
As in buried alive with you?
Pray for something else.
You said the prayers will come true.
Then you can pray
that you won't be buried alive.
Let's see whose prayer
is more effective.
What are you doing in my office?
We got a tip that
your son is closely connected...
to the main suspect
of this incident.
I think you are mistaken.
The suspect only said...
Stop. You can defend yourself
during the investigation.
An inspector...
should always stay objective.
Until the investigation is over,
I will take charge
of the steering wheel.
Next, the bride and groom
will say their vows.
The groom may go first.
Okay!
I, Hwang Hee Tae,
accept Kim Myeong Hee as my wife.
Forever, with love and respect,
I will cherish her.
I solemnly swear before the Lord.
Does the bride, Kim Myeong Hee,
who's known to be terrible
with words,
swear the same?
Yes.
Your voice isn't loud enough!
Yes!
Very well.
Finally, the bride and groom
will exchange prayers.
I heard that the bride...
was tormented
by the agony of creation.
Shall we hear your prayer?
The groom can go first
since he memorized his prayer.
Okay, then.
Lord.
Whatever hardship may befall us,
we will not let go of these hands
we finally get to hold.
I pray we can overcome the hardship.
More than anything,
I pray you give me...
worse pains instead of Myeong Hee.
I pray sincerely in the Lord's name.
Amen.
Darn it. My prayer's sloppy.
You said you'd pray
that I be buried alive.
- I, Kim Myeong Hee,
- Myeong Hee!
Myeong Hee.
Just now, your father...
No.
It's not my father.
Hee Tae. Look at that.
My father isn't that short.
Father.
Father. Open your eyes.
Stop teasing me and open your eyes.
Why are you lying here
on the cold ground?
Father. Father, wake up.
Open your eyes right now!
You can't... You can't do this.
To the end...
Why must you give me a hard time
to the very end?
No, no, Father.
I can't let you go like this.
Father.
Father. Let's go home.
Let's go home, Father.
Father.
Father...
(Kim Sung Wook, 18)
(We are looking for our son.)
So does this mean...
our son hasn't died...
but has been arrested?
Oh, dear. Honey, he's alive.
But didn't you say
you were arrested with him?
How were you released?
I was... Well...
Soo Chan.
If it's because you feel guilty...
Three days.
The world I believed in...
crumbled in just three days.
I was dragged away
and treated like an animal.
When I was released alone,
thanks to Mr. Hwang,
and lied down in my bed,
do you know what I thought?
I felt comfortable.
I didn't even know...
if the people who were arrested
with me were dead or alive.
But I felt so cozy and comfortable.
That's why...
I feel ashamed.
I'm ashamed of lying down, eating,
and even wearing this kind of suit
and breathing this air.
I feel like a total coward.
I feel ashamed to death.
Soo Chan.
We may not be able
to change anything,
but there are things we can do.
I'll go...
look for a way to contact Naju...
and ask about the funeral procedure.
You stay here...
beside your father.
I'll take care of
all the necessary arrangements.
(From Kim Hyun Chul,
To Kim Myeong Hee)
(Regular savings account)
(Current Balance)
This is the account where I saved
all the money you've sent me.
It's under your name,
so you can take your seal
and withdraw it anytime.
Myeong Soo said this to me one day.
That the runner who runs
way in the front...
does nothing but block the wind
for the others.
He said it was your loss
if you stood in the front...
from the beginning.
Perhaps, I lived my life...
- Let's go and...
- always in the front,
blocking the wind
with my whole body.
I was that runner
who was in the front.
I was afraid you'd be hit
by the wind like me.
What if your wings were hurt
from the hardships of this world?
I hoped you wouldn't stand
in the front like me...
and always tried...
Father, I didn't do anything wrong.
to hold you back.
But your wings...
were strong enough to endure
any kind of wind.
If I just let you be,
you would have ridden the wind...
and flew up high into the sky.
Since everything that happened
wasn't your fault,
just leave it behind with me.
And from now on,
let your wings carry you...
freely...
wherever you want to go.
She's currently at Sangmugwan
with your son.
Don't send our own men.
Use one of our spies in the militia
to get rid of her.
Make it look like
an internal conflict broke out...
and do it near
the government building.
And make sure...
you kill her in front of my son.
I'll do that, sir.
Oh, she had a little kid with her.
What shall I do about him?
Get rid of him too
if the timing is right...
What do you want?
The housekeeper...
asked if you're going to eat.
I'm working right now.
Tell her I'll eat later.
Okay.
Eat up now.
Here. Try it.
Hurry up and eat.
Excuse me.
Are you Kim Myeong Hee?
Yes.
I have an urgent message for you.
Mr. Hwang Hee Tae asked for you
to come outside immediately.
(Message from Hwang Hee Tae,
Come to the service center now.)
Hee Tae asked for me?
Do you know why?
I'm just delivering the message.
Since it's the service center,
I guess it's about the funeral.
(Divorce Agreement)
Divorce?
Are you insane?
I'm as sane as I can be.
I won't put up with this nonsense.
I'll mail you the papers again.
If you want to talk to me,
contact Attorney Choi from now on.
Jung Tae...
will go with me.
If you're going to leave, go alone.
I'll never let you have custody.
Then let's ask Jung Tae to choose
who he'll live with.
What? Choose?
Jung Tae, come downstairs.
You better stop crossing the line.
Jung Tae. Hwang Jung Tae!
Ma'am. Your son...
left urgently a while ago.
What do you want?
Excuse me.
Did you see a woman sitting there?
Did you miss each other?
She left as soon as
she received the message.
What message?
You sent her a message
to come to the service center.
Ms. Kim Myeong Hee?
Are you here to see Hwang Hee Tae?
Yes. What is going on?
The militia...
got the long-distance calls
working again.
Let me show you the way.
Go straight ahead
and turn right, okay?
What in the world?
Let go! Let go, you little brat!
- I can't.
- Jung Tae!
- Hey, let go.
- Myeong Hee, run!
- Let go!
- Don't do that.
I said, let go!
Jung Tae!
- Jung Tae.
- Jung Tae. Jung Tae!
Who did this?
Who said you could shoot the kid?
- Who said you could shoot my son?
- Is it your doing again?
Is this what you did
for your family?
What have you done now?
- Jung Tae.
- Don't come any closer!
Don't you lay a finger on my son.
Hee Tae.
- Did you bring your car?
- Yes.
Let's take him
to the hospital first.
Jung Tae. Jung Tae, can you hear me?
Can you get up?
Jung Tae.
Jung Tae. Jung Tae...
The orphan is not me but you.
No one will choose you
to be their family.
Soo Ryeon, get the cart.
Load them all.
I have another rat
in my storeroom now.
Father.
Did you two decide...
to consider me a living corpse now?
Father, I can explain. Right now...
It was my idea.
When I was little,
you said this to me all the time.
"It's pointless to prosper alone."
"We should grow together
with the City of Gwangju."
I admired you for that,
and it really made me proud
of our company, Changhwa Industrial.
If you ask me,
I think it's time, Father.
What can you possibly do
with a cartful of supplies?
Open all our storerooms.
Take everything we have.
Father.
Where's my sister?
You're awake.
Your sister went to see Hee Tae
for a second.
My goodness.
You still can't reach Mr. Park?
The phone lines are cut off,
and the roads are blocked.
There's no way we can reach someone
outside the city.
Then will she be cremated
right away?
There won't even be a funeral?
What can we do?
Dead bodies are still pouring in.
We can't keep her here much longer.
Poor woman.
She can't even see her family
one last time.
I feel so sorry for her.
Mother.
Grandma.
Excuse me.
Do you still have the map?
- What?
- The map...
you gave my father the other day.
The map? What do you need it for?
Excuse me.
Can I report a missing person here?
- No, not here.
- Okay.
Just a second.
Why don't you try
at the provincial government office?
Okay. Thank you.
Shouldn't you be there
when Jung Tae comes out of surgery?
The doctor said he'd pull through.
Once your father...
Myeong Hee.
Myeong Soo...
Myeong Soo has gone missing.
What?
I think he went this way.
But I'll go and check that way too,
just in case.
Stay away from this area.
There are soldiers everywhere.
- Myeong Soo.
- Kim Myeong Soo.
Gosh, where did he go?
Myeong Hee.
The road splits here.
I'll check this way.
You go that way.
Wait, you can't go that way.
It's the area Sun Min said
we should stay away from.
But it's not marked
on Myeong Soo's map.
We don't know where he may be.
Then I'll go that way.
You go this way.
Did you already forget
my wedding prayer?
I'll never leave you behind
and put myself in danger.
I'll just go have a quick look
and see if he's there.
Five minutes.
We'll meet here again
in five minutes.
Five minutes, okay?
I'll see you here in five minutes.
Okay?
I'm sorry.
He's my family too.
See you later.
Myeong Soo.
Kim Myeong Soo.
Hands up.
Search thoroughly.
Go ahead and wait for me in Naju.
I'll be there soon.
I don't want to.
I'm not going alone.
Kim Myeong Soo.
Father promised he'd come back,
but he didn't.
Come with me.
Please come with me, Myeong Hee.
It's more dangerous
if you stay with me.
I'm a nurse,
so no one will attack me.
I'll explain to the soldiers
and catch up with you.
On the count of three,
run as fast as you can to Naju.
- Do you understand?
- No.
I don't want to.
Little bear.
Listen to me.
I'll catch up with you soon.
I promise.
Are you sure?
Are you sure
you'll catch up with me?
When I make a promise,
I never break it.
You know that, right?
On the count of three,
run as fast as you can.
One.
Two.
Three, go.
What are you doing? Go get that boy!
I'll... I'll go get him.
That stupid moron.
There he goes again.
No.
Run. Now!
What are you waiting for? Run! Now!
What's with this punk?
He's a medical student
at Seoul National University.
Why is a student from SNU here?
I'm from Gwangju.
I'm visiting my family.
Hey.
Cut it out.
You came here to lead a rebellion,
didn't you?
That's not true.
I'm really from Gwangju.
Check my ID card.
Hey.
Just shoot him.
Hwang Hee Tae?
Yes, it's you.
The one who went to SNU
with top marks.
Hwang Hee Tae.
You know him?
He's from my neighborhood.
I'm from Gwangju.
Get up.
Where are you going?
The order is to shoot any rebel
to death immediately.
Why don't we arrest him first
to be sure?
We'll take him with us
and question him thoroughly.
That way.
If you want to live, keep walking.
Don't look back.
Hey, did you go through her pockets?
I'll do it now.
Find anything
that reveals her identity.
Sir... Sir.
My brother...
My brother, Myeong Soo...
Is he alive?
I can see the stars.
(Chungmu, Kalguksu)
- Welcome. Are you alone?
- I was impressed.
They sang in perfect harmony.
Yes. It must be the clear air.
Sure. Leave one with me.
We're down to the last entry
of MBC's University Song Festival.
Contestant number 18!
Representing Seoul,
it's the band "Sharp."
- Yonsei University...
- They're all pretty good this year.
- Engineering student...
- Who do you think will win?
I bet the med students will win.
- Do you?
- They were very good.
- Did you like that song?
- Contestant number 18.
"After the Play Ends"
by Choi Myeong Seob.
("After the Play Ends"
written by Choi Myeong Seob)
(1980 MBC University Song Festival)
After the play ends
I remain alone in my seat
(Missing Person, Kim Myeong Hee, 26)
(Seoul, 2021)
(Emergency Ward)
I only let you off
because you're a woman.
Do you have a death wish?
- Oh, no.
- What should we do?
I'm not obligated to do something
that isn't a nurse's duty.
You really need to stop
talking back.
Come on, now.
These are bad hands.
Who are you?
Step aside.
You won't?
Do you want to die too?
Oh, dear. Why are you so angry?
Who are you?
Don't just stand there.
Call security.
Okay.
Are you a patient
or a family member?
You can calm down now.
(Emergency Medicine,
Professor Hwang Hee Tae)
Come in.
Did I drop my phone earlier?
It says the power's off.
Jung Tae could've just called me.
Why does he want to see me?
Did he get on a plane?
Okay. It's not serious, is it?
What is it
that he wants to tell me in person?
Hey.
I found it.
I'm so scatterbrained.
I'll come right over.
Text me the address.
Okay. See you soon. Bye.
(Professor Hwang Hee Tae)
No, it's fine.
Thank you.
Who are you anyway?
I was told that you asked to see me.
Me?
Did I...
Oh, yes. You're that guy.
The guy who administered CPR
on a moving bus.
So, the patient.
Did the patient live?
No.
The patient died last Saturday.
(Emergency Medicine,
Professor Hwang Hee Tae)
So you want to quit the internship?
Because a patient died?
It's not just that.
I don't think
I have the right to become a doctor.
The thing is,
I have to be somewhere soon.
So I'll be very brief.
What's your name?
I'm Lee Seo On.
Seo On. Okay, Seo On.
You know,
we don't decide who lives or dies.
That decision...
is up to the Almighty.
All we can do is do our best
between the two.
Seo On, despite being afraid,
you did your best
instead of running away.
I guarantee you.
(Lee Seo On)
Seo On.
You will become a good doctor.
I have to be somewhere soon.
If you're going to stay longer,
turn off the lights as you leave.
(Punish the fake patriots!)
(The May 18 Gwangju Uprising
was the work of spies.)
The light is green.
You may cross now.
Hey, Seok Chul.
I'm sorry
I suddenly asked you to come.
You must be busy.
I'm not as busy as you.
Why did you lose so much weight?
You should take care of your health.
Come to the hospital for a checkup.
Our staff discounts end this year.
Let's go.
By the way, Seok Chul.
If you rip those banners
on the streets these days,
how much is the fine?
I'm not sure.
Why don't you ask Soo Ryeon
about legal matters?
Who, Lee Soo Ryeon?
All she knows are labor laws.
She did nothing but protest
when she went to law school.
I was surprised when I turned on
my phone earlier.
I had so many missed calls
from some old friends.
And strangely,
they were all from Gwangju.
Hey.
Myeong Soo.
How have you been, Hee Tae?
What...
Is today a special day?
Are we holding a reunion?
Why?
Did you find her?
Yes.
(Gwangju Jungbu Police Station)
We found this note
buried with the skeleton.
According to the informant,
this belonged to the deceased too.
(Gwangju Metropolitan Police)
Kyung Soo.
Hee...
I, Kim Myeong Hee,
refuse to be buried alive
with Hwang Hee Tae.
Lord,
if something unexpected happens...
and we have to let go
of each other's hands,
please don't let the sorrow...
overwhelm the lives
of those left behind.
Even if the tears we shed...
fill up to our chins,
please don't let us drown...
and give us the power and courage...
to swim safely throughout this life.
(As always...)
As always, May has come.
This year is the 41st May...
since I lost you, Myeong Hee.
All this time,
my life felt like swimming
during a rising tide.
No matter how hard I tried,
I couldn't move forward,
and I even tried
to let myself drown.
But when I woke up,
that tide had pushed me back...
to that May inside my heart.
It felt so cruel
that I lived in resentment.
For a very long time,
I lived in regret...
and thought about
what could've been.
If I hadn't gone to Gwangju
in May of that year,
if I hadn't met you in Gwangju,
if I hadn't let go of your hand
in those woods,
would you still be alive?
But...
on this 41st May
when you've finally returned,
I now realize that I was the one
who chose to do all of that.
In May of that year,
I chose to go to Gwangju...
and chose to love you
with all my heart.
I prayed every day...
that worse pains in life...
would come to me instead of you.
If I had been the one to die
in the crossroads of life and death,
and you had lived,
you would've experienced
the tides...
that I had experienced
all this time.
The life of the one
who was left behind.
Hence, I've finally realized...
that what I experienced
all this time...
was the Lord's way
of answering my prayer.
Those lonely and painful 41 years...
were merely...
my love for you.
(To Grandpa Myeong Hee)
The remaining years of my life...
will be an answer to your prayer.
No matter how many more times...
the rising tide pushes me
back to that May,
I have you here now.
Until we meet again,
I will swim against the tide
with all my might.
2021. The first May.
From Hwang Hee Tae.
(Thank you for watching
Youth of May.)
(Youth of May)
(Special appearances
by Choi Won Young and Jung Hee Tae)