[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
You're going to Haishen Island?
That place is no joke.
How could I not be worried
unless the seven of you
took on this challenge together?
It seems like
Master's suggestion was right.
When we're together,
we're very happy every day.
Without pressure,
we won't have the motivation to train.
The Shrek Seven Devils
is now only without San and Wu.
Yin.
Do you feel it too?
Dad!
[Episode 158]
Your mom and I had a feeling
that you might be in danger not long ago.
Wu is...
Dad.
Mom.
You can rest assured.
I will surely resurrect Wu.
Brother.
But
I'm afraid I won't be able to come visit you
for a long time.
This time I come back,
I'd like to ask you to help me with one thing.
It's about Wu and me getting married.
I want to
get engaged to Wu first
in your presence.
She can now only control her soul
to merge with her body in a short period of time.
Once she's recovered,
we'll get married immediately.
Please give us your approval.
Good.
Very good.
Wu is a nice girl.
It's a blessing for you to marry her.
We'll agree.
Having such a nice daughter-in-law,
what else could I ask for?
Dad.
Mom.
San.
You must take good care of Wu from now on.
I will.
This is your mother's wedding gift to you.
We'll be waiting for the day
Wu officially becomes our daughter-in-law.
Only one man can comb
a woman's hair in her whole life.
Since you've already made your choice,
I will give you this comb then.
Brother.
Come on.
Call me Sister Wu.
If you want to be my younger sister,
I'll have no objections then.
In your dreams.
I can give you my promise.
It's different.
I don't want to talk to you anymore.
You're so dull.
Brother.
Can you help me comb my hair?
My hair is kind of messy.
No matter when,
you are my younger sister.
You've always been.
I swear.
Unless I'm dead,
I'll never leave you, Wu.
I swear too.
I'll never leave my brother.
Even if I'm dead.
If I'm gone,
you must take care of yourself.
Otherwise, I'll be sad.
Wu,
will you marry me?
Yes.
[Soul Land]
Master.
Grand Sword Master.
Grandpa Sword.
Master.
What did you call us for?
You've been separated for so many years.
Before you go,
I want you to have a bonding
so you can achieve the best teamwork.
Mas...
Master.
You...
You're not going to
let Grand Sword Master give us the training, are you?
He's the top soul master of attacking
on this continent!
This is your blessing.
Grandpa Sword.
Please go easy on us.
Since you're my opponents,
I won't go easy on you.
Chen Xiang.
You can just stand aside and watch.
Come here.
Grand Sword Master is way too powerful.
Without good teamwork, they can hardly resist him.
To avoid accidental casualties,
I even forbid others to watch on the side.
Even before he strikes,
he has given out an overwhelming vibe.
Wait a minute.
Grand Sword Master is going to tutor us?
How could you do that without me?
-Brother San!
-San!
Brother San!
Brother San.
Teacher.
San.
You're here in time.
Here we are!
Guys!
Show your martial souls!
A Century Millennium Soul Ring?
This sword is called
Hepta Kill.
Attack!
Blue Silver Domain.
God Killer Domain.
It's our turn.
Third Soul Skill,
White Tiger Vajra Transformation.
Sixth Soul Skill, Cloning Sausage.
Ao.
Not bad.
First Soul Skill, Nether Spikes.
So fast.
Zhu Qing's speed is on par with mine.
Facing Grand Sword Master,
a soul master at his peak,
giving it all out
to attack
is right.
Third Soul Skill, Flying Phoenix.
But...
Again!
Jiubao Boosts!
Sister Rong Rong can boost up five people at a time?
Her Simultaneous Multi-control
has reached the level
called the Core of the Five Senses.
At this level, she can impose
five different kinds of assistance
on various targets.
He didn't attack at all
but his vibe only can push we three away.
However...
Fifth Soul Skill,
Blue Silver Emperor Tyrant Spear.
Fatty.
Fourth Soul Skill, Phoenix Strike.
Sixth Soul Skill, Tiger Wiping Kill.
Why doesn't Grand Sword Master dodge?
Purple Demon Eye.
Such strong pressure!
Come back now!
If I had been where I was,
I would have been ripped into shreds.
Combining into one with the sword.
This is Grand Sword Master's Martial Soul Form.
Mu Bai.
Fifth Soul Skill, Tiger Monstrous Transformation.
This is Mu Bai's Fifth Soul Skill,
similar to White Tiger Vajra Transformation.
The two can be used simultaneously
to enhance the power.
Soul Bone Skill of Soft Bone Rabbit. Teleport.
Invincible Golden Shield.
San.
Master.
What's this?
This is the ability of
Rong Rong's Illusory Wisdom Skull,
which is called the Space of Illusion.
It can build a spiritual network
to connect the minds of her teammates,
increasing 20% of their mind power
while undermining the enemy's.
This is...
Facing an opponent with absolute predominance,
all skills are of no use.
Check it out.
The power of my God Killer Domain
is full of fierceness and ruthlessness.
But the power of the Grand Sword Master
is immense and inclusive.
Maybe,
this is another possibility for my God Killer Domain.
Jiubao Boosts!
Fifth, Attack!
Six, Advance!
Together!
The power is too strong.
Even the six of us cannot resist it.
What's this?
When the soul power reaches level 95,
it would transform totally.
The Martial Soul will advance
each time the soul power is upgraded.
Reaching this state,
the soul masters can manage to get integrated
with their Martial Souls.
Back then, that man of the Martial Soul Hall
integrated with his Martial Soul
with the soul power of level 99,
making it to block my father's "Kill" for nine times
and hurt him instead.
Even though my father had upgraded to level 97,
he died eventually from the injury.
Therefore,
the techniques are important,
but upgrading your soul power serves
as the crucial key.
Your great-grandfather, Tang Chen
was a Grand Soul Land Master of level 99.
Back then,
the Judicial Elder, also the Head Flamen
of the Martial Soul Hall, Qian Dao Liu,
and your father were two big shots
among the soul masters.
Is that man
Qian Dao Liu?
Precisely.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 158 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1487 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2388]
[Total scene: 58859]
[Total CGI: 27742]
[Total plan of action scene: 12408]
[Total scene model: nearly 556]
[Total character model: nearly 1002]
[Total props model: 13382]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[Next episode]
So many years have passed,
I finally found someone
who can bear the Power of the Boundless Sea.
Chief Tang,
I irritated you several times
to save myself.
Please forgive me.
Your Highness,
why do you...
Those little freaks are all geniuses.
They must be aware of
how vast the gap is
between themselves and the strong.
Greetings, King of Blue Hao Tian.
[Soul Land]
[10 AM every Saturday]