(Jin Young)
(PARK Sung-Woong)
(RA Mi-Ran)
(LEE Soo-Min)
(KIM Kwang-Kyu)
(LEE Joon-Hyuk)
(Directed by KANG Hyo-Jin)
What is it now?
Dad won't give me
the Gangnam gallery.
So annoying.
So what then?
Don't wear that tie pin!
Good morning, boss!
Tell them I'd like to invest in the Uzbekistan copper mine.
And make sure we get 30 percent of the shares.
We will establish a local corporation.
So just carry on
with the deal.
What?
About the Jungwoon district mall,
we got rid of most of the tenants,
but the carpenter's shop
is holding out.
Choi.
You've been doing this
for how long?
21 years starting
from liquor distribution.
Wearing a tie made you forget
how to wield a knife?
- Bang!
- Yes, boss.
Take the boys and wrap up
the Jungwoon case.
Right away.
Is something wrong, sir?
Of course not.
I'm going to go for a smoke.
Told you there are plenty here
to use as weapons.
Pros need professional gear.
Mr. Kim Jong-ki?
Hand up.
This is illegal.
I have the right
to keep my property.
You can discuss that
with my boss later.
One clean signature
Lease Termination Agreement.
and I'll buy you lunch.
Nosong Carpentry.
I'll count to three.
One.
Two.
Three.
Whoa, look who it is!
It's big bro Jang!
Aren't you more used
to the peasant food?
I need to grease
my intestines too.
But why are you here eating
by yourself?
Where's the Mrs.?
Yang, mind your business.
Hand over Chungdo Precision to me.
I worked on that place
for 6 months.
Not because Osung Logistics
didn't work out?
Say what?
Want to get down and dirty
in this day of high tech?
You went to a good school,
were you this anal?
So what?
What what?
You smart twit,
"high tech" coming out of you
sounds very tacky.
God darn it.
Do you still see me
as your butt-kissing minion?
You couldn't even wax
my shoe properly.
Can you handle it?
Of course not.
Who can handle your face?
Never, no one can.
Let's go get some peasant food!
Yes, it's me.
Will Chungdo Precision accept it?
With private loans,
we can have the controlling stake.
I heard Yang's men
are working on Chungdo.
We got in first,
so he can't do much with it.
Don't forget.
Knife to the neck
is the norm to a gangster.
It took us 18 years
to reach this far.
Congratulations, sir.
Congrats?
That's too early.
Where are you going, sir?
To receive grace.
My, my, aren't you dressed up
for mackerel ramen?
A young woman ran this shop
10 years ago.
Did she sell it?
She's dead.
Kiddo, have your fill. Okay?
Check please.
Not going to eat?
It's not the same as before?
May I just pay?
You don't like eating alone, huh?
- Don't have anyone to eat with?
- What?
I'll be right there.
- So sad.
- How much?
Ma'am, I'm really sorry,
but I lost my wallet...
That's okay,
this gentleman will pay for it,
go on.
What?
- Take care.
- I'm in a rush...
- Thank you! Thank you!
- Don't worry, see you!
- Get going!
- Hey! Buddy!
Take care, kiddo.
Sir, ready to pay?
$10 per dish, total of $50.
$10 for ramen?
But why is it $50?
God darn fathead.
I got a gift coming your way.
You're a successful man,
you can be generous.
(Hope Snack)
I'm never coming back
to this dump.
It's me.
Did you look into Yang's gang?
(THE DUDE IN ME)
Jesus, were am I?
Right, something hit me,
and I must have fainted...
- Kid.
- What? What kid?
You're awake?
What's she saying?
Don't call me a kid.
Don't force yourself to speak,
I'll get the doctor.
You're up?
What? You know me?
You okay, kid?
Who are they calling "kid?"
What the...
Why am I lying here?
You there.
You shouldn't walk around,
return to your room.
Your father's on the way,
please wait a bit.
My father died more than
10 years ago...
- Dong-hyun!
- There he is.
- Who's that baldy?
Son, I thought you'd
never wake up!
Son?
Are you okay?
Hold on, Dong-hyun.
What are they...
That's a mirror...
I don't believe this...
Amnesia?
Yes, it's a form of amnesia caused
by accidents.
Does that affect
his speech pattern?
He doesn't talk like before.
Brain injury could lead people
to mistake their identity.
Behavior and speech
could change in that case.
It's Dad, you don't recognize me?
No, I don't!
How many times
do I have to tell you?
What's with this voice?
How was his personality before?
Well, he likes to eat,
but he'd never get into fights.
- Gentle?
- Yes.
A high school student?
That's okay.
This gentleman will pay for it.
What?
Could he be...
and...
I got a gift coming your way.
That old fart?
What the...
That snack shop went out
of business long ago!
I ate ramen here yesterday,
don't you get it?
It was that good?
Is that why?
Yesterday, a 17-year-old boy
jumped off a building
and fell on a man in his 40s,
who is currently in a coma.
In a stroke of luck,
Don Jang is in a coma.
Jang Pan-soo?
Incredible!
Stupid woman...
where the heck did she go?
Dang it...
my precious necklace...
why did it break...
Jesus...
Who are you?
Um, I am...
I'm Pan-soo.
Your husband Pan-soo.
Something strange happened to me.
Stay back!
- I'll explain everything.
- Stay back!
- Please sit down.
- Police!
Will you listen to me?
- What are you doing?
- Stay back!
I'm really Pan-soo.
I'll prove it, so put that down.
If you're Pan-soo,
then I'm your mom, fatso!
How did you know
the door passcode?
Did you escape from a psych ward?
I'll explain everything,
so put that down.
No way! Stay back!
Han Suh-yeon!
Listen to me!
Hold still!
Let me go! This is my home!
Don't move!
Why did you go in there?
To steal some food?
Listen, buddy, what did you say?
Wait! Dong-hyun!
My boy may be thick-boned,
but he's not the type
to steal other people's food.
He injured his head recently,
so he's not himself,
so he must've mistaken it
for our home, right?
Since he's a minor,
we'll release him with a warning.
It's your last warning.
Of course! My apologies!
I'll teach him properly!
Dong-hyun, come on.
Sorry, officer!
Come out, you rascal.
This doesn't work.
I got it.
Huh? Excuse me.
Hey, jerk!
What were you doing to my boss?
It's not what you think.
Then what?
Did Yang send you?
You son of a... wait a minute...
you're fat... it's you!
The butterball!
You crushed my boss with your fat!
So savage!
Bring my boss back! Wake him up!
I hear you.
Let go.
Let what go, you nitwit!
What's going on?
This is ICU!
Let's talk later.
Hey! Butterball!
If I catch you again,
I'll smoke and grill you!
Go inside.
- Good.
- Thanks for hospitality.
I'll leave when I get
my own place.
This is your home, Dong-hyun!
Why do you keep saying that?
You got a job?
Huh? I did.
I work at a grocery store
for the moment.
Wait.
A man must look tidy.
Go ahead and eat, son.
All this... by myself?
It's half your usual amount,
but I can cook more if you want.
You must be mistaken.
I don't eat junk food.
Give it a try.
These are your favorites.
Here, for the sake of my effort.
What's wrong?
See? You love them.
I love that you eat so well,
my dear son.
So greasy...
Get some sleep
and we'll go to school tomorrow.
School?
I have to go
and see what exactly happened.
I can't let this slide.
How dare they do this to my son.
(Basic Carpentry)
Mr. Vice Principal.
Hello.
Good to meet you, I'm Jang...
I mean Kim Dong-hyun.
Dong-hyun injured his head...
I see.
- Please sit down.
- Yes, sir.
Dong-hyun, over there.
I've been told
that he can't remember that day.
Did something happen at school?
He's not a boy
who'd attempt suicide.
Maybe he had a reason...
Are you implying that
my students did something to him?
Well, who knows.
Mr. Kim,
I've told the police,
but nothing like that happened.
Hey, I'll look into it,
so you can go home.
What?
Vice principal, right?
Let me get back in class.
Quiet!
Dong-hyun's not fully himself
due to the accident,
so please help him out
until he recovers.
Yes, ma'am!
Go take a seat.
I had to cover for you
while you were away.
All right, open your books.
Jae-ik, share your book
with Dong-hyun.
Page 111.
What's "adjust?"
Alter or regulate, right?
Then the correct answer is D,
right?
Imagine how I feel.
Where's mine?
- So cute.
- What a cutie.
It's Hyun-jung.
Not eating?
- Too bland?
- Maybe it's not good.
That looks delicious.
It's seasoned properly.
- Go on, eat.
- Eat.
Look at her poker face,
no reaction at all.
Stop it, please.
- Stop it.
- Please.
Oops, sorry. My mistake.
Hey, children!
Let me eat in peace.
So eat, fatso!
Why does he need our permission?
He must be starved.
Is this happening?
This super loser must've
lost his mind as well.
Super loser?
Should I help you remember?
Hey!
What's going on there?
Those rascals.
See me after school.
Wow, he really came.
- Go easy, Tae-wook.
- Don't kill him.
Who are you?
You sure you don't
remember anything?
Talking like an idiot.
Buddy.
Nothing's changed,
listen carefully.
Come see me at every break,
with a burger and strawberry milk.
Was I your so-called
snack delivery boy?
Are we not good together?
Need a beating?
Then you'll remember!
- You rascal!
- Sorry.
I don't like getting hit.
You crazy rascal!
Not again! Dang it!
Wait!
I got a question.
Did this Dong-hyun bloke...
did he do anything to offend you?
Listen to this guy.
There's no such thing,
you fat pig!
Which means,
in a word,
- he's easy?
- Yeah.
Not just easy,
he's too frigging easy!
Did you start going to the gym?
This joke is too much!
Kim Dong-hyun!
You okay?
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
- You rascal!
- Hey! Stop!
Let me go!
Frigging jerk...
Did you see us yesterday?
I didn't see anything...
You rascal, you want to die?
I'll kill you if you're lying.
Buddy!
This guy's got big balls.
Let's strip him
and film him as insurance.
That's a good idea.
No, please!
This isn't sound between friends!
What did this idiot say?
Strip him.
Hold still, Jae-ik.
- Here we go.
- Wait a minute!
- Don't move.
- Please, don't!
Dong-hyun...
Give me that, you fat idiot!
What?
Give it back before I hurt you!
Is there something
I shouldn't see?
Give it to me!
You okay? Dude!
I'll return it tomorrow.
What do we do?
Tomorrow for sure!
This is Kim Dong-hyun,
how about a comment?
I... I just have to bring
that back?
Yup.
I won't bother Hyun-jung again,
I promise.
But walk all the way down
that rail
to retrieve her shoe.
Then it's mission clear.
Hey, what are you doing?
Dong-hyun, stop it!
He's going all out
to get your shoe.
It's really dangerous!
And I was right below?
Did I tell you to delete
that video or not?
That loser won't do anything.
Hey, high school boys!
You fat jerk, give me my phone!
Interesting video.
So what?
Going to take it to the cops?
You gained balls
after smashing your head.
I'm not a big fan of cops either.
Nor getting involved
in other people's affairs.
Other people's affairs?
I made a copy, as insurance.
Stay out of my sight.
Got it?
You're finally here!
Dang it, I almost died waiting!
Mrs. Jang! Good evening!
Yang?
Choi, have you been well?
Zip up, man.
Just kidding.
What's going on here?
Yo, bring it!
My boys took a lot
of photos of you two,
so I was going to send them
to Chairman Han.
This is nasty! So much skin!
You know how much
your father hates affairs.
He's got a weird moral compass.
What should I do with this?
What do you want?
Who ordered you to guard him?
You fat twit!
Didn't I tell you I'd grill you?
Should I get the BBQ ready?
- Stupid rascal!
- Bang Man-cheol!
43-years old, single,
DB Community College graduate.
Began working for Hanho Group
on October 21, 2001.
Promoted to supervisor
in February, 2004.
How did you know?
Because I'm Jang Pan-soo.
Bull, my boss is over there.
Your eye,
was slashed with a broken bottle
at 11 PM, March 21, 2005.
20 stitches at Jinsung Hospital,
costing me $385.20.
How did you...
I received the wrong grace.
You sure eat a lot.
My appetite won't die down.
What is it?
Those eyes...
you really are my boss.
My apologies.
When else would I pinch
your cheeks?
Why are you guarding me every day?
There's a rumor
about Yang's next move,
that he's after your life.
Don't worry.
I'll return to my body.
No matter what.
But you shouldn't.
What?
You obtained a fresh new body.
Well, doing military service again
could be drawback,
but it's better than
being a veggie.
Don't eat.
Meet us at Burger Prince
after 7th period, okay?
Burger Prince.
We have some proposals.
Sorry, but I have
student council meetings later.
We got plenty of time,
we can wait until midnight.
I can't do that.
- Of course you can.
- We're good at waiting.
Could you step aside?
She can't walk through.
Go ahead.
She stinks up the hallway
whenever she walks by.
- What?
- Stop it.
It's nothing.
I'm going to quit school.
Find me a place to stay.
Right away, boss?
I figured out the cause,
so no need to stay any longer.
And the boy's father's a bit much.
You should stay a while.
Enjoy the youth
and school meals too.
What the heck?
Hey, kiddo!
Take this.
Do you resent me or something?
I told you not to get involved.
You did all that for nothing.
I'm sorry, I don't remember well.
Hyun-jung!
Where did you go
after skipping class yesterday?
You didn't even come by to eat.
I can't eat at the bar.
You can eat before
the drinkers come in.
(Hyun-jung's Bar)
Mi-sun?
Wait, Dong-hyun?
Hey, kiddo! It's been so long!
You look so much better
since I last saw you!
He injured his head recently
and lost his memories.
Go home.
Stay for a meal.
Mi-sun, why are you here?
Where...
are your manners?
How dare you call an adult
by the first name!
He injured his head,
he's not himself!
That has nothing
to do with manners!
You little brat!
Am I your pal or something?
Run! Go!
Mi-sun...
is Hyun-jung's mom?
Are you dying for a beating?
You've got a foul mouth
for a newscaster hopeful.
There's, uh...
something on your hair...
Ow! What are you doing?
Dong-hyun grabbed
Hyun-jung's hair.
I'm sorry.
Two losers splitting up?
(Paternity Test Results)
(99.999% positive)
It's too dangerous!
She's... my daughter?
Hyun-jung?
That's what the science says,
99.9% positive.
She is definitely your daughter.
It's an awkward situation,
but may I congratulate you a bit?
Caramel macchiato
and mango banana Frappuccino
is ready.
Dang it.
Is something wrong?
- Bugger!
- What is it?
Where is it?
Hey, Oh Hyun-jung!
Hey!
Did you steal my lip stain?
It wasn't me.
I left it in my locker earlier.
Only you stayed behind
during gym class!
Yoon-ji, it's useless now.
Anything she touches rots.
- I stole it!
- What?
I've always wanted one,
so I took it.
You stole it?
He went full crazy.
Then show me.
I put some on and tossed it.
It wasn't my color.
Stupid idiot.
Pervert?
What's going on?
Back to your seats.
Turn to page 206.
Invasion of Japan
and deployment of national guards.
4 targets.
Break one limb each.
Show no mercy.
But boss...
I don't think this is right...
minors aren't my field
of expertise.
So, you won't do it?
I think you should consult
with her directly.
My baby is a loner?
Because of me?
Not just because of you.
It's complicated,
with her grades and all.
I should call her teacher--
It looked like the teachers
were overlooking it
to avoid any problems.
Then...
what am I supposed to do?
Um, I came here
to consult you about it.
It's all my fault...
I shouldn't have raised her
as a single mother.
Jang Pan-soo, that rascal!
Hope he rots in hell!
I bet he's enjoying
a blissful life.
Not knowing
how his own kid is suffering.
Then, how about...
I take care of the situation?
You?
If I talk openly with the kids,
maybe it could help.
Pan-soo embezzled $3 million?
Check for yourself, Dad.
(Transaction Record:
Total - $3 million)
What...
can I do to...
become close to my kid?
I'm still single...
Right.
I think physical affection
could be the best solution.
Plus, it helps body and mind.
Is that so?
By the way, boss.
You should work
on this body a bit.
Before you return to your body,
diabetes and high blood pressure
could get you first.
The doors are closing.
It was you?
You told my mom to send me here?
What do you mean?
I came here to lose weight.
I can't do this with you here.
I'm going to go.
Says who?
I'm your trainer, Master Bang.
Could I just get a refund?
Shut your mouth, girl!
There's no refund,
no absence, no mercy!
You won't get away with this.
I sure will.
Keep your eyes wide open.
Not like that!
Look.
Your waist, use your waist!
Shut up and go away.
Fight!
Ow!
Do it right!
Come in! Good!
Keep going!
You okay?
One more.
Why do you have to eat ramen
at my place?
I'm starving to death, okay?
Wait a bit.
Sure.
(My Child Can Be Happy
Even Without Dad)
(Would we be happy
if he was here...)
We're eating steaks tonight,
wait for me, my son!
Jong-ki!
Made some money?
Boys, don't hit his face.
What's that?
If you give me
a little more time...
But there isn't any!
Hey, muscle heads!
Muscle heads?
We got a brave kid.
Who are you?
And you?
Kiddo!
He's got a loan
he needs to pay back.
Head on home now!
Using violence is so 20th Century.
Dong-hyun, go home, okay?
Your son?
Boy! Come here.
- You come here.
- Did you hear that?
Dong-hyun, listen to me!
Go home!
How did you raise him?
Look at his attitude!
Watch your own attitude.
I've had it with this twit.
God darn it!
For goodness' sake!
Dong-hyun! No! Please!
Dong-hyun, no, not him!
Step on him! The kid.
Let me go!
Kick that little scoundrel!
That's enough, stop it!
What a tenacious twit.
I'll give you 1 week,
call me with $80,000.
Get off of me.
They're gone.
Mister, can you hear me?
Hey, Kim Jong-ki.
Wake up!
Who are you?
- Got a boyfriend?
- What?
Close your eyes.
What's with the commotion?
Who's Choi Dong-gu?
Hand up.
That'd be me,
who the heck are you?
Hand.
You have a client
named Kim Jong-ki.
Yes, yes, yes.
Let's lightly erase his debt.
It's not a small amount,
we can't just erase it.
Never used white-out in school?
If it summed up to $80K
over 2 years...
The principal must've been
about $5K, no?
Yes, you are indeed correct,
but that's still...
You know Don Jang
of Hanho Partners?
Of course I do.
But what about him?
Kim Jong-ki is his father.
What?
It's okay.
Just accept it.
But that doesn't...
What's this? This is amazing!
Incredible!
How are you feeling?
If I pass out,
you should take me
to the hospital, you know.
I got a call from the loan sharks.
They'll drop the interest.
My defensive strategy worked.
So what?
Hey, son!
Don't lose so much weight.
You're handsome as is.
Hot, that's hot!
So hot!
Teacher! Teacher!
- Dang it.
- Sorry.
Screw that,
my lunch is all rotten now.
My gosh...
you stink like crazy.
Want a new plate?
Forget it.
What if it's not rotten?
What?
Want to bet $100?
Here, you eat first.
What did you just say?
Are you nuts?
You freakin' trying to be cool?
So desperate to mess up
your school life?
Doesn't matter,
it's already messed up.
But I'd like to change that.
Dang it!
Dig in.
I'm treating you
for helping Hyun-jung's problem.
Is this...
It's Mackerel ramen.
Not sure if it's your taste.
I used to eat this a lot
with someone.
It's great,
you should put this on the menu.
No way.
Don't need a reminder of him.
Him?
Hyun-jung's dad.
Things ended badly with him?
I still regret it
when I think about him.
What regret?
Not killing him.
I'm sorry.
Actually, you remind me
of him quite a bit.
He used to wipe everything down.
I'll pack you a few dishes
so you can go eat with your dad.
Thank you.
Ma'am!
- A Soju, please.
- Sure thing.
Where did you go?
I had a guest.
I was saying...
Here you go.
- Hey!
- Firm butt!
What was that?
Ma'am, is this your son?
Your mom's pretty,
so I touched her.
Got a death wish?
How dare you bark at the customer!
Don't want to make money?
Don't yell at the boy!
You witch!
Let him go!
Dong-hyun...
Go inside, I'll take care of this.
You go home, all right?
Bugger, that's so sweet, eh?
Mi-sun, are you okay?
Get in the kitchen. Now.
- You...
- Listen to me.
How dare you...
If you're drunk, you rascal,
you should head home.
Look at this punk.
You good for nothing!
You grabbed my woman's hair?
Who are you?
You sleeping with her?
Stop, please!
You'll kill him!
Who are you?
Answer me!
Why do you keep calling me Mi-sun?
You expect me to believe that?
You body-swapped
after an accident?
Yes, I admit that you talk
and act like him.
But that doesn't mean
you're Jang Pan-soo.
You have a small peach-shaped mole
by your belly button.
What?
Want me to tell you about
more intimate spots?
Wait...
which restaurant did we
first meet?
Arpeggio in Yeonnam,
you ordered a caffé latte,
I ordered a Bud.
Where did we break up?
Coffee shop in Sinsa Hotel.
The last time we met,
you ordered a lemon tea.
Are you...
really Jang Pan-soo?
Yes.
Why didn't you tell me
you were pregnant?
Sorry, but she's not your child.
I already did a paternity test.
Right, that's what
Jang Pan-soo would do.
My turn to ask.
Why show up here out of the blue?
We were long over.
You thought I'd be moved
if you kicked out a few drunks?
You'd still be...
a gangster.
And get it straight,
I did not raise your kid,
I raised my own.
You don't deserve to be a father.
Leave.
- Mi-sun, listen...
- Get out!
Should I call the police?
[VIU Ver]
Ripped by Soultreeagasshi
You never answered my calls...
you even moved away.
You said you can't live
with a criminal.
Of course!
What kind of woman
wants his man to be a criminal?
That's why.
I told you
our paths are different.
I'm getting married next month,
to my boss' daughter.
What?
Leave memories in the past.
No need to get pathetic
and worked up.
Pan-soo...
I'm leaving.
Did you say something wrong
to my mom again?
She told me to stay away from you.
I made a big mistake
to your mom.
You called her
by her first name again?
You're Oh Hyun-jung, right?
Um, yeah...
Want to come to my birthday party
at my villa this weekend?
I want to throw the last party
before we become seniors.
I can come?
Of course!
I'll take that as a yes
and call you later.
Let's go.
Someone you like?
No way.
He must be, you're blushing.
No way!
I'm off.
(Please see me, I'm begging you)
You came.
Uh, happy birthday.
Thank you.
Shall we?
Hey, hi.
Get us some grilled meat.
Sure, go inside.
Why isn't he here yet?
What took you so long?
You promised me
I'd get weekends off.
Yo!
Whine again
and I'll call Cheol-ho.
Leave that and piss off.
Hyun-jung must be
having a blast by now.
She was so happy to be invited.
She's so clueless, stupid witch.
She deserves it.
You came.
What'd you like?
Anything.
Caffé latte for her
and a Bud for me.
May I see your ID?
I'll take the Bud
and an orange juice for him.
Sure.
What do you have to say?
I know you won't forgive me
no matter what I say.
But I want you to know
that I regret it deeply
and I am sorry.
If it wasn't for this...
if this unbelievable thing
didn't happen,
would you have apologized?
Or even looked for me?
You lived just fine until now.
Wasn't I someone
you wanted to erase
from your life?
Mi-sun.
What's the point, then?
You're a married man!
I just...
Don't make me more miserable.
Mi-sun, what I...
You rascal!
Mi-sun, please,
listen to me, okay?
Just once, please?
I'm sorry, I really am.
How dare you kiss me!
Do I look that easy?
You're driving me mad.
Come. Let's go to the police.
Wait, don't go overboard.
What is it?
I just heard something,
Hyun-jung may be in trouble.
Where?
We'll have to go
to the station later.
I got an urgent matter.
Hey!
Bang?
Bring me a car ASAP.
Dong-hyun,
we're not old enough to drive.
Shut up and give me directions.
Is this the right way?
It is, but...
Cheol-ho will kill me.
Better than getting killed by me.
- Are you okay?
- Don't!
Here.
Drink.
Bottoms up.
No, thanks, I don't drink.
You can't back out now.
Everyone's watching,
save me some face.
How does me drinking this
save you face?
We put on this party for you,
so don't disappoint us.
Just go with it, okay?
What do you mean?
Come on, drink.
God darn it...
why would anyone invite
a loser loner like you?
Cheol-ho recommended a loser
who wouldn't retaliate.
Who do you think you are?
You witch.
Don't you know who his father is?
Forget it.
Can I help you?
This is a members only...
Did you see that?
Dong-hyun!
Who are you?
What's all this?
We're just having some fun.
Let's go, you don't belong here.
Where are you going?
We're just getting started,
she can't leave now.
Boys.
Dong-hyun!
Bunch of little brats.
Did you lose your brain
after bumping your head?
Get him.
Who the heck are you?
Hey, what's up?
He's a god darn maniac!
My punch tastes different, huh?
Cute twit.
You.
Try me.
Cheol-ho! Get it together!
I'm fine, I just slipped.
Come on!
Oh, no!
He's so cool.
For goodness' sake!
Dress neatly, huh?
Let me go, you rascal!
You want to die?
Going to hit me?
Try me, fool.
You crazy witch.
Help me!
I can't swim! Help!
You okay?
Yeah.
Well done. Let's get out of here.
What's this?
By chairman's order,
no one is allowed inside.
Everyone thinks
that you got into an accident
while embezzling $3 million.
Your wife is siding with Yang.
How should I proceed?
Hyun-jung told me everything.
How are you feeling?
You know...
how is she?
If you're worried about her,
leave her be.
Forever.
Mi-sun.
What exactly can you do
for her in that body?
What if she figures it out?
All right.
I'll do that.
What do you want?
Did you come for Hyun-jung?
Why?
Want to get your revenge on her?
No, it's not like that.
I just wanted
to apologize to you two.
Are you going out with her?
Are you nuts?
We're not like that!
In that case...
what about me?
You want me to date
a high school chick?
You're in high school too.
My answer is no.
Go home and study.
Here.
Bye!
What a pest...
Dong-hyun, I like you!
What are you doing here?
What did she want?
It's nothing.
Did she ask you out?
It's nothing like that.
So you'll go out with her?
Don't want to go to jail
when you're 40-something.
Who's 40-something?
Forget it. I won't ever date her.
- Then go out with me.
- Hey!
Don't you care about me?
Then why are you so nice to me?
I'm asking you out now!
Answer me by weekend!
Who did you ask out?
Dong-hyun.
I thought you liked him.
Are you insane?
No! Never! Not in a million years!
He's a weirdo,
don't even think about it!
I told you he saved me
at the party.
He risked his life to rescue me.
Hyun-jung.
Baby, please.
Listen to me, this is all wrong.
Tell me why I can't.
He takes care of me like a father.
That's exactly why!
I grew up without a dad.
I can't even have a boyfriend
who's like a dad?
Will you just listen to me?
What exactly did you do
to make her ask you out?
It's a misunderstanding,
I only wanted to be nice to her.
Does it feel good
to ruin our lives completely?
Mi-sun...
Leave at once,
and don't ever come back!
If you ever show up
around Hyun-jung,
you and I are both dead.
What can I do
for you to forgive me?
If there was a way,
I would have already.
Even if I did,
this is infidelity, remember?
Infidelity?
What do you mean?
Hyun-jung...
What did you mean?
Forgive? Infidelity?
What are you two talking about?
Hyun-jung.
I'm sorry.
I love...
I love your mom.
- What?
- What!
Sweetie, that's not it,
listen to me.
This is why you were mad
when I said I asked him out?
Sweetie...
So disgusting...
Hyun-jung...
Sweetie!
Jang Pan-soo,
why did you say that?
Well, what's done is done,
and it's better
than dating my own daughter.
What?
You crazy rascal!
How could you even say that,
you crazy rascal!
Can I help you?
What the heck?
Jang Pan-soo!
It's a good day to die, no?
Look at this twit's beard.
You should've led a good life.
You messed up your life,
and so you're doomed.
Pan-soo.
Don't hate me too much.
We all live once,
I'll send you away comfortably.
Mister, your zipper's down.
Huh?
Thank you.
What? You!
There.
Dong-hyun?
Good timing,
I made a special dish...
Dad...
I became a weird man...
what do I do, Dad?
Don't call me "Dad." Who are you?
I'm your son, Dong-hyun!
Kim Dong-hyun!
You have the wrong house,
this... isn't your home...
wait, you're...
Don Jang?
I'm Dong-hyun!
I have no memory
after I fell off the roof!
What do I do, Dad?
Stay back! Please!
- Dad!
- Don't come near me!
Dad!
Daddy!
What is it?
- Dad! Dad!
- Get out of here!
What in the world? You woke up?
You look like someone...
wait, are you me?
But I lost so much weight!
Dang it, yes, I'm you.
By the way,
is your body okay?
Dad! He's a thief!
He stole my body!
Call the police! Call 9-1-1!
Jesus...
Hey, why did you...
he got hurt because of you,
how can you hit him?
I'm sorry, he injured his head...
Why'd you hit me?
Be quiet and just sit down.
I'll explain everything.
That's impossible.
So you're saying this man's you,
and you're this man.
Right.
Then I gotta live my life
as an old man?
Daddy...
Yes, sir, you were saying?
I don't know
what will happen next.
You gained 30 years
but I lost a lifetime of 30 years.
This is so unfair.
Unfair?
Listen, kid.
Who lost all that tremendous fat?
- Am I right?
- That's true.
Whose side are you on, Dad?
My apologies, sir.
Stop talking funny,
it's me, Dong-hyun!
I'll get used to it eventually.
Wait a minute.
You expect me to believe all this?
You two are trying to trick me!
I'm not done, sit back down.
You little...
- Dad, sit.
- Yes, sir.
When I had measles at 6,
you had a bike accident
and we stayed
in the same hospital.
A glass piece got stuck
in my throat
when I was in Grade 3,
and you pulled it out
and saved my life.
I remember, sir.
I'm your son, Dong-hyun,
you gave me that name.
- Are you...
- Dad...
- really my son?
- Dad!
How in the world did this happen?
Dad...
You smoke, right?
I get so much mucus!
You have a wart on your butt.
It hurts whenever I sit.
In any case...
you need to help me.
Me?
You like Hyun-jung, right?
If you help me,
I'll help you date her.
Crap, when I woke up,
he was already gone!
How could you screw up?
You said you'd take care of it!
Hey!
Am I your freakin' husband?
Watch your mouth.
If he goes to Dad...
My boys are searching for him,
so you go get the darn money!
Shouldn't have listened
to that greedy pig.
How dare she!
Got it.
We found the cabby
who drove Don Jang.
Mi-sun.
What's going on?
When he woke up,
we got back in our own bodies.
I'm Dong-hyun and...
this man is the real Pan-soo.
Your souls swapped back?
This man, I mean, the kid's right.
I'm really sorry.
I want to apologize
with all my heart.
I've never once
forgotten about you.
You...
Gosh!
So hard to find!
Who are you?
Jang Pan-soo.
You should've led a quiet life.
Tie them up together
and toss them in the ocean.
Yes, boss.
Excuse me, one moment, please.
What is it?
You want to say your last words?
Don't kill us...
I just woke up,
I can't die like this...
Who are you people?
Sorry, chump,
being in a coma
made you very weird.
You two get in the kitchen.
Yes.
What's this?
What can you do by yourself?
Hold on!
Make sure she doesn't come out.
- Yes, sir.
- Wait...
Ma'am, stay here.
They're really scary men!
What a load of nonsense.
Boys.
Bring them out.
Look at this punk.
Yang, chatty as usual.
Yang?
How dare you bark at an adult,
you little twit!
Watch your mouth!
- So what?
- What what?
This is déjà vu.
Who the heck are you?
Obviously a high school student.
Got a problem?
High school?
Which grade and class?
Enough census inquiry, come at me.
Need to open up the bar soon.
This is nuts...
Why are you standing around?
Get rid of this bookworm!
Hey, Jo!
Where's Jo?
You sleeping?
Gwak?
You can fight some.
Take off your tie, schmuck.
- Boys.
- Yes, sir!
Ma'am, don't go out!
Please, stay here.
Let's wrap this up.
I told you to take off your tie.
What?
Hey.
Yo.
Buddy!
Jang Pan-soo, watch this!
Dang it,
I shouldn't be killing minors.
Stop!
Don't hurt him!
Shoot...
He's the father of my girl.
Your girl's what?
Father of my girl.
So, if you touch him, we all die.
God darn it.
I'm going to count to 5.
If you don't leave by then,
we die together.
If you want to live,
you better run.
Hey, ma'am!
If you light that, you die, too.
Do I look like I'm afraid to die?
This scoundrel destroyed my life,
and I'm barely hanging on!
Why, doesn't look it?
Thought I lived fine without you?
Why do you think I kept her,
dang it...
I wanted at least a child
who resembles you!
I gave you a chance,
but you still left me.
What is she saying?
After all this time,
did you think
a simple apology would work?
She's completely mad.
Did she just say that
she had this kid's kid?
If you want to live, get out now.
- One!
- Wait, wait, wait!
Stop it, you gangster!
You're no different!
Two!
Three!
We better leave!
But Jang's in there!
Four!
No!
Mi-sun...
are you okay?
Ma'am, I smell gas in here.
I feel dizzy.
Stay back.
I have something to say to him.
- Mi-sun.
- I know, I know!
But... the one I loved
is Jang Pan-soo over there,
so just...
I've waited so long.
Jang Pan-soo.
Watching Hyun-jung grow up
more and more like you...
whenever I see her...
I've missed you so much.
You can't even imagine.
1 year turned into 10,
and after 17 years,
we finally meet like this.
Do I look old?
Thank you.
Yes, it's this face.
What's going on, Dad?
Do you know
what I detest the most?
What?
Holding a knife
against the family.
"Dear Chairman Han,
my father-in-law,
if you're reading this,
I've fallen victim
to their conspiracy,
and I would be
labeled as your traitor."
He states the conspiracy
you plotted with Yang.
It's impossible, Dad.
How can someone in a coma
write this letter?
His handwriting has been verified!
This really is impossible!
Yang got to me after the accident,
so how could he...
In other words,
are you admitting that you
conspired with Yang?
Come in.
Boss, is it okay
to send him in alone?
Who'd believe me if I went in?
Chairman wants Jang Pan-soo.
Don't say anything else,
stick to my plan.
I called for him.
Have a seat.
Jang Pan-soo,
what exactly are you planning?
Shut your mouth!
What should we do now?
Ask the chairman what he wishes.
Ask the chairman what he wishes!
What did you say?
I mean, ask you, chairman...
what he, no,
what you would like to do.
I pronounce you
as the heir to Hanho Group!
Dad!
I'll vest your entire fortune,
including the money you stole,
to the company!
How could you?
I'm your daughter!
You won't get any inheritance,
so don't ever come back!
What about what he did to me?
He had an affair
and even has
a 17-year-old daughter.
Thought I wouldn't
investigate you?
You went straight to her bar
after leaving the hospital.
Is this true?
Uh, tell him
it's a misunderstanding.
I, um... please, help.
Sir, I can't hear you.
Hey, Dong-hyun.
Can you hear me?
Sir, I need your help.
I can't hear you.
Explain yourself!
- It's true.
- What?
But the child wasn't born
while living with this lady.
My ex-girlfriend gave birth
without him,
I mean, me, knowing this.
Do you even hear yourself?
Fact is, that you have a daughter,
you weasel!
Don't swear, ma'am.
Hyun-jung is a lovely gal.
Dad, listen to him, he's gone mad.
How could he say that?
Stay out of this!
Continue.
I finally understood,
after the accident.
Should I go in?
What's more important
than being with your family?
Are you saying you will give up
your heirship?
I don't know how rich you are,
but yes.
What did he just say?
Are you sure...
that you'll not regret it?
I've lived so far
with plenty of regrets.
But I'm telling you this
so that I won't regret anymore.
You're all crazy.
Good bye, ma'am.
As the father
of a foolish child...
I have no right to stop you.
Do as you wish.
Thank you. I'll then...
good bye.
Kim Dong-hyun!
Thank you.
You're a better man than me.
You too.
You fight really well.
Crazy idiots...
Sir, wake up!
Boss.
You have to keep the mask on!
Take care of... my daughter.
I understand.
Sir, wake up, Hyun-jung's here!
Dong-hyun!
Excuse me...
Mom, is he...
my dad?
I saw him in a photo you hid away.
Am I right?
Sweetie...
I'm... I'm your dad.
What?
My daughter, Hyun-jung.
That's absurd.
Did you...
already get married?
What?
No, I'm really your dad.
Please...
forgive me.
I wasn't there when you were born,
when you said your first word,
or for your first step.
I was never there...
What is this bull?
My baby...
don't ever forget...
that I love you...
Pan-soo...
- Dong-hyun!
- Sir!
Help! Over here!
- Dong-hyun!
- Boss! I mean, boss!
Did you like my gift?
It's you!
Was it hard taking care
of your woman and daughter?
Get some sleep.
(6 months later)
- It's Dong-hyun!
- Holy cow!
- He's here!
- Wow!
Hey, Dong-hyun!
Dong-hyun! Dong-hyun!
Thanks to you,
the bullies got transferred.
Hey, Dad!
Want to go get
some strawberry milk?
Hyun-jung, hey.
How do you feel?
I'll fully cooperate
with the police.
But it was all
Jang Pan-soo's fault!
That lamebrain high school boy!
He got a kid to fight!
Where's your strength?
Knead with more power!
Kids will rush in soon.
- What about him?
- He's way better than you.
I'm pretty good at kneading.
Oh, come on,
I even gave you this building.
You think I'd live off rents?
Know the value of labor?
Sorry, boss,
landlord, I'll do my best.
- I'm back!
- Come on in.
- Good afternoon!
- Hello, Dong-hyun.
Go get changed and start cleaning.
Allow me, ma'am.
He wants to do it, not me.
Do it together then.
Promise you'll at least
pay me minimum wage.
Or I'll file a report.
What?
Report for me
and I'll bump your allowance.
They're scheming!
- Keep kneading!
- Yes, ma'am!
Get changed right away!
- All right.
- Boss?
Where do you want this?
Go put it somewhere.
I was asking our landlord.
Put it in the kitchen, please.
Ma'am, do I have to wear this?
Yes, please do me a favor.
Quite cold indeed?
We'll open very soon!
- Knead! Knead!
- Kneading! Kneading!
Come on down!
Where are my clothes?
It's in there!
Almost done!
- Come on, hurry!
- Guys!
Is it good here?
(Hyun-jung's Snack)