Our Secret
EP21
Su,
this original piece by Xianxian
is very good.
We can expand it into 200 episodes.
It won't be a problem.
We can also convert it into an animation,
or a game,
something like that.
Guaranteed to make a hit!
Director Zhang,
I'm sorry.
I can't sign the contract.
Director Zhang, Xianxian has never signed a contract before.
I think she needs some time to think.
Young lady,
you've made a promise.
How can you break it?
I'm really, really sorry.
The artists that I contract with on my comics app
are all very popular on Weibo.
If you refuse to work with me for your own reasons,
when words get out,
what do people think of you?
Director Zhang...
Young lady,
you need to learn right from wrong.
Sign it.
What's right and what's wrong?
Party A and party B.
Collaborating upon mutual consent.
There's no reason for forced signing.
Zhou Siyue.
We're talking about Ding Xian's business here.
I'm also doing this for Director Zhang's sake.
Signing a contract hastily before reaching an agreement,
if anything goes wrong with the project one day,
I don't think you'd want
people to talk about how you made a big mistake, right?
For this piece of work,
its greatest value is in Ding Xian herself.
It's what she's always had in her.
So from a business perspective,
Ding Xian
is not the best commodity for you, Director Zhang.
Come on.
Change your shoes.
Why did you bring a pair of shoes?
I got them by the road on my way here.
It's okay.
You look so good today.
Let me do it.
How did you know my feet hurt?
Because my feet hurt, too.
Do they fit?
Xianxian.
Xianxian, I don't quite understand.
Don't you want other people to look up to you,
make a better life,
and become someone...
Su,
I just want to be the person I want to be.
I thought we were the same kind of people.
We used to be.
Su.
Director Zhang.
I'm sorry.
What happened today...
Don't worry about it.
I've given her the opportunity
for your sake.
I wonder why you help her so much.
If I'm not mistaken,
you like her?
Director Zhang, let me see you to the car.
Su,
women like this
love guys like you,
talented and rich.
Director Zhang,
I'm sorry.
I can't agree with what you said.
About the project this time,
I opt out.
I think
I dreamed of a scene like this.
You dreamed of me?
You were holding my hand like this in my dream.
At that time, I thought,
I'd never be with you.
So I had a lot of dreams about you.
I'm sorry, Ding Xian.
I promise you,
I won't ever hurt you again.
So,
how are you gonna explain to Xing Lufei?
It's none of her business.
She likes you.
It's none of my business.
Then should I talk to her...
It's none of your business.
Zhou Siyue,
you are avoiding my question.
I never thought,
that you would be nervous,
about people like Xing Lufei.
I never thought,
that you would be nervous about people like Su Bocong.
How am I nervous?
You're kidding.
Then who's the one,
feeling insecure just because
I talked a few words with him?
Ding Xian, I used to think,
I know what I want,
but then I found out,
if I don't have you in my world,
then everything is meaningless.
So, on the road ahead,
shall we walk together?
Zhou Siyue,
all these years,
I've never really changed.
If I say yes,
you'll never let me go again.
I promise you.
We will always,
be together.
This is correct, and...
there are sixteen rooms altogether, right?
Right.
And then this...
Zhou Siyue.
Boss, so,
when we were given awards,
this Mr. Chen from Hongguang Technology wanted you to contact him.
Right,
did your idea work?
I figured it out.
The meaning of my life is to eat.
I don't make super big bucks,
why should I work super hard?
Good morning.
Morning.
I'll take it myself.
Just get on the bus.
Hi.
I got it, I got it.
Please sit.
How about I go sit over there?
Just sit here.
Ding Xian,
have you finished the activity report of this Comic-con?
It should be out in our WeChat account today.
When did this become my responsibility?
On our meeting last night.
It was decided on the spot when you were absent.
Okay, I'll do it right away.
It's time to
give the report of the competition, right?
Dong Zhengfei,
you're the team leader but you don't work at all.
Shame on you.
Yuan Fang.
I'll write it. It's okay.
You can get some sleep.
Thank you, Boss.
Could you help me get my bag?
Thank you.
Would you like some music?
I have finished the report.
And you?
Not yet.
You can get some sleep first.
Okay.
I didn't know that Zhou,
could be so gentle and considerate.
Me, neither.
Let's go, Boss.
You can't read social cues at all.
Wake up.
Have we arrived yet?
Hello, Ms. Sun.
Ding Xian.
These last few episodes of "Shadows" are really good.
We thought about it,
and decided to update every three days.
If it's okay,
could you please send me a new draft tonight?
Tonight?
Yes, I want it tonight.
I see.
I'm gonna have to work on my draft.
See you then.
Zhou Siyue, would you like to have dinner together tonight?
It's okay if you don't want to eat. I know that there's a...
Can you stay away from me?
- See you. - See you.
Do you hate me so much?
I've been chasing you for so long.
Anyone can see, if he's not a fool.
Where am I not as good as her?
She is better than you in everything.
You're kidding me.
It was you who locked Ding Xian in the dressing room
the other day, isn't it?
Xing Lufei,
I'm telling you for the last time,
Ding Xian is the only girl I like.
About the thing between you and Director Zhang,
I already heard.
Why were you so impulsive?
I'm sorry, Mr. Ma.
That was my fault.
I'll try to make up for it.
Su,
do you know why,
I chose you before,
and start a business together with you?
Because you're young,
and you already know what you want.
And you're so motivated,
with a calmness beyond your peers.
But now it seems that,
you're still too young.
Mr. Ma, I heard you.
Right.
I have a project at hand,
that needs someone in charge to follow up.
Since you happen to have time,
I'll give this project to you.
Boss,
waiting for Xianxian's message?
I can't believe you've also come to this.
I guess it's fair luck after all.
I don't seem to remember you getting lucky once, have you?
You're so mean!
Professor Ye.
Siyue.
Mr. Chen of Hongguang Technology came to me yesterday.
He's interested in your robot,
and wanted to work with our team.
Mr. Chen of Hongguang Technology?
Right.
I think I kind of remember him.
I remembered.
It was at the last robot contest,
at the award ceremony,
he asked me to hand over his business card to you.
So what exactly does their company do?
You don't know?
Hongguang Technology is currently the most authoritative
intelligent robot company in China.
Their main products are
humanoid intelligent robots.
Professor Ye.
I don't really want to work with them.
Are you out of your mind?
Working with Hongguang is not only profitable,
but also you get to collaborate with the top teams in the country.
You're giving up this great opportunity like this?
What are you thinking?
Indeed, Hongguang Technology is very good.
It might even be
our best option at the moment.
But why,
why does a high-end technology company,
want to work with a team of sophomores?
What's more, the robot technology we have
is not perfected.
It does not have a relatively clear direction for application.
But
that doesn't mean we won't make progress.
So that's the problem.
Obviously they can go to more accomplished teams,
with more mature performance and techniques.
Or wait for us to grow,
and then come and cooperate with us.
With the timing that they come to us,
I suspect that the cooperation is just an excuse.
Their real purpose
is to buy out our patents.
But a buy-out of our patents,
doesn't sound like a bad thing currently, does it?
When we're not sure about whether we share
similar ideas for a cooperation,
selling out our patents would mean,
that we hand over the results
of our year-long research.
Are you willing to do that?
Professor Ye.
I think you should reconsider it.
If Zhou Siyue's not willing to,
I can lead our team and work with Hongguang.
I'll think about it.
Bye, Professor.
After a whole night of working on my draft,
it's so nice to finally get to enjoy some nice food.
Aren't you tired?
Not really.
I like drawing.
So I'm not tired.
It's just...
I ate too much.
Too much?
You ate too much, but you're still buying so many snacks?
For a girl,
we don't use the same stomach for eating dinner and eating snacks.
Is there anything else you want to eat?
I want ice cream.
Isn't that cold?
I'll just take a bite if you buy one.
What about the rest?
You'll finish it.
No I'm not.
Come on!
What flavor do you want?
Blueberry.
It's so cold.
Just don't eat if it's cold.
No, this is delicious.
Can't be wasted.
Would you like some?
No, it's all yours.
You don't want to eat my leftover?
It's so cold.
Isn't it delicious?
It is good.
I have work to do in my lab.
Why don't you go back first?
So I'll go back to the studio then.
Okay.
See you.
You shouldn't come see her anymore.
What if I'm here for you?
This is a young team from Hua Qing.
They just won the championship in the robot contest.
And they were targeted by Hongguang.
You should get in touch with them.
Talk to them.
Do you want to,
scout them?
It's not them that I want.
I want to know what Hongguang's been up to.
Oh,
I have this document here,
that's maybe of help to you.
I'm flattered,
but I'm just a student.
I'm not planning on working with any company just yet.
Not working with us,
but working with Hongguang.
You want me to hack information from Hongguang?
I didn't expect you people can
do anything by fair means or foul just for making money.
I still hope that you could consider.
There's no need for further discussion between us.
I won't do anything illegal.
You'd be embarrassing yourself.
Why don't you take a look at this before you make a decision?
With your health situation,
I keep telling you to walk outside more often, and you just wouldn't listen.
You'd rather stay in the room.
Whenever I walk around,
my brain will be packed with ideas.
Reading brings me some peace.
I won't do anything illegal.
You'd be embarrassing yourself.
Why don't you take a look at this before you decide?
We've found out
the man who set your father up.
Siyue, you're here.
No classes at school?
Class is over.
Here.
Are you feeling any better?
Much better.
I heard that,
you won a prize again.
Well done.
That's because of your teachings.
Here, have some water.
I'm sorry, dad.
What, you're in trouble?
I'm just...
sorry that I got you worried.
Your mom and I know,
that you're always
a very good boy.
We never worry about you making mistakes.
Whatever you want to do,
just go ahead and do it.
Don't worry.
But what if that thing
takes sacrifices?
It always takes sacrifices.
Doesn't it?
If it didn't happen to us,
I never knew,
that we,
could be such a happy family.
Mark my words,
no matter what happens,
as long as think it through for yourself, go for it.
I have no regrets.
I just want my son,
to have no regrets, either.
You're gonna recover.
I will.
It's such a simple thing.
Have you even put any effort in it?
It's so great to be rich.
You can even buy the truth.
But I still refuse.
You won't do it now,
but it doesn't mean you won't do it in the future.
She loves you for your honesty and integrity now,
but one day you're gonna bow before reality.
By that time,
do you think,
that she'll still love you?
I am not the same kind of person like you.
For me?
Now that the shoes are delivered,
I'll see you later.
What's the rush?
Let's take a look.
How do you like them?
Not bad.
You've got eyes for these.
Of course.
You gotta see who bought them.
Why did you transfer so much?
Of course.
I can't take advantage of you.
Then forget it.
I can't take this.
I've earned money lately.
I got paid 4,000 yuan for this draft.
I feel it's easy for me to make money.
How about this? In the future, you stay home,
and I'll go earn the bread.
You see, you've been so busy lately.
I feel bad for you.
Look at that smugly face of yours.
Happy about earning this little money.
4,000 yuan is not a little.
Plus,
I earn money with my own hands.
I don't cheat or
compromise to the reality.
Let me ask you a question.
What if...
one day you found me changed
into a person not knowing right from wrong,
what would you do?
Why are you asking that?
Are you in a bad mood?
No.
So?
Is it because of the contest?
No.
Your experiment?
I asked you first,
you gotta answer me first.
Don't forget to stay true to yourself.
I can't imagine
what you would be like if you change.
Hello.
Ding Xian, we've got some copyright issue
with the novel adapted from your comics.
Director Su,
about that blogger of the "Little Monster Diaries",
I think she's in trouble.
Hello, Director Sun.
Director Sun.
Please have a seat.
Regarding the copyright of "Shadows",
what's the deal with that?
About that copyright,
I'm sorry I didn't make things clear for you.
Look at Article 39.
After the copyright of "Shadows" expires,
the copyright of "Shadows",
should be owned by the artist and the Dream Journey Press.
Dream Journey has the right to the final interpretation.
That's why you shared the copyright with me?
So that I'd share
the risk of infringement?
You can go ask around.
Nowadays, no publishing agency
would share the copyright with their artists.
The reason we're doing this
is for your own good.
But you hid the expiration of the copyright from me!
It's clearly written in the contract.
The profits they made out of the "Shadows" comics,
is totally enough for Dream Journey Publishing
to cover the compensation easily.
I get minimal pay for my work,
but I have to take on half of the compensation.
They've planned it all along.
They made a trap and wait for me to jump in.
It's all right.
It's inevitable to be fooled when you are new in the business.
But when they asked you
to share the copyright,
weren't you suspecting at all?
I didn't think that much.
I thought that there are
always good people in the world.
How silly!
Right.
You are the smartest.
Here.
Have a cup of coffee.
Take it easy.
Your latte art
is so bad!
I'm not professional.
Try it yourself if you're that good.
Why not?
Do it.
How should I start?
Hold the coffee in your left hand,
and hold the milk in your right hand.
Pour slowly little by little from this angle.
Don't rush.
What?
I see that now. I'll do it myself.
Here.
You're adding too much sugar?
The coffee is too bitter. I prefer the sweet.
Give me a sec.
Here.
Wait.
You take a bite of this,
and then try a sip of coffee.
How is it?
Delicious.
Wait.
Got a stamp on you.
Are you happy now?
Thank you for cheering me up.
So what are you going to do next?
I want to talk to the original author.
It is best to settle this in private.
But there is another thing that is also very important.
You are also a victim of this.
So,
while you talk to the original author,
you'd better also look for
any evidence that the publisher lied to you.
Do you have the contract you signed
or chat records or anything like that?
I'll help you.
I can do it myself.
I know you're worried about me.
But I also have to learn
to solve problems by myself.
Okay.
But what if you can't find any evidence?
Then I'll pay for the compensation.
How much is that?
500,000 yuan.
Don't worry. It's not gonna get that far.
At the worst,
you could hire me.
Professor Ye.
I think I should see Mr. Chen of Hongguang.
Have you been waiting for a long time?
Give me.
No.
Sorry.
It's okay.
I saw your performance
at the competition.
But
you rejected me before,
didn't you?
Yes.
I thought,
that I didn't share the same ideas as you.
So I chose to refuse.
Then why now,
you come to me?
Because I need money.
You are very straight-forward.
To be honest,
before,
I just wanted to buy out your robot patent.
But now I've changed my mind.
I want your patent
plus a two-year contract after your graduation.
Name your price.
500,000 yuan.
Si Yue.
If it's okay,
I want the money now.
Don't be so hasty, young man,
we still have to wait,
for the procedures of the contract, don't we?
Okay.
Then I'll be waiting.
Hello?
Hello, Ding Xian.
I've got your 500,000 yuan.
I'll clarify the plagiarism case for you
on Weibo in a moment.
Don't worry.
But I didn't send you any money.
A gentleman contacted me yesterday,
saying that he'll help you with the money.
Don't you know that?
So... could you tell me,
the name of that man?
Su,
I've been looking all over for you.
Xianxian,
why are you here?
Thank you for paying the money for me.
I'll pay you back as soon as possible.
That's...
That's the only thing I can do for you.
Su, are you all right?
Are you okay?
I'm okay. I'm okay.
I'm okay. Just go. See you later.
It's okay. You don't have to worry about me. I'm okay.
What can I do?
Maybe I should just get you home first?
Su.
Can you get up?
Be careful!
Where are you going, young lady?
Just a minute, sir.
Su.
Su, where do you live?
Su?
Jiangnan Avenue.
All right.
Here we are, young lady.
Su.
Wake up!
Jiangnan Avenue and?
Hey, young lady, are you getting off or not?
What should I do?
Su, we're there.
You...
Su, you are too heavy!
Su.
You're drunk!
If I weren't drunk,
I'd never be able to say this.
Ding Xian,
I love you.
Su.
I'm already in a relationship.
I see.
Sorry about that.
You should go home and get some rest.
Zhou Siyue.
Director Su,
there is someone waiting for you in your office.
Zhou Siyue.
There is 500,000 yuan in this card.
The password is Ding Xian's birthday.
Please tell Xianxian,
I'm sorry.
What did you do to her?
I am warning you.
Leave her alone!
I'm about to lose my patience.