The sounds of Gongjin.
-Thank you.
-It was delicious.
-Goodbye.
-Taekwon!
-One.
-Taekwondo!
Ms. Yoon Hye-jin! A package for you!
This is the sound
of Ms. Yoon Hye-jin, who's from Seoul,
rushing out to receive a package.
Take it.
Right.
EPISODE 3
You work on Saturdays too?
Yes. Jin-seok broke his arm,
so I'm covering for him for a while.
That's not very good news.
-Don't I need to sign it?
-No, your face is your signature.
I mean, a face like yours
is rare here in Gongjin.
-Did you diss me?
-Depends on you.
Look who's talking.
Do you think you're good-looking?
In Seoul, a face like yours is more common
than gum spat on the ground.
Okay. Bye.
It's more common than the squid
brought into the harbor this morning.
"Hi."
-What do you think?
-Not bad.
"Not bad" isn't good enough
for armor I'll wear into a battlefield.
-Isn't it a fellow dentist's wedding?
-It is.
But everyone will be there.
They'll talk about
how I opened a clinic here
and turn me into a laughingstock.
It's going to be a bloody battle.
You dentists are so pathetic.
And I'm going to be
the least pathetic one among them.
Why don't you go shopping
at a department store then?
I wish I could.
But the boondocks
have no department stores.
You're right about that.
There's only one way for me to survive.
Ms. Yoon!
-How's this?
-It's pretty!
-It's a bit boring, right?
-Ms… Ms. Yoon.
Ms… Ms. Yoon.
What do you think?
A bit too much, right?
-Like an awards show outfit?
-Yes.
Ms. Yoon.
Ms. Yoon!
Ms. Yoon
Too much?
-This is hard.
-Very.
Ms. Pyo Mi-seon…
This is yours, right?
I don't look rich enough, do I?
-You do.
-Do I?
-Yes.
-Something's missing.
Ms. Yoon!
What are you doing?
Why do you order so much?
There's quite a bit today. Sorry.
Come on. Seriously.
You order from all over the world.
The US, Germany, England…
They're from everywhere.
I just bought some clothes. That's all.
And it's none of your business.
Why do you need so many clothes?
A fashion terrorist like you
would never understand.
It's all about functionality.
You don't know anything.
Good for you.
Are you splurging
since you have patients now?
How will you save up money to go to Seoul?
I'm going this Sunday, okay?
-This Sunday?
-Yes.
For a very important reason.
And these are the last ones
for a while, so quit nagging.
Look at that color.
It brightens your complexion.
-Really?
-Yes.
-Do I look okay?
-You look gorgeous.
Turn around.
It's perfect. Into the battlefield!
-I'll get going.
-Okay, see you.
Make sure you feed the hedgehog.
Okay.
They would've been perfect for this look.
I'm sorry.
Due to my carelessness, your other half
is probably floating in the open sea.
God, I barely recognize you.
Look who's talking.
I'm not expecting any packages today.
-I know. I have a favor to ask of you.
-What is it?
I heard you're going to Seoul today.
-Let's go together.
-What?
They all need to go to Seoul.
Ms. Gam-ri needs to give
marinated crab to her son.
Ms. Mat-i… What a beautiful hat.
Her friend's grandson
is having his first birthday.
Ms. Suk-ja's daughter
hurt her back and asked her
to take care of her children.
-We can go.
-We need to talk.
You can't do this all of a sudden.
So it's okay, right?
Let's go.
-Okay.
-Let's go.
It's okay, right? Go on. She'll drive us.
Unbelievable.
Here.
Right. Is the lid shut tight?
Yes, it is. Don't you worry about a thing.
-New car?
-That's not important.
What are you doing?
Shouldn't we hurry?
We need to make several stops.
We'll talk later.
Why did you pack so much?
This isn't a lot.
I'm actually worried
that it may not be enough for all of us.
You made potato cakes?
These are my favorite.
If you want
to avoid carsickness,
you need to keep chewing.
Dr. Yoon, have one.
I'm good. I'm driving, so…
-What are you doing?
-Don't talk with your mouth full.
Ms. Gam-ri, why aren't you eating?
I had a big breakfast, so I'm still full.
Just have one. She made it for us.
What's wrong?
They're undercooked.
Why is it so hard?
Don't blame me.
You're the one who has fragile teeth.
Just spit it out already.
Do you have weak teeth?
You should've told me sooner.
Gam-ri, ask her
to give you a nice discount.
Shut it. Stop spewing nonsense.
Ms. Kim, you should
come to my clinic. I'll treat you well.
-Gosh!
-Oh, dear!
-Goodness gracious.
-Are you okay?
I could've gotten a heart attack.
I can't believe what just happened.
We should really have
such a reckless driver's license revoked.
Why are you chasing him?
He should know what he did wrong.
Don't do it. Don't be like him.
Hey.
-How could you drive so recklessly?
-Unbelievable.
-You could've caused an accident!
-What?
You can't change lanes without signaling.
-We didn't crash, so it's all good.
-What did you say?
No harm done, so what's the problem?
Don't drive so recklessly,
or you're bound to cause an accident.
Don't cause any harm to others.
Blah, blah. God, you're making
such a big deal out of nothing.
This is why
they should forbid women from driving.
What did you say?
-Hey, watch your words.
-Gosh…
God damn it. What the hell
is that bastard babbling about?
You bastard. How dare you run your mouth
like that after what you've done?
You son of a bitch.
I ought to rip out your lungs and kidneys
and jump rope with your intestines!
Are you crazy, old hag?
I am, you bastard!
-You worthless, little bastard!
-Damn it.
You little bastard, where are you going?
Come back here, you asshole!
What an asshole.
How dare he run his mouth?
You see, my mom was from Beolgyo.
-Right.
-I see.
Right.
What should we do?
The potato cakes are all over the floor.
-Dear. What a waste.
-There are wet wipes in there.
In here?
WE'RE GETTING MARRIED
CHUNG-HO
REST AREA
FISH CAKE SKEWERS
WALNUT CAKES
Want some?
Do you seriously have
an appetite after what you've done?
Of course. Roasted potatoes
are the best at rest areas.
No, soddeok-soddeok are.
-Want one?
-No thanks.
What's taking them so long?
I'm going to be late.
We have plenty of time.
Why are you in a hurry? Take it easy.
Appreciate the view too.
Whatever.
Want me to buy you a soddeok-soddeok?
This way.
-Where are they going?
What are they doing?
This is so annoying.
So much.
-Suk-ja is good at dancing.
-Let's go, Suk-ja!
All right!
-This is nice!
-Doing great!
I'm really sorry,
but could I turn off the music?
What?
I prefer driving quietly.
Turn it off.
We shouldn't bother the driver.
You're such a party pooper.
You be quiet too.
Where are you from?
I was born in Seoul
and raised in Gyeonggi Province.
Goodness. Same here.
I got married and moved to Gongjin
from Yangpyeong at the age of 22.
Which Yoon family do you belong to?
The Haenam Yoon clan, ma'am.
So is my daughter-in-law.
Then who's your earliest ancestor?
Earliest ancestor?
I'm not too sure.
They say there's no future
for those who don't know their history.
You should at least know that much.
I'm sorry.
What do your parents do?
Well, my dad has retired.
And my mom passed away.
Why did you have to ask her that?
I had no idea. I'm sorry.
It's okay. I don't remember much anyway
since I was so little.
Dr. Yoon, is there a restroom nearby?
A restroom?
It'll take some time.
Is it urgent?
Old people need to go
to the bathroom often.
-Be quiet.
-Our bladders became weak.
Aging is inconvenient in many ways.
-Gam-ri!
-Hang in there.
-Hold on.
-Oh, dear.
BETMEORI
REST AREA
-I need to go.
-It's that way.
WOMEN'S RESTROOM
WOMEN'S TOILET
-Gosh, that must be refreshing.
-Let's go.
You should've gone with her.
-Be quiet.
-Please exit safely.
-Unbelievable.
-Be quiet.
-Goodness.
-You're just unbelievable.
-You have to go again?
-Darn it.
-Goodness.
-We'll wait here.
-Hey.
-I ate too much.
-Go together.
-I need to poop.
-We're halfway there.
-Be careful.
What's taking them so long?
They just went in.
Grandma, have a safe trip!
I thought you'd give me hell
the moment they left. Why are you quiet?
I believe in fairness.
I'm doing you a favor since I owe you one.
But admit this.
What?
Admit that what you did today
was rude, disrespectful, and out--
And out of line. Admit that.
I liked the rhythm.
Didn't you see how they were?
I couldn't let them take the bus
and hold their bladders during the trip.
And my truck would've been
too uncomfortable for them.
You did a good deed.
You're too nosy.
Like I said before,
I hate it when people cross the line.
-Don't let this happen again.
-Drop me off here.
-I clearly warned you, okay?
-At that crosswalk.
What a rough driver.
By the way, why did you come to Seoul?
-What's your business?
-Bye.
He's just not likable.
Darn it, I'm late!
HEALTH AND MEDICAL CENTER
SEOUL NEW-GEN UROLOGY CLINIC
HOPE SMILE DENTIST
PSYCHIATRIC CLINIC
Gangwon Province sure is far,
seeing how you were late today.
I had my reasons.
At least I took the photo.
Gosh, Hye-jin used to be so punctual
that her nickname was Cinderella.
You're right. Whenever we had
a get-together,
you'd leave before midnight.
That was ages ago.
Let's talk about the present.
How have you guys been?
Same old. Working on weekdays,
golfing and shopping on weekends.
Ji-won, how does it feel
to open a clinic in Gangnam?
Me? I'm not really that excited about it.
I spend most of my income
paying off my loan.
I'm barely making ends meet.
Last year, I paid
300 million won in taxes.
They awarded me
for being an exemplary taxpayer.
But that's just another way
of saying that I'm a pushover.
How much do you make
to pay so much in taxes?
Well… I think I'm making
a decent amount of money.
But in some ways, I envy Hye-jin.
A seaside dental clinic in the country.
It's so simple and cute.
You're not so up-to-date, are you?
No wonder people think
Seoulites have narrow views.
-What?
-Rural areas are more developed now.
It's truly wonderful. You don't need
to go abroad to appreciate nice views.
And the hospitals make
a hefty amount of profit.
I'm the only dentist there,
so my clinic is flooded with patients.
There's even an article
about doctors in rural areas
making more money than those in the city?
Sorry. I forgot.
You don't read newspapers.
How dare they all mock me?
I'm so annoyed.
I'll have a good trip. Don't cry.
My baby girl.
Call me once you arrive.
-Okay.
-I'm just worried. That's all.
Go home and rest.
-Don't cry. Your makeup will run.
-Okay.
-Be good to my girl.
-Yes, ma'am.
What are you staring at?
What? What are you doing here?
Are you jealous that they're married
and going on a honeymoon?
How did you know I'd be here?
I saw the invitation.
It was next to the wet wipes.
I left my phone in your car.
Still, you shouldn't have come here!
Someone might see us!
Are you a celebrity
or something? Stop overreacting.
Everyone from my university is here.
This is insane.
Follow me.
Did I do something wrong?
Fine. Come on. Why are you…
Stop it. I'm going.
I wasn't planning to get a ride from you.
Remember that.
Whatever.
Drop me off at the terminal if you want.
At the terminal?
-We've already passed it.
-Oh, well.
Then I'll just let you give a ride.
This is nice.
Let me know if you get tired.
We can take turns driving.
Forget it. I hate it
when other people touch my stuff.
Besides, this is a new car.
Fine by me. I can just relax.
I'd love to have
some wine by the Han River.
Drinking makgeolli by the ocean
is just magnificent.
That restaurant has great pasta.
Eating snow crab ramyeon
on a boat is the best.
I can't believe
I have to return to the boondocks.
There are skyscrapers everywhere.
It's so suffocating.
I can't wait to go back to Gongjin.
Can you turn the AC on?
Turn it on yourself.
Don't touch my car.
DON'T LITTER
1 MILLION WON FINE
They must've thought
they wouldn't get caught on weekends.
If I find you, you're dead meat!
What should I do? Chief Hong isn't here.
-He's not here?
-He went to Seoul.
He's been visiting Seoul often lately.
Hye-jin went to Seoul too.
Hello, Ms. Landlady.
You're that friend of hers
who lives with her.
Yes. You're right.
You're our patient, Mr. Choi Eun-cheol.
-Hello.
-You were a police officer?
Yes.
Gosh, you look so different in a uniform.
You look so reliable.
When you visited our clinic,
you were terrified and trembling.
I wasn't.
-Were you?
-No.
Next time, you don't
have to be so nervous.
See you at the clinic.
-Have a good day.
-Bye.
Did I see wrong?
Damn it. Take a photo for evidence.
We should install a surveillance camera.
The toll is 12,700 won.
We're almost home.
When did I fall asleep?
There was one traffic jam
after another, yet you never woke up.
It's very comfortable. You got a nice car.
Am I a chauffeur or what?
I've been driving all day long.
I offered to take turns driving,
but you declined.
You shouldn't have left me bored at least.
I remembered that
you preferred driving quietly.
Well, aren't you so kindhearted?
Someone littered again.
We're having a meeting at the restaurant.
Since you're driving anyway,
drop me off at the raw fish restaurant.
There's an emergency meeting,
and I'm too lazy to walk.
-Get out here.
-Sorry.
CLASSMATES CHATROOM
What?
When did this get taken?
I didn't know you had a boyfriend.
Boyfriend, my foot.
He's not my boyfriend.
I just ran into someone I knew.
Boyfriend? Gosh, he's so cute.
Totally. Where did you meet
such a handsome guy?
I was surprised too when I saw him.
He's not a boyfriend.
I'm not interested,
but he keeps chasing me.
This is cute?
How could you sleep
when I'm driving like this?
Look at you.
GONGJIN MARKET
COFFEE IN THE MIDDLE OF THE DAY
AND BEER IN THE MOONLIGHT
The ideal temperature for drip coffee
is between 88°C and 95°C.
What did I say?
-Ninety…
-Five degrees.
Now, when you pour water,
start at the center.
Slowly spiral outward
then bring it back to the center.
Once these bubbles disappear,
you start the second brew.
-It looks like bread that's rising.
-Right. Isn't it cute?
-Hello.
-Yes.
-Hello. Come sit down.
-Going to work?
-You work here too?
-At times when he asks for help.
What a strange lifestyle you lead.
Do you even know what you're doing?
Try some if you're curious.
He's one talented man.
He's a certified barista.
He's teaching me right now.
-I see.
-Pour some water again and give it to her.
-Me?
-Yes.
Really?
-Is it already time?
-Yes.
All right. My first coffee.
Where are you going?
Remove the dripper, or it'll get bitter.
Okay.
All right. You're my very first customer.
A cup of latte, please.
With a lot of syrup.
This doesn't suit me, does it?
Something's off.
Gosh, this thing…
What are you doing?
This candy wakes me up, you know.
Mondays always make me drowsy.
Just Mondays? You doze off
throughout the entire week.
You little…
-Goodness.
-Hello, everyone.
Hello.
-Here.
-Take this.
What brings you here? Gosh.
-What is this?
-Can't you see? It's trash.
Exactly. Why did you bring it here?
There have been 24 cases of littering
at the market this year,
and we've asked you nine times
to install a security camera.
However, the camera is nowhere to be seen,
and another case happened yesterday.
Are you okay?
I already asked city hall,
but it hasn't been approved yet.
Of course. I completely
understand your situation.
You have a tight budget
and a ton of work. It must be tough.
Gosh. Thanks for understanding.
So we're going to catch them ourselves.
-What? How?
-Every crime leaves a trace.
The evidence must be in here.
We're going to find out
what they ate and threw away right here.
-Should I?
-Rip it.
-Okay.
-Du-sik, don't!
Let me go!
-I need to tear this open!
-No, you don't!
-Then I'll open this.
-Hwa-jeong, don't!
"Hwa-jeong"?
Know when to talk professionally,
Mr. Chang.
God! Right! I'm sorry, Ms. Yeo.
Du-sik! Right! I happen to have
some business at city hall today.
I'll go right up to them and make sure
they understand what we want!
I'm serious. I want a camera too!
I'll get it installed!
Do you? A 3-million-pixel HD camera
with adjustable angles. Deal?
-Got it. Let's do that. I'll get it.
-Okay.
So get this out of here. Now.
What lovely weather.
It's a great day
to file a complaint. Have a good day.
Yeong-guk!
Are you okay?
Gosh.
I don't think I can live a long life.
Open the windows!
WE WILL TREAT YOU LIKE FAMILY
GONGJIN-DONG
We have a full schedule.
Yes. Make sure you stretch beforehand.
Stretch? Okay.
Hye-jin, help me out. Look.
Which color suits me better?
They're both pretty.
-This one.
-This?
What's with the makeup?
Our booked patient will be here soon.
-A booked patient?
-Yes.
Who is it? "Lee Seung-gi, Choi Eun-cheol…"
-Hello.
Hello.
-Please wait one minute.
-Okay.
-Let me help you.
-This way.
-Okay.
We're done with the root canal treatment.
Ms. Pyo, please take care of the rest.
Yes, ma'am.
-Keep your mouth open.
-Okay.
I'm going to
temporarily fill in your tooth.
Mr. Choi, what did you do last weekend?
You worked? It must've been tiring.
What do you do in your free time?
I see. You must enjoy reading.
What's your favorite book?
My Sweet Orange Tree.
Open your mouth.
What was that?
How did she understand?
Bye. I'll really get going.
Bye!
-Want a ride?
-Of course.
What are you holding?
I got a halibut as a thank you.
Grill it for your lunch.
I'm going to have it with you.
Look at you,
trying to make me cook for you.
-You caught me.
-Hold on tight if you don't want to fall.
-Okay.
-All right.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
THEATER OF LIFE
Again? Aren't you sick of it?
For me, this is
the most entertaining show ever.
No wonder there's that song.
How wonderful would it be
-If I was on TV?
-Gosh.
Stop that nonsense and eat up.
I love this soy sauce marinated crab.
What did Won-seok say? He liked it, right?
I don't know. He was so busy
that I had to leave right away.
You went all the way there
but didn't get to eat together?
Hey, mix some rice
in the shell and eat it.
-Okay.
-It's delicious.
What about you?
I'm good.
What was that back there?
Are you interested in Mr. Choi?
Yes.
Unbelievable. You only met him twice.
Hey, that doesn't matter.
He's cute and looks amazing
in that uniform.
I saw his birthdate,
and he's four years my junior.
It's game over.
Lucky it's so simple for you.
How did you know his birthdate?
Don't look into our patients' information.
You're breaching
the Personal Information Protection Act.
Dr. Yoon!
Goodness.
I know I agreed to take care of it,
but you can't barge in here like this.
I know.
But I missed it so much.
Fine. Since you're here already,
take a good look.
Dr. Yoon, have you held it on your palm?
No.
-Have you taken it for a walk at all?
-Of course not.
I've been studying about hedgehogs lately.
You can actually form a bond with them.
And when you do,
they lay down their spines
so you can pet them.
Hey, feeding it and picking up
its poop is already a nuisance.
And you'll be taking it back soon.
Still, it'll be nice
to form a bond while it's here.
When's the test? Is I-jun studying hard?
He always studies hard.
Anyway, it's his birthday today.
I see.
-Tell him I said happy birthday.
-Okay.
-Happy birthday to you
-Happy birthday, dear I-jun
Hooray!
-Blow out the candles.
-Blow them.
I-jun.
Thank you for being my son.
Here. This is from me.
I got you the most expensive toy blocks.
Have you ever seen him
play with toys before?
I-jun, I got you a book.
You got him a book? He always reads.
How thoughtless.
Thank you. I promise to repay you
for your kindness when I get older.
I-jun, I told you to speak casually to me.
You agreed to do so, didn't you?
That's how you can repay me.
He's not a kid. Let him do as he wants.
Don't force him.
That's rich coming from someone
who begged him to talk casually
and treat you like a friend.
-Don't pretend you didn't.
-When did I?
Last time, you begged him…
I have something to say.
Starting next year,
we don't need to gather for my birthday.
You two are divorced.
Right, we are.
Son, are you hurt by that?
I was when I was six.
But now that I'm nine, I'm okay.
I'm glad. But our divorce
doesn't change the fact
that you're our son.
We want to celebrate
your birthday together.
We really do.
Yes. She's right.
I-jun, your birthday is
the most important day of the year to me.
It's like a national holiday.
Okay.
Do you want to try the cake, sweetie?
I bought the tastiest one.
-Let's cut it.
-Dessert comes after the meal.
Yes. You're right.
-Right.
-Then let's eat.
Yes, let's eat first.
Go on.
Eat first.
Don't you know he waits
until the adults eat first?
Right. I forgot. All right, look.
Here I go. An entire spoonful.
Thank you for the meal.
Right.
Let's eat.
Thank you for the meal.
Took you long enough.
Your cucumber kimchi is still so tasty.
You know, I crave it every now and then.
Eat lots.
I-jun, have some japchae.
Have this.
You must have some on your birthday.
YOON DENTAL CLINIC
Ms. Dentist, you have a patient.
I said I didn't want to come.
I'm going to give you an earful
once we're out of here!
-That way?
-Gosh.
-Yes.
-Let me down this instant!
Judging by the x-ray,
you must have been in a lot of pain.
Why? Is it bad?
I'd like to speak with her,
so can you please butt out?
Talk with her.
There's not much to say.
I've been chewing for the past 80 years.
It's only natural
that my teeth have grown weak.
But they're in pretty good condition
for your age.
What?
You can still get implants.
Implants? I heard they're expensive.
Well…. I understand
why you think that way.
But your insurance will cover up to 2,
so you'll only pay 30 percent.
You just need to pay for one.
How much is that in total?
Well… Let me see.
About this much.
Oh, dear. That's too expensive.
Why would I spend
so much solely on my teeth?
I'll just pull them out.
-Grandma.
-What?
If it's too expensive,
you can get dentures instead.
But implants are
four times as strong as dentures.
And since you have strong bones,
it'd be best if you got--
Forget it. I don't need them.
Just pull out all my weak teeth.
Grandma, give it some thought and--
Ma'am.
Your teeth aren't just
something you can pull out.
It could even be
life-threatening for the elderly.
You won't be able to eat well,
then you won't get enough nutrients.
Your bones will weaken
and make it hard to walk.
It could get really serious.
Hey, you don't
have to scare her like that.
Are you short on money?
-Hey.
-What?
Do you not have enough money?
Not enough money? What do you take me for?
I own a house here and a big area of land.
That's not all.
My son works as an accountant in Seoul.
Gosh. And my granddaughter
goes to Harvard University in America.
So you just don't want
to spend money on your treatment?
Then I have nothing more to say.
-You can leave.
-Hey.
What? Unbelievable.
Fine. I'll leave.
You think being a dentist
makes you so great?
-Fine. I'll leave.
-Grandma.
Grandma.
-Let's talk about this.
-No!
-Hear me out.
-I don't want to.
Come on.
Let me just say something.
-Grandma.
-Forget it.
DOCTOR'S OFFICE
I thought you left.
-Was that necessary?
-What do you mean?
"Are you short on money?"
How could a doctor say that?
Were you going to send her away?
Watch what you say.
I only asked because she was adamant
about not getting the treatment.
You could've put it nicely.
No. A dental clinic
isn't a convenience store
where you can ask for whatever you want.
Pulling out your teeth is a huge deal.
She was too rash and stubborn about it.
I understand what you mean,
but you could've said it differently.
What if she was your grandmother?
-But she isn't, so why should I care?
-What?
And you. You're not even
her guardian, so why are you overreacting?
People don't change so easily, do they?
What was that? He's so annoying.
CHUNG-HO HARDWARE
What? Your goods haven't arrived.
You only put in the order
and haven't paid yet, right?
I already paid.
Geum-cheol.
You can't fool me.
Fine, I haven't.
Why do you ask?
I know you.
You never pay money upfront
before you check the goods.
I'm begging you. Please stop coming here.
I'll order it again next time.
And aren't I your only friend?
You're right.
But I think I can manage
without having any friends.
-Do you have any envelopes?
-I do.
Isn't the weather lovely?
Are you mad that I dragged you there?
You seem pretty upset.
But you see,
I'd like you to receive proper treatment.
Aren't your toothaches
bothering you so much?
So I'm going to give you something.
Don't get mad, okay? You know
I grew this big because you fed me.
So I'd like to pay for your treatment.
So with this,
how about we get those teeth fixed?
I'll give you three seconds to run.
-Come on, now.
-Three.
-Let's…
-Two.
Let's talk about this.
-One.
-Grandma!
Gosh, I got wet too.
Grandma!
-Get lost!
-Fine.
-Grandma, I'll come back tomorrow.
-You're still here?
-See you tomorrow.
-Gosh.
I hate him.
How dare he judge me?
And why does he meddle
in other people's affairs?
He should mind his own business.
He's always so nosy.
Does he want
to be complimented for his kindness?
-Why are you so worked up?
-Am I?
-I'm not.
-You're
at 160bpm and 100dB at the least.
I've never seen you
get so worked up over someone.
I mean, he keeps rubbing me the wrong way.
CHIEF HONG
He's calling me.
See? He's so irritating.
Why did you call me so late?
-You still came.
-Bye.
Sit down.
Do you know what those lights are?
Who cares?
They're squid boats.
Those fishermen are hard at work.
But from afar,
those boats just look like pretty lights.
Ms. Gam-ri has been cleaning squid
for decades now.
But she never gets sick of them
and loves squid the most,
although she hasn't eaten them for years.
If you're trying
to evoke sympathy, just stop.
I'll pay for the treatment.
But I have a favor to ask you.
What is it?
Keep it a secret.
Tell her it's some other cheap treatment.
I can't do that.
As a doctor, I need
to take responsibility for what I do.
I must notify my patients
of the treatment process.
Fine. Then just remind me
of the total cost.
I'll pay the rest,
so just tell her
that you gave her a discount.
Why are you doing this?
She doesn't want it.
No, she just can't.
She's been selfless all her life,
so she doesn't know
how to take care of herself.
So she endures the pain?
-How selfish of her.
-"Selfish"?
She's the most selfless woman
I've ever met.
She did everything she could
to provide for her kids.
And even now. She doesn't want
to burden them. Don't you get it?
No, I don't understand.
It's foolish and frustrating to watch.
Why are you so pessimistic?
You have no idea
what you're talking about.
Do you know
what it means to be a good parent?
It's staying healthy for a long time.
They shouldn't endure pain
to save money for their children.
They should take care of themselves.
Do you get it?
SUNDAE, TTEOK
Mom!
Hey…
Don't cry, Mom.
I'm crying because I'm excited.
Don't cry, dear.
You too.
My mom passed away.
It's okay. I don't remember
much anyway since I was so little.
No, you're not okay.
Ms. Gam-ri.
I didn't bring any money today.
I'm serious. I didn't bring it.
How could you throw water at me?
I could've caught a cold.
No one catches a cold
during the summertime.
You saw how scary I was
when I got angry, right?
I did. I won't upset you anymore.
Why aren't you using the washing machine?
There's not much laundry
to run the washer.
It's a waste of electricity.
Let me do it. Go sit down.
-It's okay.
-No, let me.
Rub it well,
-Okay.
-or it won't be clean enough.
Gosh, you and your nagging.
Fine. Look. Happy?
-Good.
-Go sit down.
I'll leave it to you.
Okay, enough nagging.
Grandma.
I'm actually upset with you.
You accept money from your son,
but why not from me?
Am I a stranger or what?
Do you want to get drenched again?
I take it back.
I love the sound
of that bell you hung for me.
Right? Enjoy the sound.
And go enjoy a lot of great views
and eat a lot of good food.
Someone told me
that the best thing a parent can do
for their child is staying healthy.
Gosh, this is a superb bar of soap.
I wonder who made it.
Who made it?
It's no other than Du-sik himself.
Ms. Gam-ri has been cleaning squid
for decades now.
But she never gets sick of them
and loves squid the most,
although she hasn't eaten them for years.
-Mi-seon.
-Yes?
Isn't the squid too tough to chew?
Really?
Hey, all squid are about this tough.
This is tough too.
What's gotten into you?
This too.
And this. Why are they
all so difficult to chew?
Hye-jin, I'm taking your food away
if you keep complaining about it.
They're completely fine.
Hello?
Won-seok, are you busy right now?
I am, but I can talk for a minute.
I see. Did you have lunch?
Of course. It's past lunchtime.
Right. Did you try
the soy sauce marinated crab?
You've always liked it
since you were little.
Well, I've been too swamped
with work to eat at home lately.
I'll have it today.
Why are you so busy?
Take good care of your health.
-You too, Mom.
-Okay.
By the way, Du-sik called a few days ago.
He did?
Hey, Won-seok. It's me, Du-sik.
Have you been well?
You see,
I took your mom to the dentist.
Her teeth aren't in good condition.
She needs implants,
but she's vehemently refusing to get them.
Right. I know.
How about you convince her?
Did Du-sik tell you about it already?
So what do you think I should do?
I heard you were refusing to get
the implants. I can't force you to do it.
I looked it up.
And some say that dental implants
are rather bad for the elderly.
So won't it be better
to get dentures later?
-What?
-You see…
money is tight this year.
Min-ju is studying in the States,
and her tuition is quite expensive.
Oh, dear. Don't worry about me.
I'm completely fine.
Don't worry about me,
and focus on your family.
How is Min-ju doing?
It's so hectic today.
You're doing well.
You know, we had more patients this week.
Do you think word has gotten out
about my skills?
It must have.
PATIENT CHART
KIM GAM-RI
Why am I here? I must be nuts.
Hello.
Goodbye.
Wait.
Did you have dinner?
No.
I didn't have any rice,
so I made some potato dough soup.
-Have you tried it before?
-No.
Try some.
I ground some fresh potatoes,
got moisture out of it,
and boiled it in meat broth.
They're very chewy and delicious.
Thank you.
How is it?
It's really good.
I'm glad.
-Eat up.
-Okay.
The elderly Ms. Gam-ri went to her room
to show us her most treasured belonging…
This is me two years ago.
We filmed it in that very room.
-I see.
-Look at this.
-Gosh.
-This is proof that my late father
served in the Korean Independence Army
in 1941
and was assigned to the second unit.
My mom gave this to me,
and I kept it ever since.
But I couldn't read
the Chinese characters.
Then 30 years ago,
a little boy read this to me.
He was such a smart boy.
-He was a prodigy.
-Grandma!
-What? Goodness.
-Grandma.
Speak of the devil.
This is Du-sik.
Yes, Du-sik.
Look. There's our Du-sik.
Thanks to him,
my late dad was acknowledged
as a patriot who fought
for our nation's independence.
When was it aired?
Two years ago.
My dad named me after the Korean flag.
As you know, there are geon, gon, gam,
and ri in the flag. I'm Gam-ri.
And my older brother's name was Geon-gon.
-That's right.
-What a great name.
You must be proud of your father.
Of course. I sure am.
Goodness. You haven't been eating
because I've been rambling on.
No wonder people say
old people talk so much. Gosh.
-Eat up.
-Okay.
Thank you for the meal.
Rather, I should thank you
for driving me to Seoul.
Thank you.
I actually came by to tell you something,
but I had dinner instead.
Of course.
Eating comes before anything else.
Nothing's more important than that.
Exactly.
If you knew that,
how could you ask me
to pull your teeth out?
Toothaches are truly a pity.
It doesn't show,
so no one but yourself
knows how painful it is.
Not even your kids.
Please come back to the clinic.
I can't do it for free, but I'll
only charge you for the materials.
What?
But you have to keep it a secret.
No one else should know.
If people get wind of this,
I may have to close down my clinic.
Then you shouldn't do this for me.
I heard squid is your favorite food.
My mom's favorite food was sundae.
I just want to help you enjoy it again.
That's all.
Du-sik must've said something to you.
He's kind but too nosy.
I agree.
He hung that bell for me.
Darn it. It must've been a big one.
What's that?
YOON DENTAL CLINIC
Hello.
All right.
I'm here
to get my implants done.
I'm glad you came.
Can I pay first?
First, you should consult with me.
We're done talking.
I've already prepared the money.
I'll pay it all at once.
I've been working like a dog all my life,
so don't you think I deserve to eat
as much squid as I want?
It's too tough, so you should be careful.
-What?
-Have it once a week.
I got 3-million-pixel HD cameras.
And 2 of them.
You can also adjust the angles freely.
It was easy but took you long enough.
Ms. Yeo, don't hurt my feelings like that.
I had to have a serious talk
with the mayor to get those.
Good job. Thank you for your help.
So why couldn't you
have talked with him sooner?
You were always a slowpoke.
Ms. Yeo, what you just said
was very private. It was personal.
Shut it and just take this.
-What is it?
-What do you think? It's cucumber kimchi.
You said you craved it.
Gosh.
Move around. Let's see if they're working.
Why, hello, Ms. Gam-ri.
Bring me some porridge this instant.
Porridge?
Grandma!
Grandma.
Where does it hurt?
Bring the table.
Okay. Hold on.
Where does it hurt?
You never asked me
to bring porridge before.
I didn't know
dental implants would be this painful.
Now that the anesthesia
has worn off, my head is ringing.
What?
I went to the dental clinic this morning.
-Grandma!
-Stop calling me
-and give me the porridge. I'm starving.
-Okay.
How did such a stubborn woman
like you have a change of heart?
Dr. Yoon visited me yesterday.
She did?
She offered to give me a discount
and told me to get the treatment already.
I thought she was
a sly fox, but I was wrong.
On the outside, she's as cold as ice.
But she has a soft heart.
She must have been
through a lot in her life.
-Spoon.
-Right.
What's going on?
Is it a blackout?
Hello, Ms. Yeo. This is Hye-jin.
I think the power went out.
Don't you have any candles?
Because blackouts aren't
that common in Seoul.
Gosh. Sure.
What was that? Did you just attack me?
I never…
Are you Hammurabi? An eye for an eye?
-Say, "Teeth."
-Teeth?
-And a tooth for a tooth.
-You're so childish.
Hold on. Let's see.
Gosh, what don't you have
in that bag of yours?
How did the blackout happen?
I was washing my hair,
and the power went out all of a sudden.
Did this happen
to the entire neighborhood?
No, just here. Did you check the fuse box?
The fuse box?
Where is it?
Forget it.
The fuse box?
Gosh.
I didn't know it was there.
The circuit breaker is still on.
I think it's the service wire.
We should call the power company.
Am I cursed or something?
It's just a small incident. Hang on.
Thank you.
There's an issue
with the power supply line. That's why.
They're looking into it.
It'll get fixed soon.
Does that mean
I have to wait in the dark like this?
What? Are you scared?
Of course not.
I'm not scared. It was just a question.
Where's your friend?
She went to have a facial.
Do you want me to wait with you
until she comes back?
Do you want some ice cream?
I'm just afraid that the ice cream
will melt due to the blackout. Hold on.
My goodness.
Isn't that Bo-ra's hedgehog?
It is.
I didn't know it was here.
Since you turned her down.
I thought you would've
offered to help her gladly.
Why did you decline?
I don't take in anything that's alive.
You guys are similar.
The hedgehog is just like you.
You're both spiky.
-What are you talking about?
-You even look alike.
You're so annoying.
I'm sorry.
What was that?
It's unlike you to apologize right away.
I've been harsh on you
when I didn't know much about you.
I misjudged you. Sorry.
Stop that. You're scaring me.
If you didn't visit her,
she wouldn't have gotten the treatment.
Thanks.
That's because… Well…
I didn't feel good about what I'd said.
And she did pay me.
I'm going to earn a lot here
and return to Seoul.
That hasn't changed, so don't be mistaken.
Fine. I hope you become filthy rich.
Here.
Thanks for the ice cream.
What was that? It was so sudden.
CHIEF HONG
Open the fuse box.
What? No way.
Chief Hong!
Where'd you get this?
Be quiet. You'll wake everyone up.
On the street.
It was swept out to sea.
Why does it look fine?
Awesome.
My God!
Is that a leg?
Why would a shoe be here?
I thought it was a leg.
What?
HOW TO DRY WET SHOES
Interesting.
HOW TO DRY SOAKED SHOES IN MONSOON SEASON
WIPE THE INSIDE WITH NEWSPAPERS
The inside too?
-Lastly, use cool air.
-Use what?
Use cool air. Remember.
He's always around
when you least expect it,
so where is he today?
You have a crush on this guy.
A man and woman can be just friends.
Many have been installing cameras
inside the examination room.
Doctor, you're quite the beauty.
-Chief Hong only has today to spare.
-I'll be there.
-Dr. Yoon must be drunk.
-What?
It's Yoon Dental Clinic.
They need us there.
Oh my.
You can ask me just one question.
Why did you come to Gongjin?
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim