Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ No longer panicking on the night of the blackout ♫
♫ You're by my side, illuminating a beam of light for me ♫
♫ Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet ♫
♫ Your breath brushes up against my cheek ♫
♫ With you warming up the stage,
happiness never comes to a close ♫
♫ Boring jokes add some sweetness to the dinner ♫
♫ Daily life is even more like a comic than comics themselves ♫
♫ Happiness and sadness make up the moments of life ♫
♫ Rainy days become very special because of you ♫
♫ Picked up a pitiful youngster off the street ♫
♫ No matter when and where, you always appear ♫
♫ Holding me tightly and spinning in circles ♫
♫ Rainy days make me so nostalgic because of you ♫
♫ Becoming some part of the memories ♫
♫ Walking down a street with lights lighting up
one after another ♫
♫ Warming up the whole world ♫
[Please Feel at Ease Mr. Ling]
[Episode 15]
Chairman.
I told you many times
to just call me dad when we're alone privately.
Dad, what brought you here?
If I hadn't come, did you plan on waiting until New Way
declares bankruptcy before telling me?
That's not what I meant.
I will take care of it.
You will take care of it?
So many years have passed in the blink of an eye, yet why do you still
act as if you are eight years old?
Did you see my transformer?
No
What are you hiding?
-Nothing!
-Let me see.
Isn't it just a stupid spinner? What are you hiding it for?
Acting all suspicious.
I warn you, never tell mom and dad.
Or else, you'll see what I can do.
Eat some more meat.
Xiao Yue!
Every time you encounter any difficulties,
you never asked anyone for help.
You didn't want your dad's help.
Ling Yue,
I owe you a lot.
But you need to need give me a chance to make it up to you.
Dad, I am no longer the 8-years-old me.
I can now solve my own problems whenever I face any.
Okay.
We are one family after all.
Family is used to care and rely on one another.
After you think this through, you can come find me then.
All done.
The last dish, perfect.
Is the sun coming from the west now?
I've always made food for you all these years.
Today, you've invited me to a home-cooked meal.
I'm helping you experience
the cooking of a genius chef.
Amazing.
What's this?
[Take-out Receipt]
Scrap paper!
I knew it. My sister's still my sister.
She didn't suddenly turn into some genius housekeeper.
I invested so much preparing all these dishes for you.
I wanted you to eat some nutrients.
Eat this. I made this one.
This one's so good! You only made this one tiny dish?
So stingy. Don't fight for it and eat the pig trotters.
Ok.
Do you...have something you want to talk to me about?
No.
What would I have to talk about?
Mr.Lin, our situation...
please allow the company to consider it.
I understand. Thank you.
President Ling, Japan's requirements this time are too strict.
If you adhere to their restrictions,
we'll make no profit and there's no benefit to speak of.
What better time to take advantage of us?
Then...what do you plan to do?
I haven't decided yet.
It's the first time I've heard you say something like that.
Anxin always says, if there's really no solution,
then don't stress yourself out too much.
Clear all the thoughts from your mind,
and new surprises might appear.
I'm going to walk around.
Ok. Then I will wait for your orders inside the company.
-Hello.
One hot Americano please.
Americano, right? One second, please.
Young man! Sheng Ju Lan's holding an event right now! Why don't you bring a set back for your girlfriend?
No need.
It's really very easy to use!
The only reason my facial skin is so smooth is all because I used Sheng Ju Lan's product.
You can use 300 Yuan to purchase the effect of a 2000 Yuan product.
It's very worth it.
You're welcome to come again.
Wait! Don't move!
Why are you touching my things?
It's empty. Aren't you throwing it away?
Empty? Didn't you see there's still this much inside?
That fingernail amount is enough for you to worry over?
You really don't understand how expensive everyday life is.
This is very easy to use and also super hard to obtain.
Of course I have to use it slowly. This tiny bit can last a long time.
What's the brand? I've never seen it before.
You know PKII right?
-Doesn't it say KAI?
This is a small English brand called KAI.
It can replace PKII.
Those are all business advertising techniques. Do you really believe 300 Yuan is enough to purchase something worth 2000 Yuan?
Of course I believe it! This was something I strategized and dug up!
It's the fighter amongst all the evaluations.
Dig?
For us poor balding girls,
how could I afford to buy PKII?
I can only search for makeup products with similar evaluations to replace PKII.
They're...all similar anyways.
Contact the business implementation department. We're holding a meeting immediately.
President Ling, according to your orders
we've collected a list of brands that are competitive against large brands in the market with their replacement products.
-Greetings, President Ling.
-Let's begin.
I need to establish collaborative relationships with all brands within an hour.
-The advertising department must be prepared to update the products list.
-Understood.
Ok. Connect them.
Hello, Mr.Ling. It's my pleasure to cooperate with New Way.
Chairman Gu, is your Shopping Carnival Celebration Event targeted towards New Way?
We've planned this Carnival Celebration for a long time.
We've just never publicized this.
Our Gu Group's primary focus for expansion is in the e-commerce field.
And New Way is an up and rising business within e-commerce.
So both company's events have similarities. It's absolutely normal.
There's no such thing as targeting.
But the rumors say the brands on your website
are all businesses originally cooperating with New Way and were intercepted by you.
What response do you have to this?
Didn't you say so yourself? They're all rumors.
As everyone knows, our Gu Group's
market impact and overall ability
is not something New Way can compete with.
This. Is clear to anyone with sense.
Also, when brands choose their collaboration partners,
it's hard to avoid situations with many different businesses.
And only the best wins.
This is the rule of business.
How can that count as intercepting?
In the future, don't let this reporter inside.
I understand, Dad.
Chairman Gu, what's your opinion on New Way's loophole problem?
This matter does not have enough evidence to prove
that New Way's technology has erred. Please write about this in a practical manner, reporters.
Stop talking! It's this situation,
-yet you're still helping him recover?
-Dad.
Of course. Young people
will make some lowly mistakes due to their efforts.
It's hard to avoid. As for this,
we cannot make anymore judgments.
But right now people on the internet claim the loophole incident is a result of Gu Group's ill-intentioned sensationalization.
Do you have anything to say to this?
Nonsense!
I, Gu Yuanchao, have been active in the market for many decades.
I've always been honest and trustworthy.
Would I do something like that?
New Way has already revealed a video.
Apparently, this matter was due to your Gu Group.
Let's go! New Way's accepting interviews!
What's going on? You still didn't deal with it completely!
Chairman, that's impossible.
Dad.
I'm sorry, Chairman.
We're being controlled by him.
Next I-
don't know what he'll do.
What's wrong?
-Dad, what's wrong?
-Are you ok?
-Go pour me a glass of water.
-Ok.
[Contract Agreement]
This is the business I wanted to speak with you about.
5G Plus Logistics Warehouse?
This can change the industry for the undertaking.
But also changing the world's business concept opportunity.
The investor invested ¥$5 billion in New Way. Within the next ten years,
- you can enjoy the rights of Ling Xiao.
- It's a deal.
But you have to remember.
Why I want to invest
in this project, it's because
you are my son.
Thank you, Dad.
Good job.
Thank you.
It's my honor.
It is said that the brand owner of New Way is now Gushi Group.
No one can influence New Way's policy decisions.
As for who that person is, for self-interest,
made use of the trust of the netizens and buyer to create disorder in the market,
you will have the answer soon.
Since everyone has asked.
I might as well announce New Way's collaboration project plan with the Ministry of Public Security.
Yes, you are right.
But let's not talk about suppression. I merely want to reveal the truth to everyone.
Will New Way still collaborate with Gushi Group?
Do you have any other news at hands? Please answer.
-Excuse us.
-Please answer.
Any more breaking news? May I ask what's the next working arrangement? Please comment.
Please let us have your comments.
Please answer!
Is the publicity material for the Anniversary Celebration ready?
Yes, it has been prepared.
Older Brother Yue.
Why are you looking for me?
I'm not some kind of harmful weapon.
Why do you have to avoid me every time you see me?
I just want to avoid unnecessary trouble.
The problem about you and my dad, I apologize.
The one that should be apologizing isn't you.
It didn't exist at all.
The one that should be apologizing is the person behind giving all these evil orders.
About this situation, I know it's my dad that did wrong.
Can you give him another chance?
Sorry, according to the time now,
the court's letter should have reached Chairman Gu's hands.
Letter?
Brother Yue, do you really have to do this step?
You should be the one going to ask Chairman Gu about this.
I am sorry to interrupt you today.
Have the legal department ready to counteract.
Okay.
With regards to Gushi Group's malicious libel against New Way
resulting in the loss of its reputation,
New Way has filed an appeal
to demand for an apology from Gushi Group as well as related compensation.
is just ¥$1.
How is Miss Gu?
Ever since the situation got exposed, Miss Gu has been staying at home.
I heard that Miss Gu went to beg for forgiveness to Ling Yue.
However, President Yue has not changed his mind.
I bet that Miss Gu's isn't feeling so well now.
How can Brother be like that?
President Ling, where are you going? Right now, the Gu Family is being surrounded by reporters everywhere.
If you go now, it's not appropriate.
I don't care.
- Did you take a shot?
- Yes.
Is this photo okay?
Yes.
Which media are you from?
First come, first serve, you know that? Go line up at the back.
Okay.
What?
Big bro, why are there so many people here?
This must be huge news.
Also, the Gu family has a daughter who's an internet celebrity.
The netizens have been keeping track of her movements.
Even more so, she has something going on with New Way. Right?
No way.
Don't tell me you didn't even know about this?
Let me tell you, if you work in this field, you need to be very alert.
You need to follow these small gossips very closely.
Alright, you go play aside. If you want to learn, go find your master.
Who was it?
- Did you see who it was?
- No.
Xin'er?
Why you are here?
I am coming to take you.
Come here and be careful.
Sorry, you had to see this side of me.
Relax, I definitely would...
But when we were little, you would only climb a wall to skip class.
What is it, you still dress up so nicely.
When did I...?
Sister Xin'er!
Lower your voice. People will hear your voice.
Just pretend you didn't see what happened today. Understood?
Or else I will...
Fortunately, you are on a lookout here.
-Why are you here?
-I'm waiting for my brother to finish class.
Fine, then you wait. I'll be going first.
Okay, bye.
Such a trivial thing, you still remember!
To me, what situation of yours is a trivial thing?
I just want to find a place.
I could take a quiet moment.
But at this time right now, isn't staying at home to avoid better?
You turn me down.  Then, I leave now.
My princess, this way.
As for Gushi Group's malicious libel against New Way
resulting in loss of its reputation,
Seriously. I didn't expect this.
Gushi is too much.
This has really taken a new turn.
and publicly admitted that they ruined New Way's reputation.
I know. Her dad is really mean.
The main point is that New Way's president is also mean. He actually asked for ten thousand dollars of compensation.
New Way's President is too awful. He's distinctly humiliating him.
Quick, let me see your shopping cart.
What are you looking at? You've been ignoring me.
Don't distract me. I'm busy adding things to my shopping cart.
So awesome! Just within 3 minutes,
sales has reached over one million!
Where's President Ling? I have to tell him this good news!
President Ling already left long ago.
I'm guessing he already knew we will win by a landslide.
In fact, you boss is indeed your boss.
President Ling.
What's up?
Miss Anxin is missing.
Missing? Did you look for her at her home?
I did.
Move aside.
President Ling, can I interview you?
- President Ling.
- Gu Ansheng.
Gu Ansheng, are you in there?
Mrs Gu came out. Take a photo now.
Young Master Ling, are you here to show off?
Auntie, I'm here to look for Gu Ansheng.
He's not here.
Don't come here again.
You are not welcome here.
Where's Anxin? Do you know where she went?
I am asking you about Anxin.
Do you think
Ain't I giving you chance to hurt her anymore.
What drunken words are you saying?
Don't you get it?
Anxin was forced to leave by you!
You...
forced her to leave.
Do you have something to tell me?
No.
What would I have to say?
[You booked D7190]
You are leaving.
Is that because of Ling Yue?
I...
The way we met.
It was purely the coincidence.
I heard it.
At first, I thought.
If he was staying with me, I am quite happy about it.
At that moment, I understood.
We are living in two different worlds.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Soaking the memory wet ♫
♫ Fate works bizarrely ♫
♫ The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly beats out of normal ♫
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Obviously, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness,
for it has always been you ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Yet the reminiscing has never been able to stop ♫
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Using all of my most beautiful adjectives ♫
♫ Is still not enough to describe your name ♫
♫ Our story is exclusively ours ♫
♫ Our palms hold onto the key to the future ♫
♫ Using love to slowly open up ♫
♫ a lifetime ♫